Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking                    Halee
Timing
arch1t3cht
Subtitle Editing
JT-421
Translation
arch1t3cht
Gaijin
Water Seven, 22 Years Ago
The Legendary Shipwright
Ahh! It's gonna eat me!
Eat this!
Outta the way, Iceburg!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Um?! What the hell are you doing, Franky?!
Idiot!
Ow!
Um!
Iceburg
16 Years Old
What are you doing here?! You're no help at all!
All you do is build dangerous crap!
Shut up!
Cutty Flam (Franky)
12 Years Old
It's none of your business, Dumburg!
This is my favorite battleship, Battle Franky!
I don't care! Just get rid of 'em all
before someone gets hurt!
I can build anything I want here!
It's Scrap Island!
Just you wait.
My next battleship will thrash those sea kings!
Um, no chance!
You'll be sea king food!
Will not!
Um, will too!
♪ A man gives his damn all! ♪
President Tom (Longhorn Cowfish Fishman)
Tom's Workers Shipbuilding
That wraps up the launch ceremony!
We've built a damn sturdy ship.
Haven't we, Yokozuna?
Yokozuna (Sumo Frog)
Tom's Pet
Ribbit, ribbit!
Let's finish it up tomorrow.
Time to head home, boys.
Ribbit, ribbit!
Ah, I'm starving.
Opposite the Warehouse Under the Bridge
Water Seven
Ribbit, ribbit!
I wonder what's for dinner.
Scrap Island
(Tom's Workers Dockyard)
Hey...
Wait, Mr. Tom!
Franky, what number is
your Battle Franky at now?
Oh, it's at eight.
It was so close this time!
Liar!
You know, Mr. Tom lets you
get away with murder!
All you do is build weapons!
Shut up, Dumburg!
What'd you say to me, Lame-ky?!
Idiot...
All right, boys.
Stop fighting already, you two.
– But Miss Kokoro, he started it!
Kokoro, a Beautiful Secretary
Tom's Workers
Oh my seas.
And that's enough laughing from you, Mr. Tom.
What's gotten into you?
Oh, by the way,
I heard pirates raided another lumber hauler.
There've been more pirates than ever
since the Pirate King's execution.
Our city's in trouble.
The pirate age has engulfed us.
It just feels hopeless.
The Aqua Laguna floods mean we need to
get lumber and iron from other islands.
Meanwhile, treacherous seas
and pirates hamper trade.
Short of work, shipyards
jockey for customers,
fights break out,
and people lose their jobs.
Left unchecked, Water Seven could become
a ghost island, waiting to sink into the depths.
Water Seven made its name
in the shipbuilding industry.
That's right.
Mr. Tom built those incredible ships!
Hey, show me the plans for a pirate ship!
Why are you laughing?!
Franky,
there's no such thing as pirate ship plans.
When sailors hoist their black flag,
that's a pirate ship.
A ship with a seagull flag is the Navy's.
It doesn't matter what he wants to build,
but a man should be
damn proud of the ship he builds!
Aren't you going to bed, Mr. Tom?
What are you drawing?
Well,
this'll give the island hope.
Hope?
This idea might just revitalize Water Seven yet.
Go on to bed now.
Okay.
Hmm?
A government judicial ship is here!
What's a judicial ship?
It's a mobile courthouse.
So who's on trial?
Wait a minute!
What did Mr. Tom do?
Get the hell outta my way!
Give Mr. Tom back, you jerks!
It's okay. Don't worry.
Mr. Tom! Mr. Tom!
By building the Oro Jackson,
the pirate ship of recently executed
Pirate King Gold Roger,
Tom the Shipwright was complicit in global piracy.
Hurry!
For his crime, Tom will be
taken to Enies Lobby...
where...
he will be put to death!
What?!
Terrible news!
Tom... Tom received a death sentence!
They say building
the Pirate King's ship was a crime.
It's finally happened.
The world's a mess.
It was coming to him.
Normally, it would not be a crime
for a shipwright to sell their ship to anyone.
However, the Pirate King
warrants an exception.
Anyone deemed to have anything to do
with his piracy poses a danger to the world.
Thus, I sentence you to death!
Take the convict away!
Yes, Your Honor!
Let's go.
Move it!
Come on, get moving!
Hey, what are you doing?
Right now, I'm...
Huh?
envisioning a steam-powered paddle ship
that could bang along tracks in the sea.
Hey, you!
Don't speak to him!
Get...
As we speak,
this island decays
due to stagnant trade.
As we speak,
the people are demoralized
by their fear that the island will sink.
Launching a sea train will surely
save our island, Water Seven!
E-Excuse us.
We will remove him immediately.
No, wait a moment.
What?
You said, “a sea train”?
A ship puffing down its tracks,
going from island to island.
Carrying passengers, goods, and other ships
without being fazed by the weather,
a sea train would allow everyone
free passage across the sea.
Sounds too good to be true.
Tracks? They would be destroyed
by the first Aqua Laguna.
That's right!
Not to mention the sea kings!
Seaborne tracks wouldn't need to be fixed.
Bobbing just below the surface,
never resisting the surf,
the tracks would act as a guide,
with the sea train using them as a rope.
Furthermore, I'm designing a noisemaker
to drive away fish using the space
between the tracks and the paddle.
Such a device would keep
the sea kings away from the tracks.
Would something like that work?
By uniting Saint Poplar, Pucci,
San Faldo, and Water Seven,
we can grow our industries
through mutual trade.
Brilliant!
I should finish the blueprints soon,
but it's not a job for just any shipwright.
What about a stop at Enies Lobby?
No problem!
If we perfect this technology and
spread it across the seas,
it would damn well change relations
among the world's islands.
The sea train is the hope of Water Seven!
How long would it take?
Ten years.
Then show us what you can do!
Tom the Shipwright,
I hereby give you a ten-year reprieve
to develop the sea train!
Impressive!
Let's go, Tom!
Save Water Seven!
Damn, I'm alive!
It's no laughing matter, Mr. Tom!
A chill ran down my spine
at the thought of what was to come.
But now, assuming everything goes well,
they might drop the case concerning Roger.
Um, I gotta say, you're amazing, Mr. Tom!
Everyone was blown away by your idea!
I know the sea tr–
Thanks for the food!
Yokozuna, you're learning the front crawl.
Ribbit!
Hey, what the hell, Franky?!
You've been sulking since we got home.
Shut up!
I'm pissed off! Everything's crap!
Gold Roger's ship is the only one in the world
to circumnavigate the Grand Line!
After making an incredible ship like that,
why does Mr. Tom deserve death?!
Those idiot onlookers act like it's only natural,
but they can't even build one ship!
I know what's going on!
This office is under this bridge
just because the city forced us
down here after Roger's execution!
Why does the world's best shipwright
have to deal with this crap?!
What's so funny, you horned tanuki?!
Get off him, Lame-ky!
I won't stand for it!
And I won't stand for him dying!
No, no. That's all wrong!
Push the water as far back as you can!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
No, that's not it!
You have to stroke harder!
What the hell is with him?
You should just kick that idiot out!
Don't say that.
He's a part of our team.
His skills are already nearly at the level
of the other shipwrights here.
His creations are a bit dangerous though.
He's always been a straight shooter.
This kid damn well showed up
on Scrap Island two years ago.
He surprised me with the cannons
he made from junk.
Take me in, old man!
My parents abandoned me!
He said his parents threw him off their ship
because they couldn't handle him.
He's a bit like one of those lousy pirates!
It's hilarious!
Mr. Tom...
He's tough.
Still, he's a good kid.
You two will surely be
world-class shipwrights someday.
You should get along with him.
That's impossible for Franky.
Every fiber of him is crazy.
Anyway, once the plans are ready,
we'll start building the sea train!
Sure.
But there's no way he'll help us.
He's welcome to do as he likes.
Suicide?
I heard he was the president
of Dock 4 Shipbuilding.
It must have been because of that accident.
They didn't have enough supplies,
so he took his own ship to buy lumber.
He got 50 people killed.
I heard they're closing the shipyard.
People are so fragile...
Is this island done for already?
Hey!
Did you guys hear about Scrap Island?
Huh, no way!
Is that true?!
Tom's Workers finished the sea train?!
Wow! Will this ship really run?!
It's gotta be dangerous.
A criminal made it.
I want to ride.
Then... I guess I will too.
Tom, do you have any comment?
We're leaving. All aboard!
It's moving!
The paddles are sticking to the tracks!
Wow! Look at it go!
Twelve years ago,
for the first time in history, the disheartened
people of an isolated, dying city...
boarded the sea train Puffing Tom
and crossed the sea.
I see.
This dingy warehouse was once the headquarters
for the shipbuilding company Tom's Workers?
A shipbuilding company?
Tom, Iceburg, and Cutty Flam.
So this is where the three of you spent
so much of your time building ships.
Calling it a “secret hideout”
is rather endearing.
Shut your hole.
Get the hell outta here already!
We'll go once we get what we came for,
shipwright Cutty Flam.
There aren't any blueprints here!
Well, that's the answer I'd expect.
Hey!
Kalifa!
Ow...
Eek!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
You bastard...
We've got plenty of time
to get the truth out of you.
We have a trump card.
It may have happened eight years ago,
but it seems you're also guilty of some crimes,
just like Tom.
Screw you!
Tom was not a criminal!
Don't talk to me like you
know anything about it,
you little punk!
Mr. Tom...!
Stay right there!
Calm down.
As a criminal, you should know
the consequences of your actions.
Franky,
you have no say in what happens next.
Keep your mouth shut!
You punks know...
nothing...
about Tom or about Water Seven!
Water Seven, 8 Years Ago
So the judicial ship will be here in three days?
Ah, Tom's trial.
I wonder how it'll turn out.
He should be fine.
Surely.
He followed through on his promise.
Indubitably.
Carry this load to the dock.
How'd the negotiations with Saint Poplar go?
Not good.
They're looking to take advantage
of our lack of resources.
Same with the steel from San Faldo.
With supplies so expensive,
the shipyards will lose money.
Next time, we'll figure something out.
Yeah! That's right!
Everyone's happy to travel
to the other islands,
but trading with them seems to be tricky.
At this rate, will the city improve at all?
At least the people are buzzing.
Results don't happen overnight, Iceburg.
Do all you can do and be damn proud of it.
Alright.
Hello and good day, sir.
Would you happen to be
the master shipwright Mister Tom?
Oh, how I've looked for you!
Hm?
Pardon me, but I have a matter to–
Uh...
Don't interrupt me! Stand down!
Yes, sir!
I have a matter to dis–
Director-General Spandam
Cipher Pol Number 5
I-I am...
Cipher Pol Number 5's...
Spandam!
Agent Spandam!
Oh! Sorry 'bout that!
I don't know who you are,
but it looks like my cannon salute hit you.
That aside, I feel super!
Battle Franky 35 is back!
I killed a sea king!
Look at how big it is!
This monster's gotta be at least 100 meters!
That idiot's at it again.
No! Stop it, Jerkburg!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
You keep building these damn
battleships one after another!
Enough is enough already!
If you can't handle it,
then today's the day I'll dismantle it for you!
Screw you!
This is my special battleship!
No way I'd let you do something like that!
Um, listen up, Franky!
You killed a sea king, right?
That means this is a deadly weapon.
I don't understand how you can leave
dozens of these things lying around.
It's not like I'm attacking people!
It's not about your intentions!
You're culpable for creating
such weapons, Lame-ky!
W-Wait...
Mr. Tom, say something!
Lame-ky is a disgrace to our company!
Oh, you're back to Lame-ky?!
W-Wait just a minute, please!
First, I would like an apology.
Then, I would like you to hear me out!
You're with the government?
Is this about my trial?
Huh? What are you talking about?
No, sir, I don't know anything about that.
Hm?
Where's Mr. Tom?
They wanted to talk alone.
He's in the brick warehouse
with some government guy.
Span... What was it again?
Spanda... something or other.
Sounds like he's not affiliated
with the judicial ship.
They're not very well organized.
I don't know!
I don't have any blueprints like that!
Nonsense!
Don't try acting humble
and playing dumbbell with me!
We've already combed through
Water Seven's past!
If we search the premises,
we'll find them in no time!
Do you have a warrant to search me?
I'm sure I could get one, Tom.
I already know you're the master criminal
who built Gold Roger's ship!
As a criminal, your freedom
remains solely at my mercy.
Oh, the government
already knows all about that.
What?!
That's absurd!
So why are you free to work
as a shipwright here?!
Do as an intelligence agent does
and figure it out. So long!
Hey, wait!
I'm not done with you yet!
Do you know who I am?!
Oh, that?
Tom followed through on the promise
he made on the judicial ship.
The charges should be dropped
when he's tried in three days.
Tom's a great man.
You've gotta be kidding.
They'll drop the charges
for his involvement with Roger?
So they do exist?
Yes, sir.
Naturally, pirates are also
ferreting about for these blueprints.
In the unlikely event they were
to fall into nongovernmental hands,
the government would no longer
have a fighting chance.
It has been 10 years since the start
of the so-called Great Pirate Era.
The Five Elders
Pirates have only grown
more powerful and more numerous.
We cannot stand idly by
while the ancient weapons are revived!
Those of us who stand for justice
should have that kind of firepower!
If we took possession of the ancient weapon,
we could bring the Great Pirate Era to an end!
You have a point that the times are changing.
First get us those blueprints,
then we'll talk more.
We're leaving this matter to you, Spandam.
I am honored! You won't regret it.
After all this investigative work,
there's no chance in hell
I'm letting this opportunity slip by!
Let's go!
Damn it!
I'm up a creek if he's exonerated!
Agent Spandam!
Forget the charges getting dropped.
Just you watch, you smug bastard.
Hey, call in five more agents!
Yes, sir!
Agent Spandam!
Iceburg. Franky.
Huh?
Come here for a second.
I need to give you something important.
Wh-Why would someone design this?!
C-Can humans build something like this?!
It's the worst monstrosity
in the history of shipbuilding.
The government is aware
of these blueprints' existence.
They're already moving in.
It's too dangerous for me to keep them.
I'm scared, but...
I understand. I'll take them.
Awesome, Iceburg! Hey!
We should build it!
You idiot!
That hurt!
Think before you speak!
I'll take care of these.
If we let something like this come into being...
Huh?
Yeah, the world would be doomed.
Anyway, it's up to you two
what you do with those.
If push comes to shove, destroy 'em.
Mr. Tom.
While we're at it,
I need to share one other cause for concern.