One Piece
Wano Arc
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Oh, Inuarashi!
Where have you been?
Something wrong, Kin'emon?
We're in a real predicament!
Kin'emon
The Mink Musketeers
An Abandoned Village
Kuri
Kin'emon
The Mink Musketeers
An Abandoned Village
Kuri
The enemy knows
about the flyer and the moon tattoo?!
That's right! It's one big mess!
What do we do, Your Grace ?!
We were distributing these covertly,
so we're unsure how this information leaked.
We chose this coded symbol
on the off chance it fell into the wrong hands.
But they've somehow uncovered
the connection between this and the tattoo.
According to our reports,
our allies in the capital are being apprehended
by Kaido's and Orochi's forces.
A Woman's Secret
You're under arrest! Seize him!
Stop resisting, rebel scum!
I found one! A flyer!
Settle down!
He's got the moon tattoo, too!
Anyone with that mark
on their ankle is a traitor!
Report any you see!
Word travels fast.
The entire capital will have heard by now.
This is no time for leisurely
visits to bathhouses.
How fortunate for you.
What's that supposed to mean?
As expected from Stealth Black!
I'll get him next time!
You're just as culpable
for letting them escape.
Komurasaki-dayu !
Boss Kyoshiro.
Komurasaki's wake has been canceled.
Things might get out of hand
if this many grief-stricken people pour in.
A Pleasure Hall
Flower Capital
The funeral tomorrow will
probably be even more crowded.
May she rest in peace!
Many are placing the blame
for this upon your shoulders.
Please be careful.
They should mind their own business.
There was no other way.
Besides, the one with the most to lose...
is me.
Indeed.
Lord Orochi is still in a foul mood.
I'd wager this is the thorn in his side.
Ebisu Town
Stop it, you two!
Arguing won't resolve any of this!
We're all in this together!
They started arresting anyone
suspected of rebelling against Orochi...
right after your crew slipped up!
What was that?!
That little bear and his pals...
must have leaked our plans to them!
Bepo and the others would die before talking!
Do not disrespect them!
Wait! You're doing exactly
what the enemy wants, Traf!
I don't wanna hear anything
from you, Black Leg-ya !
You both need to simmer down.
You're the one who
needs to cool your head!
You have to...
You have to trust each other!
You're the least trustworthy person here!
But I didn't see a thing...
How'd getting hit do that to you?
Ain't never seen a face like that...
You coward!
You must eliminate
those who were captured!
Silence them!
What did you say?!
This is the way of the shinobi !
When'd you get so scary, Shinobu?!
This isn't some game we're playing!
We've been waiting 20 years
for this moment!
If we fail,
we won't get another chance!
That's enough, Shinobu!
Master Kan...
Things do not always go as planned!
I understand your frustration,
but it's a miracle we found allies
whose goals aligned with our own!
Without them, Lord Oden's wish
will never come to pass!
Pardon the intrusion, good people!
I was outside and couldn't help but overhear!
And my, they are some lovely voices!
Hold it! Who are you?!
Oh?
Wow! What beauty! A goddess, no less!
Oh, you!
Please, come in.
Oh, sorry to intrude.
Hey!
As I live and breathe...
Shinobu-chan ?!
Kanjuro-kun !
Oh, my! It's true! It's true!
Then this is indeed the genuine article!
It's all anyone can talk about in the capital!
It really sent my heart racing!
Is it set to begin?! The great battle?!
The Northern Cemetery
Ringo
My sword...
My sword!
You're...
You scared me!
Please, you need to rest...
or your wound will reopen.
Right! Right! You don't need to get up yet!
So where... where am I?
You saved our lives earlier.
Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you!
But you were terribly wounded!
I am truly...
at a loss as to how to apologize.
My own inexperience got me hurt.
It's got nothing to do with you.
So where'd that guy go?!
He's still got Shusui!
You mustn't leave!
Please remain inside with such an injury!
Yee-ow!
Are you dense?!
That's my wounded shoulder!
I'm so sorry!
Honestly!
See ya!
Don't go!
You must give it time to heal.
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
I just said that's my wounded arm!
What's wrong with you?!
I-I'm really sorry!
Ow, ow, ow.
It'll be okay, samurai-san !
You'll get better soon!
There was some special toad oil
in the capital, so I stol...
I mean, I bought some!
You stole it.
D-Did not.
Well, I don't care either way.
This toad oil is amazing!
It makes sword wounds disappear!
Toad oil, huh?
Well, hopefully it works!
Say, samurai-san !
Don't leave us!
Got something to eat?
Yes! Would you like some now?!
Gyukimaru?
Th-That's right.
The whole city is familiar
with "Gyukimaru of Oihagi Bridge."
The named blade Shusui has already
been returned to where it belongs.
It was callously robbed from the grave
of Wano's legendary samurai, Ryuma!
I can't tell you where the warrior monk lives,
but he'll confront anyone armed
who attempts to cross the bridge.
Ah, so he's always there?
No need to rush then.
I'm still curious about Gyukimaru,
but who are you two anyway?
Why was that grim reaper-looking guy after you?
It's because we earned
the wrath of Wano's shogun.
The shogun, huh?
Oro... Oroshi?
It's Orochi.
Say, samurai-san !
My name is Toko!
TOKO
If you use the "O" honorific,
you get Otoko, and that means "man."
O
It's funny cause I'm a girl!
No, it's not.
What? What?!
Everyone says it's funny!
What's with you?!
Beats me.
Though you wear the garb
of a Wanese samurai,
you are actually from overseas, correct?
You don't look like a ba–
A bad per–
A bad person.
Trouble with words?!
My apologies!
Samurai-san, you're pretty scary!
But you're a really nice person
because you saved us!
Um...
I wish to tell you a secret,
but you must keep it.
What is it?
I'm... I'm looking for my older brother.
We were separated 20 years ago.
And now, I think he might be in Wano!
His name is...
Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'm his younger sister.
My name is Hiyori!
Momonosuke's
younger sister?!
I knew it!
I'm so glad I summoned
the courage to tell you!
I took a bit of a gamble.
You do know my brother, don't you?!
And he is okay, right?!
Wait! Settle down!
I need to collect my thoughts.
Lately, rumors abound concerning
the return of the Kozuki Clan.
Coincidentally, a courageous and kindhearted
samurai from overseas is here.
I thought he might be my brother's ally!
Or are you an enemy
trying to track him down?!
I'm his ally.
Rest easy; I'm his ally.
Thank goodness.
Do you know if Kin'emon is alive?
Are Kanjuro, Raizo,
and Kikunojo all with him?
Kikunojo?
Oh, you mean Kiku?
Yeah, but wait...
I'm trying to wrap my head around this.
Are you really Momo's sister?
Let me explain.
I see.
That's right.
Momo came here from 20 years ago,
so he looks like he's eight years old,
and you're his supposed younger sister,
but you aged during those
20 years, making you 26.
Yes.
By the way,
is it okay for her to hear all of this?
It's okay! Because I already knew!
It was a secret between Big Sis and me!
Otoko is one of the few close friends
who knows my true identity.
Her cheerfulness always keeps me going.
Twenty years ago,
I was still a little girl like her,
but I will never forget
what happened that day.
You must escape... to the future!
Mother, please don't do this!
Mother! Mother!
I couldn't make sense of anything
that was happening.
In the blazing fire,
my brother and the others
disappeared right before my eyes.
It was the same day
I lost my father Oden,
and even my mother.
In a single day, I suddenly lost everything.
I was told my brother
would return in 20 years,
but for something so uncertain,
my hope was fleeting.
I did not have the will to go on
for all those years.
Is there a reason you couldn't
travel through time too?
In case something happened
either to my brother or to me,
they did not want
the Kozuki bloodline to end.
That's too cruel.
But my father's eternally patient retainer,
Kawamatsu the Kappa,
provided emotional support and raised me.
Kappa ?!
Indeed.
It is hard to believe such creatures exist,
but he takes great pride in being one.
On the day that the castle burned,
we were surrounded by the enemy,
but we escaped undetected
through a drainage channel in the moat.
Princess! Just a bit farther!
After losing my father, mother, and brother,
I fell mute from shock,
but he was always upbeat and supportive.
Princess! This is the Kappa Odori!
Come on!
♪ Kappappa, kappappa, kappappa and pa! ♪
♪ Kappappa, kappappa... ♪
Go ahead and eat, Princess.
Kawamatsu, you're hungry too, aren't you?
No, my tummy's upset.
That's why it's growling.
Please... Please eat at least half.
No, I'm fine. I found a grilled fish
swimming in the river earlier.
A grilled fish in the river?
That's right!
So I filleted it real quick
and ate it on the way.
He did not eat much himself,
but he did his best to feed me.
Due to the kindness
of my dutiful protector, Kawamatsu,
I gradually learned to laugh again.
Where's this guy now?
I think...
back when I was about 13...
we were separated.
But Kawamatsu is a fierce samurai,
so he must still be out there,
waiting for the day of the great battle!
How I wish to see him and the others again.
I want to see a kappa too!
Uh-huh!
Zorojuro-san.
Are there any others
preparing for the great battle?
Well, let's see...
What?!
Then Dog-chan and Cat-chan are there too?!
Yeah.
I heard that they were both dead,
so I thought I would never see them again!
Nekomamushi might not be in Wano yet...
What are you doing?
I am so very happy...
You crack me up, Big Sis!
But I will not cry!
I am the daughter of a samurai!
If Dog-chan and Cat-chan will be there,
then it's possible the entirety
of the Nine Red Scabbards will assemble!
I'm not so sure of that.
Kin'emon.
Kanjuro.
Raizo.
Okiku.
Inuarashi.
Nekomamushi.
THE NINE RED SCABBARDS
All we know is those six and Momonosuke.
We haven't met the last three yet.
I spoke of the first
of those three, Kawamatsu,
KAWAMATSU
DENJIRO
ASHURA DOJI
and there's Denjiro and Ashura Doji.
I do not know where they are
nor if they are safe.
But now with everyone in the capital
in an uproar over this flyer,
I just know they will appear!
Is that the flyer we handed out
to our potential allies?
Yes.
The uproar has thankfully spread the message
like wildfire, which you'd think is a good thing.
But, it actually puts us in a tight spot,
seeing as the rendezvous point
was compromised and our allies caught.
Things are looking a bit dicey.
It will be all right.
That is my belief.
Well...
Too many captains sink the ship.
I'm gonna stop fretting.
Oh, yes! Certainly!
Before anything else,
I want you to get well!
Now, get some rest.
All right, you don't have to tell me twice.
Otoko, this is a miracle!
I am overjoyed!
My brother is alive!
I'm happy for you, Big Sis!
Toko, this is great!
Can't they keep it down?
I'm supposed to sleep!
But he is only eight!
How peculiar.
My brother is still a child.
I suppose Kin'emon and the others
have also remained 20 years younger.
I cannot help but wonder
how our reunion will be.
Perhaps it is better not to see them
before the great battle.
My presence could weaken their samurai's resolve.
Agreed, Otoko?
FLOWER CAPITAL
Rasetsu Town
Flower Capital
PRISON
RASETSU            PRISON
Prisoners' Quarters
AKA the Public Cells
Rasetsu Town
Prisoners' Quarters
AKA the Public Cells
Rasetsu Town
I didn't think so many ruffians
would be rounded up in here!
People, take a good, long look at them!
Take in the faces of fools who would rise up
against His Excellency Orochi and Lord Kaido!
Get your ass in there already!
Too bad for you.
You've been outed, your scheme revealed!
You have failed.
Master Fukurokuju, please wait!
What is it about these ankle tattoos
that leads you to think we are traitors?!
This is just a popular design! We have
nothing to do with any kind of rebellion!
Silence!
How would you explain this rebus, then?
With the reversed crescent moon at its center?
A sign of rebellion
against His Excellency Orochi, perhaps?
It's a dead ringer for your tattoos.
His Excellency Orochi is the one
giving the order, so sit down and shut up!
We're in a serious jam.
Will everyone think...
that we blabbed about the plan?
Don't worry!
Our captain... will still believe in us.
Prisoner Mining Camp
Udon
Come on, come on!
Wipe the floor with them already!
I wanna take part in this sumo match!
I'm Madilloman! A gifter who ate...
Madilloman
A Gifter
Armadillo SMILE Fruit
Madilloman
A Gifter
Armadillo SMILE Fruit
an armadillo SMILE fruit!
Oh, you look pretty solid!
Perfect for my training!
You moron!
I'm rockin' seastone bullets
in these bad boys!
You're finished, fellas!
They're "finished"?
How blind are these idiots?!
It's far from "finished."
Old man.
Go right, duck, and then jump.
Huh?!
Get dead!
– Run!
– Okay!
Going right!
Duck!
And...
You little–
Jump!
What?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn, damn!
Good job, old man!
Keep it up!
What?!
Can you foresee the future or something?
Screw you!
That's some nonsense!
What'd you actually do?!
Old man! Go left next!
What?!
Got you, you f–hnn!
Left!
Dammit, that geezer!
Try this on for size!
Left! Left! Left! Left!
You little cheat!
Bull's-eye!
Guns can't take me down!
Y-You sneaky mongrel!
It's not over yet!
Without laying a finger, send him flying!
That's not it.
That's just the normal armament.
Oh, crap!
Armadi-Guard!
This isn't it.
This is still just the regular armament.
Huh?! Weren't you gonna hit me?!
Alpaca Fencing!
Hey! Which way next?!
Sir Straw Hat!
All right! Stop right there!
This good?!
It'll be easier this way!
Preposterous!
Ready when you are, Alpacaman!
Bring it!
Put me down!
It's not right for me to burden you this way!
Nope. Actually, the heavier the better.
Wha–
It's good for my training!
I get it! I get it!
This flyer told us all we needed to know
of the upcoming battle!
Two birds on fire: That means
twilight on the day of the Fire Festival!
And the snake is the raid's
rendevous point: Habu Port!
Kin'emon-kun must've put
his brain into overtime for this.
Kin'emon... kun ?
Oh, why are you giving me that look,
Shinobu-chan ?!
So, that's how things are. The dejected
looks on your faces make total sense.
The plan's as good as ruined,
what with our enemies aware of it.
Mm-hmm. That is correct.
Allies who bear the reversed crescent
moon tattoo—the sign of our rebellion—
are getting rounded up now.
If only there was some way
to take it back and tell them, "It was all fake!"
But that would mislead your allies as well.
Before this, however, I didn't
know about the crescent moon ankle tattoo.
Think of all the potential allies like myself!
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
What?!
In the midst of all this, every time
you hit a foe, you say, "That wasn't it"!
What are you up to?
I wanna throw knock-out punches
without having to touch anything.
If I do that,
I think I'll get past Kaido's armored scales!
Throwing knock-out punches
without having to touch anything?
Yeah. I won't know if it works
until I actually do it.
The thing is, I've seen it before.
Both Rayleigh...
and that battle-axe guy...
used the same armament haki.
How is theirs different from mine?!
Haki must be a foreign concept.
You know something?!
In Wano, we utilize an invisible power that
stems from the body and covers one's blade.
A good katana will cut even iron
when you need it to,
and yet, it will not mar a sheet of paper
if so desired.
It's at the swordsman's discretion!
Old man.
Check out this geezer!
Now you're eager for us to off you?!
Sir Straw Hat.
Watch as I demonstrate the power honed
through my days of sword fighting.
Despite being the centerpiece
of a sick execution game,
he's using it as a training opportunity?!
Sir Straw Hat! Give me directions!
Okay!
He'll swing down his right sword, full force!
I got it!
You damn geezer!
He knocked him back!
Old man!
Old man Hyo dropped that gifter!
Alpacaman!
That old weakling...
I swear he had one foot in the grave.
But he's surprisingly spry!
Could old man Hyo actually be
the renowned Hyogoro the Flower?!
Sir Straw Hat,
if this is something that
you are striving to accomplish,
perhaps I can be of some assistance.
You gotta teach me!
That's exactly it!