Wano's Grand Sumo Tournament
That's a huge komainu!
Who owns it?
How do we find this Otama kid?
The townsfolk won't tell if we ask them.
They're all under Orochi's influence.
But some of them look like
ordinary people, not fighters.
There have always been regular villagers here.
Until 20 years ago,
this was a vibrant castle town.
But one day, Orochi's subordinates came
and seized the houses they desired.
Then they expelled everyone from town,
except for the merchants they needed.
That's the story behind Bakura Town.
A sumo wrestler? How did he...?
Something must be going on in town.
Since a sumo wrestler came flying out...
I suppose it's a sumo match.
Once again, is there no one
who can take down...
the yokozuna of the Flower Capital, Urashima!
Urashima
Yokozuna, Wano Professional Sumo
Another bunch of weaklings-pe.
There's more.
Sumo, huh? It sounds fun!
The number of wrestlers
who fought against Urashima...
is now 19.
But the number of bones
that have been broken is...
10 arm bones,
15 leg bones,
52 ribs,
4 skulls, and...
7 backbones!
That's 88 bones in total,
and four wrestlers are missing!
Overwhelming!
His strength is inhuman!
The undefeated monster!
Yokozuna Urashima!!
We're hosting an exhibition match today!
Peace reigns                          over the land.
Peace reigns                     over the land.
Peace reigns                   over the land.
If anyone can defeat Urashima they'll
earn a staggering, 500 gold coins!
Peace reigns                   over the land.
Take down Urashima!
I bet on you!
You guys can do it!
We have the perfect plan!
We'll win the prize!
Beat those jerks!
Urashima-sama!
Oh! Look at this!
Ready...
Go!
Okiku!
I knew you would come!
This means you've decided
to be my wife-pe, right?!
Excuse me.
You're too big to hide behind me.
I can't believe it!
This woman is engaged to Urashima?!
How lucky!
She's loved by a yokozuna!
This is a big scandal!
What?! Urashima-zeki's wife?!
His wife?
No...
As you saw earlier,
he just wants me to marry him.
Okiku! I have a match
in Bakura Town later-pe!
If you're interested,
come and see how strong I am!
I have my own plans.
I see.
You guys!
We're looking for someone!
She's a little girl named Tama!
Tell me where this town's boss is!
She should be with them!
That woman! How disappointing!
That damn gold digger!
She's huge, but just right for Urashima!
I'd be a better match!
They're not listening!
Okiku came to see me.
Guys, bring her to me!
Yes, sir!
Big Bro! I didn't know you
were such a player!
Everyone wants to be like you!
No wonder she fell for you!
Okiku!
Okay, we're gonna look
for her ourselves! Let's go!
Lady! Big Bro Urashima wants you!
Come with us!
Who are you fools?! Out of our way!
Kick their asses!
Don't get in our way!
What?!
Nice charge!
I guess the winning technique
was a frontal thrust.
Come with me, lady!
No... please stop!
Would you really slash an unarmed naked man?
Yahoo!
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Kiku!
Outta my way!
Hey, Zoro!
Why did you let them take her away?!
I'm sorry,
I thought that it wasn't right to...
slash a naked man.
Besides...
she's not just a teahouse waitress.
Hey! Isn't she a girl from
the teahouse in the other town?!
With her rank, it's presumptuous of her
to even enter this town!
Is that so?!
Then we gotta kick her out!
She's just a vulgar tramp!
Shut up, you commoners!
To the samurai-class, all you fools are
all the same, vulgar, lowly chattel-pe!
Your lives are worthless.
It's up to me...
whether you live or die!
So, Okiku!
Why don't you...
be...
mine?!
This humble servant doesn't recognize any human...
as chattel!
You must be joking.
The only vulgar thing here is your heart.
The yokozuna's topknot!
So cool!
Kiku is so awesome!
It's getting exciting now!
He got rejected by that woman...
and he lost his topknot!
This is a quick way to get
the attention of their boss!
Okiku!
You...
betrayed me!
How could I do that...
in front of everyone?!
He looks like a wrathful deity!
Okiku!
Oh, no! That pose is...!
His Transcendent Slap
that sends opponents flying!
Please forgive me, Urashima-sama!
Although...
It seems that you truly are
the kind of man who would hit a woman.
Die!
Rubber Rubber...
Sumo Slap!
Oh no, oh no... No, no, no...!
Damn!
What did you do to my slap?!
Damn you...
who are you to Okiku-pe?!
Get out of my way!
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
Otherwise, I'll lose face!
Okay! No problem!
Assuming...
Dosukoi!
You can beat me!
I'm...
good at sumo!
Luffy-no-umi
Sumo-Wannabe Pirate
Record: Undefeated
vs. Usopp
Get...
out of my way!
Bodhisattva Slap!
He's dodging Urashima's slaps!
He's so agile!
Keep it up, you runt!
You can't win by just dodging!
Ear Smasher!
Hey!
Eye Gouger!
Hey! Those are all illegal moves!
Shut up!
I'm...
a yokozuna!!
Well, whatever!
Holdem-sama! We have a problem!
Huh? The yokozuna got his topknot
chopped off by a woman?
Everyone's upset!
And we don't know what to do!
I don't care!
What do you expect me to do?!
I'm busy tearing her cheek off!
Have mercy on me!
You can have your baboon back!
Please stop!
I won't!
I heard that you mentioned the name, Kozuki.
When the Kozuki clan returns,
they'll teach you a lesson!
You must be aware...
that saying the name, Kozuki...
is a serious crime!
So consider this as your punishment.
You should've stopped chasing ghosts.
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
that tried to destroy
Wano twenty years ago!
Get out of my way, you little turd!
What Okiku did is unforgivable-pe!
She turned down the honor of marrying
and serving me, a samurai,
and insulted me!
I'll smash her head in
and set an example!
Just shut up!
It's like I said, you can do as
you like after you beat me!
But you can't beat me.
What do you mean?!
I'm...
the greatest yokozuna in Wano!
Transcendent Slap!
What's this?
I don't know. What could it be?
You may be a yokozuna...
but I'm...
the man who's gonna be King of the Pirates!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Big Bro Luffy!
Rubber Rubber...
Gigant...
Sumo Slap!
Dosukoi!
No!
What the...?
A-Am I safe now?
Th-The yokozuna...
was sent flying!
Yokozuna!
No way! He couldn't have lost
to a little guy like him!
Now I'm the yokozuna!
I don't care who you are,
just bring it on!
I guess we did enough to get
the attention of their boss.
I think so!
Th-That guy...
I remember!
He killed a magistrate!
Wanted - Zorojuro
Zorojuro?!
So what?
Don't tell me he's that guy's ally!
Hey!
Bring the boss of this town!
We're here to take back Tama!
Editing:
Feeso
Timing:
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control:
Feeso,
Galaxy 9000,
Grug,
Pepperjack
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Karaoke:
KaitouYahiko
Translation:
Crunchyroll,
Gaijin