Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
danpmss
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
danpmss
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
My Turn
I've cried my heart out.
I've whined enough, too.
I've made my decision!
I have to go. Everyone's fighting!
I thought that they had a chance.
Was it just a dream?
What did that damn shark do?
I don't know.
He just sprayed them with water, but they went flying, coughing up blood.
I can kill humans like you
without so much as touching you, if I have some water.
That's the difference between
fishmen and humans.
Give me a break!
This is no joke.
Playing with a water gun for him is like getting hit with a shotgun for us.
So this is the power of a shark?
And he's in a class
by himself among fishmen.
He's in another league.
Die already.
Your lives are not worth that much.
Arlong!
Big Sis Nami!
Nami!
Nacchan.
Hey, Nami! I was just about to crush these two-bit pirates.
Why'd you come here?
To kill you.
To kill...
me?
You never learn, do you?
How many times did you try to kill me
during the eight years you were with us?
You tried assassination,
poison, ambushes,
but I'm still here.
You should've learned that mere humans like you can never kill me.
Now, listen. I won't kill you...
and you can't escape from me.
Nami,
you'll be our surveyor forever.
But, as you know,
I'm a good-natured man.
If possible, I want you to be our
surveyor of your own free will.
So, how about this?
I intend to kill everyone here except you.
If you're willing to come back to the Arlong Pirates
and draw sea charts
as one of our officers,
I don't mind letting those people from Cocoyashi Village live.
These guys are finished, though.
They went too far.
The question is who you'll side with.
You either join me now and
be spared along with the villagers,
or team up with these weaklings and try fighting me together.
If you depend on these guys in the shape they're in,
it'll clearly end in tragedy for you.
Nami,
are you a member of my crew?
Or...
their friend?
How unfair!
If I say I'm friends with
Luffy and the others,
everyone will get killed.
And if I say I'm in Arlong's crew,
then everyone from
the village will be saved.
It all depends on my decision!
That's despicable!
No matter what she chooses,
he's going to keep Nami in chains!
Still!
Luffy,
help me!
Of course I will!
I must not doubt him!
Everyone, I'm sorry!
Please die with me!
All right!
We'll go for it!
We'll fight!
I see.
Everyone wants to die.
P-Please! Please!
Live! Live! Live! Live! Live!
Hm?
What the?
Finally!
All that's left is to free his legs.
Oh.
So that's what you meant?
Could it be?!
Big Bro Luffy!
What?!
Hey, hang in there!
Come to your senses!
30 seconds!
I won't last longer than that.
Zoro!
That'll be enough!
There isn't a fountain over there.
Could it be that rubber man?!
Don't worry about that.
It's nothing, you damn half-fish!
I warned you not to
say those words ever again,
dead man!
If I can smash that block with a kick,
he can fight.
Luffy, you're the only one who can settle this now!
Those with devil fruit powers struggle to use those powers in the sea,
let alone fight to survive, so he should be dead by now.
If he's still alive,
that means someone is interfering with our little game.
Are you all right?!
I'm glad you're okay!
Yeah! Oh?
What?! What's the matter?!
Pops, what did you do
with your pinwheel?
It was so cool.
Who cares about that right now?!
Interfering?
It didn't seem like a fair game
from the start.
At any rate,
if something's getting in the way,
I need to check on it.
Out of my way.
Egg Star!
I've got your back, Zoro!
Big Bro Usopp!
Is he all right?!
How brave! What an epic arrival!
Go for broke!
That's where you are?!
Usopp!
Listen, Nami!
I beat one of the officers!
One of the officers! Me! I beat him!
The guy with a face like this.
Fishmen are a piece of cake!
You defeated... Chew?!
Serves you right!
With my arrival, the fight suddenly reaches its climax!
The final chapter begins!
Hey, is there anything you can do to get out of this?
Oh, that's impossible.
I don't have any energy at all.
Come out! Come out! Come out!
Big Bro Cook!
I don't know what's
going on in the water,
but he must be the key!
Big Bro Zoro!
Stand firm and stop Arlong!
Okay!
We have to somehow prevent Arlong
from going into the sea, huh?
I'll stop him from moving.
I won't let you have your way!
Hey, Arlong! Look here!
Wha?! Big Bro Usopp!
How brave!
Usopp!
Standing in my way
Rubber Band of Doom!
leads me to believe you want to die first, Roronoa Zoro.
Now! Go, Zoro!
What are you trying to do?!
No way will I die.
I'll break that nose you're so proud of!
You fool.
I'm proud of it because it's unbreakable.
If you were at your full strength,
you might've been able to scratch it.
Big Bro!
Look over there!
Hm?
Ahh! That damn octopus is up!
And... what the hell's he doing?
Dammit! I thought the rubber band
was going to hit me!
What?!
See?! He was my target!
You yelled, "Arlong," didn't you?
The octopus.
Roronoa Zoro! I won't
let you have your way!
I'll crush your friend
who went into the sea!
You don't have to be concerned
since you'll all be dead, after all.
Big Bro!
Nami's big sister!
Leave the rest to me!
A fishman!
Move away, Big Sister.
I'll break that rock with my kick!
That octopus!
Takoyaki Punch!
Big Sister!
Zoro!
So that was it?
That was too quick.
What's up with these bandages?
Did you fall down or something?
What's this scar?
How can he still be alive
with wounds like this?
How can he still be standing?!
What is that look in his eyes?
Is that the look of someone who's dying?
He's a man I need to kill for sure,
right here, right now!
Staying still...
would have kept some of the wounds from opening.
That's right.
You find your situation amusing?
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking about the octofreak.
What?!
I thought I told you,
we win this game.
Dammit!
That scared the crap outta me!
You're the one who complicated everything in the first place!
He did it!
Go beat down that shark bastard,
you damn idiot!
Is it coming, kid?
It's coming!
Wahhhhh! I'm back!
Rubber boy!
Big Bro Luffy!
Luffy!
That damn rubber jerk!
You're late, idiot!
Zoro!
Huh?
Hey! Stop it!
You wouldn't!
It's my turn!
You idiot!
Gum-Gum...
Bell...
and...
Whip!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Gatling!
All right!
Did you do something?
He didn't feel a thing!
Yep. That was my warm-up.
That idiot!
I'm gonna kill him!
It's admirable how you scum have held on by the skin of your teeth.
Though, you'd have been happier dying at the bottom of the sea.
Hm? Not really.
I'm glad they saved me.
Can you understand my anger?
It's the anger of seeing my dear
brothers crushed by worms.
You'll soon wish that you
had submitted to your deaths.
Is Big Bro Luffy gonna be okay?
His furious assault had no effect whatsoever.
More importantly, how far did Big Bro Zoro fly?!
Go Luffy! I've got your back!
You don't have to worry
about his back.
If he loses, you guys will all die, too.
Yeah, we will.
If that happens, it's the end for the East Blue, as well.
What's the bleak difference between you and me?
Our noses.
Our jaws?
I wonder if Big Bro's joking.
No, he's definitely serious.
Our webs!
It's our race!
Such a fool! He hurt himself
by biting on a rock!
Now his teeth are crack–
He crushed the stone
pillar with his teeth!
Ahh! That's scary!
Did you see...
the inherent power of a fishman?
Heaven created you humans to have you bow before fishmen.
You're inferior creatures.
We're on a different level
from the moment we're born.
I'll show you the real difference between you and me.
Oh, yeah? Let's see it.
There's no way I'm losing to you.
I am the man who'll be
king of the pirates!
King of the pirates?
Don't make me laugh.
Can you inferior humans do something like...
crush a pillar with your teeth?
If that jaw gets you,
it won't just leave bite marks...
it'll tear clear through your bones!
So what?!
Stop...
bragging over stuff like that!
I can break stone without biting it.
Nice! Score one for Big Bro Luffy!
That's right!
The result's the same!
Th-That's beside the point!
Humans are stupid and weak.
If you fall into water and can't pull yourself out,
then what'll you do?!
Nothing! That's why I need help!
Hm? He can also use swords?
Take that... and that... and that!
What're you doing?
It looks like you're just
swinging those blades around.
I'm not looking to play your little game.
I've had enough of this nonsense.
Clench your teeth!
Wha...?! He shattered Arlong's teeth!
I don't know how to use swords, you bastard!
Huh? What's he saying that now for?
I don't know how to sail.
I can't cook.
I can't lie, either.
Hey!
I'm confident that I can't
live without help!
Fully admitting how
pathetic you are...
You sure are honest.
I bet your crew is
bothered by having
such an incompetent captain like you.
I wonder why your crew tried
so desperately to save you.
How can someone like you, with no damn pride, be a pirate captain?
What in the world can you do?
I can defeat you!