Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The World Conference,
also known as the Reverie...
is a grand assembly of fifty kings and queens
that represents over 170 countries
affiliated with the World Government.
It is held every four years.
As always, the Reverie concluded
in a state of great confusion
and all the representatives returned home.
Then...
one week later...
Good grief, I'm finally home.
Truly, the surface world is so far above us.
Um, thank you so much for escorting us,
Luffy's grandfather!
It was a pretty long trip, huh, Neptune?
You must be tired!
I'm exhausted.
Garp, stay here with us
and replenish your energy.
Well, maybe I'll have a cup of tea,
but considering the situation,
I can't stay here for long.
The Reverie always leads to turmoil.
When fifty countries gather,
a simple "let's get along" won't suffice.
Each of them has their own internal troubles.
Large and mighty countries
just stare quietly at each other
and let their proxies bicker.
They use resources
and technologies as leverage.
They say that all countries
are on equal footing, but that's just talk.
Wealth, poverty, and religious differences
won't allow them to be equal.
Even if they appear to shake hands and smile,
they'll gladly step on each other's feet.
I wonder how many leaders can speak for both
their citizens and those of other countries.
It's only a roundtable in name.
You're right. Conversations among
the sovereigns were touch and go.
We're no exception, but quarrels between
countries can't be solved so easily.
The further a country's history extends,
the deeper the roots of its conflict will grow.
Even if there is a disagreement,
as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
But what happened this time was disastrous!
This may be coming a bit late, but there's
one thing I haven't told you about yet.
This occurred right after the Reverie
was dismissed and we set off.
I received a report while aboard our ship.
We, the Navy, will do our best to resolve it,
but please do not be afraid
of the surface world or of us humans!
What happened?
Garp, what kind of report did you receive?
It's an incident concerning
the Kingdom of Arabasta.
The Kingdom of Arabasta...
Vivi!
Before all of this transpired...
At World Economic News,
right after the Reverie was dismissed...
Unbelievable! It's just one thing after another!
I can't understand how
so much happened at once.
Listen up! Find me
the greatest headline yet!
Sir, which one should make the front page?!
Listen! We have a death on our hands!
Big obituaries move papers!
Then, the headli–
No, wait!
The resolution they passed is also good.
But a murder attempt is exciting as well!
That's right!
Okay, let's have two front pages!
The back page will have the same format!
– Okay!
Sir.
Express mail from the government.
A check, huh?
Oh, that's a lot!
I see. It's an order to manipulate information.
But for which affair?
Hushing up this incident?!
No way in hell!
Throw this back in their faces!
Hey, what's wrong?
My, my, my...
Do as you're told, Morgans!
The secret agency,
Cipher Pol?!
You must obey orders
from the World Government.
Don't move!
Never underestimate Big News Morgans!
When did he sneak in?
Sir! Members of Cipher Pol
are government officials!
I know!
It's dangerous to stay here, guys.
Let's fly!
I may be avaricious,
but I am first and foremost a journalist!
I make people dance to the tune of my lies.
I'm a DJ of words!
I decide what to publish!
Mr. Morgans!
You have a call from King Wapol!
King Wapol?
What does he want?
Well, it sounds like he has information to leak.
What?!
What's going on?
A special report?
Don't worry...
It's gonna be okay...
With the government's failure
to hush up what had happened,
the decisions the leaders made at the Reverie,
as well as the incidents that occurred there,
instantly became known throughout the world
and left many people in shock.
Vayyt!
Vhaat the hell is this?!
This cannot be true!
It is just a story in the paper, right?
That is just the WEN! Their bird president
must have written nonsense!
I am sure of it!
This is Sabo after all!
It just cannot be...
I do not buy it!
Calm down!
First, we must confirm the facts.
But with all of them out of contact...
how can we confirm?
It's not true, is it?
Sabo...
My lady!
He was in Mary Geoise?!
M-My brother?!
What happened to Makino?
The bar is closed today.
What?!
So much has happened in the world...
I could use a drink.
Sabo is...
And I had just learned he was still alive...
Tell me it's not true!
Sabo!
I never get bored with this world!
It's getting interesting!
Hey, guys!
Let's set sail!
Instead of watching the Navy snatch it away,
I'll take it for myself!
And now, we return to the present...
Koby, it's me.
Hold on a second.
Let me go somewhere private.
Okay.
Oh, yeah! Sea!
Fog!
As always,
you're a stickler.
Well, it is a rule...
Oh, right! It's terrible!
There's something I need to report to you,
Commander!
What?!
That's the situation?!
Yeah. Even with all
the marines in the world
it's too much to handle.
So just as we planned,
the Navy won't get involved
with what's going on over there.
They don't have enough manpower.
That's fine.
Wano is not affiliated
with the World Government.
Now, about Big Mom arriving at Onigashima...
Yes.
Kaido and Big Mom
have been at odds for so long
that the Navy is hoping those
two pirates will ruin each other.
Yeah, I guess.
As we expected, Kaido and Big Mom
were at each other's throats...
but now they've joined hands!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you mean?!
As for Straw Hat Luffy,
there's been no word of a breakout.
The situation is at a standstill.
There's also one more unpleasant thing.
I saw Cipher Pol 0 in the capital the other day.
What?! Why are they in Wano?!
I hope I'm wrong,
but it must mean the World Government
is doing business with Wano,
a country ruled by a pirate.
When I found out,
I was stunned for a few minutes.
By the way, where are you now?
Right.
We're heading toward the Isle of Women...
to capture Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Oh, my...
Are those ships approaching from the Calm Belt...
a Navy fleet?!
Marguerite!
What's going to happen?!
The news spread all around the world.
They should have done this a long time ago!
It was a mistake to team up with pirates...
They're evil!
For those who think all pirates are bad...
Those government dogs will finally go away!
Screw that Pirate Empress,
Hawk Eye, and Clown!
They're nothing but looters!
...and for those who hate looters,
it's good news.
But I thought they did great
in the Summit War!
That's what they decided?!
The Navy is ready to take immediate action.
Is this really wise?
They were one of the world's
three great powers!
For those who knew of
their feats in the Summit War,
and those who are concerned about disrupting
the balance of the three great powers,
it was truly an alarming situation.
The news story from the latest Reverie
that stunned people across the world the most...
was...
the abolition...
of the Seven Warlords system!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea were pirates officially recognized by the government.
While they were allowed to pillage,
the government used them
as deterrents against other pirates.
The roster of the Seven Warlords
has changed over time.
Crocodile.
He clashed with the Straw Hats
over the Kingdom of Arabasta.
He was trying to take over the kingdom
but was ultimately defeated by Luffy
and expelled from the Seven Warlords.
The man who replaced Crocodile
and joined the Seven Warlords...
was Marshall D. Teach.
However, he announced his resignation
after achieving his goal.
Jinbe, Knight of the Sea,
opposed the Summit War and grew disdainful of the Navy.
He, too, declared his resignation.
Gecko Moria.
This man who had once clashed with the Straw Hats
was also called to the Summit War.
However...
just after the war, an order for an ambush
came from high up in the government,
and he was expelled.
Heavenly Demon Donquixote Doflamingo.
All while governing Dressrosa as its king,
he trafficked an artificial devil fruit, SMILE,
as an influential underground broker.
However...
he lost the kingdom
in a struggle against Luffy's group,
and his title of warlord was revoked.
And finally, Trafalgar Law.
He allied himself with the Straw Hats
to take down Doflamingo
and was stripped of his title.
The four pirates who reign supreme
as if they're emperors:
the Four Emperors.
And trying to contain them:
Navy Headquarters.
Last but not least:
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
These three great powers
have kept the world at peace.
However,
two kings had suffered terribly
at the hands of warlords:
King Nefertari Cobra
of the Kingdom of Arabasta,
and Riku Doldo III
of the Kingdom of Dressrosa.
They fought for the abolition
of the Seven Warlords system.
Then, after a heated debate at the Reverie,
a large majority supported
the proposition, and it passed.
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea
will automatically be stripped of all their rights,
and their connection with
the World Government will be hereby cut off.
That means...!
Buggy,
you're just another pirate!
That's not fair, you backstabbers!
A decision was made without telling us,
and since we're no longer useful, you arrest us?!
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
Whether Crocodile and Doflamingo
outsmarted you is none of my business!
Don't take it out on me!
They've got the whole coast surrounded!
What should we do?
My entire life's plan is going to the dogs!
Oh?
The Navy should be on our side,
but they're closing in on us!
What should we do, Mommy?!
Mommy!
Surrender yourself now,
Hawk Eye Mihawk!
Surrender yourself now!
Snyake Princess, we have a problem!
Your title of warlord has been stripped away!
Elder Nyon!
There are Navy ships off the coast!
What?!
They've already gone into action?!
Don't panic!
Snyake Princess!
They've obviously forgotten something...
don't you think?
This is no good, President Buggy!
Should we run?!
Of course not! We'll show them a flashy fight!
Show some guts, you sad sacks!
– That's our President Buggy!
– Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
How incredibly unforgivable...
Weevil!
I give you approval to annihilate them!
R-Really?!
In that case, I'm gonna kill 'em...
in the name of Whitebeard!
I feel a tremor of excitement.
It's been a long time...
since I was the one being hunted.
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
because of our might!
I'm counting on you guys.
In the meantime...
Editing:
Gigglebot
Timing:
Gab
Typesetting:
PhosCity
Quality Control:
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Scolines
Soundtracking:
Halee
Graphics:
Datenshi
Karaoke:
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing:
AphantasticRabbit
Ravenfire
Silence
Westfal
Zenef
Translation:
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
PamkinPinguin
rangicus
I'll get the hell out of here!