Team One Pace
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Timing
Datenshi
Graphics
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Pekoms Injury Fix
KaitouYahiko
Typesetting
PhosCity
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Special Thanks
Maktree
Cacao Island
The Straw Hat crew's
planned rendezvous at Cacao Island
12:28 a.m.
is in 32 minutes.
Nobody has come out yet.
One Last Thing
I guess the battle is dragging on.
Is there any chance that
Big Brother Katakuri might lose?
What?! You think there's
a chance Katakuri might lose?!
Newji! Are you...
serious?!
The chance of that is zero!
Ouch!
Why did you hit me?! I'm Newsan!
I wasn't the one who said that!
Katakuri will never be defeated
for the rest of his life!
He's right, you idiot!
Big Brother Katakuri is a perfect man!
Ouch! I'm Newshi!
I'm sorry, Newsan, Newshi...
Ouch!
That's what you get!
What?!
You idiot! You idiot!
But... he hasn't contacted us in a while...
It's strange.
If I were Straw Hat, here's what I would do:
he is planning to rendezvous with his crew
at one a.m., here on Cacao Island.
In other words,
his crew won't arrive until one a.m...
If I were in his shoes, I'd capture Sister Brûlée,
the only key to the Mirro-world,
and wait out the clock
in the Mirro-world or on other islands!
That makes sense!
Sister Brûlée is currently missing, after all!
That's right!
In other words, it's highly likely that Straw Hat Luffy
will try and run away from his duel with Katakuri...
and come out of this mirror at one a.m. sharp...
I see... I agree.
Sister Brûlée is a bit dense,
so she's easy to capture.
Akimeg, our sister might be listening
through the mirror.
Oh, oops!
We've got 30 minutes...
We need to stay alert.
Hurry up and come out, Straw Hat!
I'll chop you in half with my sickle!
Are they all fighters?
Seems like that's the only mirror
that they left intact...
When Luffy comes out,
we need to leave immediately...
or both of us will be killed...
When Luffy comes out,
that'll be when we part ways...
Pudding-cha...
So far away!
Can you hear me, Pudding-chan ?
D-D-D... Don't look at me!
I-I-I am listening to you!
Sanji...
...-san !
Looking back, we sure met
during unusual circumstances...
This is your bride-to-be...
Madam Charlotte Pudding!
Let's get married tomorrow.
I had a lot of fun with you, Pudding-chan,
but it's almost time for us to say goodbye.
Thank you for everything!
I fooled you and tried to kill you...
So don't thank me, Sanji-san !
I want to apologize!
I really need to apologize!
Shut up!
No! No! I did it again!
You're right!
We're enemies, after all!
To you, Pudding-chan,
our marriage was just a trap.
The whole thing was staged
by the Big Mom Pirates...
But...
maybe it was unpleasant
for you, Pudding-chan...
but I'm glad that you were the one
in the role of my fiancée, Pudding-chan !
Ah, no...
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to insult you!
No! Stop crying!
Stop, tears!
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't mean that, Pudding-chan !
H-Hey, Sanji...
...-san...
Could you do me a favor?!
Just one last thing...
This is all I ask of you!
12:37 a.m.
Whole Cake Island
I can't believe they've survived this long!
12:40 a.m.
The Straw Hat crew...
If they're able to escape
from such an all-out attack formation,
it'll be unbelievably big news!
Shut up, Morgans!
You won't be getting a scoop!
In order to ensure we avoid that,
we swallowed our pride
and sent a horde of soldiers to Cacao Island!
Even if Gold Roger, the former pirate king,
were to come out of the mirror,
he wouldn't be able to escape!
Once we catch them all, we'll execute them
and line up their heads for display;
you should put that
on the front page tomorrow.
It'll serve as a warning!
How vulgar...
There's no need to go that far.
Don't be silly!
It's almost too kind!
We'll get good news soon!
There's no way that one ship can
get through our gigantic fleet!
12:43 a.m.
Wait!
Bege's Ship
At Sea
Give me the cake!
The sails are on fire!
Put it out now! We're gonna sink!
We can't go on-rero, Father!
This is the end-rero !
We're gonna die before we
reach the island-rero !
Let's throw the cake off and flee, Father!
Don't falter now!
Rero ?
We may have all come
from different places,
but in the face of death,
we should stick together!
Father!
I see it!
It's Puffs Island!
Rero !
We're almost there!
Stay strong, guys!
Yeah!
12:45 a.m.
We'll make it by one a.m.,
just as we promised!
But what I'm worried about is the key
to escaping the Mirro-world: Brûlée.
Even if Luffy wins,
he can't get out of there without Brûlée!
I don't think Luffy is the type of person
who can think that far ahead...
You're right! He can't!
He definitely can't!
What should we do?!
First of all, we don't even know
if he knows the current time...
That too?!
So much could go wrong...
but we believe in you, Luffy!
12:47 a.m.
Even when he falls, he falls forward...
Listen carefully, Luffy!
At the earliest, we'll arrive in 10 hours!
That's around one a.m.!
So after you beat that guy up,
search for a mirror that leads to Cacao Island!
We'll meet you there!
What time is it right now?
Someday... will you...
come back here to defeat Big Mom?
Of course! I am the man
who will be king of the pirates!
You're seeing pretty far into the future...
Branch, let's go...
What? Branch?
She escaped!
Oh, no! I can't
get out of here without her...
W-What should I do?
I don't have time...
Big Brother!
Big Brother Katakuri!
Branch!
The name's Brûlée, Straw Hat!
What foul tricks did you use
to take down my big brother?!
So you were able to defeat Katakuri!
I can't believe it!
You're...
I am... Nazoms!
Nazo: Mysterious
NAZOMS
The Mysterious Savior
In order to help you escape from here,
I captured Brûlée and have been waiting for you!
So you're okay...
Pekoms!
NAZOMS
The Mysterious Savior
Pekoms
Yeah! Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself
to save your lives!
So I can't let you die here!
Come on, Straw Hat!
Let's go meet your friends at Cacao Island!
Okay!
Let go of me!
12:50 a.m.
There it is! Cacao Island!
How many are there?!
That's a massive fleet!
Sanji-kun ! How is it over there?
Luffy hasn't come out yet.
Don't get close
to the fleet at the shore.
I'll find a way to get Luffy to the ship!
12:55 a.m.
Does everyone have their weapons ready?!
Yeah!
If he's gonna come out,
it'll be in five minutes!
Now, come on out...
Straw Hat Luffy!
Four minutes to go...
That's...
I'm sure it is!
The Straw Hat crew's ship!
It looks like they saw us!
How could they assemble that many ships?
Sink Straw Hat's ship!
Here they come!
Oh no! We're gonna die!
Luffy, hurry up!
Keep our distance from the island!
All right!
What should we do, Smoothie?!
We'll continue to reinforce the back side!
They have nowhere to run.
The Totto Land Grand Fleet
led by Snack is ahead of them,
Plaza with the Mirror
Oven's Army
The Sunny
Smoothie's Fleet
and our fleet is behind them.
Even if they somehow
make it to Cacao Island,
Brother Oven's army is waiting for them.
They're already cornered rats.
This is their final destination!
Whole Cake Island
Link the transponder snails!
We need information from all angles.
Certainly, Seigneur Mont d'Or.
Cacao Island
Prepare yourself, you brat!
Come on out, Straw Hat!
Come on!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Help!
Sulong?
That's right!
We Minks can transform into our primal form
by looking at the full moon!
But I've always had trouble controlling it.
When I turn Sulong,
I'm nothing but a rampaging monster.
A monster?
I'll run wild and destroy
everything around me!
No one's voice can reach me, except...
for one person!
That person was Big Bro Pedro!
Stop, Pekoms!
For some reason, Big Bro's voice was the only one
that could calm me down in that mindless state!
Pedro...
So there's no one left in this world
who can stop my rampage!
Listen, Straw Hat.
It's the full moon tonight!
When I go out to Cacao Island
through the mirror,
I'll transform into my Sulong form!
When I go out of control,
that'll be your chance to escape from Cacao Island!
You idiot! It's no use, Pekoms!
You damn traitor!
There is a force at Cacao Island
large enough to launch a war!
Even if you transform,
they'll take you down instantly and it'll be over!
I'm gonna fall!
Shut up, Brûlée!
We're almost there, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Pedro sacrificed himself!
No matter what,
don't let it go to waste!
Okay!
Thanks!
Now, do your job for us!
What?
Let's go!
It's coming from inside the mirror!
Help!
Isn't that Sister Brûlée?!
Just as we thought,
she was captured by Straw Hat.
That bastard!
He's coming! Take aim and fire!
What?!
Is that...?!
Pekoms!
What?!
I'm Nazoms!
Pekoms! Why are you here?!
What?
D-Don't move, Big Mom Pirates!
I-If you do something stupid...
I'll blow your precious sister
Brûlée's brains out!
Brûlée!
Sister Brûlée!
Stop it, Pekoms!
Pekoms, what are you thinking?!
Why don't you calm down?!
Let go of Sister Brûlée!
Help! Everyone!
My identity was going to be revealed
by going Sulong anyway...
so it doesn't matter now!
I'll keep Straw Hat alive!
He's the man that
Big Bro Pedro bet his life on!
No way!
He's trying to turn Sulong!
Stop, Pekoms!
You won't be able to control yourself!
No!
Hold him down!
It's too late...
Prepare yourselves!
Hey!
You bastard!
Hey, hey, what's going on here?
Neither Katakuri nor Straw Hat
came out of the mirror!
How dare you point a gun at my sister...
for no reason?!
Ouch!
Big Brother!
Heat...
Cross!
Ouch!
No!
Yes!
That's Straw Hat!
Luffy!
This is Sanji!
It's Sanji!
Luffy...
made it!
Yes!
It's Straw Hat!
Pekoms was hiding him!
Get him!
He somehow was able
to outwit Big Brother Katakuri and escape.
That's pretty impressive!
I'm gonna go first!
Yahoo!
Look up!
You should know...
that jumping makes you an easy target!
Just surrender!
Brother Raisin!
Who is that guy?!
Sanji!
Did you win?!
Yeah!
As expected!
They're trying to escape through the sky!
That's Black Leg!
How naive...
We were prepared for this!
We can use Moon Walk, too!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Make it so he'll
never see the full moon again!
Pekoms!
Not paying attention....
is disrespectful!
When you're vastly outnumbered,
it's meaningless,
no matter how hard you struggle.
Dammit!
What?!
There was an explosion at the harbor!
What is that?!
Hey, what happened?!
The ships by the coast are burning!
What's going on?!
Was there a bomb?!
It's a fleet, Snack-sama !
Who the hell is it?!
I-It's...
Germa's fleet!
Why are they here?!
They were supposed to have been
wiped out hours ago!
Next, prepare to fire!
Germa 66!
Why are they here?!
Dammit!
You bastards!
Thanks for taking care of us
at the tea party,
Big Mom Pirates!
Germa 66!
Why are you guys here?!
What a coincidence, Sanji.
We also wanted a chance...
to shake things up!