Video Editing
Sewil
Timing
Bastia
Sewil
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Danpmss
DolphinWeabu
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Quality Control
Danpmss
DolphinWeabu
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Funimation
Yibis
Translation
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Funimation
Yibis
Opening Raw
Gavynnnnn
Run, Luffy!
No... No way!
I can't believe it!
Captain, we're screwed!
Sabo's Sea
There's no way to put out the fire!
We gotta give up the ship!
We can't flee to the sea!
That damn king!
Why would he go back on his word?!
I'll show that bastard!
Honestly!
It's so annoying that the sky
in the south is bright even during the night.
We apologize, Your Majesty.
Allow us to close the curtains.
Father, why aren't the people
in the Gray Terminal human?
Why burn them?
As the phrase goes,
"As a man sows, so shall he reap."
Think about it.
They could have avoided their fate
if only they were born nobles.
Born nobles?
You're right!
They should have chosen to be born nobles!
They're stupid!
Now, enough about those people,
you have to study for tomorrow.
You better go to bed.
Okay!
Goodnight.
Blocked off on this side too!
We're losing ground to stand on!
I don't wanna die here!
Think those old guys got out okay?
We can't worry about anyone else right now!
Damn! I don't even know where we are!
Who said you could escape, you brats?!
Bluejam!
Why are you still here
after setting the fire?!
I thought you'd be long gone by now!
Shut up, you little punk!
We're at our wits' end, you see.
We're in a bit of a pickle.
Humans are strange creatures, aren't they?
When we hit rock bottom,
we can't help but stand there and laugh.
They're being weird.
Luffy, let's go!
Stop them!
We all worked together as crewmates!
So let's die together!
We're not gonna die with you!
Never in a million years!
Cold shoulder, huh?
Come to think of it, you still haven't told me
where you stashed your treasure.
I'll rescue it from the fire for you.
Now tell me where it is!
You're about to die,
and you only care about treasure?!
Well, if you don't care, then tell me.
You've really lost it.
Not salvaging it would be such a waste!
If we just stand here,
it'll get reduced to charcoal like my ship!
Truly a waste.
Don't be dumb! That treasure is–
Fine! I'll tell you.
Ace! You and Sabo worked so long to–
Sabo would understand!
Right now your life...
Right now our lives are more important!
Ace...
We keep six-years-worth
of treasure in this tree.
I see.
Don't cry!
It's all right.
This isn't where it ends.
What are you doing?!
I told you where it is!
You're right.
"This isn't where it ends."
There's a chance you lied.
You're coming with us.
No way! You're gonna get us all killed!
Just go by yourself!
You don't wanna mess with me right now.
Even if it means robbing a few kids,
I swear I'll make a comeback
and get my revenge on the nobles.
And your brother is one of them.
They think they're so special,
looking down on us as if we're trash!
Sabo doesn't think like that!
He's one of them, you fool!
He spent time with you
because it made him feel superior!
That's not true!
His parents are loaded.
He wants for nothing!
This was all a cheap thrill for him.
All this time, he was looking
down his nose at you two.
Stop badmouthing Sabo!
Yeah, Sabo just wants to be free!
You little shit!
Luffy!
I'm gonna kill you!
Let go of me!
Don't hurt Luffy!
Luffy! You okay?!
What did you do?!
Dammit...
You creepy brat!
You looking to pull one over on me too?!
Shut up, scumbag!
You bastard!
Ace!
Don't do it!
Dadan!
Stop it, you sea mongrel!
Don't you touch Ace!
What are you guys doing here?
We found you!
These are pretty serious wounds, Luffy!
Are you okay?
Dogra...
I don't see Sabo anywhere!
Sabo went home. He's not here.
Ace!
You must be that
boss monkey from Mt. Corvo!
I'm Dadan: a mountain bandit!
It's a pain, but for better or worse,
I foster these brats!
That said...
Run!
You got it, boss!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Ace, hurry up!
Ace!
I...
won't run!
What're you saying, Ace?!
Don't try to fight him!
Bluejam's about as devilish as they get!
A kid like you has no hope of besting him!
– M-Me too!
– No, Luffy!
Fellas. Get Luffy far away from here.
B-Boss!
You can bet your asses...
Ace is coming home with me!
Boss!
Go!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Ace!
Boss! Come home in one piece!
A woman... and a child.
If you overestimate your abilities,
you'll pay in blood!
Only the strong and the cowardly
survive in battle!
The brave always die first.
Remember that.
Yadda, yadda.
Fools!
Damn!
It's no good!
We're surrounded by flames!
How did this even happen?!
– It's hot! It's hot!
– There's no way out!
It's hopeless!
What just happened?
There's a path!
That explosion created a path!
Whatever the reason, we're in luck!
Hey! Look! It's a ship!
I see a ship!
This path leads up to the shore!
It'll get us outta here!
Run before the fire returns!
Vhaat an awful sight,
burningk the land and its residents!
By the vayy,
I am curious to know vhyy you keep vaatch
over such a remote kingdom in the East Blue.
There is somethingk special
about thiss country, no?
This nation is a microcosm
of our world's future.
Happiness is but a pipe dream in a country
that eliminates those they deem unnecessary.
I swear to you all,
I will change this world someday!
If I stay here, I'll...
never be free!
Children are born innocent,
even in a country like this.
Those of you with the desire to fight for freedom,
come aboard my ship!
Yeah!
Royal Palace
Goa Kingdom
Is Edge Town really safe? The flames look
like they could consume us at any second!
What are the odds they would
let us up into High Town?
Zero.
Not even a bug could enter: nobles only!
– Boss!
Ace!
Boss!
Ace and Dadan,
left in the flames of the Gray Terminal,
did not return.
Now, now... Wait, Luffy.
Where are you going in that condition?
I'm gonna go look for Ace and Dadan!
Don't be stupid!
Your wounds are really deep.
Now, now, take it easy.
Right now, the Gray Terminal is crawling
with soldiers cleaning up after the fire.
And they're not just
"cleaning up" the burned trash
but "cleaning up" any survivors
they find as well.
If you go there now, you'll get killed.
But...!
I wanna see Ace!
I'm sure Sabo's worried too!
The Remains
of the Gray Terminal
Our orders are clear:
shoot all survivors on sight.
As if anyone survived this!
But I expected a lot more bodies.
It was a hell of a fire!
It must've burned them, bones and all.
I was really worried that the fire would
jump the wall and reach the city yesterday.
I heard even Bluejam's ship burned as well.
I'm just glad those thugs
were at least caught in the fire.
No matter how many times you run,
you can't get away, Sabo!
Both the city's police and military
have a picture of you now!
You will never escape High Town,
much less this house!
Discard those uniforms. From here on,
you two work for me as his bodyguards.
But we have our duties...
There is nothing that a nobleman can't do.
Your superiors will approve my order.
Sabo, you will hole yourself up in your room
and resume your studies
on upper class etiquette.
No!
As you know very well, I can make
things happen by just giving the word.
Imagine what I could do to you...
or to your two friends.
Understood?
Dad...
Ace... Luffy...
If you understand, then commit to a
change of heart and study hard like Sterry.
And now, go forth and study; bring happiness
to the mother and father who gave you life.
This in turn is your happiness.
Agreed?
Father!
Don't worry! I'm here for you!
You're so dependable, Sterry!
Alright! I'll buy you a marvelous new outfit!
The ceremony is in two days, after all.
There, we will see the
Celestial Dragon in person!
Make sure you have your
homework finished by tomorrow.
Well then, have a wonderful day.
Ace... Luffy...
There's no way you'd
die in a fire like that, right?
I hope you two are safe.
I really want to see you.
But if I do,
I'd only put you in danger again.
I feel like a bird in a cage.
I can no longer bear living in this country.
The air here is foul.
Freedom... what's it like?
Where can I find it?
Well then, we're off!
I leave Sabo in your care.
Very well, Master.
On this day, one of the world nobles visits
Goa Kingdom from the Grand Line.
A grand ceremony has been
prepared to welcome the ship.
Hey, hey!
There's a boat out there!
– What?
– Is it a fishing boat?
Hey! Turn back!
You'll disrupt the ceremony!
It's a child!
There's a child on the ship!
A child?
I wonder which family he's from.
The weather's great!
The perfect day for a voyage!
Hey, hey! That's my ship!
He stole my fishing boat!
Look!
He's flying a black flag!
Does he think he's some kind of pirate?!
No way!
Kids don't just decide to be pirates!
Where's he heading?
He's ruining the ceremony.
The World Government ship is almost here!
Hurry up and do something!
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey!
Kid, come back here now!
The thing I'm most afraid of...
is being consumed by this country,
and becoming someone I'd hate!
I'm never going back!
That's not Sabo, is it?!
The government ship is here!
What a huge ship!
It'd be bad news to run into it.
I'll steer clear.
To think we get this rare chance
to lay eyes on someone so divine!
An honest-to-goodness
Celestial Dragon is on that ship!
What is that?
Sir, it appears to be a fishing boat.
It'd be nice to be captain
of a ship like that someday!
Ace isn't dead!
Now, now, take it easy.
I know how you feel.
But you're in no state to go to the Gray
Terminal, especially with all the troops there.
– But...!
– But no buts! That fire was massive!
And chances are slim... but we all want
to believe that the boss and Ace are alive.
Dogra is already there searching for them,
so trust he'll succeed!
We are all just as worried as you, Luffy.
– The fishing boat's been hit!
– What about the kid?!
He angered the Celestial Dragon!
Sabo!
Damn! The ship caught fire!
Why'd they shoot at me?!
Saint Jalmack!
There's a child on that boat!
No matter who he is,
flying pirate colors makes him a pirate.
But most importantly...
Dammit!
How dare that lowly commoner
cross paths with my ship!}
Hey! What was that ship doing?
This is an important ceremony!
We don't wanna put the
Celestial Dragon in a bad mood!
Clean up that flotsam already!
Hey!
Hey, everyone, those two...
What is it?
Those two... they returned!
Thank goodness!
Ace... Boss...
She's severely wounded!
Hurry up and treat her!
Are you okay?
Ace!
Luffy!
Did you think that I was dead?
– But...!
– What're you crying for?!
You're acting like I died, you idiot!
Now, now, take it easy.
Luffy is just happy.
Ace, can we ask about the night of the fire?
After we left with Luffy,
what happened to you and boss?
After you left, we fought Bluejam...
and managed to defeat him.
We hurried and tried
to catch up with you guys,
but by then, the path was blocked.
Dadan was badly burned.
We hid by the river in the midway forest,
safe from the fire.
I snuck into town to steal food and medicine.
It was all I could do to keep Dadan alive.
Now, now, is that so?
Well, I'm glad you both made it out alive.
Sorry if I made you worry.
I never thought something like this
could happen to the Gray Terminal.
I'm sure Sabo is worried.
More insolent commoners might show up.
Remain ever vigilant.
Yes, sir!
I wonder what Sabo's up to.
Still, I'm glad Ace came back,
and Dadan is getting better.
Ace, back then...
I...
won't run!
...why didn't you run?
Sometimes, my blood just begins to boil.
I feel like, if I run,
I'll lose something I can't get back.
This time...
Luffy was right behind me.
I don't know for sure,
but I think that's why.
Even when facing an army
with no chance at winning,
Roger would stand his ground and fight.
Did he have death wish?
Fleeing is half the battle.
True, but he never ran.
Indeed, those dearest to him
were standing just behind him.
If they ran away together,
his crewmates' lives would be in danger too.
More accurately,
it's not that he never ran,
he just didn't want anyone coming after
his crew, so he never let the enemy flee.
When he got like that,
Roger was as fierce as a demon.
He was known to crush entire armies
just because they badmouthed a friend.
True, if you made him mad,
he was brutal, short-tempered, and selfish.
However, his actions were always
motivated by a pure, childlike intention.
He had a similar upbringing to Ace.
It's probably why he hated the
thought of losing his loved ones.
It was his reckless lifestyle—and the luck that
kept him alive—that made him the Pirate King.
Despite his worldwide infamy,
his crew trusted him implicitly.
Even though I'm a marine,
I could never bring myself to hate him.
That's why I decided to raise Ace.
I'm the one raising him!
Huh?! Got a problem with that?!
No. No problem.
Society continues to vilify Roger to this day.
Even if Ace hates his father,
the apple still didn't fall far from the tree.
Alright... Who's gonna win?
Dogra!
You went looking for Ace and Dadan, right?
They're already back!
They are? That's great news.
Wh-What?!
Sabo is...
You liar!
Don't even joke about that!
Take it easy, Ace!
It's not a lie, nor is it a joke!
It was so sudden that
I doubted my own eyes!
I kept thinking it was
some kind of bad dream!
Cut the crap!
Sabo went back to living a noble's life.
There's no way he'd sail out to sea!
That's right! Sabo went home–
Outlaws like us understand
how he must have felt!
We all have places we really
don't want to go back to!
Do you really think he'd go to sea...
if he was actually happy?
Do you really think he'd fly a
pirate flag and set out on his own?!
Sabo...
He really wasn't happy!
I was on my own even with parents!
Why... Why didn't we try
to break him out of there?!
Where is the person who killed Sabo?!
I'll go kill him right now!
Th-The Celestial Dragon?!
There's no way you can do th–
I'm gonna avenge his death!
Wait, Ace!
Drop it, you brat!
Get off me...
Outta my way!
Talk big all you want, but you're not
strong enough to do this alone!
What do you even plan to do?!
You'll just wind up dead!
You'll die, and you'll be forgotten tomorrow!
That's all you amount to right now!
It was this country that killed Sabo!
It was the world itself!
Think you can do anything about that?!
Your father's death brought about a new era!
Once you become a man of his caliber,
then you're free to live or die as you want!
Go tie up this moron!
Uh, right...
Sabo!
Damn it!
Shut up! If you're a man,
then stop sobbing like that, Luffy!
Have you finally calmed down, Ace?
Untie him.
Right.
I'll loosen these right away.
Where's Luffy?
He cried all night.
He's asleep now.
Boss! You have to see this!
I-It's a letter! From Sabo!
"To my brothers at Mt. Corvo - Sabo"
He sent a letter before setting out to sea!
Give me that.
I swear I won't go into the city.
That letter is addressed to us, right?
Ace, Luffy.
I hope you weren't hurt in the fire.
I'm worried, but I'm sure you're okay.
I'm sorry about this, but by the time
you read this letter, I'll be...
out at sea.
A lot has happened, so I decided
to set sail ahead of you guys.
My destination: anywhere but here.
There, I will become stronger.
I'll become a pirate!
Let's become pirates,
more free than anyone else,
and meet up again someday.
The three of us.
Somewhere out on the wide, free ocean.
I'm sure that someday, we'll meet again!
Oh, and Ace...
I wonder who's the older brother
between the two of us?
Two eldest sons, and one younger brother...
It might be strange,
but this bond between us is my treasure.
Luffy might still be a weakling and a crybaby,
but he's our little brother!
Take care of him for me!