Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Quality Control
Gab
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
Villager
Westfal
Zenef
Gab
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
Villager
Westfal
Zenef
Karaoke
Villager
Timing
Closed Captioning
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
Funimation
[MARINES muttering]
[ZORO]
You're going to be
King of the Pirates?
Right...
You must be completely
out of your rubbery mind.
Do you have any idea
what that means?
Yeah, when he first told me, it was
shocking, but he's completely serious!
That's how he is, I suppose.
[LUFFY laughing]
The First
[LUFFY]
Here's what I promised you.
There's three.
I couldn't tell which was yours,
so I just took all of 'em.
All of them belong to me.
I use santoryu: The three-sword style.
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Just know that if you fight with me now,
you'll be a government-defying villain.
So it's either that...
or you're left out here and killed
by the Marines execution-style.
What are you, the son of the Devil?
It doesn't matter
'cause if I don't choose your side,
I'll just end up dead on these sticks.
So let's do it.
[laughs]
So you're finally gonna join my crew!
This is the best thing ever! [laughs]
Would you quit celebrating already
and get these ropes off me?!
All right!
[LUFFY laughs]
What the...?
[mysterious music]
What is he?
Bullets just bounced right off him!
Straw Hat's no ordinary
human like the rest of us.
He must have eaten one of those devil fruits
that we've heard all those rumors about.
Devil fruit?
The hidden treasure of the sea.
[KOBY]
Come on! Hurry!
[LUFFY]
They... got... these...
things... on here tight!
Come on! Quit screwin' around!
It doesn't matter what abilities they have,
all who oppose me are executed!
If the guns won't work, we chop!
[MARINES yelling]
[KOBY yelps]
[LUFFY]
That's funny...
The knots got tighter
instead of looser.
Gimme one of my damn swords now!
[MARINES yell]
[KOBY screams]
Luffy, look!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[KOBY screams]
[energetic music]
Roronoa Zoro!
[KOBY gasps]
Wow! That's so cool!
Make one move and you die.
[BOTH sobbing]
He's scary!
[ZORO]
Today I officially become a criminal,
having fought the Marines.
So, I'll become a pirate.
That, I can promise you.
But I want you to know one thing...
While I'm with you, the only thing
I dedicate myself to is fulfilling my ambition.
[LUFFY]
Which is...?
To be nothing less than
the world's greatest swordsman.
If somewhere along the way
I have to give that up,
then I want you to
accept responsibility.
After which you get
to apologize to me.
The world's greatest swordsman.
Sounds pretty good.
The King of the Pirates wouldn't have
any less than the best on his crew.
Big talker.
From this point on,
no matter if I'm a criminal or not,
I will spread the name Zoro
throughout the world!
What're you standing
there frozen for?!
I want you to kill
all three of them right now!
You might wanna duck.
[bombastic orchestral music]
[ZORO gasps]
Gum-Gum...
Whip!
Yes!
You knocked 'em all down! [laughs]
Wanna tell me what you are?
I'm just a guy who ate
the Gum-Gum Fruit.
What's the Gum-Gum Fruit?
A rubber person?
[MORGAN]
It looks like he does have
the devil fruit powers.
Captain, we don't
stand a chance against them.
Yeah, just look at them!
They're insane!
We couldn't even take on
Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order!
Every Marine that just spouted weakness,
pull your gun out and shoot yourself!
I can't do anything with weak soldiers!
What babies.
This'll be easy.
[KOBY gasps]
Luffy!
Bring those Marines
crumbling to their knees!
[MORGAN]
Rankless, lowlife bums!
You have no right
to defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain
Axe-Hand Morgan!
And I'm Luffy.
Nice to meetcha.
[MORGAN yells]
[KOBY screams]
Look. He's been hit!
[MORGAN groans]
You runt...
Now, die!
[LUFFY]
I don't think so!
The captain's getting
pummeled out there.
It's embarrassing.
Call yourself a Marine...
but you destroyed
my friend Koby's dream!
[MORGAN groans]
Straw Hat!
Stop right there!
Look at what I got!
[HELMEPPO]
Are you stupid or something?!
I said stop!
If you would pay attention to me,
I have a hostage here you might wanna look at!
Helmeppo's crazy...
Hey.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
If you value your squatty little friend's
life, you won't move a muscle!
I'm serious! One move
and I'll shoot him! I swear!
[KOBY whimpers]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[KOBY gasps]
Luffy, listen!
Don't let anything that happens to me
stop you, no matter what!
Even if I die!
Of course. You got it.
You hear that, you big idiot?
Koby is ready to die by your hand!
[HELMEPPO]
Don't you move!
I said don't move or I'll shoot!
I swear it!
[energetic music]
Luffy!
[LUFFY] Gum Gum...
[KOBY] Behind you!
[MORGAN]
Time's up!
For I am fearless Marine Captain
Axe-Hand Morgan!
Daddy, hurry up and kill him already!
[LUFFY]
Pistol!
[HELMEPPO screams]
Nice one.
[MORGAN groaning]
[LUFFY]
Thank you.
I'm just doing my job, Captain.
[whimsical orchestral music]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[KOBY whimpers, sighs]
[MARINE A]
Captain Morgan's been beaten.
[MARINE B]
Unbelievable!
[MARINE C]
Those guys are unreal!
If there's anyone else who wants to
step forward to fight us, then do it now.
[MARINES gasping, murmuring]
[MARINES cheering]
[MARINE D]
We're free!
[MARINE E]
Finally! Morgan's reign is over!
[MARINE F]
It's really happening!
[MARINE G]
Such a glorious day!
That's weird...
Looks like they're all happy
that their captain was beaten.
They must've been afraid of him
for a long time before we showed up.
[ZORO groaning]
[LUFFY, KOBY gasp]
[KOBY]
Zoro! Are you okay?! What's wrong?!
I'm just...
hungry.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[whimsical music]
[ZORO]
Whew! I am stuffed!
[sighs]
Having not eaten for three weeks,
I was ready to gnaw
through my boot straps.
[GROUP laughing]
I can't believe you're finished.
Lightweight.
How the hell can you have a bigger appetite
than a guy who hasn't eaten in weeks?
[LUFFY]
It just tastes too good,
I guess. Right, Koby?
Uh, yeah, It's great.
Thanks for fixing it for us.
My pleasure.
After all, you guys did save the town.
You're the most amazing
man I've ever met!
Yeah, I am, I know.
I'll be more amazing when I'm King of
the Pirates, and I have the One Piece.
Oh, and the best crew on the seas.
Luffy?
Where are you and your crew
planning on traveling when you leave here?
You mean it's not obvious?
We're headed straight
for the Grand Line.
No! Have you completely
lost your mind?!
You have two crew members!
There's no way you're equipped
to handle the Grand Line, Luffy!
I've heard about it, but I never
knew it was such an awful place.
It's worse than you think!
You know that this world
has two oceans, I'm sure.
There is an enormous landmass
that cuts across both of them.
This is called the Red Line.
Legend tells of a town that sits
dead center on the Red Line.
The Grand Line is said to cut
through this town at a right angle
and stretch all the way around the rest of the world.
The story goes on to say that
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
had once obtained everything
this world had to offer.
Before he died, he said that he left
the great One Piece treasure at this location.
Ever since, pirates have set sail
for the Grand Line.
Today, the place
is nothing but a battlefield,
and some even call it
the pirate graveyard.
[RIRIKA]
I heard stories about it
from people passing through.
The customers say that no one
who has ever entered the Grand Line
comes out of that place alive.
Which is really too bad
'cause that's where the One Piece is said to be,
and that's exactly where we're going.
I guess we have to live with it.
No! You can't agree!
[ZORO]
What do you care?
You're not going with us, are you?
No... But I still worry...
Is it so wrong to care
about the two of you?
Luffy and I haven't known
each other for years or anything,
but I'd still consider him a friend.
Wouldn't you say?
Of course!
We may have to part ways
but we'll always be friends.
[KOBY]
When I was a just little kid,
I never had any friends,
much less anyone who would bother
fighting on my behalf.
[soft music]
So I always tried my hardest
never to fight for anything.
But the two of you have taught me a
lesson I could never learn on my own:
How to live for what I believe in!
So I've decided to make
my one childhood dream a reality,
and I'm going to join the Marines!
[ZORO]
Then don't you think you should be
a little more concerned with your situation?
[KOBY gasps]
I mean, you did spend two years
on Alvida's pirate ship,
even if you were nothing
but her cabin boy.
The Marines' information
gathering is top-notch.
They'll find out about your time
with Alvida, and you'll never join.
I... never thought of that...
[LIEUTENANT]
Hey! You there.
[KOBY, RIKA gasp]
We heard that you fellas
are actually pirates.
Is this rumor true?
Right, and I just added
the first member to my crew.
So pretty much the whole thing
just became official.
We appreciate everything
you did to save our town
from that horrible tyrant
who terrorized us all for so long.
However, now that
we know that you're pirates,
we cannot sit idly by and watch
you go about your business.
Therefore, you and your crew
will need to leave this town immediately.
[menacing music]
But out of respect
for what you've done,
we will not report
you to headquarters.
Are you crazy?
How do you find
the nerve to talk like that?!
[MAN]
Before these pirates came along,
you guys were as scared
of Morgan as we were.
[WOMAN]
Without them,
we'd still be under his reign.
We owe them our lives!
[TOWNSPEOPLE grumbling]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Well, time to go!
Thanks for all of the food, lady.
Hey, wait a second.
You're leaving already?
Yeah.
[LIEUTENANT]
Aren't you part of the crew, as well?
[KOBY gasps]
Uh, well, I... uh... I...
[LIEUTENANT]
Hold it!
Is he with you or what?
What I can tell you is what
he's been busy doing up to this point.
[KOBY]
Luffy! You wouldn't!
Yeah, there was this
fantastically fat pirate lady.
I think her name was Alvida.
Luffy...
[KOBY]
If they find out I ran
with a pirate crew,
I'll never join the Marines.
She carried around
this huge iron club and, boy,
she was the nastiest looking
woman I've ever seen.
For two years, this wimpy kid
was her own private cabin boy.
[KOBY]
Please stop!
You can't do this!
Luffy, no!
[KOBY yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[MARINES gasp]
[ZORO]
Hm.
[KOBY whimpers, gasps]
[LUFFY chuckles]
Now that was a dumb move!
[KOBY, LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY] Bastard!
Get out of here now!
We can't have you pirates ripping up this town
any more than you already have, you hear me?!
[ZORO]
Enough.
You made your point.
Now let him fall to the ground.
[KOBY panting]
It's obvious you're not
crewmates, so stop badgering
the poor kid and take your leave
of our town this instant!
[LUFFY]
Heh.
[KOBY]
Huh?
That was on purpose?
Luffy did that just to help me out...
He worked me up and got me so mad that
I'd hit him and look like I wasn't on his side.
Even at the very end
of our journey together,
I wound up continuing to rely on him.
I couldn't do anything for myself.
Nothing's changed for me at all.
[KOBY]
I am such an idiot!
Sir!
[LIEUTENANT]
Hm?
Please, sir!
Please, you have to
let me join the Marines!
I'll clean and scrub and do
any chores that you'd like me to!
I'll do anything to become a Marine!
Lieutenant.
I can't say I fully trust this kid.
I wouldn't be against the idea
if there weren't clear cases
of certain Marines
actually being pirate spies.
I say, we should conduct
a background check first.
No matter what you say, I am
a man who will become a Marine!
[LIETUTENANT]
Hmm...
I can't tell you
how many of our comrades
have been killed
by pirates over the years.
This is a big step you're taking.
So...
[LIEUTENANT]
Permission to join granted.
Sir!
[ZORO]
That was a thin act
you put on back there.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they see right through it.
[LUFFY laughs]
Koby should be able to handle the
rest on his own. I have faith in him.
[ZORO]
It is a fitting way to leave this place,
unable to turn back 'cause
everyone here hates us now.
Very pirate-like.
[laughs]
Yeah. It sure is.
[KOBY]
Luffy!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
I can never thank you enough!
You've done more for me
than anyone ever has!
[ZORO]
I've never heard of a Marine
thanking a pirate before.
That's one for the history books.
[LUFFY chuckling]
[LUFFY]
We'll meet again, Koby!
Someday!
Bye, Luffy.
Hope to see you again someday!
All hands...
salute!
[KOBY gasps]
See ya!
[LIEUTENANT]
That's a good friend you have there.
[grandiose orchestral music]
Yeah!
[LIEUTENANT]
Men!
Seeing as our current salute
is in violation of Marine law,
we will all go without food
for three days!
Do we all understand this?!
[MARINES, KOBY]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY]
Now! Let's go!
It's time for us to set our heading...
for the Grand Line!