Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Girl-Krillin
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Gab   Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack   Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Gab
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit   EvoWarrior5
panda :>   Poppy   Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll   Gaijin
PamkinPinguin   rangicus
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Ohara vs. The World Government
What's the matter, Robin?
Was my mom here?
What are you saying?
Why would your mother be on Ohara?
...I must sever ties.
I can't let her become known
as a criminal's daughter.
What's this about all of a sudden?
W-Well...
Oh, that's right! There's trouble!
I heard that Marine battleships are coming
to arrest all the scholars here!
Is the town blowing things out of proportion?
What?
There are no battleships.
We did hear about
a government ship making landfall,
but it's for an investigation,
likely more rigorous than ever.
Listen, Robin, although
the government representatives are here,
you absolutely cannot tell them
that you're an archaeologist.
Since you're such a small child, no one will
think that you're a scholar. Understood?
Move!
Stop what you're doing!
Hands in the air, and step outside!
Now, that's going too far.
The Ohara Research Center is suspected
of a criminal offense: deciphering poneglyphs!
We must conduct a thorough search,
so everyone outside. Now!
Treat this place with care.
The treasures kept here are
more valuable than you can imagine.
You're wasting your breath!
Get him out!
– Yes, sir!
Listen up, townspeople!
It is our suspicion that the scholars of this island
are devils plotting to destroy the world!
What?! Why?!
They're world-renowned scholars
and the pride of this island!
And so, we will conduct an extensive
search of the entire island!
In the meantime, those
uninvolved in archaeology
will prove it with identification and board
the evacuation ship at the western shore!
An evacuation ship?
Is that really necessary?
If it's the scholars' problem,
we have nothing to do with it.
We shouldn't be required to leave the island.
It's merely our duty
to pass that message to you.
What happens to those
who ignore our warning...
is none of our concern.
Leave town!
Evacuate to the western shore!
The World Government is up to something!
I've been shot! Th-This is the end!
I'm a goner, dammit!
Tell the higher-ups...
to give my position as chief to my boy!
Chief, please take a close look.
The bullet barely grazed your jacket.
Oh, I see.
I won't miss next time.
Well, if it isn't the fugitive
who craftily escaped the Marines' prison!
Fancy seeing you on this island, Nico Olvia!
You kept denying any connection
to the Oharan scholars, yet here you are.
It's almost as if you're telling us
this is where you call home...
and that the scholars here are
guilty of the same crimes as you.
Just my being here
isn't proof enough for that.
I'm sure you've come up with lots of excuses.
You're a smart woman, after all.
But none of that matters anymore.
We have no need to prove
your connection to Ohara.
If we dig up every square meter of this island,
evidence of your poneglyph
research is bound to turn up.
The government estimates a 100 percent
probability of this outcome.
For six years now you've eluded us
at every turn, escaping from sea to sea.
Capturing you is just
the start for the government.
We've apprehended many
a poneglyph researcher across the world,
each time searching for a connection to Ohara.
Can you guess why?
No...! You'll make an example of Ohara?!
Exactly!
If the holy land of archaeology were destroyed,
all scholars would get the message.
Then the world would see what happens
to those who dare research the Void Century!
Then, those Marine battleships standing by...
Hey now... Just how much do you know?
You are correct.
They are there to ensure
that not one criminal escapes.
But for legitimacy, we must first verify
a crime has been committed.
We're not pirates, after all.
That's why I came all this way.
I need to conduct a thorough investigation
of the island and evacuate those who aren't involved.
Yes, that's why I'm here.
Get her.
Hey, stop it! The books here
are a world treasure!
Another one?! Take him outside!
Come with me!
Dammit, you bastards!
There must be a hidden room!
Make sure you find it!
Northwest Coastline, Ohara
(Saul's Present Location)
This is terrible!
The battleships are already within sight!
Is this all of them?!
Now, gather all the scholars here!
Look. The scholars have been captured.
What could they have done?!
They said the scholars
wanted to destroy the world!
That can't be true.
Where's the evacuation ship?!
It's at the western shore! Hurry!
Hurry up and get to the western shore!
Robin.
There's an evacuation ship.
There's no telling what the government will do.
Hurry and head that way too!
No! Even if I get on that ship,
the people there won't be nice!
I'm staying here with you guys!
Robin...
Just like you guys, I'm a–
Just go already!
Working hard, men?
– We appreciate the visit, Chief!
I tell you, this is the last place
I expected to run into a ferocious animal.
I was nearly killed.
Olvia!
Olvia...
All right, listen carefully.
This woman is a fugitive.
Her companions were recently put to death
for deciphering the ancient script.
However, we still don't know
who the ringleader is.
Of course, if you guys are connected
to this woman, this will go much smoother.
They're treating her so cruelly...
Robin, go to the evacuation ship. Hurry!
Robin...
Robin!
You've...
gotten so big!
Olvia...
Wh-What have they done?!
Have they no respect for the library?!
To think they'd take things this far...
Oh, what a spectacle!
Hello? Is this the chief?!
Yeah, it's me.
We've found it!
In a hidden room underground,
there are research papers on ancient texts
and a large stone believed to be a poneglyph!
All right. Well done!
Well then, scholars of Ohara...
that means you all get the death sentence!
It is indeed regrettable that the world's
premier archaeologists will lose their lives today.
Man, what a letdown.
My job's done here!
All I can do now
is report it to the Five Elders.
Roger.
Professor, are they really going
to kill you?! They're lying, right?!
Just for reading ancient text?! Why?!
You dumb brat!
The purpose of their research is to revive
a powerful weapon and commit mass murder!
That's a lie! That's not at all what they're doing!
Robin, please stop.
As an errand boy, he wouldn't understand.
What'd you say?!
Is it really the weapon itself
that the government is afraid of?
– Professor!
– Professor Clover!
It's connected, Chief.
Okay.
This is good timing.
Huh?!
If I'm doomed to die, let me first speak
to the Five Elders, the world's leaders.
We, the scholars of Ohara,
have dedicated many years to our research,
and while we must stop halfway now,
we have a hypothesis about the Void Century.
I'd like to report it to them.
What a waste of time....
Hey.
Yes, sir.
Robin, get away from here now!
Listening to what I'm about to say is a crime.
Professor...
Hey, apparently the scholars
have been found guilty.
Is that true?!
Hey! Marine battleships are
sailing this way from the east!
They're gonna do something!
Let's hurry to the evacuation ship!
Wh-What the...?!
It's a giant!
Where are you, Robin?!
You need to hurry
and escape from this island!
Has the buster call been sounded yet?
We're still on standby.
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
So this is a poneglyph?
Yeah. Apparently, even explosives
won't put a scratch on this thing.
What a creepy stone.
I can't believe these things
are scattered around the world.
Is that right?
Yes, they will receive the death penalty.
We've seized all the evidence,
so now we'll carry out your next order.
It cannot be helped.
This is quite unfortunate;
however, they violated the world's laws.
We cannot overlook it.
Cut the transparent pleasantries, Five Elders!
Wha...?!
Don't be rude!
You're talking to the leaders of the world!
Is this Ohara's Professor Clover,
the eminent authority on archaeology?
Your reputation precedes you,
given your world-renowned cultural contributions.
To think that someone of your caliber
would take the wrong path...
The past belongs to all mankind.
No one has the right to stop us
from wanting to know our unspoken history!
Professor...
Deciphering the poneglyphs makes it
possible to revive the ancient weapon,
bringing danger upon this world.
Though your intentions are pure, it only takes
one person to find and abuse your research.
No matter what happened in the past,
we must accept it as our shared history.
If we fearlessly learn all we can,
we will be ready for any future incidents.
How idealistic.
Is that so?
Isn't that reasoning
just a convenient excuse for you?
Of the remaining unanswered
questions about this world,
we are most interested in the poneglyphs
and the very reason for their existence.
Why would the ancients take the trouble to etch their
messages for future generations on such durable stone...
inscribing history upon unbreakable stones
and scattering them around the world?
Is it not because they thought that their message
would be eradicated if they wrote it on paper or in books?
In short, it's proof that those who left
the poneglyphs most certainly had an enemy.
What are you trying to say, Professor Clover?
If we assume these people
were destroyed by said enemy,
then that enemy would have lived on,
unopposed, in the years to follow.
Coincidentally, just when the Void Century
ended 800 years ago...
the World Government was founded.
If the current World Government was once
the enemy of those that ceased to exist,
then the Void Century might be an inconvenient history,
brushed under the rug by those in power.
By analyzing the ancient documents
and what poneglyphs we could find,
we eventually discovered
evidence of a lost civilization.
The documents brought to light
that there once existed a grand kingdom.
It seems to have boasted
hegemony in its time,
but information on this country
has been rewritten into oblivion.
They likely anticipated defeat at the hands of the allied
nations who later became the World Government,
and so they inscribed their truth
upon those stones for future generations.
Indeed, those stones are the poneglyphs
that remain to this very day.
I see.
Quite a bold hypothesis...
It's true that the ancient weapon
would threaten the world.
However, isn't it actually that
the World Government is more threatened
by people becoming aware
of that kingdom's existence and ideology?
We have yet to fully analyze
the nature of this threat,
but this once-prosperous kingdom
is the key to everything!
And its name was...
Eliminate him!
Professor!
Ohara...
You bastards!
How dare you...!
– Professor Clover!
...has learned too much.
Signal the attack.
Don't move!
No one leaves the island.
Now, with this golden transponder snail,
which Admiral Sengoku has entrusted to me...
Professor!
Robin...
You fool! You shouldn't be here.
Run!
I'll initiate a buster call!
It's out of my hands now.
He did something!
Hurry to the evacuation ship, Robin.
No! I don't wanna be alone!
This is no time for foolish sentiments!
Robin...
Silver Transponder Snail
Receiver for the Golden Transponder Snail
That's the buster call order!
All battleships, to your positions!
Prepare to open fire!
Hey...
Look!
The Tree of Knowledge is on fire!
Hey, World Government! What are you doing?!
Taking our lives should be enough!
Don't look at me. It must've caught fire
from the explosions earlier.
This isn't a joke!
Do you have any idea how many
scholarly treasures are in there?
Hey! Don't move!
Listen. We don't need guns anymore.
Government agents, clear out!
Hurry up and get the books!
Put out the fire in the library!
Form a bucket brigade!
Get the books outside!
Bring that woman with us.
Come on.
There's a piece of information that only she knows.
We can't have her dying here.
Mommy.
Robin...!
Please... make sure you escape.
Don't die, no matter what!
Nose! Nose!
Robin, make haste!
Hurry and leave!
– Robin!
Are you... my mom?
Olvia! Are you coming aboard or not?
Mommy!
I'll hold her, so go already!
Don't go!
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
I'm sorry, Robin.
I can never call myself your mother again.
After all these years,
I shouldn't even think about it.
– Monster!
Her mom abandoned her!
Robin! Those are my daughter's clothes!
I'm sorry, Aunt Roji!
I wanted to try them on just once!
You eat an awful lot for a freeloader.
Are you...
my mother?!
What? You have a child?
No.
Olvia...
I'm sorry...
but I think you're confusing me
with someone else.
I can't let you become known
as a criminal's daughter!
Olvia...
What a weird brat.
Hey, let's go!
I'm Robin!
I've grown, but don't you remember me?!
I've waited so long for you to come home!
Are you...
really not...
my mother?
I wanted you...
to hold my hand...
and walk with me someday.
So I studied hard and was
able to become an archaeologist!
I can read poneglyphs, too!
That brat can do what?!
Stop it, Robin!
So...
please let me stay by your side!
Mom!
Robin...!
Please...
don't leave me...
alone anymore!
What?!
Why the hell are they attacking us?!
I'm exercising a buster call.
Commence concerted fire!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology!
The research by the Oharan scholars has
reached a level we never imagined.
Knowledge can be transferred.
Don't let it leave that island.
In the name of justice,
annihilate the devils of Ohara!
Dammit! What's going on?!
We haven't gotten off of the island yet!
Are they trying to kill us?!
The Tree of Knowledge is taking direct hits!
The military might of Marine Headquarters...
The government must have been
planning to do this all along.
How senseless.
Chief, the brat said she's an archaeologist.
Yeah, she did say that,
though I don't know whether it's true.
Eliminate her too, just in case.
Remember her face and ensure
she doesn't escape the island.
Let's move!
I'll take Olvia with–
Forget her! No time for that now!
Just leave her here!
If we stick around any longer,
we're goners too!
And my life is the most important of all!
Full retreat!
Get back to the ship!
Do something about the fire in the library!
Protect the Tree of Knowledge!
I've wanted this...
for so long!
Robin!
Mom!
It's my fault, Robin.
Is it true that you can read poneglyphs?
If I had properly kept an eye on you...
I’m sorry.
I just wanted–
I can't believe how capable you've become!
I'm so proud of you!
You must've tried hard and studied a lot.
It's not something just anyone can do.
You're amazing, Robin!
Fortunately, the officials from earlier
are the only ones who know about it.
This is no time to be sitting around here.
Olvia! Take Robin and run!
If you can sneak Robin aboard
the evacuation ship, she can leave the island!
Robin!
There you are! I looked all over for you!
Saul!
So you were able to see Olvia!
What are you doing on this island?!
By some twist of fate, I got shipwrecked
and was saved by Robin on the beach.
Anyway, the situation is really bad!
You have to leave the island immediately!
Please take Robin!
My daughter must escape the island!
What?!
No! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you coming with me?!
Olvia, what are you...?
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
Mom! Don't leave me!
I finally got to see you again!
I'll stay here too!
Robin...
As an Oharan scholar,
you should understand this well.
History is the legacy of mankind.
It will illuminate the future for your generation.
But the history we obtained from the past...
will disappear unless
we pass it on to the next era.
Put out the fire!
Protect the books!
Ohara doesn't want to expose our history.
We only wished to preserve
the voices of the past.
Our research ends here...
but even if Ohara is obliterated...
we cannot forsake
the future of your generation!
I don't understand!
You will... someday.
Now, go, Saul!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
I don't wanna go!
I wanna stay with you, Mom!
Mom!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Thank you!
From now on, for you and me both...
Live, Robin!
What?!
Vice Admiral! Vice Admiral Kuzan!
On the island... Yes, there's no doubt about it!
What's the matter?!
Just spit it out!
It's the deserter, Vice Admiral Saul!
Saul! Go back! Please!
No! I can't do that!
Robin! Hold your head high, Robin!
Your mom is honorable!
Ohara is honorable!
Someday, pass down
this island's history, Robin!
Ohara fought against the world!
Stop it!
Capturing them is enough!
They aren't exactly bloodthirsty pirates!
Are you too weak to capture them alive?!
We've captured many ships
that were on history expeditions,
but I don't understand
why this crew had to die.
Vice Admiral Saul! We found a lone survivor!
You killed my associates!
Do you really want the weapon?
What pitiful people...
You're just tools, yet you judge us...
Hey! He's a vice admiral!
...blindly believing your justice
prevents the weapon's revival!
You're terrified of a history
you don't even understand!
This is a top-secret mission.
A buster call?
Five vice admirals command ten battleships
in an all-out assault, and I want you to be one of them.
They are just scholars!
Why do we have to go that far?
Even all the ones we've captured just
seemed really intent on studying history!
If their research is dangerous,
the government should help them out!
My men and I will be
the ones taking their lives...
so give me some kind of proof
that they're evil!
Are you doubting the government?
Shut up and follow orders!
I'd like...
to ask you some questions.
This is an emergency! Vice Admiral Saul
took a criminal and deserted!
He knows everything about the operation.
After them! Capture Saul and Olvia without fail!
Shoot them if needed!
We're being chased!
I'll handle them!
You'll never be able
to return to the Marines, Saul.
That's fine.
I can't stay in the Marines
if I can't even trust them.
This may be a government-sanctioned action,
but this operation is too tyrannical.
I need to follow my own sense of justice.
Now, hurry to your homeland
to inform everyone.
I'm not thanking you for this.
Good luck.
Fire!
They're aiming at me!
Saul!
Oh! It hit him!
I'm sorry!
Don't apologize! He's already
an accomplice of those evildoers!
I'm sorry, Robin.
That must've scared you.
Hold on a sec.
It was you...!
Firing at this close range?!
What if you had hurt Robin?!
Vice Admiral! Please stop!
What are you doing?!
I don't know what justice is in this situation,
but I know I should protect my friend!
Stop it! Saul!
Get ready!
Making an enemy of me
will be the last thing you do!