Video Editing
Feeso
The Great Pirate Era
has proven to be a more tumultuous storm
than the World Government expected.
Graphics
Datenshi
The figures in the eye
of this relentless tempest are...
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Monkey D. Luffy...
Soundtracking
Halee
and the Straw Hat Pirates!
To confront the furious Great Pirate Era,
Timing
KaitouYahiko
PhosCity
fifty world leaders have come
together for the Reverie,
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
a quadrennial conference that will commence shortly.
Translation
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Now is a time of great change.
A Beautiful World
Here stands Fleet Admiral Sakazuki’s new Navy Headquarters:
New Marineford.
Two years ago,
the forces of Navy Headquarters
triumphed over the Whitebeard Pirates
during the Summit War.
However, the battlefield of Marineford suffered massive devastation.
Though Marineford
was long the seat of justice,
the World Government built
an even more impregnable fortress
to prepare for the rising fury
of the Pirate Era.
This latest fort of justice
at the entry to the New World
is New Marineford.
Fujitora is in Mary Geoise?!
Y-Yes, sir!
I told him to stay away
from all naval bases
until he brought me
Straw Hat's and Law’s heads!
I won't hear any lip
about how he forgot
what I told him on Dressrosa!
Oh, scary!
How dare he come slinking back!
That mongrel!
Y-Yes, sir, we all know
what you told him.
Then why didn't you send him packing?!
Well...
he had an airtight counterargument, and we had no rebuttal.
This is not a naval base.
That's just a technicality!
That damned vagabond monk!
Oh?
Difficult job, isn't it,
Fleet Admiral?
S-Sengoku-san !
Butt out, you semi-retired has-been!
Who else has gone to Mary Geoise?!
A-Admiral Ryokugyu-san !
Ryokugyu, huh?
Contact him immediately!
Yes, sir! What should I tell him?!
That should be obvious!
Tell him to turn Fujitora
away if he sees him!
All of you, go!
Y-Yes, sir!
Idiots! Every one of them!
And why aren't you also
returning to your post?!
It's strange, isn't it?
Straw Hat's bounty...
went up to 1.5 billion.
They say he's
"the fifth emperor" of the sea!
I'm amazed!
Do you see it?
The maelstrom keeps growing.
It was still negligible two years ago.
But now, the turbulence
of the Great Pirate Era
has rocked the whole world.
One Piece...
does exist!
It was just a dead man's
bad idea of a joke!
That damn Whitebeard!
Every last one of them
has fallen for his nonsense!
They don't know what it means
to rebel against us!
I'll teach them!
Despite its new location,
New Marineford remains the gatekeeper
to the Holy Land of Mary Geoise,
the home of the Celestial Dragons.
The place where the Summit War was fought is now Branch G-1.
The two naval bases are situated
on both sides of the Red Line
to protect Mary Geoise against invasion.
This is the Red Port.
It and another huge port like it
straddle each side of the Red Line.
They act as a means for the government to
scale the cliffs and cross to the other side.
Bondola 1, now departing.
Oh, Papa! It's going up!
Bondolas, gondolas that run on bubbles,
ascend to the Holy Land of Mary Geoise.
Look! Ships are arriving
one after another!
Yeah!
Make way for the royals!
Oh! It's King Beer VI of Roshwan!
The Matryoshesses are with him!
How cute!
Queen Mororon of Tajine!
She’s simply stunning!
Here's looking at you, world!
Better to die on one's feet
than to live on one's knees!
That's King Tacos
from the Kingdom of the Dead!
King Ham Burger of Ballywood
has also arrived!
Why does he walk so slowly?
I am a slow walker, but...
I never walk back!
That ship is...
Oh, that's...
the Great Knight of the Sea,
King Neptune!
And the big three
of the Neptune Army!
The Ryugu Kingdom
is attending the Reverie!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Akamambo! Akamambo!
I wanna have fun on land!
It's so bright on land-do-re-mi-fa-so !
Let's go, guys.
Akamambo!
Sir Garp!
I thought I was gonna die down there!
Hey, Little Miss Princess!
Get out here!
Okay, Shirahoshi.
Let's go to Mary Geoise!
Okay.
So this is the surface!
Mermaid Princess!
The Ryugu Kingdom has been a member
of the World Government for 200 years,
but this is only its second time
attending the Reverie.
Indeed, this is history in the making.
Since you fight the World Government
on behalf of the fishmen,
do you have mixed feelings, Koala?
Feelings on how the Ryugu Kingdom
is attending the Reverie?
Not at all, Betty-san !
Our true enemy isn't
the World Government itself.
Rather, it's those who control it:
the Celestial Dragons.
What a beauty!
Fire! The rumors don't do her justice!
Should we do a feature on her,
President Morgans?!
Princess Shirahoshi!
President Morgans?
Oh, no!
He's totally captivated by her!
Mermaid Princess!
Garp, Shirahoshi is very popular-jamon !
Even on land, Fishman Island's Mermaid Princess is rumored
to be as fair as
Pirate Empress Hancock!
But it looks like she surpassed
everyone's expectations!
What's more, she's huge!
S-Sir Luffy's dear grandfather!
Could that be what they call
a "forest” here on land?
That's just a tree.
Hey, Garp the Hero!
You know who I am, don't you?
No, you little turd!
Get out of the way!
"Little turd"?! Did I mishear you?!
Of course you did, Sterry!
You must have, right?!
What insolence!
I am the ruler of your homeland,
the Kingdom of Goa, King Sterry.
And since you're a citizen,
you're one of my subjects!
Remember that!
Sterry became nobility
when he was adopted by Sabo's parents.
With that as a stepping stone,
he sought any opportunity
to be part of the royal family,
and so he married
Princess Nantokanette.
A few months ago, following the untimely
deaths of the king and prince of Goa,
Sterry made his ascension to the throne.
The king of Goa, huh?
It's a peaceful rural kingdom,
but it's home to quite a few outlaws.
Garp being the exception,
there's the Revolutionary Army's
Commander-in-Chief Dragon and Chief of Staff Sabo,
and the pirates:
Fire Fist and Straw Hat.
What an intriguing place!
Now, prostrate yourself
before me, Garp!
Move it! Your face irritates me!
His insolence leaves me speechless!
I'll cut to the chase, Garp.
Clue me in to your connections
with the world nobles.
It's high time
I became a Celestial Dragon.
So you wanna be a scumbag?
What?!
Did anyone hear that?!
We could be put to death for that!
Right! I can't say that.
Forget I said anything.
This guy is scary!
Are you okay-jamon, young man?
What?
He moved?!
I thought he was a building!
Then is he a giant?
I heard they eat humans
and dissolve rocks with their saliva.
No, wait. What are these guys?!
Fangs?
Scales?!
Look at their skin color.
Are they the half-fish fishmen?
They’re classified as fish,
and people catch rare diseases
just by touching them.
Don't touch me!
Bondola 2, now departing.
All right, take care of yourself!
Sir Luffy's dear grandfather,
thank you very much.
It was fun to travel with you!
It's so high.
Unbelievable!
What's the matter-jamon, Shirahoshi?
Father... It's the sun.
Brother! The sun is shining so bright!
Yeah!
The sky goes on forever!
Also, the sea is endless
and sparkles in the sun!
Yeah, it's really amazing! Mambo!
I never knew the surface
would be so breathtaking!
What a beautiful world!
Mm-hmm.
The Sunlight Tree that lights up
the sea floor can't compare-jamon.
Father, I...
If possible, I want to live
up on the surface!
I would like to share
this world of sunlight with our people.
Then let us ask.
That's why we came to the Reverie-jamon.
Sakazuki-san said to find you
and give you the boot.
Is that a challenge?
No-siree!
That'd be a pain in the ass!
Besides, even you wouldn't
destroy this place, right?
Not so much.
What I mean to destroy is...
the system.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious!
You've traveled a ways to get here.
How's that old geezer Vegapunk?
Though I couldn't catch sight of it,
he has completed something incredible.
Oh? And that would be...?
We no longer need
the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
You're crazy! For real!
Anyway, the food here
is as good as expected!
You should try a bite.
Or are you still fasting?
Maybe if some young lady served it to me, I'd take a bite!
I guess I can't be bothered!
Haven't eaten a thing for three years now!
We're so high! Scary!
The wind is making us shake!
You're far too noisy.
D-D-Did you just see that?!
Pray tell, what did you see?
There was a g-giant in the wall,
staring at us!
H-H-He had a trident!
Clearly, you're hallucinating...
Consider our tremendous altitude.
But I really saw it!
And look there!
Now there are crows!
It's strange to see them so high.
Are these birds?
I've heard stories about them.
They fly!
If they peck at the bubble, we'll fall!
Hey, guard! Pull out your gun!
Shoot down the crows!
They'll pop the bubble!
Don't worry.
Please rest easy, King Sterry.
Eventually, the bondola arrives
at the top of the Red Line.
Thank you for riding with us.
Please watch your step.
Merfolk!
This altitude exceeds the limit of your bubbles,
so use these reinforced ones.
Yes, sir!
Wow, it's so spacious!
Guests must climb this large staircase to
reach the top of the world's largest continent,
at the very center of the world.
Somebody, carry me on their back!
We're almost there, King Sterry.
Those descended from the world's
creators reside here.
The name of this magnificent place is...
the Holy Land, Mary Geoise.
This is where the Celestial Dragons live.
I wanna live here!
What a beautiful place!
Is that green area a forest?
Yes, a man-made one.
So this is Mary Geoise!
The castle's still a ways off.
Everyone, please come this way.
Her Highness Shirahoshi and family, please use these handles.
Is it an earthquake?!
It's started moving!
I'm gonna die! Save me!
This is a travelator.
It moves the very ground.
Father, shall we
take the regular walkway?
Shirahoshi, you wanted
to see the forest, right?
Fukaboshi...
The scenery is beautiful!
Let's take our time!
Oh, I agree, Brother!
Hey, Father. Shall we?
I don't see why not!
We'll escort you!
I bet they're afraid
of modern technology!
Stupid fish!
Let's procure one for Goa!
This troublowter is so useful!
It's a "travelator."
You can call it that too!
What's this?
Something feels wrong...
Move at a nice, slow and steady speed!
Keep one pace with the other slaves!
Don't stop! Keep it moving!
Save me... or just kill me.
Daddy dearest! Daddy dearest!
What is it, Charlos?
It's a mermaid-ee !
A very big one!
Open the gate!
Seems like royal families and their bodyguards
from across the world are here.
Their bodyguards look formidable.
We're probably safe here.
The food looks fancy too!
If every day of the seven-day
conference is so festive,
none of the families attending
will get bored-fa-mi-re-do !
We love samba more than anything!
Would you like to dance with us?! Samba!
I'd be happy to! King of Samba! Mambo!
Mambo, mambo! Shake, shake!
Samba, samba! Shake, shake!
Even Father is enjoying himself.
That's a relief.
U-Um...
L-Lords and l-ladies...?
O, dear Princess from under the sea!
The rumors do your beauty justice!
Please consider him as a suitor!
He's royalty and single!
Papan! Not bad.
Not bad at all!
U-Um...
Your Royal Highness,
our royal-born son is also available!
P-Pappy! I like her!
Um... uh...
No, Your Royal Highness!
Please consider my royal-born son!
Our royal family has three handsome sons!
Now, which royal suitor do you like?!
Oh, um... uh...
Um... well...
None of you are my type!
What?! Even though they're royalty?!
Shirahoshi!
How dare you!
This is humiliating!
No, my sister was saying
"I'm not married, either."
That is, in an undersea dialect...
Brother Ryuboshi?!
When this happens, just say "How lovely"
or "Let's have dinner sometime,"
and turn them down
gracefully, Shirahoshi!
But then I'd be lying...
It's just dodging, not lying!
If you upset someone, it could become
an international incident-fa-mi-re-do ! Let's go!
How cute!
You're so cute! You're like a fairy!
That's not a compliment to a warrior!
Are you okay, Leo?!
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean to offend!
What?!
In that case, it's fine!
Oh good! She seems nice!
You're really quick. I wouldn't have
noticed you if it weren't for Karoo.
I showed myself because I heard you say you knew Luffyland.
We're subordinates of Luffyland's crew!
We're pirates!
Pirates?!
So cute!
It's nice meet you, Leo-san !
Nice to meet you too!
I never thought I'd be able to talk
so much about Lucy at the Reverie.
But it only makes sense if they're traveling the world.
Did Lucy visit your country, Vivi-san ?
No, I mean, did Luffy?
That's right! Luffyland!
Yes.
My home country, Arabasta,
only exists today
thanks to them.
Princess Vivi hails from Arabasta,
the Kingdom of Sand in the Grand Line,
and years ago became friends with the Straw Hats,
even sailing with them for some time.
All right! Anyway, no matter
what happens, our left arms prove...
we're definitely crewmates!
In order to take control of the country,
the former warlord
Sir Crocodile instigated a civil war
between the Royal Army and the Rebellion.
Please... stop fighting!
Please stop fighting!
Please don't fight... anymore!
Our nightmares... are all over.
Luffy and his crew foiled Crocodile’s plot
and saved the Kingdom of Arabasta.
However, the Straw Hats didn't get the credit,
as the government reported that
it was the Navy's achievement.
Since they never want
to be seen as heroes,
they received bounties
and earned infamy instead of fame.
I'm sure they haven't changed.
When I read about Dressrosa,
I knew that Luffy-san and the others
had decided to save somebody again!
That's right!
To us, Luffy...
The Straw Hats mean the world to us.
I miss Lucy.
Um...
Were you talking
about Sir Luffy just now?
Oh, the Mermaid Princess!
Shirahoshi!
Talking about him
doesn't mean they know him!
Luffy-kun is a pirate!
No one can know he's your friend-la-ti-do !
The Mermaid Princess knows Luffy-san ?
Hey, did you say
"Sir Luffy" just now?
Wait, Rebecca!
If we heard wrong...
Yes!
I did! Do you know him?!
Stop! Everyone knows his name!
I'm deeply indebted to Sir Luffy.
So are we!
Hey, Luffy-san sure
eats a lot, doesn't he?
Uh-huh! He had
an unbelievable appetite on Dressrosa!
It was the same at Ryugu Palace.
They're having fun.
They really are.
It's a good sign when those responsible
for the future of their countries get along.
Although, it's a strange connection.
Yes, it's all thanks
to Straw Hat and his crew.
Hey! Aren't you Rebecca from Dressrosa?!
Oh, I know him!
It's me, Sai!
I didn't expect to see you again so soon!
How have you been?!
I'm doing fine!
He’s from Kano’s Happo Navy.
I heard he replaced Chinjao as leader.
Yes, he's the new don.
Sai!
Hey there, Brother!
You came too, Leo!
I'm a secret bodyguard!
You're so reliable!
Right?
Is he a friend?
We both swore an oath to Luffyland.
Leo.
Up until now,
I've been working for Kano,
but I'm cutting ties
once I finish up here as a bodyguard.
This will be my last service for them.
I'm deeply indebted to Straw Hat
and the others for saving us in Dressrosa.
The Straw Hat Grand Fleet
numbers over 5,600 total troops.
We seven representatives should
be ready to assist him at a moment's notice.
Uh-huh.
The others are preparing too.
What did you say?!
You're suddenly leaving
the Standing Kingdom?!
Explain yourself!
I owe someone a great debt.
Barrier!
Barrier Crash!
You put up a barrier
by crossing your fingers.
Even children know that!
W-We surrender!
We lose! We'll serve
under you, so spare us!
Well then...
Put this on.
Wh-What is it?
Let's all support the Straw Hats!
Let's!
Two unidentified ships are approaching!
Are they remnants of Doflamingo's forces?
Cavendish.
As you may know,
I'm the former prince of Bourgeois.
Prince Cavendish!
But all the women in the country
were crazy about me,
and not a single one was
willing to marry another man.
I was expelled from the country
for being too popular.
So,
we don't need to attack them
since they're not our enemies.
Straw Hat is now sure to face
far more dangerous opponents
than Doflamingo.
We have to become stronger.
Yes! My crew and I are training too!
I hope we can fight together
for Luffyland again!
Yeah!
Well, well, Princess Vivi!
Wapol!
You hippo!
What are you doing here?!
It must seem strange, right?
Sure, Straw Hat Luffy
sent me flying to a distant sea!
But now I'm back!
Do you wanna know
how my darling came back?
Is he Sir Luffy's friend, too?
No. He's an enemy, Shirahoshi!
Old King "Straight-laced" Cobra
is well, I hope.
Oh, pardon me.
I noticed his failing health;
how tasteless of me
to have asked.
Oh, darling!
You're the funniest man
in the whole universe!
Wapol!
Give it a rest!
I can't believe you became a king again.
I pity your new country.
The World Government must be desperate!
I can't believe they'd admit this idiot again!
Dalton! The old witch hag!
You're still alive?!
Hm? Wanna know how I stay young?
I wasn't asking!
Dalton-san ! Dr. Kureha!
It's nice to see you again!
Hello, Vivi-chan. You look more dignified than ever.
Are ya happy?
If I knew that you were
a princess back then,
I would've charged you more.
Who are these people?
I met them when I was traveling
with Luffy-san and the others.
Nami became ill on our way to Arabasta,
so to find her a doctor,
we made landfall at a winter island.
Back then, Luffy-san helped Dalton-san get rid of Wapol.
Following that, the citizens
made him their new king
and renamed the country the Sakura Kingdom.
I see.
Hey, hey, hey!
Dolt-on! Earlier,
you told me to "give it a rest,"
which is strange to hear
from a subordinate.
That was long ago.
Now...
we are on equal footing!
Darling!
Dalton-san ! You have mastered
that kingly demeanor!
What? No...
Listen up, Dalton!
You bastard in shining armor!
An honest throne won't help you
run your country!
I'm living proof,
since I came back by making
a fortune with my
Munch-Munch Fruit power!
The higher you climb, the wider your view
of the corruption around you!
Consider this both a lesson and payback for–
By the way, did you read
that article about Luffy-kun ?
Yes, many times over.
Say, maybe... Dalton-san...
Do you like Lucy?
You like Luffyland, don't you?
He's the best.
This is gonna be fun!
Impel Down, the undersea prison.
The lowest level.
It's where the most dangerous
of criminals are locked away.
Level 6,
Eternal Hell.
What's with the solitary confinement?
I'm all by my lonesome here.
Or are you saying this is
for my protection, Magellan?!
Have they come for me?
An assassin from above?
They'll of course want to silence me
so I don't give away the secret of Mary Geoise.
Did they send an assassin to keep me quiet?!
And why should it matter if I tell?
Power is fleeting
with corruption close on its heels!