Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
Lance
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Translation
Funimation
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Captain Usopp
It'd be reckless to go straight
into the Grand Line now!
Yeah, some meat would
be nice to have first.
Eating nothing but fruit
everyday is no good...
We need some booze too!
What're you talking about?!
Forget that!
The Grand Line is the most
dangerous sea in the world!
On top of that, it's crawling with strong
pirates who are also after the One Piece!
And they're all on
powerful ships, of course!
We need more people, too.
The lack of crew members,
the lack of equipment...
There's no way we
could survive like this!
Yeah, we need a cook.
And a musician.
A musician?!
You're so stupid...
A little to the south of here is
an island with people living on it.
It'd be best if we can get
ahold of a real ship there...
Alright! Time to get some meat!
Don't forget the booze!
You guys!
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are attacking!
Pirates! Pirates!
Run for your lives!
Pirates!
The pirates...
are just a lie!
Oww...
You lying brat! I'm gonna
get you today for sure!
Stay right where you are!
I'll show you a thing or two!
Here they come!
Here they come! Here they come!
Get back here, you damn kid!
Just try and catch me!
Come and get me!
Dammit! He got away again!
He's one hell of a troublemaker!
He's in trouble if I find him!
Where the hell'd he go?!
Usopp
Village Youngster
Another job well done today!
I sent the wind of excitement
into this boring village!
There he is!
Oh, it's you guys!
Good morning, Captain Usopp!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Ninjin
Village Boy
Piman
Piman! Ninjin!
Is it just you two? Where's Tamanegi?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Oww!
Terrible news!
Tamanegi...
What's he freaking out about?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Terrible news! Pirates are here!
There's a boat with a skull
mark at the north shore!
Yeah, right!
Tamanegi
Village Boy
It's the truth!
Th-The truth?
It's true! This is bad!
Oops! It's time for my snack!
– Don't run away!
Actually, I have "I'll Die if
I Don't Eat My Snacks-disease"!
– Liar!
Don't you want to be
a real pirate, Captain?!
What good is a pirate
who's afraid of pirates?!
If I recall correctly, it was
Buggy the Clown's mark!
B-B-Buggy the Clown?!
I think I'll just...
But it was just two small boats!
And three people or so...
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
We must protect our peaceful village!
Alright, let's go! Follow me!
– R-Right!
There's a village past here?
Yeah.
It looks like it's a small one though.
Ah!
Finally on dry land again...
Careful!
I sense something!
Look out!
That's awesome!
Is this the time to be impressed?!
I am Usopp, leader of the great pirates
who reign over this village!
People praise me—and then they praise me
more—and refer to me as Captain Usopp!
If you're thinking of attacking
this village, then forget it!
My 80 million subordinates
won't sit by quietly!
Awesome!
You're lying, aren't you?
She saw through it!
See, you admitted it.
I admitted it to her!
What?! He was lying?!
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
80 million may have
been an exaggeration,
but I do have great men
under my command!
Like maybe three people?
– She saw through it!
R-Run!
H-Hey, you guys! Don't run away!
You're a riot!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
I'm a very proud man!
Because of my great pride,
people call me...
"Proud Usopp"!
You saw it yourself just now!
My slingshot skills are far greater
than your average pistol!
Now that you've drawn your pistol...
you've put your life on the line.
Huh?!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
Real pirates definitely have way
more punch behind their words...
Awesome...
We stole those lines!
Eh?
From Shanks, a pirate I respect!
Sh-Shanks?!
You know the great pirate,
Red-Haired Shanks?!
Yeah!
Village
Restaurant
Good, huh?
I met Shanks when I was a kid!
So, do you have any friends
in this village who know how to sail?
Or anyone who can supply a big ship?
As you can see,
we're just a tiny village...
Sorry, but we can't
live up to your hopes.
On the top of the hill...
There's a huge mansion.
Say! Do you know them, Usopp?!
Think you could ask them
to help pay for one?
You can't go there!
I-I just remembered
something I have to do!
I have lots of influence here!
So, eat and drink
as much as you want!
Alright! Later!
Why was he in such a rush?
Is this really the place?!
Yeah, the pirates dragged him inside!
We gotta save him!
But they're real pirates!
They might've grilled and eaten him!
You idiot!
It's old hags who eat people!
This will be the most epic battle
since the Usopp Pirates' formation!
– Yeah!
– The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Who are they?
Th-The captain is gone!
You don't think he...
H-Hey, pirates!
What'd you do with Captain Usopp?!
– What'd you do with him?!
That meat was yummy!
Meat?!
Don't tell me they...
W-What?! What did you do?!
If you're lookin' for your captain...
we ate him.
– Old hag!
What're you looking at me for?!
You just had to say something stupid!
Village
Mansion
You wish to see Usopp?
Not this again...
May I?
I want to talk to him.
That will not do.
That man is the biggest
liar in the village!
For the condition you are in,
Usopp's nonsensical stories
are the last thing you need!
But...
Klahadore
Mansion Butler
Your late parents entrusted me
with taking care of you...
to the fullest of my abilities, Miss Kaya.
Now then, I'll leave your medicine here.
Please be sure to take it.
Kaya
Mansion Owner
Jerk.
"Jerk" is fine.
What's bad is bad.
Usopp!
Heya!
You seem as down as ever!
I'm sorry!
I'd really like to invite you in
as a real guest...
but Klahadore
refuses to allow it.
He's not a bad person, though.
Don't sweat it!
After all, I am
a brave warrior of the sea!
I'd only feel cramped
inside a fancy mansion!
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
Hmm, let's see...
Alright!
When I was five years old,
I fought a giant goldfish
that lived in the south seas.
Goldfish?
Yeah!
What first shocked me...
was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
It's huge!
If our captain ran off
at this hour, he'd be here.
Oh? What's he come here for?
To lie!
That's a bad thing!
He's not bad! He's great! Right?!
Yeah! He's great!
How does that work?
Kaya, the girl who lives here, is sick.
A ship was stopped by the goldfish,
and on it was a pirate bigger
than even a mountain!
And she's been depressed ever since
her parents died from an illness a year ago.
His face was hilarious!
Even though she has lots
of money, she's so sad.
So our captain tells his special
made-up stories to make her laugh!
'Cause our captain's
the best at telling lies!
Never heard of a pirate with
a face like that, have you?
Oh, he's a good guy!
Yeah!
I like the captain
because he's a meddler!
I like how bossy he is!
I like how boastful he is!
And that's helped her feel better?
Yeah, a lot better!
Great!
Let's go ask her for a ship then!
Just getting in is impossible!
There are strong guards at the gate!
– Huh?
Where'd Luffy go?
I'll go ask!
Wait, you're not gonna...?!
Gum-Gum...
His arms stretched!
He's a monster!
Pardon...
Hey!
the Intrusion!
Huh?
Yahoo!
That worked great!
It did not!
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
to join the Usopp Pirates!
Hm? No we didn't.
We're here to ask a favor!
A favor? Of me?
Yeah! We want a big ship–
You, there!
What are you doing?!
Klahadore...
I don't appreciate you all...
breaking in here without permission!
A-Actually, Klahadore,
these people are–
That can wait for now.
I can hear all about your reasons later.
Now leave, all of you!
Or do you have something to say?
Well, actually, we want a ship!
No!
Usopp!
Crap!
I've heard all about you.
You're well-known in the village.
Quite impressive for your age.
You can call me Captain Usopp, too!
Since you admire me so much!
I've heard all about
your father, as well.
What?!
Klahadore! Stop!
You're nothing but
the son of a filthy pirate!
Nothing you do will surprise me,
but I ask that you stay away
from the lady of this house!
F-Filthy?!
You and the lady are from
completely different worlds!
Is it money you're after?
How much do you want?
That's enough, Klahadore!
Apologize to Usopp!
Hey, now! Be careful, Kaya!
What reason is there to apologize
to this savage man, my lady?
I am merely stating the truth.
I feel for you.
You must truly hate
your idiot of a father
for abandoning his family and village
because of his lust for treasure!
Klahadore!
Don't you dare insult
my father any more!
Usopp!
What are you getting
all worked up for?
Why not simply tell another
one of your outrageous lies?
Perhaps how your father is really
a traveling salesman,
or maybe that he's not
even your real father...
Shut up!
– Captain!
S-See! You immediately
resort to violence!
Like father, like son!
Shut up!
I'm proud that my father is a pirate!
I'm proud that he's
a brave warrior of the sea!
You're right, I am a liar!
But I'll never lie about
proudly being related to a pirate!
I'm the son of a pirate!
Captain...
A pirate, a brave warrior of the sea?
That's quite a twisted way
of putting things...
But you're the undeniable
proof of his savage blood!
You run around spouting lies,
and act violently
whenever you're angry!
And to top it off,
you cozy up to the lady of this house
so you can get her fortune!
What?! I only–
The fact your father is a pirate
is more than enough proof
that you'd hatch such a scheme!
Damn it, you still won't let up?!
Stop, Usopp!
Please, no more violence!
Klahadore isn't a bad person!
He's just...
He's just trying too hard
to do what's best for me!
Leave this place!
Never come near this mansion again!
Yeah, I get it.
I don't need you to tell me!
I'll never come back here again!
Usopp...
You stupid butt-ler jerk!
Our captain's not that kind of guy!
Yeah! You stupid-head!
Stupid-head!
Why're you saying it too?
– What's your problem?!
– Hey, now! Stop!
Come fight me, if you can!
You will all leave at once, too!
Your meal, my lady.
No thanks.
I don't want it.
The cook would be sad
to hear you say that.
He works his hardest to come up with
meals that suit your needs.
Why did you talk like that?
I know I was wrong to talk with
Usopp without telling you.
But you didn't need to
kick him out like that.
May I sit?
Go ahead.
It's been nearly three years...
since the day I came to this mansion.
I'll never forget what
happened that day...
I was kicked off the ship I worked on
because of a mistake I made.
And with no work or money,
I was on the verge
of dying like a beggar.
In my eyes, I owe my life
to your late parents...
And to you, their daughter.
I realize that it isn't my place
to interfere with your friendships.
But that Usopp kid isn't exactly
known for his upstanding character!
If... if anything should happen to you,
I would never be able to ask for
forgiveness from your kind parents!
Do you think ill of me
for what I did earlier?
No, not at all!
I'm glad to have you too, Klahadore!
But please don't misunderstand.
Usopp is a very nice person.
However, whether he's
nice or not is irrelevant!
Klahadore! You blockhead!
Yes, "blockhead" will do just fine!
Where'd Luffy go?
Who knows. Probably ran
after the "captain."
Our captain would be at his spot!
Yeah, the shore!
He always goes there
when something happens!
Well never mind that,
isn't one of you missing?
– Yeah, Tamanegi!
He always disappears!
Yeah! And then he
shows up all freaked out!
Bad news!
See?
A backwards guy!
A weird guy is walking
backwards this way!
– Liar!
It's the truth!
Just look!
Hey! Who's calling me weird?!
Jango
Hypnotist
I'm not weird.
You seem pretty weird to me.
Don't be stupid!
I'm just an ordinary, passing hypnotist!
H-Hypnotist?! Awesome!
Show us something!
Yeah! Do a trick!
What?!
Don't be dumb!
Why should I have to reveal
my techniques to
a bunch of strangers?!
Alright.
Watch this ring closely.
So, you are going to?!
You'll fall asleep at the count
of "one, two, Jango."
Alright, here we go!
One.
Two.
Jango!
Hey! What's with this guy?!
Yo!
Here you are!
Oh, it's you! Don't just
sneak up like that!
So what? Do you want something?!
Yeah. Your dad's Yasopp, right?
Oww...
Yeah, Yasopp is my old man...
But how do you know that?
No matter what anyone says,
Yasopp is a great pirate!
Awesome!
That's nothing. I could even shoot
an ant right between the eyes!
Y'know, Luffy,
I got a kid named Usopp,
who's just about your age!
I know! You've already
told me lots of times!
What?!
Well, I'm gonna tell you some more!
It was sad to say goodbye,
but there was no other choice!
There was but one reason:
the pirate flag was calling me!
Stuck! Stuck!
Really?!
My old man's on such
an awesome ship?!
I dunno about now,
but I bet he's still with him.
After all, your dad is
a great sharpshooter!
In this day and age
where pirates are everywhere,
I'm proud of my old man
for risking his life out at sea!
Yet, that bastard stomped
all over his name!
He'll pay for this!
I hate that guy too.
So you're not gonna go
see that girl anymore?
Y-Yeah, I dunno...
If that butler comes and apologizes
to me, I might consider it.
That butler?
Yeah, that butler...
What's that butler doing out here?!
Hey! Let go!
Hey, Jango.
I told you to avoid doing
anything to make you stand out.
Yet there you are sleeping
in the middle of the village...
Don't be stupid.
I don't stand out one bit.
I'm not weird, either.
There's someone else with him.
Some weird guy...
Never seen him before. Who is he?
So, preparations for the plan
are ready, I hope?
Of course.
We can start anytime...
The Mistress Assassination Plan!
A-Assassination?!