Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
It was warm just a little while ago.
All right! Done!
This is the man that fell from the sky, Mr. Snow Barrel!
That's such a crude snowman...
What?!
Look at my soulful artwork, the Snow Queen!
Whoa! That's incredible!
Okay then! Snow Barrel Punch!
What the hell are you doing?!
Ahh! Mr. Snow Barrel!
How dare you...!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
How come they're so energetic when it's this cold?
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Nami! How much snow shoveling of love would you like me to do?!
Please continue until it stops snowing, Sanji!
Yaay! Nami!
Hey, you. Doesn't this ship have a heater?
I'm cold.
Shut up! You guys aren't guests! Go help shovel snow or something!
Lightning?!
What on earth is going on with the weather around here?!
It was sunny up until recently.
The next moment, it started snowing, and now lightning...
The seasons, as well as the weather, go around randomly.
That's how it is in the Grand Line.
It's just like what Crocus said.
It seems that you guys're clueless about the Grand Line.
You haven't been steering for a while now. Is that really okay?
I just checked the direction.
Ahhhh!
Wh... What?
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Nami?!
Ahhh... No way!
Turn the ship around 180 degrees! Hurry!
180 degrees?! Why're we going back?!
Did you forget something?
The ship has turned around and is going in the opposite direction!
When I looked away from the log pose for a second...!
The waves were calm earlier...
Are you really a navigator?
In this sea, you can't trust the winds, sky, waves, clouds... anything...
The only thing that doesn't change is the direction that the log pose points.
Do you understand that?
Stop bossing me around in those cozy blankets and go help already!
Brace the yard!
Receive the wind from the starboard! Turn the ship 180 degrees to the left!
Got it!
Usopp! Take care of the lateen sail!
–Sanji! Take the helm! –Leave it to me, Nami!
You guys! I'm counting on you!
She's such a slave driver.
Hey, wait! The wind has changed.
No way!
It's the first spring gale!
Why?!
Don't just sleep there while the snow accumulates on you!
Hey! I saw a dolphin jump over there! Let's go there.
You keep quiet!
The waves are getting high!
I see an iceberg in the 10 o'clock direction!
Nami! It's getting foggy!
What the hell's with this sea?!
W-w... we're gonna crash!!
Hey! Water's leaking at the bottom of the ship!
We have to patch it right away!
Got it!
The clouds are moving fast!
W-wind's coming!
It's strong!
It's coming!
Unfurl the sails! That wind is too strong!
If we take it directly, we'll overturn!
Everyone! Eat this! Let's gather our strength!
You're eating too much!
Oh crap! The sail is gonna be torn!
Forget about things up here. Go fix the bottom of the ship!
There's another part of the bottom of the ship damaged!
Dammit!
Ahhh, that felt good.
Hey, no matter how nice the weather is, you guys shouldn't be so lazy.
We'd better be on the right track.
You...
Hm?
Why're you guys on this ship?
You're slow!
We're heading to their town right now. It's called Whisky Peak.
You mean we're taking them back? We don't owe them anything.
Right, we don't.
Well, not like it matters to me...
Yeah, your faces say that you're thinking bad thoughts.
What were your names again?
I-I'm Mr. 9.
I'm Miss Wednesday.
Right... Something has been bothering me ever since I first heard your names...
I feel like I've heard them somewhere before, or maybe not...
Well, either way...
How dare you sleep comfortably all this time...
You kept sleeping no matter how many times we tried to wake you up...
What?!
Don't let your guard down, everyone! We don't know what else might happen.
I was finally able to realize the danger of this sea just now.
I was able to understand the reason why it's called the Grand Line.
There's no doubt about it since my navigation skills don't work at all.
How blunt... Are we gonna be okay?
We'll be fine! Things will still work out for sure.
In fact...
Look! Our first journey is over.
It's an island!
So this is Whisky Peak...
But it's really a funny looking island.
Those cacti are huge!
Hm?
Well then, we'll be leaving now.
Thanks for taking us home, honeys.
If we're linked by fate, we'll meet again!
Bye bye, baby!
Huh?
They're gone...
Who on earth were they?
Who cares! We're landing!
Huh? Something's moving.
Humans? Humans are there!
Welcome to the Grand Line!
Welcome to our town!
To the welcoming town, Whisky Peak!
F... Far from monsters, we're being welcomed!
What's going on?
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
Hurray for the heroes on the sea!
Whoa! There're lots of cute girls!
Ahh! Look this way! They're handsome!
Maybe pirates are people's heroes after all.
Heeeey!
Welco...
Ma-ma-ma...
Welcome.
My name is Igarappoi. I'm the mayor of Whisky Peak.
Okay. I'm Luffy. Nice to meet you.
Pops, you went overboard on curling your hair.
Whisky Peak is a town that thrives on making liquor and music.
Hospitality is the pride of our town.
As for our proud liquor, it's as bountiful as the seawater.
Would you allow us to throw a party for you so that we may hear your tales of...
Ma-ma-ma...
your tales of adventure?
We'll be glad to!
All right!
Three idiots...
Say, by the way,
how long will it take for the log of this island to be stored?
Log? Forget such boring stuff.
Please just rest after such a long journey.
Now, everyone! Prepare for the party! Sing to entertain the adventurers!
Party time!!
Then I said with utter coolness, "Sea Kings, don't you touch my friends."
Wow...
–Captain Usopp!
You're so amazing!
Well, regarding the Calm Belt, even I trembled a bit, though.
A tremble of excitement, that is.
Amazing!
Whoa!
Cheers to Usopp!
Whoa! Amazing! He finished his 10th cup!
This is it. I can't drink any more.
This girl's downing her 12th cup!
Take that!
More food!
Whoa! The captain finished a meal for 20 people!
The cook is down!
Please, I can't go on...
Whoa! This young man is trying to hit on 20 girls at the same time!
What's with this gang?!
It's really a fu...
Ma-ma-ma...
a fun night!
I'm glad that you all seem to be having fun.
Yes, indeed, I'm very glad...
For that reason, we failed our mission of securing food... however,
we'd like to report that we succeeded in leading the gang to Cactus Island. Baby.
All right! If we submit this, we somehow should be able to clear our names.
Right. I'll drop it in the Unluckies Box immediately.
They'll deliver it for us...
to the boss...
This is it. I quit. I'm gonna sleep.
Whoa! The young man is finally down after his 13th cup.
What?! You're hopeless, Zoro!
There're only two left.
They're at the 15th cup. She's competing against the sister.
You should quit soon, too, for your own sake.
Don't be silly! I definitely won't quit until I get the prize money.
Ahhh! Thanks for the food. I can't eat any more.
Three cooks are also down!
Glad you enjoyed it.
I can't drink any more.
I won!!
Ahh, what fun!
She's finally down.
What a nice town...
This is a paradise.
So they wore themselves out partying and fell asleep...
Sweet dreams...
adventurers...
Again tonight the Cactus Rocks look beautiful,
dancing under the moonlight.
You're such a poet, Igarappoi, no, Mr. 8.
Oh, it's you guys...
What happened to them?
They've fallen...
to hell...
Geez... Since they were so stubborn, I added a little alcohol in their drinks.
Otherwise they might still be up and having a good time.
But was it really necessary to put on an elaborate act...
for just five weak looking brats?
We should've beat them at the harbor. This town is already short of food.
Also we didn't have our hopes up for the whale meat anyway.
You didn't have to say it like that! We did try our best!
Calm down. Look at this. I've checked them out beforehand.
Th-thirty million belly?!
Them?!
It's foolish to judge a pirate's ability based on their looks, Miss Mon...
Ma-ma-ma...
Miss Monday.
S-sorry.
But we've already settled.
Looks like we can send a good report to the boss.
Confiscate all the money and other valuables on the ship immediately.
What do we do?
If we kill them, the bounty drops by 30%.
The government wants to hold public executions.
Go! Capture them alive!
Hey... Sorry, but...
do you mind letting them sleep?
They're all exhausted from the journey this afternoon.
Mr. 8! Miss Monday!
The guy with the bellyband escaped from the room when we weren't looking!
He's over there.
You bastard...! I thought you were completely asleep!
Swordsmen never make the mistake of letting their guard down that much.
So, let's see if I've got this right. This is a nest of bounty hunters.
You dupe pirates who are in high spirits after having just entered the Grand Line.
Looks like there're about 100 bounty hunters here.
I'll fight you all... Baroque Works!
You bastard! How is it that you know our company's name?!
When I used to be in a similar line of work, I was recruited by your company once.
Naturally, I rejected it.
Employees don't know each other's identity and are called by code names.
Of course, the boss' whereabouts and his identity are also a mystery, even to them.
Baroque Works is a criminal group that just faithfully carries out their orders.
Humph...! Was it a secret?
This is surprising...
If you know our secrets,
then we have no other choice but to kill you.
Another gravestone...
will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Kill him!
H-he's gone!
Wh-where the heck did he disappear to?!
What?!
Ahh!
All right then.
Shall we?
How dare you mock us!
Fire!
Idiots! They shot each other!
H-he disappeared again!
Darn! Kill him already! It's just a single swordsman!
Let me ask you a question.
Are you sure that you need to add only one gravestone?
There he is!
I-idiots! Don't! Are you gonna shoot me, too?!
Stop! Igarappa!
Where did that man disappear to?
Phew.
So that's a shotgun? That thing sure is dangerous.
It seems he's good enough that even we must be cautious.
Does he seriously think that he can fight all of us by himself?
It's hard to believe that he challenged us
even after knowing we're with Baroque Works.
The new recruits that I got in Loguetown, Yubashiri and Kitetsu III...
This is a good chance to try you guys out in earnest.
I'm going to go all out!
There you are!
Die!
Tsk! Dammit!
First, I'll try Yubashiri.
It's light! This is a good sword!
There he is! This way!
Hold it!
Looks like they found me!
He went up!
Welcome!
Whoa! That thing's dangerous!
This is it for you.
Miss Monday!
Ahh... That was an expensive drink.
What a waste!
What was that feeling in my hand just now?!
How sharp this Kitetsu III is!
A legendary sword cuts only when its master wishes it,
but this one is a problem child. So this is what a cursed sword is like.
Huh?
I beg you for mercy.
Lord have mercy!
Lord have mercy! Please save us!
Merciful Lord Blinding Powder!
You should use such a cheap trick on someone with a pure heart.
I used the back of the blade, so forgive me.
He went further up!
There's nowhere to escape up there!
Corner him!
S-Stop it!
Help me! Help me!
The ladder's falling!
Ahh! He's jumping over here!
Shoot him!
Two Swords Style!
Hawk Wave!
Watch out. That place is unstable.
What?
That was close! It grazed me!
Don't try our patience.
There's no man who can best my strength.
This is the end of you.
Superhuman...
Brass Knuckles!
We've wast...
Ma-ma...
We've wasted time, but we finally settled it. The End!
What?!
M... Miss Monday!
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Didn't you want to have a contest of strength?
Well?!
Shall we continue, Baroque Works?
Fighting isn't a joke.