Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking                    Halee
Timing
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
JT-421         Galaxy9000
TheFVguy
Translation
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Rokitoki
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Rokitoki
Klabautermann
Fire!
Hey, everyone! Get up!
Dammit! Did the pirates do this?
There's still a bunch of people inside!
Where's Mr. Iceburg?!
What's going on upstairs?!
Let's go check!
Hurry!
Pitch in and put out the fire!
The fire has started to spread.
I don't care if you're
a leopard man or whatever...
I won't let you lay a hand on Mr. Iceburg!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Oh, no!
Carnivore zoans are far more ferocious!
That's right.
Whether logia, zoan, or paramecia,
all devil fruits have their unique characteristics.
But the only one that offers
pure physical augmentation
would be the zoans.
The more we train,
the more power we gain.
Zoans are head and shoulders
above the rest in close-quarters combat.
– Mr. Iceburg!
– Foremen!
Lucci, the shipwrights are coming upstairs.
Don't worry.
They won't make it here.
Tempest Kick!
Get back! The ceiling...
Nami!
Chopper!
Paulie, what're you doing?
Ain't no way in hell I'm leavin' you here!
You can't! Not with those wounds!
Stop, Paulie.
Don't talk to me... like we're friends!
Damn it!
Why did it have to be you guys?!
I...
After all this time...
I always thought of you guys as my friends!
The feeling isn't mutual.
You dumb pigeon!
Straw Hat!
Finger Pistol.
Luffy!
Have a nice flight off the island!
You bastard!
Iron Body.
Zoro!
You too.
Did you get everyone out?!
We can't go back inside!
Have each team account for its men!
Hey, where's Mr. Iceburg? Did you see him?
Don't tell me he's still in there...
I'm sure he's okay!
Three foremen were with him;
no way they left him behind.
You guys go check over there too!
This woman...
She's one of the Straw Hats.
I'm sure of it!
Did she jump out of a window?
She must've narrowly escaped from the blaze.
What should we do with her?
Seriously... They caused this mess.
We'll make her tell us where the others are!
We'll round up the rest of them
and hand them over to the Navy!
A pirate's testimony
will never pass as evidence.
This incident will fade into obscurity.
Mr. Iceburg...
You may be a renowned shipwright
and the mayor of a great city...
but you, a mere citizen, should never
defy our glorious World Government.
Let's go.
We'll find Tom's other disciple Franky—
rather, Cutty Flam,
and take the blueprints from him.
Grandma! Grandma! It's a huge fire!
Meow!
That's Galley-La's main office.
This is just terrible.
What do you mean?
Did somebody set the fire?
Well, I don't know for certain...
but often,
a bad feeling turns out to be right.
I do hope Iceburg's all right.
It's a shame that one little thing
can be at the root of so much trouble.
Blueno, you said Franky was at your bar?
Yeah.
But he ran off to find Straw Hat.
I see.
I don't suppose he'd make
himself easy to find.
Talk about being in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Look.
Listen, Straw Hat!
We've got long nose!
That's right, we do!
If you don't want us
to sew him to a tree–
Idiot! How do you not get it yet?
It's, "If you don't want us
to throw him in the sea!"
Sew him in–
Throw him!
Dammit, do you even listen?!
What matters more is getting
the message to Straw Hat, right?
Well, your message doesn't make any sense!
Bro's gonna beat you up.
"If you don't want us to throw him in the sea,
come to the warehouse under the bridge!
From, Franky!"
Got that?!
Even if he does come,
Big Bro's still gonna beat the piss outta him.
Who did you say is waiting for whom, and where?
Hm? Who the hell are you?!
We're in the middle of somethin', so scram!
Answer me in three seconds,
or you're all dead men.
Huh?!
This guy's talking outta his ass.
Don't you know who we are?
Where is this warehouse under the bridge?
Franky is there, isn't he?
What business do you have with Big Bro?
If you wanna talk to him,
you'll have to go through us first!
Main Bridge Opposite the Garbage Dump
Northeast Shore, the Narrows, Water Seven
A Warehouse Under the Bridge
(Franky's Secret Base)
I can't believe you and your East Blue friends
came all this way just to split up over a ship!
Why are you guys crying?
Don't be dumb!
We're not crying, dummy!
It was just so moving that you
stuck it out with your ship
even with everything going on!
We're not crying!
Nobody here is crying!
What's wrong with these people?
Anyway, you gotta realize I'm not friends
with those guys anymore, right?
I...
Here's a little ditty about your hardships!
It's called,
"Falling Out: Northern Wind Chop!"
Yay! Big Bro!
Are you making fun of me?!
Hey, is the tea ready yet?
I'm thirsty.
– All done! Coming right up!
I'm exhausted from crying...
Not that I was crying, though.
Here, Bro. It's a little hot.
Thanks.
All right, I get it, bro. You know...
Ouch, it's hot!
Just chill out, damn it!
Sorry 'bout that, Big Bro.
Why don't you take a break
and have some tea, too?
I don't blame you.
You must be pretty mad at us for stealing
that 200 million belly from you guys...
especially since it led to such a big fight.
What happened, happened.
Holding a grudge won't do me any good.
Y'know, you're all right.
Cool.
But that 200 million...
We spent it all!
I'll knock you flat on your ass.
Now, now... Simmer down there.
You've shown me how manly you are.
So that means I have no room to be upset
over how my home and dismantling yard—
my beloved Franky House—
was completely and utterly destroyed!
And then you guys just
had to beat up my boys!
Why, you rotten bastards...!
Big Bro!
You're too worked up!
Bastards!
Y'know, little bro, a lot's happened,
but we should let bygones be bygones.
Let's believe in Steven
and work something out.
You mean "call it even Steven."
Yeah, it's "call it even Steven," Bro.
Any plans now that you're on your own?
You don't have anywhere to go, right?
If not, I can take you in.
Come work for me!
I've taken a liking to you.
Forget it!
I don't wanna dismantle ships.
Sure, I left my crew,
but I'm still a pirate!
Here's one I call, "Pirate's Creed."
Yay! Big Bro!
You're making fun of me again!
C'mon... I'm just tryin' to help you
figure out what to do next!
It's none of your business!
Besides, is this the best place
to relax right now?
A storm surge is coming soon, right?
Yeah, that's exactly why...
when Aqua Laguna comes,
we'll need everyone to pitch in.
By midnight, the sea will reach
the second floor of most homes.
Right now, anyone in the Narrows
or on the cape wouldn't stand a chance.
Leave your ship here,
and you won't need to worry.
Oh... Thanks. I appreciate it.
You dummy!
Don't be so cold!
It must be tough to deal
with a flood like that every year.
Well, at this point, everyone's
used to this annual evacuation.
The actual problem is how the
sea level rises with every year.
The Narrows visible above the sea
were built on the rooftops of an
old town that existed centuries ago.
It's said Shipyard Island and the Narrows
were once on the same landmass.
But now, so much of the area is underwater
that it's called a floating city.
The sidewalks became canals.
Technically, it's not
the water level that's increasing,
but rather, the island's foundation is sinking.
At this rate, there won't be
many places left to live in town.
Huh... So even the floating wonder city
has its own share of troubles.
But if push comes to shove,
you can take the sea train
and go live somewhere else.
You can say that... now.
But the sea train has only existed
for a little over a decade.
Before then, it wasn't so simple
to just up and travel across the sea.
Huh?
Naturally, it was rare to see folks
travel between islands.
The island existed in isolation...
Its residents grew restless.
They became preoccupied with the thought
that their land might one day sink.
What eased peoples' fears about the future
was the sea train, Puffing Tom.
Once it arrived, you could
travel without a log pose.
This was some real progress!
It's all thanks to the sea train's creator,
a great shipwright named Tom.
He saved this city and its people.
Big Bro!
Help...
I'll say "hello" to Big Bro for you.
We have the location.
Let's go.
Ouch!
So, little bro...
Huh?
I'm gonna cut to the chase.
What're you gonna do after you fix that ship?
What am I gonna do?
I'll go on adventures with her again,
and someday we'll go back
to our home, the East Blue!
It's not like we made it around the world,
but this ship has traveled the Grand Line.
That should be good enough
to call it a triumphant return.
I'll hold my head up and–
Nope! There's no going back
to the East Blue.
It's just too far.
Bro?
When we brought the ship here,
I got a real good look at her.
That ship is at the end of her life.
Galley-La's assessment is spot-on.
As someone who's in the dismantling business,
I suggest scrapping her.
What...? That's ridiculous!
I'll help you dismantle your ship!
What?! What're you saying, you jerk?!
Wait! What're you doing?!
Stop right there!
Big Bro!
It's just a friendly offer
to help scrap your ship.
Don't be ridiculous!
I won't let you!
The Merry... is my ship!
No, she ain't! In fact...
she's no longer a ship.
What?
What'd you say?!
I asked you earlier what you were gonna do
after you fixed this ship, didn't I?
If you had said you were willing
to die at sea, right alongside this ship,
I would have let it go.
However, you said you wanted
to sail back to the East Blue,
so I'm stopping you here and now, little bro.
This ship...
won't even make it to the next island.
Listen. Ships are born with the promise
to carry you across the sea
from one shore to another.
In other words, once a ship can
no longer carry you to shore...
Hey!
Stop it!
Once she can't carry you to shore...
she's no longer a ship!
Big Bro!
Stop it!
You bastard! Get away from Merry!
You stubborn idiot!
If you won't listen...
then you should at least
take a good look at her...
with your own eyes!
Sorry, Merry.
I'll fix you right away.
I'll fix you right away...
I'll do it...
as many times as you need...
I'll fix you as many times as you need!
As many times as you need!
Hey! Enough already, long nose!
You saw the bottom of the ship, right?!
With a broken keel, the outer panels
are misaligned, and the frame is a wreck!
In her condition, one good wave
would tear her apart!
And yet, a total amateur
like you thinks you can–
Shut up, you moron!
Don't say another word!
Shut your mouth,
or I'll shut it for you, you metal freak!
Deep...
Deep down...
I already knew...
Huh?! What did you say?!
Deep down...
Deep down... I already knew.
I know that Merry is at the end of her life!
Deep down...
I... knew...
When I heard the assessment,
I was finally convinced that
what I saw back then really happened.
At first, I thought I was dreaming.
I thought, "What I'm seeing can't be real."
On a foggy night...
in a forest under the moonlight,
I heard the strikes of a wooden hammer.
It came from the ship, even though
no one was supposed to be aboard.
That sound was coming
from our battered, grounded ship.
Despite how thick the fog was, I definitely saw someone there,
using a wooden hammer.
I just... couldn't figure out who it was.
But then, when morning came,
though the work was lousy,
the ship was fixed.
The broken mast was also
restored to its former shape.
But the weirdest part was...
whoever fixed the Merry
knew her original design.
Despite how much we had refitted her,
someone restored the Merry
to how she used to look!
It was something we couldn't answer, but...
for some reason,
I remembered these words deep down...
I don't know if the person I saw actually
said it, or if I was imagining things...
Don't worry.
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
I know this sounds stupid, but...
I... I feel like it might have been the incarnation of the Merry.
I bet she was already at her limits back then.
She might've assumed that form
so she could let us know.
When I heard the assessment,
that's all I thought about.
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
You don't have to believe me.
Bro?
Believe you?
This person looked like a sailor
holding a wooden hammer, right?
What...? Why...?
Do you know?
Little bro...
You saw a klabautermann.
K-Klabau...?
The klabautermann.
It's a legend known among sailors.
It's a sprite that only lives
in ships treated with great care.
I suppose you could say
it's a ship's incarnation.
They carry wooden hammers
and wear sailor's raincoats.
When danger approaches,
they run around inside the ship
to inform the crew about it.
It's said that they sometimes
help sailors quite a bit.
But honestly, this is the first time
I've heard someone say they saw one.
The more care the ship receives,
the more it appreciates its crew.
This ship must've wanted to make sure
you made it to the next island.
She encountered a crew
she wanted to carry so badly
that she took the form of a human.
I bet she's been very happy.
Merry...
I see...
Then, the one...
who talked to me then...
really was you, huh?
Merry...
But you've gotta be kidding me...
You had a big fight with your friends,
knowing your ship was at her limits, then?
It's not that simple.
Men are so inept!
They're morons!
Looks like someone's here.
"Someone's here"?
It's gotta be Zambai and the boys!
Why are they coming from the sea side?
Yeah... they usually use
the upper entrance...
Maybe they brought Straw Hat.
Oh, that's right!
I forgot I used you as bait
to lure the Straw Hats here!
They won't come.
We're no longer friends.
Didn't I tell you that?
Why aren't they coming in?
Okay, okay. I'm coming!
Okay, okay... Hey, stop already!
Listen, little bro...
Go back to your friends.
I can't do that now.
I dueled my captain.
Besides, the ship stuff isn't settled yet, so...
What do you mean it hasn't been settled?
If you know that your ship can't
sail anymore, it's simple, ain't it?
Leave her with me.
I'll take care of her in a way
that you'll appreciate.
That's all I was trying to do, you know...
Destroying that ship for you,
so you wouldn't have to.
Don't stick your nose into it!
It's my business!
Hey, I'm trying to solve your problem!
Zambai?
You should be thankful!
Thankful? Give me a break!
Don't you get it?!
It's a nuisance for the ship too!
She loves you guys so much
that she appeared in human form.
If she sinks in the middle of the sea
while you guys are on board...
Hey! If that happens, even if she dies,
she won't be able to rest in peace!
So, you'd just walk away
from a dying friend, saying,
"Well, I hope you rest in peace"?!
Oh, that's a whole different
topic of conversation!
As if! This is exactly that topic!
You just don't get it, do you?!
Huh?!
Mozu!
Kiwi!
Pardon me... for interrupting.
It's just, these two ladies didn't let us in, so...
What the hell are you bastards doing here?!
Iron Body!
Huh? What the hell is this?!
Blueno! What's the meaning of–
Huh? What's this? How cocky!
Who do you think I am?!
You do know who you're
picking a fight with, right?!
You're just the owner of some sleazy tavern!
What's with that getup?!
You're acting strange!
What's going on?!
Tch.
Enough, Blueno.
H-Hey! A-Are you okay?!
We can't kill him yet.
Don't forget our mission.
Hang in there!
Sorry.
Wh-Wh-What's going on?! Hey!
A-Aren't they shipwrights?
What the hell? How did he...?
What are you people?!
You sure are acting pretty super, aren't you?!
How dare you hurt those innocent girls?!
They're like my little sisters, you bastards!
How do you know about this place?
This is my secret base!
We don't care about that.
I'll keep this simple. Listen carefully.
We were undercover here.
In reality, we are
World Government intelligence agents.
You must know what that means...
as well as the reason we came here.
Franky, we already know everything.
Cutty Flam...
Tom's other disciple,
who apparently died eight years ago,
is you.
I don't know how you found out,
but color me impressed.
At the same time,
that's pretty unsettling.
Is that idiot Iceburg doing okay?
We killed him.
Don't try to play dumb now...
We already know everything.
It's only a matter of time
before they come for me.
Take them and leave the island, Franky.
Tom handed them down to Iceburg...
and Iceburg to you.
Both of you, come over here.
I wanna entrust something
important to you two.
Our mission took quite a while,
but it's finally checkmate.
Now, hand over the blueprints
for the ancient weapon Pluton, Cutty Flam.
Flam...? That's a strange name.
"Franky" would do, right?
"Franky" works.
Anything is fine.
Can you hear me?
I'm saying hand them over, Cutty Flam.
I've got nothing for you, you snakes!
Wha...?!
Wh-What just happened?!
It was so fast I couldn't see a thing.
Hey! Are you okay?!
This is...
What's the matter, Lucci?
What is this filthy room?
A drafting room?
Oh?
It'd be a good place to hide blueprints.
Find them!
These are... nameplates?
Cutty Flam.
Iceburg.
Tom.
This name is...
This is...
Don't touch anything!
Don't just mess with people's memories!
We were raised here.
It was the shipbuilding company, Tom's Workers,
home of the world's best shipwright!