Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
fedew
Zenef
Graphics
Datenshi
Quality Control
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
Westfal
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing/Typesetting
Gab
Subtitle Editing
Pollychan
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Nikki
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Fantasia
Chestnut head! Monkeys!
Can you hear it?!
The City of Gold...
was right here!
Son of a...! He actually did it!
How beautiful...
What a pretty sound!
What is it, huh?!
I had faith that this moment
would arrive one day...
So this is the sound
that Noland heard.
Suu...
I wonder...
if the vearth is singing...
So gods...
really exist?
What a miracle!
I had almost given up on hearing it
ring again after its 400-year silence.
Great Warrior Kalgara...
Can you hear...
the echo of the Light of Shandora...?
What's happening in this country?
What is this tone?
Could it be...?
Is this the legendary sound?
Can you hear it...
Mont Blanc Noland?
Sorry to have kept you
waiting so long.
I truly hope...
this reaches your descendants!
You like the sound
of this bell too, huh?
Boss! Th-That sound...
Yeah!
There's no doubt about it.
Only one bell in the world
could echo so far!
Now this is romance.
From the sky...
I'm all excited now...
Y'know, there used to be
a tale about the monsters...
that appear with
the cumuloimperator clouds.
If a person were to stand high
in the sky against a strong sun...
their figure would be projected
onto the dense mist far below.
That shadow would loom
like a giant monster.
So those monsters are really just
the shadows of people in the sky?!
Then does that mean we've finally
confirmed that people live up there?!
Yeah.
I had dismissed that story
as nothing but pointless fantasy...
but it seems like it was all true.
I can clearly hear the ringing
of that massive golden bell.
The City of Gold really does
exist in the sky!
Noland
the Liar
Noland... My ancestor...
was no liar!
Noland
the Liar
That's what you're telling me
all the way from the sky...
right, kid?
I appreciate it!
MONKEY
Boss?!
What's the matter?!
Are you sick?!
I'm just glad those kids are safe...!
I was... so worried...
Look! That's...
God's ship...
It's God!
They're sinking...
God Enel and his ship are...
sinking...
The sound of that bell...
is known as the Light of Shandora,
which rings in the glory of that ancient city.
It's the song of the island
that declares this conflict over...
After 400 long years,
the bell rang as promised...
Although this restless floating island's
journey was long,
its distant memories
are not easily forgotten.
Its people once entrusted the sound
of that bell with a message...
so that their proud words
would ring out across the vast sea.
My friends...!
It rang...
Yeah.
I wonder if chestnut head
and his friends heard it...
They did. I'm sure of it.
We are here!
Tie the ropes to some
sturdy-looking trees!
Aisa...
Were you worried?
Here... your treasure!
I don't care about that!
Raki...
The others...
They're fine!
Just save your energy...
Someone's there!
I'm... still alive?
No! We have to treat you right away!
My treatment can wait.
Huh?!
I'll be fine. You should help him first.
He's barely even alive.
You're right!
His whole body is falling apart!
This is terrible!
Hey, that's one of the guerrillas.
We don't owe him anything.
True.
I don't really know why...
but it felt like he was
risking his life, so...
Huh?
What the heck?
You feeling sorry for him?
Who knows...?
Um...
Is he gonna be okay, little tanuki?
I'm a reindeer! Look, I have antlers!
Don't worry. He'll survive.
Thank you!
Pierre, you should rest
with those Blue Sea folks.
Pierre, hurry and bring the families!
So in the end, the golden bell
and Enel's golden ship...
...both fell, right?
I guess now it's the City of Gold
in name only, huh?
Which means our journey
in poverty continues.
Gold, schmold! I'd rather have
some of those dials!
You can't find stuff like that
back on the Blue Sea!
I just really hope Nami's alright...
And I wonder where Conis could be...
Is it okay to leave Wyper
with the Blue Sea dwellers?
It's fine.
Aisa seems to have
made friends with them.
At any rate, we have to hurry.
There's no point
if our enemies wake up.
Gather those who can move!
We'll send the priests to the clouds.
– Yeah!
Are you done with him?
Yeah. All he needs now is rest.
Guuuys!
Luffy!
Nami my sweet!
Conis my love!
Luffy!
You guys!
I'm glad you're okay!
I was so worried,
but I couldn't do anything.
You were really that worried
about me, Conis?!
Not a chance.
What's in there? Food?
Where'd you get it?
We found the priests' food storage
on our way back through the forest.
There was lots left.
But how'd you get back down
from all the way up there?
We used my Gum-Gum Balloon.
By the way, Conis,
where's your old man?
Huh?
Well... um...
he protected me...
and then Enel...
Don't tell me...
Conis...
– Wait, we're talking about you!
I'm sorry but I'm still alive!
Father!
The lower White Sea?
Yes. I found myself there
after being knocked off.
One by one, the people who fled to
the lower level toward Cloud End
are returning to the White-White Sea
using the milky roads they restored.
However, without
Angel Island to return to,
they're all coming
to Upper Yard instead.
– Thank you so much!
– Thank you so much, God!
That is no longer who I am.
To think that you were forced to work
in such a place for six long years...
Please forgive me.
We have no place to return home to.
The Shandians have lost
the Village Hidden in the Clouds too.
Is the fighting really over?
God's Army is gone, but...
Can we really mend
a 400-year-old rift that easily, Chief?
Man, I'm stuffed!
It's dark out now.
Wanna head back to the ship?
Nami, what're you saying?!
What do you mean?!
Usopp, are you hearing this?
Yeah, how horrible.
To say that after all this,
you're a failure as a pirate–
No, as a human!
What the heck
are you talking about?!
I'm headed home
to where God belongs...
Nothing in this sky must be
allowed to obscure my vision...
All of you were in my way.
No one else may have it.
It is fit only for me!
This land without end,
like something from a dream!
Now, let us go, Maxim...
To the realm of the gods
that floats brightly in the night sky...
To that boundless land...
the Endless Vearth!
Where am I?
Inside the ruins of Shandora.
Gan Fall!
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
You... You're a Skypiean!
Just rest for now.
Chief!
All of those injured in battle
will be treated the same.
The golden bell...
We still have a duty to protect it!
This is...
the sound of war drums!
The ruins are on fire too?!
Calm yourself, Wyper.
Just be patient and observe.
Whatever noble reasons there may
have once been to justify this conflict,
to those of us who remain,
this sky has already
long been our home.
The land, at least,
is not refusing anyone.
Indeed.
Feel free to see it for yourself.
For at the present moment...
not one, single soul wants to fight.
It's party time!