One Piece
Wano Arc
Video Editing
Meggo
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Taylor Lindise
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Taylor Lindise
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Taylor Lindise
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Gaijin
Remember, you're the one
who doubted my crew.
Without mutual trust, we won't have
each other's backs when death is on the line!
Sparks of Rebellion
Traf was fuming when he left!
Who knows if he'll come back.
Shinobu went too far saying all that crap!
Don't tell me you can't
see what set her off.
Kaido invades their country,
destroys everything they had ever known,
and yet they held off on their plan
for 20 years while they endured hell.
Whatever. Even if Bepo and them had blabbed
about the plan, I wouldn't blame them.
Sure, I mean, you'd have talked.
I can say the same about you!
Torture, huh?
I'd last three seconds.
Hold out just a bit longer!
Get outta here!
I have no business with any
of you damn peasants!
What's going on?
An angry shout seems out of place in Ebisu.
You there, old bean-grinding ghost granny!
Stop it!
He's a new arrival to our town
who was kicked out of the capital yesterday.
What the hell're you lookin' at?!
Get outta here, punks!
Kicked out?
Yeah.
Only those who produce wealth and show loyalty
to the shogun can live in the Flower Capital.
I heard they were into some
pretty dirty stuff, though!
First,
we have the humble Bungo.
You damn kids!
Night after night,
he'd roam the streets setting fires,
but he'd bribe officials to avoid punishment.
Bungo
An Arsonist
He's an arsonist?!
Where's the payoff in arson and bribery?
Someone else was profiting from those fires.
Enter the man who sells the wood
for rebuilding those houses:
Bongo, the lumber dealer.
Bongo
A Lumber Dealer
What?!
That's not all.
Yet another targeted those who mourned
the loss of family in the fires,
extorting large sums of money from them.
Meet Bingo, a priest and cooper.
Bingo
A Priest and Cooper
No! So those three...
That's right. Bingo, Bongo,
and Bungo were in cahoots.
I knew it!
Those jerks!
You're not wrong.
But no matter what evil they committed,
they'd buy off officials to avoid any charges.
They'd put on a good face in public,
while actually being downright scoundrels.
But here's the thing.
Interestingly enough, Oiran Komurasaki,
that beautiful girl who died yesterday,
had the three of them smitten.
All three spent so much on her
that they ended up bankrupt!
The gods were watching after all!
And them's the rumors!
That's a good story.
Those are pretty detailed rumors!
It's all true, isn't it?
If so, that means the oiran knew
what she was doing!
Incredible!
Who was Komurasaki really?
Hey, those are the guys!
That's right! I saw them!
They made a scene
during the oiran's procession.
Yasu-san took them in
and provided a place for them to live,
but they're still acting all high and mighty.
Tonoyasu really likes taking care of others.
Even jerks like them!
I'm certain this symbol inspired a great many people!
Be sure to tell Kin'emon-kun and the others:
We'll be ready to fight at the appointed time.
Kin'emon-kun ?!
It brought me great joy
to see you two again!
Well, I've got a lot to do!
Hey, old guy!
After all, plenty of people are likely to die
in the few days before the final battle!
Then, I beg your pardon!
The ladies' man!
The classy dame!
And the girl next door!
I bid you three farewell!
So, who was that old man?
I didn't quite catch
what his relationship is with you two.
Ditto.
Yeah, Tonoyasu's really friendly.
But who is he?
The two of us...
...have no idea!
You have no idea?!
You kept talking to him
without knowing who he is?!
Well, he just kept going on and on.
How could anyone forget such a quirky guy?!
He addressed us using "kun" and "chan,"
so I thought it rude to ask
if he had once been someone of import.
He was so casual, so perhaps
he's a childhood friend?
Or a teacher?
An older schoolmate maybe?
Who was he?!
For real?!
You bastards!
Get 'em, Madilloman!
Let's fly, gramps!
In Wano, we use ryuo to refer to what you call "haki."
"Ryuo"?
RYUO
It means, "to flow."
Your "haki" should also be
flowing through your body.
You must first feel that flow.
All right!
The haki flows through me...
Don't force it!
Damn it! That's not it!
You cannot force it.
Channel the haki into your fists
from body parts that do not require it.
Straw Hat!
I'll end you!
That's not it!
That's not it, either!
Damn it!
That's not it! That's not it!
Crap! Where is it?!
My haki!
It won't flow into my fist!
Hey hey, he's beating too many of my men.
These idiots.
Damn!
Fists of rage won't attract haki.
Who's next, already?
Bring 'em on!
Grandpa. Hey, grandpa!
How's the colic?
Oh, Yasu-san !
It's not much,
but I brought you some millet and water.
Take care of yourself!
You're so kindhearted, Yasu-san.
What a compliment!
What a joy to be called "kindhearted"!
Here're two more grains of millet!
So long, grandpa!
Hey, old nori maker, do you have enough medicine?
I'm all out, but I feel better already,
having seen your face.
You seductress!
Oh, how's the knee, old man?
Come play with me, Yasu-san !
Little man, how's your mother doing?
Osaki-san, how's the baby?
Coochy-coo!
– Yasu-san !
– Please come see us too!
All right, everyone!
Come and get it!
Thanks again!
What a generous guy, that Tonoyasu.
It's sweet how he goes around
handing out food.
It's not what you think.
Laborers get paid peanuts.
Peanuts?
He had to sell Toko-chan, his only daughter,
to an employer in the capital.
She sends most of her earnings to Yasu-san.
Toko?
I'm not a boy!
Oh, her!
Toko-chan sends him money,
but he believes keeping it to himself is wasteful.
He spends his days handing out food
to those who can't work,
even though he has nothing to eat himself.
He may look ridiculous,
but he's a long-beloved figure in our community.
He's a saint.
Daddy...
Daddy!
Lights out! Go to sleep!
Dammit!
We gotta wait until tomorrow?!
Let me fight some more!
So hungry...
You gonna feed me or what?!
Listen to 'im, barkin' like some dog.
Shut up and sleep!
I'll be a mummy by tomorrow!
May I ask you something,
Sir Straw Hat?
What?
Why do you wish to fight Kaido?
I heard he thrashed you in Kuri.
These guys are annoying.
All right, we're good now.
Old man,
have you heard of the Four Emperors?
No, I haven't.
Four pirates known as emperors sail the world's seas.
Kaido is one of them.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates,
so I've gotta beat the four of 'em.
The king of the pirates?
Is that like the man called Roger?
You know Gold Roger?!
Yes, from when he came
to this country many years ago.
Oh, Kin'emon said the same thing.
What? Kin'emon?!
How would you know that name?!
What's going on?!
What?!
You! You're... Raizo!
Straw Hat-san.
You?
That's Raizo... isn't it?
It is I!
What?!
What's going on with you two?!
How are you alive?!
Raizo!
Allow me to explain, Boss Hyogoro.
Arrest him! Arrest him!
There he is! It's Ushimitsu Kozo!
Enough already!
Seize him!
Is that so, Raizo?
It's hard to believe you are
the same Boss Hyogoro I once knew.
Th-This is difficult to fathom.
You all truly traveled
from 20 years in the past,
from that fateful day in Wano's history?
That is correct. It was
due to Lady Toki's sorcery.
I cannot believe it.
I can't believe you, Caribou!
Please don't be so cruel, Straw Hat-san !
What the hell, Raizo?!
You thought you had the keys to my cuffs,
but they were actually to his !
All this hate doesn't suit you.
Surely I can help in some way.
From now on, I'm your lieutenant!
And... as a reward...
please let me leave with you on your ship.
Ah, so you can't get home?
Please forgive me for my past misdeeds!
I'm a changed man!
All right, as long as you've changed,
I forgive you.
What?!
Ah, I mean,
thank you very much!
Is this some kind of trap? What's truly
frightening is how easily he forgave me.
Sir Luffytaro, this man uses
quite the fascinating sorcery.
He could be useful.
I never knew when to let go,
stubbornly clinging to life,
but it was worth it.
Boss Hyogoro!
I was a hair's breadth away.
I thought I'd die here.
I had made peace with that.
If not for your timely arrival,
I would have remained ignorant,
and I would be dead.
The Red Scabbards yet live?
Oden's child, Kozuki Momonosuke, survived?
The fires of rebellion...
do they continue to burn?!
Raizo! Sir Straw Hat!
Insomuch as this is true,
there is yet life in this old man!
It would be an honor to assist you!
Oh, this is an unexpected boon!
Sir Luffy, this man was once
the boss over all the yakuza in Wano.
Really?! So, you were the real deal
back in the day, old man!
You mentioned that you have been
gathering allies in the Flower Capital?
Indeed.
It must have been fate
that brought you here to Udon.
There are four adjoining mining camps
of a similar size to this one.
There are tens of thousands of prisoners here.
However, not all of them were arrested
for theft or violence.
Most of the prisoners in these camps
are guilty of one thing:
treason against Orochi!
Is that so?! That was an oversight!
Udon is the nexus of the anger
felt throughout the country.
The yakuza bosses who once supported Wano
from the shadows are all here.
I will speak with them.
They will gladly fight for the Kozuki Clan.
Also, Raizo, see that cell?
I am already aware.
I briefly spoke with Kawamatsu.
I intend to release him first.
I got it.
If we smash this place to pieces,
everyone will join our cause?!
Sir Luffy, you're too loud!
It won't be that simple!
All right! With that decided,
bring us some food!
Please...
feed me.
I'm hungry... and sleepy.
Are we close to the oshiruko, Okiku-chan ?
The sharkodile is also exhausted,
but we have already reached Udon.
Udon Wilderness
Wait for me,
my sweet oshiruko !
Is it okay that we're here?
Oh, that hits the spot!
Another bowl!
Oshiruko !
Extra! Extra! Breaking news!
The cause of the uproar in the Flower Capital,
Flower Capital
the burglar known as Ushimitsu Kozo,
has finally been caught!
Lord Orochi!
Lord Orochi, I have some news you should hear.
It is about Ushimitsu Kozo,
who was apprehended the other day.
Be silent!
Have you any sense of how I feel,
having lost the love of my life?!
I am deeply grieved by the death of Oiran Komurasaki.
But with all due respect, my lord,
Kyoshiro's decision was most prudent.
If we let anyone who opposes the shogun live,
it could ruin His Excellency's authority and prestige.
Lord Orochi–
I couldn't care less about Ushimitsu Kozo.
Komurasaki... No other woman
could match her beauty.
Do you not understand that?!
Thank you for the honor
of your presence, Lord Orochi.
But I beg you, please hear me out.
Ushimitsu Kozo was not
your run-of-the-mill thief.
He was an insidious criminal who
wreaked havoc throughout the Flower Capital.
He stole from the rich and gave to the poor,
becoming a petty villain with heroic intentions.
He is currently in custody at Rasetsu Prison.
His true identity is...
What?!
It's him !
H-He... lives?!
No! I cannot believe it!
It's him!
You are of the Kurozumi Clan?
Why did you hide it?
It's him! He lives!
My lord? My lord?!
What shall we do about Ushimitsu Kozo?
Isn't it obvious?!
Execute him!
Make an example out of him!
Broadcast it immediately throughout Wano!
The light scrolls are already in place.
Kyoshiro!
Today, Komurasaki's public funeral
will also take place in the capital.
Large, grieving crowds hold the potential
for disorderly conduct,
so I have made preparations.
Just as I'd expect from you, Kyoshiro.
What are your orders, my lord?
I've made up my mind.
We will have Ushimitsu Kozo
join Komurasaki in death.
Komurasaki will have a martyr's funeral!
Yes, my lord.
It's ironic poetry to have the capital's
two biggest stars share the stage in death!
That is exactly the stroke of genius
I expect of my shogun.
I, too, will attend.
I wish to witness the execution!
Ready my palanquin!
Prisoner Mining Camp
Udon
It can't be!
I can't deal with these bad jokes
in the morning, Kaido-san.
It's not a joke.
No... It can't be!
If you don't believe me, connect a
light-scroll snail and see for yourself!
No!
Komurasaki-tan !
Hey.
Huh?
He found out Komurasaki died.
Queen's gonna be in a bad mood for a while.
This is bad. What should we do?
Hey, balloon!
Hurry and get out here!
Shut up!
I don't have time for your nonsense!
Hey, balloon!
When we gonna start today's sumo match?
Don't waste my time!
Did you guys get fat overnight or something?!
That's impossible!
You're just imagining it!
Hey.
O-Oh. I see.
Do we report that the oshiruko vanished overnight?
Anyway, that's not important right now!
No way! What do you think Queen would do
after a double shock like that?
Good point.
But where in the world did that oshiruko go?
I warned Sir Luffy they would notice
if he ate too much.
But eating every last drop of oshiruko
was just excessive!
How has this idiot survived this long?
More importantly, it's sumo time! Sumo!
Let's go! Dosukoi !
I don't have time for idiots.
I gotta know the truth!
Hey, get me a video feed
of the Flower Capital now!
Ready the light-scroll snail!
The light-scroll snail is in place!
Show me the Flower Capital.
A video transponder snail?
Oh, it's the Flower Capital.
Mount Atama
Kuri
Mount Atama Thieves,
how dare you scum
steal my weapons and provisions?!
The Mount Atama
Thieves were here.
Shutenmaru
Let me return the gesture...
and give you a taste of my trick sword!
I'll devastate Mount Atama!
This is the end of the Mount Atama Thieves.
It's too late!
The fire is spreading too fast!
There's no extinguishing it,
Shutenmaru-san !
That bastard Holdem!
Head to Bakura Town!
Bakura Town?!
But we'll run into Kaido's forces!
That's the idea!
Crush them all!
An Abandoned
Village
Kuri
An Abandoned
Village
Kuri
An Abandoned
Village
Kuri
I see. It's a shame to hear that
this is happening to Ashura Doji.
Indeed, but it is for the greater good.
It was unavoidable.
We'll head to Bakura Town.
Our plan was foiled,
and we have no solution in sight.
For now, we'll get Ashura
to see the Beast Pirates as his enemy.
His joining us is crucial to our cause!
Northern
Cemetery
Ringo
Northern
Cemetery
Ringo
I'm h–
H-H-Huh...?
What?!
Who is this?! What is this?!
Wh-Wh-What's the story here?!
Brook? What's wrong with you?
Why are you here? Hm?
Zoro-san, my eyes are popping
out of my skull just seeing you like that!
I'm a skeleton, though,
so having eyes isn't really my thing...
So sorry for the interruption!
Hey, don't get the wrong idea!
Get back in here!
Oh? Well... you don't say...
If it's no trouble, I'd be happy to.
Wow, I'm smitten!
If you would be so obliged,
may I see your panties?
A ghost!
Wait, he's with me!
I'm so hungry. Woe is me!
How scary!
Kin'emon-san tasked me
with saying that around here.
Oh, I see.
That's why there are
so many offerings out there.
At any rate, it's hard to believe
you're Momonosuke-san's little sister.
You're as beautiful as an oiran.
She sure is.
I mean, she is an oiran.
I'm jealous, Zoro-san. How'd you get
someone like this to tend to you?!
I just went to sleep.
That's all.
I am so sorry.
You just looked like you were cold.
Truth be told,
everyone longs to lie with me!
Did it make you happy?
It definitely did!
You're just dripping with conceit!
I am!
Anyway, I have no idea
where Nami-san and the others went.
Yesterday, they went to the bathhouse,
but they weren't there
when I arrived to retrieve them.
Oh, that reminds me.
The Flower Capital is in an absolute frenzy.
I heard that today is the funeral for
Komurasaki, Wano's most beautiful oiran.
Plus, they caught Ushimitsu Kozo, the master
thief who shared his spoils with the poor!
That was bigger news than the first!
Ushimitsu Kozo?! Are you sure?!
Yes, I'm positive.
Look, here's the extra edition on it.
It says that he will be executed in the capital
today. They even discovered his true identity.
Ushimitsu Kozo
Arrested
It appears he is someone
renowned in Ebisu Town.
In Ebisu Town?
Yes, his name was something like...
I'm fairly sure it was something like Yasu-san.
Tonoyasu?!
Ah, yes, that's him.
Toko!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Wait, Toko!
Thank you for yesterday.
I will be forever in your debt.
Wait, you idiot!
You can't protect her on your own!
Whaaat?! What the heck?!
I only just made it back here!
Wait for me! Hey, you guys!
Daddy!
Hey, get up.
You're here for me?
How nice of you to drop by.
It... It can't be.
He looks like...
Where are you going?!
They want your head!
Let me go!
I need to go!
Hey, just relax!
Let me go!
Is she okay?
Toko!
They're gonna execute him!
Let me go!
They're gonna kill him!
He's my dad!
Toko...
What'd you say?!
Looks like another beautiful day
in the Flower Capital.