Video Editing
Gigglebot
Galaxy 9000
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
arch1t3cht
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Scolines
TheFVGuy
arch1t3cht
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Scolines
TheFVGuy
arch1t3cht
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Scolines
TheFVGuy
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Gaijin
Then, we're counting on you, good sir.
Leave it to me.
I shall assume full responsibility
and ensure that Lord Yasuie is buried in Kuri.
Please provide him with the utmost of care.
Naturally.
Lord Yasuie was a great benefactor to us.
We're all set!
Let's get a move on, you two!
– Okay!
– Ah, I'll be right there. We should hurry!
Have a safe journey!
From the Flower Capital to Kuri:
At one of its ports.
We have set up checkpoints
all around the Flower Capital
to capture the vile fugitives
who are plotting to take Lord Orochi's life!
All of you, show your faces!
What should we do?
It looks like our escape won't be so easy.
We can't get to Kuri
if we don't get on that boat.
We've gotta figure out a way
past that checkpoint.
What?!
Woe is you!
Aah!
Th-They're possessed!
Y-You may pass!
That went better than expected.
How's Otoko-chan?
She's all tuckered out from crying
and is sleeping in my arms.
I honestly don't know what to say to her...
Daddy!
Bonekichi, give her to me.
You don't provide enough warmth.
How cruel!
That's not true, is it?
Wh-What's this?!
Ships,
ships,
and more ships!
I'm speechless, Ashura!
They'll need a bit of work,
but we salvaged them from the harbors
that Kaido laid to waste throughout Wano.
These should be enough to ferry
a few thousand soldiers to Onigashima.
How reassuring!
I'm impressed, Ashura!
As am I.
You were never known to be so sensible.
I wasn't the one idle for 20 years.
I'll ask Master Franosuke
to service these later!
The journey thus far
has been long and arduous,
but our revenge is finally in sight!
I'm certain I dropped her ship over the falls.
King, you bastard!
Always doing things half-assed!
Brother Queen, why did you bring her here?
Shut up!
We lost comms in Udon!
What was I supposed to do?!
King!
I'll forget what you did to me,
if you join me.
Totto Land is still missing three races.
One seems to have
faded into history...
yet you still live.
I refuse!
That's too bad.
Well, unlock these handcuffs already.
What the hell do you mean, "Well"?!
You're staying put, you old bag!
Have you heard?
Big Mom and Lord Kaido were once
part of the same pirate crew.
What's going on here?
Set her free.
Lord Kaido!
So you finally showed your face, Linlin.
Kaido.
Hey, you!
You were told to set me free.
No way!
It had to have been a joke...
Set her free!
Kaido-san...
How long has it been?
Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
Oh, I'm glad you're back to normal!
It hasn't been easy since I'm so shy.
I told you I'd kill you
if you showed your face here.
What idiot travels this far
to her own execution?
Two-Sword Style...
Seven-Twenty-Pound Phoenix!
I'm the greater hunter here!
What is with you?!
Are you friend... or foe?!
Who the hell are you?!
What are you planning
to do with all the weapons
you keep taking from passersby?
Give me back my katana already.
Don't throw away your life
over a single blade.
I'll never give it back!
That katana is special!
The blade you carried, Shusui, is
a national treasure that was stolen from Wano!
What?! Shusui?!
Our misfortune began
the moment that blade was taken!
The God of the Blade grew wrathful,
bringing defeat after defeat to each region,
until the entire country fell to the invaders!
What's this "god" drivel?!
Blasphemer!
Cease your fighting!
What would compel a samurai and a monk
to fight, and in such a backwater locale?
What's most humorous is that
neither of you intend to kill the other!
A fishman?
Kawa... matsu...
Kawamatsu?! Is that you?!
Hm? How do you know my name?
When are they gonna stop fighting?!
Should we evacuate to the mainland?!
Listen up, men!
What kind of idiot would run away
while the boss is fighting?!
Feckless cowards!
Queen-san, when'd you get here?
So, you're sayin' we should run?
Ugh!
Th-That's not what I meant.
Anyway, any word from Udon?
About that,
the smail still isn't connecting.
All right!
I'll go check it out!
You're trying to escape, Your Awesomeness!
That's not fair!
Say what?!
I said, "I'll go check it out!"
Give me that!
Ah, yes, sir!
– Hey, Queen here.
– Woo! Queen!
This is Warden Babanuki in Udon.
Right.
It looks like the smails are back online.
Yes, as of just a moment ago.
I ended up taking a lot of men back with me.
If you need reinforcements,
I'll head your way.
He's trying to nonchalantly leave Onigashima!
– Reinforcements aren't needed at this time.
– Tch!
– Denied!
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid,
and all the troublemakers
are locked in their cells.
I see.
So, all is well.
Tell me all is wrong!
Your Awesomeness!
Over and out.
How was that, Master?!
Good job! Thank you!
You're a good boy!
Thank you!
Wow! What sort of sorcery is this?!
How can these kibi dango
turn a foe to friend?!
They seem to work on animals
and people with animal powers.
It all went so swimmingly.
It's all thanks to you, Caribou.
Oh, yes!
It's all thanks to me!
Now, we'll–
We've got thousands of prisoners
who were meant to be quietly locked away.
I wonder how surprised the enemy
will be on the day of the battle!
You owe me!
Understood!
Now, we can finally contact Kin'emon's group.
Doctor Chopperemon!
We will repay you for this,
even if it costs us our lives!
It's fine.
It was a relatively easy virus to treat.
Besides, a samurai's debt would be
too much of a burden for me.
Thank goodness.
Luffytaro is also back to 100%.
Let's go, you guys!
Yeah!
– Let's do it!
– That's what I'm talking about!
He seems healthy and popular again.
The mere company of Lord Momonosuke
earned him immediate trust!
There's no mistaking it.
He has not changed.
I'm glad to see you...
Boss Hyogoro.
Hm?
Oh, it's them!
Omasa, the Sanguine Pen!
Torn-Hat Tsunagoro!
Evening Blossom Ocho!
Snake-Eyes Yatappe!
The bosses from each region
were here all along!
I never thought I'd live to see the day
we could work together again.
I'm delighted you're all safe and sound!
Your compliments are wasted
on the likes of us.
Indeed, as wasteful as
a bowel movement after a bath.
Absolutely.
That's for sure.
What a stuffy bunch!
And look at what a big boss the old man is!
Old man?!
Oh, no!
– Tug off his nails!
– Cut off his toes!
Tear off his ears!
You better straighten up, you punk!
Which one and how many?
– Your orders, Boss?
That's enough!
I owe him my life!
We'll quickly move to gather the rebels
still hiding throughout Wano.
– I'm counting on you.
– Understood.
He saved your life, young one.
Watch yourself.
Like I care, you jerk!
What a surprise!
So, the ones from Kuri
who stole the blueprints
were you guys!
We have been looking for these blueprints
of Kaido's Onigashima compound.
I put Franosuke
through the wringer for nothing.
These blueprints will give us options
for invading hostile territory.
You're amazing, Ashura!
Were you always so clever?
Shut up already, Dog!
Is that you, Raizo? How are things?
Did you rescue Luffytaro?
That... and much, much more!
It's a long story,
but a rough estimate of our current forces is...
Th-Thirty-five hundred?!
How'd we get so many?!
Sir Luffy's safe and free,
and you even found and freed Kawamatsu?!
Oh, Kawamatsu had been caged as well?
You took control of the mining camp too?!
Luffy-kun's release has brought us
the leap forward we sorely needed!
Here we come, Onigashima!
There are yet warriors
who would join our ranks!
However, I must inform you of a lingering issue.
Several weapon factories
are scattered throughout Wano,
but they mostly produce
weapons for export use.
Our samurai wish to use
katana blades and yari spears.
Orochi's decree has made weapon possession
illegal in Wano, giving us procurement issues.
The fight is over before we even begin
if we cannot arm our rebel fighters.
Right, that makes sense.
The problem is serious indeed.
Where do we find katana?
We've made progress too.
Remain there for now.
I need to assess our overall military might,
so I'll head to Amigasa Village
and make it our base of operations.
Raizo, gather as much intelligence
there as you can.
Understood.
Right, let's go!
I don't believe it.
Is it really you?!
Kawamatsu!
Hm?
Could it be?!
Wait... Are you...
Kawamatsu!
What a surprise to run into you out here.
I could not be happier
that you are alive and well, Lady Hiyori.
That's right, she mentioned
that a kappa raised her after her parents died.
Please forgive me for running away
out of fear back then.
You always offered me
the scraps of food you would find.
Ugh, I still need more training.
Kawamatsu...
I couldn't bear watching you
waste away, year after year.
You could survive on your own,
but I was worried my presence was killing you.
Princess!
What's this?
I'm sorry, Kawamatsu.
You'll die like this.
I was so afraid, I ran away.
Dear Kawamatsu,
Thank you for everything.
I'll be okay now. Hiyori
L-Lady Hiyori...
Lady Hiyori!
Princess!
Princess...
She's not here either.
Ah! Lady Hiyori!
Where are you, Lady Hiyori?!
Lady Hiyori...
Where did you go, Lady Hiyori?
Princess... Hiyori!
I'm sorry.
I'm truly so sorry.
What a kind-hearted reason!
So that's what happened!
Thanks to you, I've plumped right up!
Who's that?!
We've come to take our revenge, Gyukimaru!
We're done with you stealing our weapons!
Today, we take them all back!
He's down.
That's a big-game magnum for ya!
Get to the treeline, Lady Hiyori!
Okay!
Hm? Are they with Gyukimaru?
Whatever. Kill 'em all!
Die!
Kappa Style...
Two-Sword Style...
Reprisal River!
Rhino Cycle!
Sir Kawamatsu!
Kawamatsu.
Are you okay, Lady Hiyori?
Sir Kawamatsu...
Hey, wait!
Are you running away again?!
Bastard!
Give me back my Shusui!
Sir Kawamatsu, I'm so glad
to see you alive and well!