Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country and live freely!
Starting today...
we're brothers!
– Yeah!
How long are you gonna keep moping?
All the treasure we hid
in the midway forest is gone.
But that pile of loot doesn't matter anymore.
Sabo and I were gonna use it.
It was our pirate fund.
But in the end, Sabo didn't use it.
So I'll just let it go, too.
There's no point in gathering
treasure you can't even protect.
A-Ace...
I...
I wanna get stronger!
And stronger...
and stronger...!
Stronger and stronger!
Lots stronger!
Stronger!
Lots and lots stronger!
Stronger and stronger!
So much stronger!
And stronger and stronger!
And even stronger than that!
And then, I'll be able to protect anything.
I won't have to lose anyone ever again!
So please...
Ace, please don't die!
Don't be ridiculous!
Worry about yourself first!
You're way weaker than me!
Listen up, and remember this, Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!
Uh-huh.
Sabo made that request, too.
I promise. There's no way I'll die!
How could I die and leave my
wimpy little brother behind?
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Uh-huh... Uh-huh!
I'm not very smart, so I don't really
know yet what it was that killed Sabo.
But... it must've been something
opposed to freedom.
Sabo died before he could truly be free.
But we shared the same cup of sake
with Sabo and we're still alive!
So, listen up, Luffy.
We have to live our lives without regrets!
Uh-huh.
Noble-born boys...
become true noblemen
on their eighteenth birthday.
That's why I need to leave this country
by the time I turn seventeen!
Someday, we'll head out to sea...
and we can live however we want!
We'll be more free than anyone!
Uh-huh!
I'm sure we'll make lots
of enemies because of that.
Even Grandpa will be against us.
We'll be risking our lives.
We set sail at seventeen!
And then...
we will become pirates!
Video Editing
Sewil
Timing
Bastia
PhosCity
Timing
Sewil
Bastia
PhosCity
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Yibis
Translation
Crunchyroll
Yibis
Opening Raw
Gavynnnnn
Again, we turn back time a little...
to the night when the Celestial Dragon's
ship docked in Goa Kingdom.
Will of the Winds
In a certain region of the East Blue,
in a small seaside village...
Did you see the guy with
the huge face this afternoon?!
Yeah! I've never seen anything like it!
Look! His ship is huge too!
Five hundred and eighty...
Five hundred and eighty-one...
Five hundred and eighty-two...
Five hundred and eighty-three...
Five hundred and eighty-four...
You are late, Dragon!
How long did you plan to make us vayyt?!
Sorry.
Vhaat did you...?!
This is awful!
Quickly! Get a doctor! It's an emergency!
Roger!
But really! Vherre have you been?!
I was watching the world noble's
arrival ceremony.
You vennt on your own viithout telling me?!
With you there too, we would've
stuck out like sore thumbs.
You mean... this...?!
We must strive to grow
ever stronger, and with haste!
How are our provisions?
There was a village dojo that offered us food.
Then we set sail!
We will return to Baltigo!
Some months later, the World Government having
concluded their inspection of the Kingdom of Goa...
They've brought more trash!
The people have settled
into their old routines...
and the trash mountain has accumulated anew.
Here I come, Ace!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
What the hell was that? You call this a fight?
You might pack a punch,
but what's the use if you miss every time?
I told you, rubber really isn't suited for battle.
Shut up! Don't say that!
What, do you think I'm wrong?!
Sure, attacks bounce off you,
but you sink like a rock now!
Stop making fun of the Gum-Gum Fruit!
I'll make you cry someday!
Soon, I'll have attacks even
stronger than my pistol!
Luffy, great work!
Your arm stretched a lot farther
than it did yesterday!
Sabo! You're too soft on Luffy!
I knew I was stronger than yesterday!
– Right, Sabo?!
Sabo was a nicer older brother...
Say what?! You wish I'd died instead?!
Ow. Huh?
I've founded my own country.
A country?
What's this?
Me too!
Ace's Country
Luffy's Country
What is it this time?!
I'm gonna learn to survive on my own.
You guys can be Dadan's country.
I'll borrow the bath sometimes.
Ace's Country
Luffy's Country
Ace! Help me out! It's a bear!
You're gonna survive on your own, right?
Dammit!
Luffy!
Hey! Dadan's country! Anyone there?!
Luffy got hurt! Please help him!
Magra! Please, help Luffy!
Take it easy! Hurry! Bring him in!
Now, take it easy. This is no joke.
If his wounds had been any worse,
he could have died!
You used to take on these
wild beasts as a trio, right?
It's my fault!
I should've learned by now that fighting
on your own doesn't prove that you're strong!
I'm worthless!
Completely worthless!
Ace...
I'm so sorry, Luffy!
So sorry!
Hey, you guys!
Makino came all the way
out here to bring us some drinks!
You want to learn how to thank someone?
Uh-huh.
This is new for you.
Seeing as I'm Luffy's big brother and all,
I'd like to meet this Captain Red Hair and properly
thank him for everything he did for Luffy.
Say something, will you?!
I'm sorry.
Okay then, here's what you say...
So, first of all...
It's a dine and dash!
Stop!
Oh, we're being rude here!
Oh, right...!
– Thanks for the food!
Shut up, you damn kids! Just pay the bill!
I'm gonna win today!
– Alright!
Tonight, we're having bear stew!
7 Years Later
Ace, 17 Years Old
Luffy, 14 Years Old
Take care, Ace!
Will do! See you later, Luffy!
I'm heading out now!
Yeah! And I'll be a lot stronger
when I set out in three years!
Give it your all, Ace!
Take care of yourself!
Try not to catch a cold!
Just you wait! I'll make
a name for myself real soon!
Ace, the son of the Pirate King,
grew up in complete secrecy...
and he quietly departed from
the shore nearby Mt. Colubo.
There he goes!
Honestly. How is Garp going to take this?
You're gonna raise him, Dadan!
No, wait! Whose kid is that?!
Boss...
Ace just left.
Did he, now?
I'd better brace myself for Garp's outrage...
What a hopeless little shit.
Oh, and Ace left a message for you!
What?! He's gone, but he wants
to complain one last time?!
He said, "Sorry for all the trouble, and thanks."
Why'd that moron have to go and say that?!
What? Boss, are you crying?
I'm not crying, you idiot!
Only three more years for me!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Damn... Just a little off...
That was close, Luffy!
Try aiming just a little lower.
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
I'm getting stronger!
Several Months Later
Luffy!
Check out the newspaper!
What's up?
Just look!
So cool! Ace made a name for himself!
It's a picture of his pirate ship and crew!
Amazing! Ace is amazing!
But I'm not gonna lose to him!
3 Years Later
Luffy, 17 Years Old
Hey, come on!
I'm leaving now. You're not gonna see me off?
Hey!
Shut up...!
The mayor and Makino might know us,
but we'd send the rest of Windmill Village
into a panic if we came down the mountain!
But...
Just get going already!
Oh, okay. Well then, guys...
Thanks for everything!
Oh, don't embarrass us.
No need for thanks.
Take it easy and take care.
Yep! Sure thing!
Oh, right!
Dadan, I hate mountain bandits...
Shut up, you little turd!
...but I like you guys!
Don't say dumb stuff like that!
Just get lost already, dammit!
Damn! Every last one of you...!
What, are you crying?
No! I'm absolutely not!
Windmill Village, at the outskirts of
the Kingdom of Goa on Dawn Island...
Hey! You're going out to sea, so just
take my old fishing boat, Luffy!
You'll sink right away in that thing!
A rowboat? C'mon!
I'm really fine with this!
It's the start of my journey!
Sabo!
Look at me! I'm setting out to sea too!
Sabo was first. Ace was second.
I'm third, but I won't lose to them!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll catch up to you soon enough!
What're you doing, Luffy,
shouting to yourself like that?
Is it some sort of good luck charm?
It's not a charm. It's a challenge!
Who's Ace?
Not a clue.
Alright, I'm outta here!
Well, Mayor, he's finally off.
I'm gonna miss him.
He's disgracing our village
by becoming a pirate!
What a nice day to set sail!
Th-That's...!
If it isn't our local sea monster.
You don't know who you're messing with.
Check out this technique
ten years in the making!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
That'll teach you! Damn fish!
Incredible! He beat the
Lord of the Coast with one punch!
He's sure grown strong.
First, I've gotta gather a crew.
Ten people oughta do it!
I'll also need a Jolly Roger!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna be...
King of the Pirates!
We return to the present.
His brother Ace is dead,
and Luffy mourns his loss.
Luffy...
Me, the King of the Pirates?! Yeah, right!
I'm...
so weak!
It's Garp!
Windmill Village, Kingdom of Goa, East Blue
Garp's returned on his battleship!
On business?!
Garp, we read all about the war!
A resounding Marine victory, right?!
Yeah, and everyone here is safe?
Is Luffy okay?!
With Whitebeard dead, what'll happen
to the world?! Tell us, Garp!
These past few days, we've seen
a lot of pirate ships on the open sea.
The thought of being raided
keeps us up at night!
Rest easy! I just sank
three of 'em on the way here.
Really? That's good to hear!
Amateurs like them don't know
the first thing about a fight!
Although, Whitebeard was
a stabilizing factor...
With him gone, every sea in the world
will be a turbulent place for some time.
Don't let your guard down just because
you live in a remote part of the East Blue.
Hey!
– Yes, sir!
"Security, courtesy of Marine HQ's
Vice Admiral Garp," huh?
That's so reassuring!
There's nothing to be afraid of now!
Garp, we have another problem.
Bandits came down out of the
mountains and took over Makino's bar!
Bandits?
Stop! Don't!
Hey, Garp!
Oh, that's her!
You've got some nerve
showing your face here again!
Garp!
B-Boss!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Stand down! She and I go way back.
You...
You were right there on the battlefield!
They were right in front of you!
So, what the hell were you doing?!
What the hell were you doing?!
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why?! Why?!
Why did you just stand there and let Ace die?!
Is duty more important than your family?!
Right, Garp?! And they
call you the Hero of the Marines!
Shrivel up and die, you geezer!
Take it easy, boss! That's too far!
– Boss...
Garp, cat got your tongue?!
You could have saved him!
Why'd you let it happen?!
Stand up! Get on your feet!
You inhuman filth!
That's enough, Dadan!
Makino...
They may have been within arm's reach,
but there was nothing he could do!
The one hurting most here is Garp!
Y-You're wrong...
You're wrong...
You're wrong!
Luffy's the one who's hurting most!
Now, try to imagine that he's
right here in front of you.
I'm Ace! Who the hell are you?
Boo! That's a no-go.
"Who the hell" is too rude.
Is it, "Oh, it's you?!"
Who might you be?
Boo!
And just who are you?
Is it, "Who's that?"
Boo! Boo!
All wrong. Are you even trying?
It's your fault for buzzing
around with nonsense!
Quit it!
Hey, Ace!
Yesterday, I found the nest of a giant snake,
and it was filled with humongous eggs!
Let's go get them!
Huh? Humongous eggs?
No, not right now!
I'm studying how to greet people!
It'll be real bad if that giant snake
catches me when I go by myself!
But I'll be fine if you're with me. C'mon!
Shut up!
You have to know how much
he looked up to his brother!
Makino!
Garp...
How's Luffy? The newspapers
say he's gone missing.
Mayor...
He escaped in a submarine.
The Marines pursued him with everything they had,
and they searched the area thoroughly.
But the vessel eluded them.
At least for now... he's alive!
Thank goodness!
Still, don't you think it's strange that
Marine HQ's Vice Admiral Garp
and this bandit know each other?
Who knows?
Luffy might be an idiot,
but no matter what kind of pirate
he becomes, I will always stand beside him.
When I think about how he must be feeling,
it only breaks my heart.
Luffy!
You'll get through this!
Now, we take a look far away...
to somewhere in the second half
of the Grand Line, the New World.
Red Hair...
How can I thank you for this?
Don't be ridiculous.
He might have been my enemy,
but Whitebeard was a pirate worthy of respect.
Even Sengoku agreed.
Well, it's time we parted ways.
Yeah. Thanks.
Luffy, this must be difficult for you.
Word of Ace's final moments
took me by surprise.
Take back what you just said!
Don't you dare mock the man who saved me!
This era will be named after Whitebeard!
His actions were unmistakably...
Captain Roger's.
I often wished my captain would retreat.
I wished he would cry.
Listen to me, Luffy.
When you experience both victory and defeat,
and when you flee from battle and shed tears,
that is when you become a man.
It's okay to cry.
Overcome this!
Isle of Women, Calm Belt
Dammit! I'm so weak! I can't protect anyone!
Luffy.
Go away!
Leave me alone!
I can't do that! If I did, that would mean
letting you hurt yourself further!
It's my body to hurt! I'll do what I want to it!
Then by the same token,
Ace was allowed to hurt his own body...
and died regardless of how we felt!
Just shut up!
One more word, and I'll kick your ass!
You're welcome to try
if it'll make you feel better!
I, too, am injured... but I won't
lose to you! Not as you currently are!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Jinbe...
While I was out chasing Teach...
I met my little brother for the first time
in three years in the Kingdom of Arabasta.
As soon as I saw him, I felt relieved.
Do you know why?
Ow! That hurts!
I said that hurts, you punk!
What happened to that clarity of yours?!
You believed that you
could overcome anything!
And you never doubted your strength!
But a horde of enemies ruthlessly shattered your
beliefs and rendered you unable to do a thing...
And your brother was your
guiding light on this sea!
You've lost so much...
The world itself has become your
greatest obstacle yet, blocking your vision!
You can no longer see the path ahead!
Dark clouds of regret and guilt consume you!
Your pain overwhelms you, Luffy,
but overcome those feelings!
You can't just dwell on what you've lost!
What's gone is gone!
What is it that you still have?!
Luffy, don't mess around up here!
My regimen needs focus!
Luffy, hurry and get everyone into position!
A storm's just ahead!
Luffy, check it out! You'll
bear witness as I snag a huge fish!
Luffy, it's almost done. Be patient and wait!
Luffy, no matter the injury,
you're in good hands!
I'll always fix you up, good as new!
Oh, Luffy.
If you're interested, I can
teach you about archeology.
Hey, Luffy! The cola engine
is purring like a kitten today!
You can leave everything
about the Sunny to me!
Good morning, Luffy! Rise and shine!
Well then, let's get started
with a morning ditty!
Luffy.
Luffy!
– Luffy!
My crew...
I still have my crew!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp!
Sanji! Chopper! Robin!
Franky! Brook!
My friends are still here!
I see.
We promised to meet up somewhere.
Guys, meet back at the Sunny in three days!
– Okay!
I gotta get there...
even though I'm running late.
I'm sure they're all waiting for me!
What I saw there... Jinbe...
I have a reckless little brother,
which worries your big brother.
And I'm sure he does nothing
but stress you all out.
Take care of him for me.
I saw that Luffy's no longer that kid
who couldn't help but follow me everywhere.
You see now...
he has a crew he can rely on.
No matter what happens, he'll be just fine.
I was so relieved.
I... wanna see them.
I really wanna see them!