Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Sewil
Graphics
Datenshi
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing & Typesetting
Gab
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit
Poppy
Ravenfire
Westfal
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
PamkinPinguin
rangicus
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Hundred-Million Man
Here they come! Dodge!
These praying mantises aren't normal!
– Our net!
– What's with this forest?!
It's him!
Who's "him"?!
The south bird is
commanding the insects!
Why is a bird bossing bugs around?!
They're close!
Where's the call coming from?!
What's that?
I can hear something else...
Up ahead!
Huh? Boulders?
They're rolling this way!
Are they dung beetle balls?!
No! They're bugs!
Ladybugs!
They're huge! Oww!
Damn pests!
There's no end to 'em!
Why is a mole cricket army attacking us?!
You're in the way!
You think you stand a chance?! Huh?!
I can hear it, but I can't see it...
A slug!
Salt! Throw salt!
Sanji! Your Somersault Kick!
Roger–
No, not that kind of "salt"!
I'm sick of running! Bring it on!
No, Luffy! Kumabachi bees
are super venomous!
– Fireflies!
– So pretty!
Cockroaches!
Pigs!
Oh! Would you look at that?
What wonderful gold!
You guys... have no right to that gold!
No right?
How's this for a right?
Big Chop!
Reckless fool...
We're way stronger than you!
That's all the right
we need to claim your gold.
Well, geezer?!
Watch out, Boss!
Havoc Sonar!
B-Bastard!
Wait, Sarquiss!
I'll shut him up for good.
Not that again...
The power of the Spring-Spring Fruit...!
Run, Shojo!
Spring...
Snipe!
Shojo!
Boss! We found gold!
It's a bell-shaped ingot!
Look! It matches the bells
described in the logbook!
Alright, pack it up.
Load the gold on board.
Grow up, old man!
That "City of Gold" is just
a figment of Noland's imagination!
If you wanna be a pirate
in the coming era,
then you need to realize
that dreams never come true!
The City of Gold does exist!
Hey, now! Simmer down!
It's a small house!
Hold on, punk...
You're a spineless whelp
who won't fight for your dreams;
you have no claim to being a pirate!
What was that?
No luck. We didn't see a single one...
We saw one, but we got swarmed by bugs.
There was no time for the bird...
All we could do was run...
Man... Seven people,
and you get zilch?!
Get it together, you guys!
That includes you!
I can't run anymore!
"You really think you can catch me? Idiots!"
What?! It showed itself
just to tell us that?!
Dammit! This'll shut you up!
All I needed was to see one.
Chestnut head! We caught a bird!
Chestnut head!
Masira!
Shojo!
What in the world happened?!
Damn it! Who did this?!
Hey! Gimme a hand!
Right!
Look! The Going Merry...!
What the hell?! Who did this?!
Dammit! Who was it?!
Sorry...
Chestnut!
Hey, are you awake?!
I'm truly sorry!
There was nothing we could do!
We're pathetic!
But, there's time yet...
to reinforce the ship before dawn!
Wait, chestnut head!
Tell us what happened first!
No... It's okay. Forget about it.
Doesn't matter now...
More importantly, did you guys...?
Ah! Great! You caught
yourselves a south bird!
Perfect!
Luffy!
Hm?
The gold... It's gone!
Ah, it's alright...
Forget about that junk...
You need to focus on...
What do you mean "junk"?!
It took ten long years
of you diving into the ocean
and torturing your body
to find that gold!
You can't just...
Shut it!
It's alright... This is our problem.
Listen!
With the entire
Saruyama Alliance working on it,
we can fix and reinforce
that ship, no problem.
I'll have 'em finish before morning!
There won't be any trouble
with your departure tomorrow!
Mark my words, you will be
soaring into the sky tomorrow!
Mister...
Hey, Luffy.
Bellamy's mark...
Want help?
Nah, I've got this.
No, Luffy! Don't be an idiot!
We set sail in only three hours!
If I run along the coast, will I reach
that town from earlier today?
Yes, you will.
Hey, kid! Where are you going?!
Don't do anything rash!
Do you know who you're dealing–
If you wanna stop him, use this.
K-Kid...
I'll be back by dawn!
I'm all empty!
That's every last drop in my body!
Now I won't shed
a single bead of sweat!
This ol' drunk is broke and dry!
O, God of Alcohol,
thank you for today!
But I guess there's no such thing...
A newspaper?
Let's see! What bad news
is there today?
Oh, this isn't a newspaper.
It's a stack of wanted posters...
Honestly, in this lawless town,
I'm sick of meeting new bad guys!
This is that spineless kid
from this afternoon!
Boy, that sky island talk
was a real hoot!
I think he was worth thirty million...
Huh?
Crap! I had a little too much to drink!
Let's see...
1,000
10,000
100,000
1,000,000
10,000,000...
Yikes! I really did drink too much!
1,000
10,000
100,000
1,000,000
10,000,000...
100,000,000!
Three hours, Luffy!
If we delay our departure any longer...
you'll lose your only chance
to go to the sky island!
He probably kept diving
every day without taking time
for those bubbles
to dissipate from his body.
This is a duel with the man
who screwed up my life.
Sorry! I'm truly sorry!
There was nothing we could do!
We're pathetic!
That bastard!
Those big apes were hilarious!
The tears and snot running down
their faces, their bodies covered in gashes
as they cried, "Boss!"
If he's that important,
they should've protected him better!
Right?!
Talk about lame!
Don't be like that.
Against you and Bellamy, they stood no chance.
After all, our captain is a major
rookie worth fifty-five million belly!
Bad news!
What's the big deal?!
It's the middle of the night!
This afternoon!
Those guys in here, they–
Oh! Bellamy!
You're still here?!
You gotta get out of here!
You're in the most danger!
What are you talking about?
Me, in danger?
One hundred million...?!
Sixty million?!
That's right!
Those two from this afternoon...
have bounties way higher
than yours, Bellamy!
You're dead meat!
Are you serious?! Crap!
We laughed at the wrong people!
Think they remember our faces?!
It's dangerous to stick around!
I've never met anyone
with a bounty of 100 million!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! You morons!
Are you panicking over
a few scraps of paper?
Do you need your eyes checked?
You saw their captain in the flesh!
I made it!
Did you know there have been pirates
who would fake their own wanted
posters to bolster their infamy?
People would see their bounties
and just curl up and surrender
even though they could've
won in a fight...
Just like you guys now!
You saw how weak they are,
but look at you now!
Pathetic!
You're right! Boy, those
bastards had me scared!
Bellamy's right! Some brat
with a bounty of 100 million
has gotta be involved
in some serious stuff,
so then why hasn't
he been in the papers?!
Right! I ain't heard of any straw hat kid!
Whew! Had me scared for a minute...!
Bellamy! Where are you?!
To think he'd call me out...
Hey!
Speak of the devil...
You got business with me?
Yeah! Give back chestnut head's gold!