Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Arlong Park
The weather's so great!
Is the Grand Line far,
far away that way?!
Or maybe this way?!
That way?! This way?!
This is so exciting!
You're annoying. Sit still, will ya?
Sorry! Sorry!
Now that we finally have a cook,
we just need to get Nami back.
Then we're finally going
to the Grand Line!
Nami, huh?
Just remembering her beautiful
visage makes me happy!
How I can't wait to see her again!
Hey, Yosaku. We're almost
to where Nami is, right?
You guys're soft-minded!
Too soft-minded! Don't you get it?!
We're heading right toward the
infamous Arlong's lair as we speak!
Big Sis' eyes were glued to
Arlong's picture when she saw it!
She wasn't her normal self!
Big Sis Nami plans to
take down Arlong
and collect his
20-million-belly bounty!
She may already be inside
his compound as we speak!
Well, let's have some food!
Yeah.
Don't tell me you guys've
never heard of Arlong?!
Arlong? Who's that?
Never heard of him.
All right, listen up! I guess I'll just
have to fill you in about everything!
Arlong is a fishman who used to
rampage throughout the Grand Line!
Fishman?
A fishman, huh?
I've never met one.
Say, I hear that
Fishman Island in the Grand Line
is full of beautiful mermaids!
Do fishmen...
look like this?
That's a masterpiece!
Can't you guys stay focused?!
All right, then. I'll explain
from the very beginning.
The reason the Grand Line's called
a pirate graveyard in the first place
is because of the three
powers that reign over it.
One of which is the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Seven Warlords?
Simply put, they're privateers.
What? Why would pirates get
the government's approval?
By paying the government a cut
of the loot they take from pirates,
the Seven Warlords
are allowed to roam free!
In other pirates' eyes, they're
no more than government dogs,
but they're strong!
Even Hawk Eye Mihawk, the guy
Big Bro Zoro lost to, is a warlord!
That's awesome!
There's seven of those guys?!
The Seven Warlords are awesome!
So, one of these Seven Warlords is
Jinbe, the Fishman Pirates' boss.
And the fishman Arlong is
a pirate right on par with him
who used to commit atrocity
after atrocity in the Grand Line!
Like this?
That's just your last
picture standing up!
Arlong has taken over 20 towns
since coming to the East Blue!
He's far stronger than Don Krieg!
But why would Nami go
to this guy all by herself?
I told you, she's after
the bounty on his head!
No, who knows? Maybe Nami
is actually a mermaid!
Especially given how lovely she is!
Like this?!
I'll kill you, you bastard!
Do you guys even understand
what I've told you?!
Yeah, there's a strong
fishman, right? We get it!
No, you don't get it! You don't
know how strong fishmen are!
We'll find out when we get there.
Quit worrying.
Anyways, let's have some food.
Yeah! Food!
Oh? Food?
What do you want?
Meat things with bones in them!
I want sautéed bean sprouts!
All right! Leave it to me!
I'll be done in no time!
Meat and bean sprouts...
Having a cook really is great!
Y-Yeah!
Meat! A huge serving of meat!
And bean sprouts for me!
A huge serving!
Northwestern
East Blue
All right. Here is this
month's payment. Take it.
Captain Nezumi
Navy Branch 16
Arlong.
You have a different approach than
your run-of-the-mill pirates.
You truly know how to
get ahead in the world.
Captain “Sawtooth” Arlong
Arlong Pirates
Likewise!
Befriending me means you can milk
the East Blue for all it's worth!
For a Navy captain,
you're wise to realize that!
Thanks, as always.
Now you say that?
The world is better off
when cash flows easily.
Money is great. You can
trust it more than anything.
Don't you agree?
Indeed.
I hate humans, but good sports
like you are an exception.
Well, I should be going.
Come drink with us sometime!
It'd be fun!
A naval patrol ship shouldn't
dock at a pirate's island.
I'll kill anyone who tells
headquarters for you.
Well, I'll be leaving.
Hey! The captain's heading back!
Take him to his ship!
Right!
Officer Hatchan
(Octopus Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
Officer Hatchan
(Octopus Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
Get in the octopus pot!
I'll take you there!
Right. Thanks.
You always have such a funny face!
It looks just like a rat's!
Hey! Hachi! Watch your mouth!
The captain is a valued guest!
Oh, right! Sorry!
No, it's all right.
Okay! Here we go!
Damn fishmen. You're creepy as hell.
But your money's good!
Hey, you! Out of the way!
I'm here to kill Arlong!
Arlong killed my daddy!
Move, or I'll kill you, too!
Hey!
Arlong doesn't have time to
bother with little brats like you!
Now go home!
Just take this and look after yourself.
Darn it!
Oh! You're back, Nami!
That was a long trip!
Well? How was your haul this time?
Couldn't have gone better!
I earned a ton!
I found so many suckers who were
fooled so easily! Look here!
Betrayal is your forte!
I guess.
Hey! Brothers! Our comrade
has returned! Let's party!
– It's Nami!
– Nami's back!
Officer Nami
Arlong Pirates
W-W-We're finally here! Arlong Park!
So this is the hideout of Arlong,
the fishman from the Grand Line?!
Is Nami really here?!
Big Sis Nami was
on the Going Merry,
so let's first see if it's
docked on this island!
G-Good idea!
We're busting in.
Wh-Why are we
suddenly doing that?!
Are you stupid?! We haven't
even found any clues yet!
We're dealing with fishmen, you know!
We gotta have a strategy first!
We don't have time for that.
Luffy told us to bring her back.
I'm gonna do just that,
no matter who we're dealing with!
Not good.
Let's go!
There it is! I found it!
It's the Going Merry!
Why's it over there?
So Big Sis Nami is here!
Hey, you bastards!
What's the big idea?! Untie me!
We're farther east of Arlong Park...
at Cocoyashi Village.
But it's strange. Why's the ship
stopped so far from the village?
I said to untie me!
You nearly died from your injury!
Just take it easy!
Leave this all to me!
I am so going to kill him someday!
I'll bring that girl back!
You're in high spirits, now that
you know she's not in Arlong Park.
Right rudder, full!
Pull the boat up to the Going Merry!
Right!
All right! I dub this brave moment,
in which I tread unknown soil,
“Captain Usopp's Grand Adventure”!
Fishmen!
Full speed ahead!
Yes, sir!
Why did you just pass by them?!
Did you see that?!
There were fishmen there!
They're Arlong's crew! They're scary!
Somethin' wrong with that?!
Don't you snap at me!
I guess this whole area is
really under Arlong's control!
What now?
All right! We'll just say we
couldn't bring Nami back!
Untie me, you idiots!
Never seen that boat before.
Suspicious.
– Escape!
– Agreed!
Hold it, you two!
Bye!
Hey! At least untie me!
Wait, what? It's just him?
Were you banished from
somewhere or somethin'?
I-I guess.
I'm gonna kill those guys!
Ah! So you got these injuries
from being tortured!
All right! Let's take him back
to Arlong for now!
Forgive us, Zoro! I'll tell Luffy
you were a truly brave man!
What an unlucky person!
I'll never forget about you, Big Bro!
All right, then!
Let's get on dry land for now!
Right!
There should be a town
called Gosa up here!
Wh-What happened here?!
I heard Arlong ravaged it
a few weeks back, but...
A-All the houses have
been flipped over!
I hear fishmen are naturally
ten times stronger than humans!
Is this the caliber of people
from the Grand Line?!
How'd the street even get like this?
A monster called Momoo did it.
A monster?
This place even has monsters?
We brought him from the Grand Line.
From the Grand Line, huh?
“We”?
You're with that banished guy,
aren't you?!
Bye!
Get back here!
Escaped by a hair...
No way!
Please stay safe, Big Bro Usopp!
I'm going to wait here for
Yosaku and Big Bro Luffy!
Even if you're a fishman,
no one can catch me on dry land!
I'm used to this!
Just try and catch up to me!
Wh-What the...
I found you, fishman!
I'm gonna avenge my daddy!
Don't mess with the fishmen!
Chabo
From Gosa Town
Nojiko
From Cocoyashi Village
Have you forgotten?!
Everyone here in Gosa
was slaughtered because just
one villager defied them!
For real? You look like a fishman,
but you're human. Just barely.
Just barely?!
Where are you?! Over there?!
He's coming!
A fishman!
There was a real one, too?
Get back! I, Captain Usopp,
will protect you!
I should be able
to handle a single one!
Take this!
Lethal Lead Star!
Wh-Where am I?
My house.
You awake?
Wh-Who are you?!
I'm Nojiko. I grow tangerines here.
That's right! You clobbered me!
Just when I was trying
to save you, too!
I'm the one who saved you.
Had you done anything
to that fishman,
there's no question you'd be dead.
This is why I hate outsiders!
But you're a kid from Gosa, right?
Surely you know all too well
from firsthand experience
that you'll be killed if you
mess with the fishmen.
I know!
I know, but they killed my daddy!
They stole everything,
destroyed our town,
and killed tons of people!
They have to pay!
No matter what, they have to pay!
So I went to Arlong Park! But a
woman from his crew got in the way!
She... was like a witch!
I hate this! I don't care if I die;
I'm going to avenge my daddy!
Then die.
If you're prepared to die,
then go get your revenge!
But remember this:
Now that me and that witch
at Arlong Park have stopped you,
you've escaped death twice now!
Leave when you're
done with your tea.
Hey! Isn't that being
a little harsh on the kid?!
Kid or not, if someone wants to die,
then just let 'em die!
He doesn't have the guts to live
through hard times anyway!
Say what?!
I know a kid who's
focusing on the future,
while she endures a life
more painful than death.
That's why I hate people like him
who throw their lives away!
What should I do?
I hate this! I'll endure it!
What should I do?!
What about your mom?
She's alive.
She's worried about you.
Go back to her.
Okay.
You're actually a nice person!
Even though you have tattoos.
Prejudice!
I don't know anything
about you, you know.
Oh, right!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I'm looking for a girl named Nami.
Nami?!
You know her?
What?! Nami's an officer
of the Arlong Pirates?!
Yep. Everyone here knows about her.
Even that little boy said
she seemed like a witch.
Even more surprising,
that witch grew up in this very house!
Nami and I are adopted sisters.
So this is...
Nami's house?!
Nami and I are both orphans.
We were brought up in this house.
Our foster parent is dead too,
but the three of us used to live
happily here in Cocoyashi Village.
Then, Nami betrayed her own
parent and fellow villagers
and joined Arlong's group?!
Yeah, pretty much. A real witch, huh?
Damn it! So that's the deal?!
So she had us fooled the entire time!
She was after treasure
from the very start!
Even after she helped fight
to protect my village
and looked so happy sailing with us!
Oh? She looked happy?
Her?
We came here to bring
her back with us,
but I guess there's no need for–
That reminds me, a friend
of ours was unfortunately
caught by the fishmen.
This is bad.
I wonder how he's holding up.
Open the gate!
We've brought someone suspicious!
I'll ask again.
Just why have you come here?
I told you already, I'm looking
for a girl! Half-fish freak!
You've got a big mouth
for a lowly human.
I'll excuse you this time,
but never say "half-fish" again.
We fishmen are evolved humans
who've gained the ability
to breathe underwater.
Those fish abilities make
us superior to you.
As proof,
we possess numerous abilities
that surpass those of humans!
Get it through your head that
fishmen are the lords of all things!
Humans defying fishmen is basically
defying the laws of nature!
I'm sick of your
ridiculous dogma, Arlong.
Why'd ya gotta be so serious, Nami.
You may be human,
but you're an exception.
You're a skilled surveyor and a prized
member of the Arlong Pirates!
You make truly accurate
sea charts for us!
I'm much more intelligent than
you guys. It's only natural.
Hey! Nami! What does
he mean, “surveyor”?!
Why are you acting all
buddy-buddy with this guy?!
Oh? He's an acquaintance of yours?
Don't be ridiculous.
He was just my prey.
I just swiped a whole load
of treasure from this guy.
I can't believe he'd follow me here,
without any idea he'd been tricked.
How naive.
So these are your true colors, huh?
After you talked so much
about hating pirates.
Surprised? It was all an act.
Does this make it clear enough?
Th-That's...
I'm a pirate, plain and simple!
I'm an officer of the Arlong Pirates!