Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
KaitouYahiko
Typesetting
Gab
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Gaijin
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Tsuru Returns the Favor
The probability of you two
surviving the month...
is 19 percent.
It's time you cut your visit short.
Don't you know who pulls
the strings in this country?
No idea!
It's Kaido, right?!
We're here to...
take down an Emperor!
Hey, Luffy!
Kin'emon said we shouldn't
say things like that, either!
Wha...?
Ahh! That was a lie! I don't know who!
By the way, where'd you get that sword?
Some named blade, thus and verily.
Yeah, I'm certain it's a named blade.
Let me see it for a sec.
No way!
You can't use a sword anyway
so just give it to me!
I'll cut them up, verily!
Charge.
This is a sword fight, verily!
Don't throw the scabbard!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
It's not a damn pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Even the lizard's after me!
Damn you!
Straw Sword.
What kind of sword is that?!
That poor lizard!
That was fast!
Impressive.
What just happened?!
Minus One Life.
These strawmen represent my subordinates.
I can store them in my body
with my Straw-Straw power...
so I won't be harmed.
If I store ten of them, I can die ten times.
Now, let's play a game.
A game?!
That's right, with this Strawman's Card!
I'm not so honorable that I'd face two of
the Worst Generation on equal footing.
He's a bigger pain in the ass than I thought...
but I should've figured!
Let's begin.
The Reversed Fool!
Damn, this signifies internal discord.
Sorry, I'll draw a better card next time.
I must accept the risks because...
some cards can push me beyond my limits.
Hey! What are you doing, boy?!
Hawkins!
Fear not.
Tama! Stay with us, Tama!
She's burning up!
That's must be why the dog's in a hurry.
You bastards!
We won't let you get away!
Get them!
Stop!
We've gotta hurry up!
Yeah, I'm gonna finish them off!
Hawkins! They're getting away!
I drew a good card.
The Reversed Hierophant...
The card of pursuit!
Hey, Luffy!
Protect the kid!
I'll...
handle...
this!
Hang on a little longer, boy!
You're actually pretty tough.
Nails?!
Two-Sword Style...
Nigiri...
Toro...
Samon!
Should we go after them, Hawkins?!
The Hierophant.
It's the card of assistance.
Someone will lead them away to safety...
What an annoying guy...
So, how's the kid doing?
So warm!
Her temperature keeps rising.
Wait... are you...?
Are you lost?!
We've got no time to waste...
Let's just... go right.
You should go left.
You samurai are so strong.
Who are you?!
I can't believe you repelled Hawkins.
You're...
I'm the one you saved earlier,
green gentleman.
My name is Tsuru.
Otsuru
Teahouse Owner
Were you hiding in his tail all this time?!
Yes!
Thank you for saving me.
Here!
Could you at least wipe the sweat off of her?
Oh! Thanks!
I hope this doesn't sound too presumptuous...
but would you allow me
to care for young Otama?
You know her?
Yes.
I see! Please do!
She drank the polluted river water
because she was so hungry.
I thought so...
That's not good.
Instead of searching for a doctor...
please bring her to my teahouse.
Tea?!
This is no time for tea!
If we don't hurry up, she's gonna die!
I don't know this kid, so it might
not be any of my business but...
No, no...
We have a medical herb that is
effective against the river's poison.
That'll be the best way
to treat Otama's condition.
I see. Then please, help us!
Thank you!
Okay, I'll show you the way.
If you go left, you can get to the town.
Let's go, boy!
To return the favor I owe you...
let me treat you, too, green gentleman...
Okobore Town
Kuri
Wano
Here you go.
Oh, the teahouse's dumplings are a rare treat.
They're the only things...
that keep me going.
You exaggerate...
Soon, you'll be able to eat as many
as you want just like you used to.
I hope so...
Okiku
Teahouse Waitress
Hey, old man, the place is closing now!
Get lost!
Now, Okiku.
You can't pay the street tax, right?
All I'm saying is that I'll help you.
If you become my wife...
you won't have to work!
Every day, you'd be able to eat as much
delicious food from the farm as you want!
Our social standings are too different.
If you're not ordering anything, would you please...
take your leave?
I don't wanna eat anything from this place!
The dumplings and tea are made
from others' leftovers!
Say, you do know who I am, right?
I'm a famous yokozuna from the capital.
I'm the best sumo wrestler in Wano,
Urashima!
It's time you quit this seedy teahouse!
You need to stop living off of
someone's leftovers, so that you and I...
so that we can... y'know...?
Okiku!
Miss Otsuru!
Otama drank poisoned water from the river!
Oh! That's serious!
Please! Do what you can to help her!
Of course, right away!
Hey!
Who are you idiots?!
Get out the way.
Why would I have to do that...?!
Okiku! I have a match in Bakura Town later!
If you're interested,
come and see how strong I am!
Hey, Shachi! Is that them?
Yeah...
It's them, isn't it?! It's the Straw Hats!
I hope they won't mess up the plan.
Should I go tell them
before they make any trouble?!
You'd better not!
You'll draw people's attention!
They'll wonder why a bear's here and panic!
I'm sorry.
For now, let's just report this to the captain.