Video Editing
Gigglebot
Galaxy 9000
iconsumekidneys
Gigglebot
Galaxy 9000
iconsumekidneys
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
DraSleek
Subtitle Editing
Byron
CyanRyan
EvoWarrior5
Veggieguy
Byron
CyanRyan
EvoWarrior5
Veggieguy
Translation
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Gaijin
Rokitoki
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Gaijin
Rokitoki
What?! Ah...!
You mooks!
He got away because of you!
He was our golden goose!
Dive, Dive, Dive!
Vacate the premises!
Don't think we won't arrest all of you!
What are you doing, Navy?!
Don't interrupt Soul King!
Hey, what's happening in there?
It's a riot!
The Navy suddenly stormed in here
ready to arrest Soul King,
but he got away because
his fans blocked the marines!
Damn it all!
Why, that backstabbing...!
That's right! This is big news!
The musician Brook
is on Straw Hat Luffy's crew!
He's actually a pirate!
You have my thanks!
That's what I'd call good timing.
Big Sis Shakky sent me!
Your friends should be waiting at Grove 42!
It's been a while!
My heart is filled with anticipation!
Oh, I don't have a heart to be filled.
Grove 41
That's right!
The Navy is on the move,
and Luffy is in the area!
We're taking the Sunny to Grove 42,
so we'll see you there!
Roger.
What was that?
Hey, weren't you listening?
Well...
Navy. Come. We. Ship. Run.
Understand?
No, I don't! Why are you talking
like that?! Just say it normally!
A meathead like you wouldn't understand it.
What?!
Okay. You. Later. Slashed.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, do you hear that uproar?
Huh?
You're right. There. Noisy.
Shut up, morons!
We've gone and found
one of the perpetrators...
who dared to show me disrespect!
This guy!
Huh?
I'll start by teaching this guy a lesson!
I'll show him... just how terrifying I can be!
And what I'm about to do to him...
will be a warning
to each and every one of you!
Mess with me, and this is
what you're gonna get!
Ya get my meaning, lubbers?!
A guy with a 400-million-belly bounty
sure is scary!
What's the matter with this guy?
Zoro, Sanji, do you know him?
Huh?
Well, earlier...
Hold it, you pirates!
Straw Hat Luffy and all his followers,
surrender now!
Th-The Navy...?!
We've blocked off every exit from Grove 46!
There's no escape now!
H... How did the Navy find out about me?
What do you mean by that?!
Hey, Captain! We're under siege!
Don't panic, idiot!
Why do you think we got
all these new members?
Some of 'em are worth over 100 million!
But we're outnumbered...
Just watch, dumbass!
Hey, Caribou!
Use that marine as a shield to clear a path!
"Marine"...?
It seems like they may have
caught one of our scouts!
Damn, that's not good!
What are you doing, Caribou?!
Using him is our ticket outta here!
I can't do that, Big Boss!
What?
Because this soldier told a lie...
He said he hadn't called the Navy yet!
Don't do it!
That lunatic ignored my order!
Uh-oh, he did it...
They seem to follow an underhanded rule
that lets them lie to their enemies!
Boy, do I find that distasteful!
Looks like they have
no intention of surrendering!
After them! Get those pirates!
Knuckleheads! Our boss is worth 400 million!
He's Straw Hat Luffy, y'know?!
Bring it on!
This ain't good, Captain. Let's run!
You ingrates! Listen to your captain!
Huh? Why would they be calling me "boss"?
Again, what do you mean by that?
Fight with courage!
You're...
the man worth 88 million,
Lip "Service" Doughty!
I just love the way you fight.
Don't be scared! Get ready to shoot!
He's got a bounty of 92 million...
Albion "the Maimed"!
Don't back down! Fight for justice!
Yeah!
It stinks! Hypocrites' blood!
A bounty of 210 million...
Pirate "Wet-Haired" Caribou!
Surrender now!
Oh, no! You've eaten a devil fruit?!
You shouldn't have done that!
It's not healthy to push yourself too hard!
My sword...!
Wh-Whoa! Now what's going on?!
Pacifista!
What?!
Why are the Navy's human weapons here?!
Those're the guys that look like Kuma!
But Hancock told me not to cause trouble...
Seriously, what the hell
do you mean by that?!
Pirate Straw Hat Luffy: Confirmed.
Are those actual pacifista?
And they're actually shooting at me?!
Pacifista, you say? How thrilling!
88-million-belly bounty,
Lip "Service" Doughty: Subdued.
Captain Doughty!
Follow the pacifista! Catch the pirates!
Yeah!
One shot?!
Even with a bounty of 88 million,
he was no match.
This is bad news...
Wait, Captain, where are you going?!
Wait for me!
Hey, hey!
Morons! He wrecked Doughty,
so we got no chance! We better run!
Boss Straw Hat, do something!
If this keeps up,
those human weapons will kill us all!
Big Boss–
Huh?
Big Boss is gone!
Big Boss?
Do they mean Straw Hat?
Wait! My side hurts!
You morons...! Run, or they'll kill–
You're in the way, idiot!
Huh? Who are you?
That's...
Big Boss!
Why are you going around as Straw Hat?
H-H-Hey, bastard!
Don't you know who I am?!
Get out of my way or I'll kill you
and tear out your guts!
Haven't you heard?!
I'm the son of Dragon the Revolutionary!
I'm the grandson of Garp the Hero!
I'm a famous pirate
with a 400-million-belly bounty, Straw–
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
Wha...?
Huh?
Ah...!
– What?!
Boss Straw Hat!
Now I get it.
They all got tricked into joining
a fake Straw Hat crew.
PX-5, who is this guy really?
Pirate "Triple-Tongued" Demaro Black.
Bounty: 26-million-belly.
– What?!
Twenty-six million? That means he's...
a fake?!
They found out! Run for it!
What's with this loser?!
He posed as Straw Hat Luffy and tricked us!
Because the real one is dead!
Damn! I almost took orders from a weakling
with a measly 26-million-belly bounty!
What?
He was pretending to be me?
Sanji and Zoro too?
They looked just like the real ones!
I'd better leave before anything else happens.
That faker is an idiot,
but you morons are also out of luck.
You're all under arrest!
And as it so happens,
the real Straw Hat is here too.
PX-5 detected him
the instant we entered this area.
Shoot him, PX-5!
That was close!
What was that for?!
This bag is holding all my precious lunches!
His... His face...
It's just like the poster!
So that guy was the real Straw Hat!
Form up!
We were already prepared
to catch the real one!
– Aye, sir!
Straw Hat!
What?! Are you gonna
try and stop me again?!
I'm supposed to stay out of trouble
so I can set sail!
Don't worry! You won't need to set sail!
Unlike two years ago,
I'm officially a member of the Navy now!
So, this is where I capture you!
PX-5!
Too slow...
What?!
Gear Second!
Gum-Gum...
Jet Pistol!
Straw Hat...
That's... haki!
He beat the pacifista with a single blow!
See ya!
I bet we'll meet again somewhere!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Don't let Straw Hat escape!
– Yeah!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh?
Luffy! I knew it was you!
How'd you get in trouble already?!
Ohhh!
It's really you this time!
It's been a while, guys!
Roronoa! Black Leg!
So they really were alive!
PX-7!
– Outta my way!
I cut him!
No, I broke his neck!
It's the Straw Hats!
The real ones!
They're nothing like the fake Straw Hats!
Hey, Luffy, you're ninth.
Shut up! Imagine gloating about that!
Luffy, hurry up!
Everyone's waiting at the ship!
Okay!
Don't let them get away!
Catch them at any cost!
– Aye, sir!
It's been such a long time!
I hope everyone's doing alright!
I'm so happy!
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh!
Rayleigh!
What?!
No way!
Dark King Rayleigh?!
I came here to check on you,
but you seem to be doing fine.
You've refined your skills even further.
Uh-huh!
Now get going!
Your friends are waiting.
Uh-huh! Rayleigh, thank you
for everything these past two years!
This isn't like you at all. Just go!
Rayleigh!
I'll do it!
I'm gonna become the pirate king!
What are you guys doing?!
Get Straw Hat already!
Oops!
Hurry up, Luffy!
Rayleigh, thank you for everything!
Well then, Rayleigh...!
Thanks again for everything!
I'm going now!
Yes...
They went that way!
After them!
Don't let them get away!
Rise to the top!
The Straw Hats are heading for Grove 42!
Don't let them get away!
What was that?
Dark King Rayleigh!
My protégé is setting sail!
Don't be too hard on him.
Wh-What is this line?
I recommend you do not cross it.
Oh, bon bags! There're so many!
What's in them?
They're filled with food. I imagine everyone's
stomachs got bigger over the past two years.
I'll let you fill up later!
Really?! I can't wait to eat your food!
There they are! They're this way!
Oh? They circled ahead!
No other choice, huh?
Everybody, charge!
Yeah!
I wanna... become a flea...
What's wrong? What're you...?
I wanna become a mite...
What?!
What in the world...?
I... I...
I wanna become a louse...
Hey!
It must be...
As I suspected,
this mess is your doing.
I can't believe it!
You haven't gotten anywhere yet!
That's right!
I remember you from Thriller Bark!
Who was she?
What are you still doing here?
You should be nicer to the one
who brought you back to this island!
If I hadn't directed you, why, you'd be...
Just try a little gratitu–
A real woman! A real woman!
Of course I am!
What are you, sick?
Anyway, set sail already!
I saw some Navy ships around here!
– What?
Soon, there'll be no way out!
The Straw Hats' Rendezvous Point, Grove 42 Shore
Oh?!
That voice...!
Usopp-san! Nami-san! Robin-san!
Frrranky-san!
Brook!
Hey! I can't believe you abandoned stardom!
Attaboy!
It's been a long time, everybody!
You two have become even more beautiful!
Alright, Nami-san!
It's been two years, so...
Ah! You wrote a song for us?
...would you be so kind
as to show me your pa–
What do you think?!
I never let you see them two years ago either!
I-I'm so excited to see you again... See?
It's... making my heart quiver...
Although...
I don't have a heart that can quiver...
Hey... The rock star just hit rock bottom.
Honestly! You guys are still immature.
By the way...
I don't see everyone on board yet.
Oh, right.
Chopper went to pick them up–
Hey!
– Huh?
Took 'em long enough!
Hey!
Everybody!
I found them!
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Hey!
Luffy-san! I missed you so much!
You guys sure do look manlier!
We're all back together again!
Finally–
Oh!
Guys!
What?!
Sanji!
Well then, thank you!
Say hi to everyone
in the Torino Kingdom for me!
Usopp! Is Sanji alright?!
One... One... One beautiful woman...
Hey, stay with me!
Two beautiful women...
Chopper, this is real bad!
We gotta stop the bleeding!
F-F-Franky, you're...!
What's the matter?
Is there something that concerns you-mecha?
"Mecha"?! I wanna try too!
Wait, Luffy!
Leave that crap for later!
It looks like the Navy ships
are already here!
Oh, no! When did they get here?!
Three Navy ships!
Hey, we need to get them
before they get us!
Fire! Send them to the depths!
Slave...
Arrow!
Wha...? What just happened?
I-It's...
The Kuja Pirates!
Who...
put a Navy ship...
in my way?
That's... the Kuja Jolly Roger!
The "Kuja"?
They're strong, Amazonian pirates led
by the Pirate Empress, one of the Warlords.
A warlord?!
Her name is Boa Hancock.
They say anyone who sees her becomes
infatuated and turns into stone.
Oh, too bright! She is dazzling!
There is no end to her beauty!
You weren't kidding! She's a goddess!
Goddess?!
Where is she?!
Goddess? Goddess?
Goddess... Oh, goddess... Oh, goddess... G... G... Goddess...
He turned to stone!
Hey, that's Hancock and her pirates!
–Huh?
– Huh?
Move your ship, Boa Hancock!
Are you trying to interfere with our duties?
Cease your baseless accusations!
I just don't feel like moving out of the way.
Sh-She's acting like a child!
Is that a problem?
Go, Luffy. Now is your chance!
She just winked at us...
She helped us.
Let's set sail now!
You know that warlord?
Yeah... I was sent to the Isle of Women
and became friends with them.
That's the legendary island
full to the brim with women.
I didn't know it was real...
Friends with the Pirate Empress?!
Hey! Did you even get any training done?!
Yeah, I'm all set!
Damn... It's not fair...! It's not fair...!
You doing okay, Sanji?
Whoa, so they're Luffy's friends!
There are a bunch of creatures
that I've never seen before.
– One, two, three, four...
– Looks like they're having fun!
Okay, let's get ready to set sail now!
– Yeah!
– Yes, Nami-swan!
Huh? What's the matter, Usopp?
It's just that...
did you guys beat back all those marines?
No. We could still hear them
shouting as we were flying away.
Then, why aren't they coming
after us from inland?
This is Reinforcement Platoon 3!
Can you hear me?
What's wrong? What happened?
We can't get to Grove 42!
Why?!
B-Because...
there are huge bugs standing in our way!
What? Bugs?!
What are they?!
Fire!
I won't let them mess
with Usopp-un's new adventure-un!
When men part ways,
we don't shed tears-un.
Good luck, Usopp-un!
As long as they're not coming, that's good.
If they're having trouble, we're lucky.
Let's just leave now!
Nami, lead the way!
Leave it to me!
Alright!
This is Platoon 4.
I'm sorry.
It suddenly started raining,
and the wet gunpowder won't ignite!
Rain? Where is it raining?
Sabaody Archipelago should be
clear and sunny today!
No thunder.
We don't want civilians to get hurt.
The bubbles are so bothersome...
I can't believe we caught
such a perfect wind.
It brought us right to Sabaody Archipelago.
That's because Nami-chan is a good girl.
Best of luck!
We'll miss you up here on Weatheria!
Oh, it's inflating!
What? This jelly inflates?
Oh, we got a bubble roof!
Listen, everyone.
A coated ship can mitigate
any kind of pressure.
Once Franky removes the buoyancy bag
supporting the ship's keel,
the Sunny's coating will make her start to sink.
That's how it works.
– I see.
Too complicated, huh?
Anyway, lower the sail now!
Sail?
Rather than the wind,
sea currents drive a coated sailing ship.
So it doesn't just sink to where it's going.
Alright! Let's hurry
before the Navy shows up again!
This is Central Platoon 5 at Grove 42!
This is an emergency situation!
The troops that came before us,
Platoon 2, have all... er... become negative!
What are you talking about? "Negative"?!
I wanna become like moss...
I'm no good.
I wanna become a water flea...
According to them, Straw Hat Luffy
got on a giant bird and flew away!
Bird? What are you guys doing now?!
We're fighting against unknown enemies!
Navy reinforcements!
We were about to leave...
Everybody!
Straw Hat's ship is in range now!
Wait a minute!
A giant bird is coming toward us!
It's him!
They're behind us now!
I got it!
How's that, Nami-san?
Please be watching me...
See how much stronger I've become.
Sanji!
Respond, Platoon 5! What's going on?!
W-We're...
We're facing...
an unexpected obstacle...
Don't do it!
How dare you reject us like that!
Maybe they're all shy.
You don't have to be ashamed!
Let's go out for tea sometime!
I-I-I'm going...
I'm going crazy, aren't I?!
Oh! You've got such a cute face!
No, don't do it!
What's wrong? Answer, Platoon 5!
Sanji-kyun, now's your chance!
Hey, hey, what's wrong, Sanji?!
I-I-I don't know... Suddenly, it felt like
someone was squeezing my heart...
I removed the buoyancy bag!
Okay! What about the sail?
We're ready when you are!
Is it time to go, Nami?
Yes, at your command, Captain.
Alright...
You guys!
There's so much I want to tell you,
but first of all,
thank you for going along
with my selfish decision for two years!
It's not as if that's the first time.
He's right! You've always been that way!
Rear Admiral,
the pirate ship is submerging!
What?! Curses!
Damn you!
Do you have any idea...
how evil those pirates are? Hey!
Rear Admiral!
Take care, Luffy...
Unfurl the sails!
– Yes!
– Yeah!
Set sail!
Let's go to Fishman Island!