Jitto dekinai tomarenai
Gotta keep movin’, just can't stop
Yoake ga osokute jirettai
Rarin’ for the dawn to arrive
Ichi, ni, SUNSHINE, yon... WE GO!
One, two, sunshine, four, we go!
Hata wo ageyou BREAK OF ROMANCE DAWN
Hoist the flag for the break of romance dawn
Namikaze tateyou SLEEP kara no JUMP-START
Jump-start your day, ready to make waves
Arienai sekai wo yuku nara
Reachin’ for fantastic realms
Kimi no TOUGHNESS sore ga hitsuyou
Need to put your toughness on display
Medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Is bein’ brazen such a crime?
Shimeitehai tsumari WINNER
If you’re wanted, you’re a winner
Ah, jiyuu dake ga ore tachi no RULE
Ah, freedom is our only rule
Shinpai nante dokofuku kaze
Worries don’t bother us at all
Zettai ONE PIECE ichiban nori
No matter what, we’ll be the first to One Piece
Yume miru kokoro wa chou dekai
My dreamy heart has room for more
Samenai koto ga daiji
So whatever you do, don't wake up
Jitto dekinai tomarenai
Gotta keep movin’, just can't stop
Yoake ga osokute jirettai
Rarin’ for the dawn to arrive
Ichi, ni, SUNSHINE...
One, two, sunshine...
Ichi,
ni,
SUN
O
n
SHINE,
yon…
Ichi,
ni,
SUN
SHINE,
yon…