Samishii nara koe o kikasete
When you're lost and alone,
call out and lead me to your side
Samayoinagara sora o mitsumeteru
As you wander far from home,
you search the sky and never hide
Tsuki no you ni
You are so much like the moon
Matataku koto mo wasure
Calmer than a star, your twinkling's lost
Shizuka ni kie fukaku utsurikomi kaketeku
A deep reflection shines, you slowly leave,
fading, and what's the cost?
Kono mama kawarazu
Stay as you are, don't lose your way
Sono kotonoha ni nosete
Let my words guide you,
and look ahead until the day!
Yume o mite ikusen no yoru ni
Don't give up on your dreams,
through endless nights they come to you
Tada nagareru tabibito-tachi yo
If you stop, you'll never see them shining through!
Tatoe modorenakute...
Will you return? Maybe not...
Will you learn? I hope you do
Sore demo mata ayumu deshou
Please put your past to rest,
and live your life anew.