Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Meggo
Graphics
Datenshi
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
arch1t3cht
Gab
Subtitle Editing
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
Translation
arch1t3cht
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Storm
What's the big idea?!
If we invite the pirates aboard,
they'll take over the entire restaurant!
That's only if they have
the will to fight.
Isn't that right,
you Grand Line washout?
N-No way.
Don Krieg failed on the Grand Line?
Even the most powerful man
in the East Blue
couldn't make it with
a fleet of fifty pirate ships?!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Grand Line?
You're...
Red Leg Zeff.
You're alive.
You were a cook and a captain,
a pirate unlike any other.
I'm alive. So what?
It's none of your concern.
As you can see,
I spend my days as a chef now.
It sounds better
when you say it like that.
As I see it,
you're not just passing
time as a cook.
I doubt you could survive
as anything but a cook.
Red Leg Zeff was a master of kicks
who never used his hands in battle.
His mighty legs were said to shatter
bedrock and even leave footprints on steel.
And "Red Leg" referred to your boots,
washed in the blood of those
you kicked into submission.
But it looks like you've lost
one of your esteemed legs.
Seems the rumors were true.
A stroke of bad luck
doomed you to an accident at sea.
I suppose losing a leg would mean
you lost the ability to fight.
I don't give a damn about fighting.
I may have lost a leg, but I can cook
so long as I have these two hands.
You need to get
to the damn point already.
Red Leg Zeff,
you once sailed the Grand Line
and returned unscathed.
You must have the ship's log
from that year-long voyage.
Hand it over!
Wow, Boss Man!
You sailed the Grand Line too?!
A lifetime ago.
The ship's log?
Sure, I've got what you're looking for.
But there's no way in hell
I'm giving it to you.
That ship's log is the pride
of all those who sailed with me.
The likes of you
couldn't even handle it.
Then I'll just have to take it!
I admit the Grand Line
got the better of me.
I may have faced defeat there,
but the indomitable Don Krieg...
is plenty capable of crossing
even the most treacherous seas.
I had the men.
I had the ambition.
The only thing I lacked
was information.
I just didn't know what to expect.
I will have that ship's log.
With it, I will reassemble
my pirate fleet, seize the One Piece,
and rise to the top
of this Great Pirate Era!
Wait just a minute.
I'm going to be the Pirate King!
Cabin Boy?!
Hey, back down, Cabin Boy!
You're no match for him!
I can't back down. Not about this.
Did you say something, kid?
We can pretend
I didn't hear you say that.
No need to pretend.
I'm only saying what'll happen.
This is no game, boy.
You're right.
I will conquer the Grand Line.
You're taking it too lightly, punk!
Putting aside what we didn't know,
our fleet of 5,000 sailors
only lasted seven days
on that devilish sea!
A child like you
doesn't stand a chance!
S-Seven days?
The Krieg Pirates only
lasted seven days?!
What the hell happened to them?!
I'm sorry, but I hate it
when people joke around like this.
If you persist with your claim,
I'll just crush you right here and now.
If you can.
Perfect.
As you wish, I'll be
sending you to the afterlife.
You gonna fight, Luffy?
Need some help?
I-I'd also let you
fight him yourself, though.
Zoro? Usopp?
I didn't see you there!
I'm fine, but you can
watch from there.
O-Okay.
Are those your men?
Don't you think
your crew is a bit small?!
What are you talking about?!
We have two more!
Hey, don't go counting me in!
I'll deal with you later.
I'm going to feed my men first.
Anyone who wants to live
needs to clear out before I get back.
I'm only after your log and this ship.
If you still want
to throw your life away,
I can spare the time
to bury you at sea!
Make your choice.
I'm so sorry, Sanji.
I had no idea he'd go this far.
You don't need to apologize, grunt.
Every cook here did
what they thought was right.
That's all there is to it.
Chef Zeff!
You're not seriously taking
Sanji's side in this, are you?
That's right!
It's his fault this happened!
He's trying to destroy
your precious restaurant!
Shut up, peabrains!
Have you ever been so hungry
that you thought you'd die?!
Do you know the terror of running out
of food and water on this vast ocean?!
Can you comprehend such suffering?!
Huh?
Ch-Chef Zeff, what do you mean?
What sets Sanji apart from the rest of you
is that he knows exactly what I mean.
What does he mean by that?
Does Sanji know something we don't?
If all you're going to do
is bitch and moan,
crawl out the back door and get lost!
I'll stay and fight!
I'm too pissed off to let
myself get whupped like that!
Me too!
This is where I work!
I got nowhere else to go.
What are you doing?!
You saw what the don's capable of!
Hey, Gin.
Let me tell you something.
My duty as a cook is to feed
those who are hungry.
That said...
when those looters
turn on me with full bellies...
I'll beat the hell out of them,
even if they're in your crew.
That goes for you too.
Just try to take this restaurant,
and I'll kill you
without a second thought.
Understood?
Sanji, I can't believe you'd kill him
after keeping him alive.
Shut up, you crappy cook!
Look at that!
He's pretty cool, huh?!
That's nice, but enough about him!
We have to get out of here!
Settle down!
Did you see Krieg? He's in bad shape.
Gin, you said you don't know anything
about the Grand Line, didn't you?
You've been there, right?!
The Grand Line is indeed
a mystery to me.
What we saw on our
seventh day on the Grand Line
might have been a dream,
or it might have been real.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
It was unbelievable!
How could a lone man...
destroy a fleet of fifty ships?!
– What?!
It happened out of nowhere.
Before we even realized he was there,
the ships began to sink,
one after another.
If we hadn't been lucky enough
to encounter that storm,
our flagship would have
met the same fate.
I don't know how many
of our ships survived.
It's just too horrible
to believe it was real.
I want to forget what happened!
I want to forget that man—
how he could seemingly kill
with just a glance—
with that hawk-like glare!
What?!
Huh?
Could it be...?!
There's no mistaking it.
That must be the man
known as Hawk Eye.
Just telling us that his eyes were like
those of a hawk wouldn't be proof in itself.
But knowing he was capable of something
so devastating is plenty convincing for me.
The hawk-eyed man!
Huh?
Do you know him, Zoro?
Yeah.
It's who I've been looking for.
I'm guessing he had a serious
grudge against your crew.
I'd never seen him before!
Maybe you woke him
from a nap or something.
Don't be ridiculous!
Who the hell would
smash a fleet over that?!
Don't get so worked up.
I'm just saying...
that sort of thing is possible
in the Grand Line.
What kind of place is that?!
It means anything could happen.
Hey Luffy, we shouldn't
go somewhere like that!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy?
Whoa, that's so freaking cool!
I knew it had to be crazy there!
At least acknowledge
how dangerous it is!
Well, that settles it.
My only goal at this point
is the Grand Line.
I'll find him there...
I'll find that man on the Grand Line!
Are you nuts?
You're the type
to charge in and die first.
You're right, but saying I'm "nuts" is going too far.
I threw my life away when I decided
to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Only one person can call me nuts,
and that person is me!
Yeah, the same goes for me!
Yeah, me too! I'm a man of the sea!
You're lying.
How ridiculous...
Alrighty then!
Do you numbskulls have any idea
what's going on here?!
Outside this restaurant is a massive galleon
from Pirate Commodore Don Krieg's fleet!
You can build your castles in the sky
when the battle is over!
– We're saved!
I'm so glad we're gonna live!
It's like I'm dreaming!
We're free from that nightmare!
We made it back alive
from the Pirate Graveyard!
That's right.
We can once again turn
our sights on the Grand Line.
Huh?
What's with those looks?
W-We're going back there?!
Anybody else have any objections?
First,
we'll abandon this irreparable wreck
and take over the restaurant.
It's staffed by a gang
of thuggish cooks.
They've got nothing on us.
Attack!
They're coming!
I can hear them yelling!
Hold them off!
This ship is our restaurant!
Make way, you scum!
What was that?!
What happened?!
Don Krieg!
Our flagship was...
...sliced in half!
Sliced in half?!
Did I hear that right?!
Our massive galleon?!
How could...
something so preposterous happen?!
Weigh anchor!
It'll bring the whole ship down!
Yes, sir!
Not good!
Nami, Yosaku, and Johnny
are on the ship out front!
Dammit! It's probably too late!
Big Bro!
Yosaku!
Johnny!
Are you guys okay?
Where's the ship?! It's gone!
What happened to Nami?!
Well...
I'm sorry, Big Bro!
She's already gone!
See ya! Tell Luffy and his crew...
Big Sis Nami...
“See you again if our paths cross!"
She took all the treasure and ran!
– Wha...?!
– What the hell?!
That man...
What'd you say?!
Nami took the Going Merry and ran?!
What the hell is she doing?!