Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
Lance
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Translation
Funimation
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
To the Sea
H-He beat Captain Kuro!
Not even the Marines were a match
for Kuro, Man of a Hundred Plans!
But he really beat him!
Just who are you?!
Monkey D. Luffy.
I'd never lose to a pirate who ditches
his name and runs from the sea.
The only time a pirate should
abandon his name is when he dies!
Luffy?! Yeah, I never
heard that name before!
Remember my name
for the rest of your lives!
I'm the man who's gonna
be King of the Pirates!
This guy's...
Take him and leave!
Never come here again!
Run!
Well done...
Raise the anchor! Hurry!
I'd expect even you to collapse
after all you just went through...
Say...
what were you mad about earlier?
I hate them.
They're wrong.
That's not how friends should act.
What're you talking about?
That's natural.
Pirates aren't the lovely things
you make them out to be.
I'd say Captain Kuro's
more standard than you.
I want some meat.
You're unbelievable!
Can you keep everything that's
just happened here a secret?
What?! A secret?! How come?!
Yeah! After we just fought
for the village's sake!
Everyone will change
their opinion of you, too!
You could be the village hero!
– Yeah!
Usopp... You need to clear up everyone's misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? I was only
called an exaggerator, like always.
There's no need to scare everyone
with something that's already over.
Aside from things like this...
no pirates will show up to attack
a remote village like this one.
I'm just going to pretend
that nothing ever happened.
It was all a lie.
I won't force you to, but...
No, I can do it! If it's
for the best of the village!
Me too!
Me too! I'll never say a word, ever!
Kaya...
Will it be hard for you?
No.
Where is Usopp this morning?
It throws everything off for
some reason... I can't get motivated.
Mommy...
Is the liar guy not coming today?
That damn exaggeration-spewing kid...
Where is he today?!
Do you think maybe
I was too harsh yesterday?
He'll be back to his
old tricks come tomorrow!
I'm sure of it...
Thanks!
I wouldn't have been able to protect
the village without you guys!
What're you talking about?
If you hadn't done anything,
I would've done nothing!
Me too!
Who cares about that?
I got me some treasure!
Thanks to this incident,
I've finally decided upon something.
Captain Usopp! What did you
want to talk to us about?!
You guys fought well against
those Black Cat Pirates!
As captain, I feel very proud!
You were scared to death,
but you managed to keep Kaya safe!
We overcame our biggest
and greatest battle since we formed
the Usopp Pirates five years ago,
when you guys were just four!
– Yes!
So, I know this is sudden, but I've
decided to set out to sea by myself!
I'm gonna be a real pirate!
I had always been unsure if I wanted
to stay here forever or not...
But, once I saw them,
I finally made up my mind!
I feel that as a man, I must
set out onto the vast ocean!
So I'm leaving this village!
There's but one reason:
The pirate flag is calling me!
Captain! You're lying, right?!
You're lying again, right?!
It's way too hasty to do that!
Don't you love this village, Captain?!
What'll happen to the Usopp Pirates?!
You've been great to me, guys...
I plan to leave without
telling the villagers.
Give them my regards.
No...
I don't want to!
Don't go, Captain!
Do you remember this place?
This is where we first met.
All done!
Liar guy!
Who're you guys?!
Don't treat me all buddy-like!
But you're famous!
Yeah, you're a famous person...
I see!
So, people have finally started to
respectfully call me Captain Usopp!
Everyone calls you Liar Usopp!
Alright! From this day forth,
you're members of the Usopp Pirates!
– What?
Don't give me that!
A lot's happened, huh?
A cerberus! Scare it away!
A dragon! Capture it!
Flour Star!
You're amazing, Captain!
But of course! I am
a brave warrior of the sea!
We don't wanna hear
about the old days!
Yeah! We don't wanna hear about that!
This isn't like you, Captain!
Why are you saying this stuff now?!
It's almost like you're...
You're so stupid, Captain! Stupid!
What are your ambitions in life?!
To run a pub!
To be a master carpenter!
To be a novel writer!
Then swear here that you'll
continue on each of your paths
and never let the fires
of your ambitions go out!
As of today...
the Usopp Pirates...
are disbanded!
Well, we've eaten.
We should get going now.
Yeah...
Here you are!
Hey, Miss!
Are you alright, being out of bed?
Yes...
My sickness this past year
was caused by the mental dismay
from having lost my parents...
And Usopp really
cheered me up, too...
I can't stay coddled forever!
You've done so much
for me. Thank you.
I've prepared a present for you
from the bottom of my heart!
Please accept it!
All packed...
Guess it's farewell to this house, too!
What?!
What the...? I can't get out!
Darn it!
A caravel!
Can we really have this?!
Yes, please use it!
It's a slightly older model,
but I personally designed it!
A carvel-make caravel, with lateen sails
and a central stern rudder...
the Going Merry!
Let me explain the running rigging!
First, about the Kruger
net yard adjustment–
No, no! You can explain
the ship stuff to me!
What a good ship!
Especially this front—it's so cool!
We've loaded it with everything
you might need on a voyage.
Thanks! It leaves nothing to beat tired!
That's, "Leaves nothing
to be desired," you idiot.
Stop this thing!
Usopp!
What's he doing?
Let's just stop him for now.
He's on a collision course with the ship.
Th-Thanks...
Sure thing.
So you are taking
to the ocean, Usopp?
Yeah. I've decided to get going
before I start to change my mind.
Don't stop me now.
I won't. I could just tell somehow.
That's kind of sad, too!
The next time I come to this village,
I'll tell you adventure stories that
seem even more lie-like than lies!
Okay! I look forward to it!
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
How come?
Huh? How come?
Man, you're antisocial...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
What're you talking about?
Get on board already.
What?
You're one of us now, aren't you?
I-I...
I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
There goes the captain...
Yeah. But he's with those guys,
so I feel less worried now.
Yeah. I've never seen anyone
as strong as them before.
Guess it can't be helped.
He always talked about how
he wanted to be a pirate.
The villagers will probably be sad
when we tell them, though...
It's all so sudden, plus he
livened things up all by himself...
I just had an idea!
– What is it?
Merry...
Yes?
Lying hurts...
Are you referring to Klahadore?
No...
You mean how you really wanted to stop Usopp from going?
Miss, the villagers once told me
a story from his childhood.
Shortly after Usopp's
father left the village,
his mother passed away.
Pirates are here!
Dad's pirates are here!
H-Hold on, Usopp!
You mustn't shout!
Dad came back for us!
D-Don't be silly... Usopp...
But he said he'd take us with him
when you get better, Mom!
Your father won't be coming back...
But... I'm proud I married him...
Th-There's a legendary medicine!
It can cure any sickness!
You're so silly...
You dream too much...
I don't care if I'm silly! I do dream!
I am the son of a pirate!
Grow up to be a brave man
like your father...
Pirates are here!
Perhaps out of his loneliness,
he continued to shout it out
after his mother's death...
in the hopes that one day his father's
pirate ship would be at the shore...
in the hopes that one day
he would come back for him.
The villagers say that lie of his
also contains his wish.
Pirates!
As someone who lost his
own parents in this village,
he probably couldn't ignore you,
seeing as the same happened to you.
You will need to grow
stronger now, too!
To live up to everything
he's done until today!
Yes!
To our new ship and crewmate!
– Cheers!
They said they were
fighting to live, not die.
Usopp's lies always spoke
about the joy of living.
They cheered me up
and told me to live!
Indeed.
Here we go!
Are we really gonna do this?!
You bet! We're following
in our captain's footsteps!
– Pirates are here!
You know what, Merry?
I'm going to be a doctor!
That's a wonderful goal to have!