dore dake hashitte kita no ka?
Running so long, lost track of just how long it’s been
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Collected scars while striving, not even trying, beneath my skin
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
But in the back of my head the dream is not dead, I remember a map
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
to a treasure still gleaming, it’s within our grasp
hontou no yakusoku wa
Can you feel my heart? Feelings I impart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
The promises are there; they're deep down but still primed to share
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
Peerless dreams kept close, the dreams that always matter most
tada hitotsu dakishimete
Before we set sail why not raise a toast?
taiyou no you ni warau anata e
So I pen this note to you! Dear sunrise, I’ll see you soon
ano hito onaji uta wo utau yo
See the smile I saw the day that I sang this song to you
otona ni natte mo wasuretakunai
And regardless of our age, these mem’ries will still remain
kono negai ga todoku made
Won’t forget until this wish makes it to you