Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
"Deliver Princess Vivi! The Luffy Pirates Set Sail"
Damn, they're annoying!
What's their problem?!
This can't be! What strength!
Unbelievable!
Alright, then. Let's settle this!
Yeah!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Knock that off!
What the heck are you guys doing?!
It's just a good thing you managed to keep the girl safe!
You almost let a billion belly get away from us!
Understand?!
What are you talking about?
Why did you save me?
Right! We need to talk about that!
It's like this... Won't you make a contract with me?
Contract?
Quit fighting!
Oh! You shoulda just said so, Zoro!
I just figured you cut them all down
'cause they didn't make any food you liked!
Don't compare me to you!
It's a pretty good offer, if you ask me.
C'mon! Don't sweat it!
I can't!
I do appreciate your saving me. Thank you.
Why can't you?! You're a princess!
One billion shouldn't be much...
Do you know of the kingdom known as Arabasta?
No.
It's a peaceful kingdom known as a great civilization and nation.
Well, it used to be.
Used to be? What about now?
It's in the middle of a civil war.
For years now, signs of a revolution have begun to appear.
The people revolted, and the kingdom fell into total chaos...
Then, one day, I heard the name of an organization...
Baroque Works!
I learned that the populace was being manipulated by this group.
But there was a tight lid on any other information than that,
and there was nothing I could do.
That's when I asked Igaram,
who always meddled in my business since childhood, for help.
The old tube hair guy?
Tube? Oh, yes.
I asked him if there was a way I could infiltrate Baroque Works.
Because that would let us see who was pulling the strings,
and what their goal was.
You're a pretty high-spirited princess.
So? Did you figure out this goal of theirs?
"The founding of an ideal nation."
That's what Igaram said, anyway.
Oh, does that mean...
Yes.
The boss says it's to create an ideal nation,
but it's an enormous lie!
The true goal is to take over Arabasta Kingdom!
I have to hurry back, tell everyone the truth, and stop the fighting!
I see.
So that's the deal. Now everything finally connects.
There'd be no money during a civil war, huh...
Hey.
Who is pulling the strings?
T-the boss' identity?!
You shouldn't ask that!
You know who it is, right?
Don't ask me! Anything but that!
Your lives will be put in danger, too!
I think I'll pass on that!
After all, these are guys trying to take over an entire country!
They're obviously insanely dangerous people!
Yes! They are!
As strong as you people may be, you'd never stand a chance
against one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
Crocodile!
Who, now?
You just said it.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What was that bird and sea otter?!
Are they going to tell someone?!
Hey! A Warlord!
Not too shabby!
I- I'm very sorry! It just slipped out!
Like that really fixes things now!
Why did you have to drag us down with you?!
Being hunted by a Warlord the moment we enter the Grand Line
is too much to handle!
I wonder what he's like!
We're lucky we can see him so soon!
Shut up, you two!
It's been a short acquaintance, but I thank you for everything!
Where are you going?
They don't know what we look like yet! I'm running away!
Wow! That's so good!
I guess this means there's nowhere to run now, huh?!
I'm sorry!
She's funny!
Where was she planning to run to, anyway?
Guess that means all three of us are on Baroque Work's hit list now.
That's exciting for some reason!
I- I do have 500,000 belly in savings...
Fear not!
It's–
It's all right! I have a plan!
Igaram! What are those clothes?!
You look hilarious in those, old guy!
It's idiot after idiot...
Vivi. Please listen to me carefully.
Once Baroque Works' intelligence network learns of something,
A thousand or so people will come after you.
pursuers may come after you almost immediately.
Therefore, I will pretend to be you, like so,
and sail straight to Arabasta with three dummies on board.
These are us?
A decoy, huh...
While the pursuers are busy with me,
all of you will head to Arabasta via the normal route.
We still haven't come to an agreement, you know!
Take the princess there? What now?
You haven't heard?
Pops here wants us to take her home.
Oh, that's what this is about? Sure!
Crocodile is gonna come after us, you know!
Is Crocodile really that strong?
He's one of the Seven Warlords of the Seas.
He's a legally-recognized pirate, and thus has no bounty on his head.
However, the bounty he did have long ago was 80 million belly.
80 million?! That's four times Arlong's bounty! Say no!
I am ever grateful!
Now, then. I, Vivi, will leave from here.
That's a perfect imitation, old guy!
Imitation of who?!
Now then, Princess. Please give me the Eternal Pose.
Eternal Pose?
You've never heard of it?
I suppose you could say it's a permanent version of a log pose.
Whereas a log pose always leads ships to the next island,
an Eternal Pose will never forget the magnetic energy of the island
that is stored in it.
Meaning it will forever point to that island alone.
And this one is set to Arabasta.
You're going to use this to go to Arabasta?
Vivi. Please take the indirect island-hopping route to Arabasta.
I've not taken the path myself,
but it should only be two or three islands if you follow the Log.
Please take good care of the princess.
Igaram...
Yeah!
I expect it will be a harsh journey.
Be careful on your way.
You, too!
Let us meet safely at our motherland.
You must save the kingdom by your own hand!
There he goes.
He was a funny old guy, to the very end!
He really is reliable.
No!
That's impossible! They're already after us?!
He was a great person!
Nami! What's the Log say?!
We're okay! It's stored up!
Bring her with us! We're setting sail!
Vivi! Vivi!
Hurry! If they find us, it'll all be for nothing!
Don't worry! We will get you there!
–I know they don't look like it...
I know they don't look like it...
Luffy! Go wake those two up!
but they saved the East Blue!
I'm going to the ship!
Just the four of them!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Baroque Works?! Crocodile?! Ha!
The Seven Warlords are nothing at all!
Let's go!
What the–?! Oww! What the–?!
What the hell're you doing, Luffy?! Hey!
My nose is coming off!
Let go, dammit! What's goin' on?!
Hurry, Vivi!
R-right!
Karoo is missing!
A decoy. How foolish...
Hey! I brought 'em!
Get on! We're ready to leave anytime!
Huh? These guys are still sleeping!
There's no time to look for him!
But I can't just leave him here!
Still!
Hey! What's the problem?!
She says her duck is missing!
He won't come when we whistle for him!
This him?
He was here even before me.
You're there?!
There's a tributary just up the river!
We can use it to get out to sea a little faster!
Alright! Let's go!
Hey.
Mr. Bushido...
Just how many people are gonna be chasing us down?
I don't know.
There are about 2000 people in Baroque Works,
and I've heard there are several town-like bases like this one nearby.
They really might send 1000 people?!
H-huh?!
Hey! The ship's leaving!
Finally awake, I see.
Wait! Let's stay just one more night!
Yeah!
This town is great! And the girls are cute!
There's no telling when we'll have this much fun again!
–Let's take it easy! We are pirates! –Plus, it's not even morning yet!
They have some nerve. They don't even know anything...
Hey! Explain to them!
Yep! I just did!
That was fast...
Yeah, I left out the complicated parts.
We should be able to leave the island soon...
Cool! There's fog now!
It's almost morning...
It's good we managed to escape the people chasing us!
That's for sure!
We need to be careful not to crash the ship into the rocks.
This is a nice ship.
Who're you?!
I ran into Mr. 8 a short while ago,
Miss Wednesday.
You killed Igaram!
Who cares about that!
What're you doing on this ship?! Who are you?!
What are you doing here...
Miss All Sunday?!
Miss All Sunday?! What number is she partner to?!
She's the partner of Mr. 0... the boss!
The bo– Crocodile?!
Is she bad?
She was the only one who knew the boss' identity.
We found out who he is by following her!
More accurately... I allowed you to follow me.
Oh! Then she's good!
I know that!
You're also the one who told him we discovered his identity, right?!
Correct.
So she really is bad!
Pipe down, you!
What exactly is it you're trying to do?!
Good question.
You were all so intent and serious that I found myself helping out.
The idea of a princess trying her hardest to save her kingdom
while making herself an enemy of Baroque Works...
It was just so ridiculous, you see...
Don't you mock me!
Hey! Sanji! You do realize what you're doing?!
No, not really.
I just sense that my beloved Miss Wednesday is in danger...
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't point such dangerous objects at me.
You don't mean...!
A Devil–
A Devil Fruit?!
Which one?! What's her power?!
Oww...
Upon closer look, you're actually a beautiful lady!
Now, now. Don't be so hasty. I haven't been given any orders.
I have no reason to fight.
So you're the straw hat captain I've heard so much about...
Monkey D. Luffy.
Hey, you! Gimme my hat back! Are you tryin' to start a fight?!
I deem you an enemy! Leave this instant!
How unlucky you are...
You people who picked up a princess Baroque Works is out to kill...
And a princess being protected by a mere handful of pirates...
But what's even unluckier is the course your log pose indicates.
The name of the next island is...
Little Garden.
We don't even need to do anything,
you'll be wiped out long before you can even reach Arabasta.
You wish! You big dummy!
Will not! Gimme my hat back!
What are you, a kid?
Do you not think letting yourself get wiped out is a bit foolish?
An Eternal Pose?
You can skip past Little Garden with that.
It points to an island just before Arabasta:
Nothing At All Island.
None of our employees know that course, so no one will chase you.
What? She's a good person?
Why are you giving this to us?!
It's a trap, isn't it?
Is it, now?
What do I do? I don't want to accept this from someone like her.
But now that they've let me onboard,
taking the safest route might be best...
Who cares about that!
Are you an idiot?!
She just went out of her way to show us a nicer course!
What if she's actually a good person?!
You're not the one who decides this ship's course!
I see. That's too bad.
Urgh!
She blew up the old tube hair guy, so I hate her!
I don't hate high-spirited people.
If you survive...
let's meet again.
No!
Let's go, Bunchi!
Don't tell me it's a Sea King!
W-what is that?!
No...
A turtle!
What a huge turtle!
I can't tell what that woman is thinking one bit!
Then there's no point in thinking about it.
We already got someone like that on this ship, anyway.
Hey! Explain what's going on! None of this makes sense!
Oh, Miss Wednesday! Don't tell me you've joined the crew?!
Hey! Explain already--!
Whoa! There's an ostrich onboard!
C'mon, what's going on?!
Is it for food?
Explain what's going on!
I see.
It's too bad I missed out on it,
but there's still opportunity for me to shine, too.
Don't worry!
Now that this sleeping prince has awoken, your safety is guaranteed!
Whoa! Good thing I slept through it!
--Nami. Jealous any? --Nope!
Is it really all right for me to be on this ship?
I'll only trouble you all...
What're you talking about?! We know who you are now!
If you didn't want to trouble us, you should've done so from the start!
I'm sorry.
Right, Luffy?
Yeah! I'm hungry!
Maybe it doesn't matter at all?
For now, looks like our next destination is set.
Little Garden, huh...
H-hey, now! Will we be alright there?!
Who knows! Let's go, men!
Yeah!
It'll be quite the sight...
Little Garden...