Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Soundtracking
Halee
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Quality Control
JT-421
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
JT-421
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
His final words lured all sorts
of adventurers to the sea.
Timing
PhosCity
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
Feeso
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
My treasure?
It's yours, if you can find it.
Translation
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Everything is right where I left it!
Now, pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
The Dawn of an Adventure
Hey, Luffy!
What are you trying to do?!
Monkey D. Luffy
Village Boy
I've had it! I'm not a little kid anymore!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Get on with it already...
whatever it is you're up to!
Ouch!
You idiot!
What'd you do that for?!
Guys! A toast!
To Luffy's guts and to another
successful voyage!
Ah, it didn't hurt one bit!
Liar. You can't pull
dumb stunts like that.
I'm not lying!
I'm not scared of getting hurt!
So, take me with you when you set sail!
I wanna be a pirate too!
Like you'd ever make it as a pirate!
"Red-Haired" Shanks
Pirate Captain
There's no use for a pirate that sinks like an anchor!
I'll be just fine if I don't fall overboard!
And besides, I'm a good fighter!
I've been training,
so now my punches are like pistols!
Pistols? Oh, really?
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
What's that supposed to mean?!
Luffy!
You're getting so worked up!
Loosen up and have some fun!
Yeah! Being a pirate is about having fun!
The sea is boundless!
There are tons of islands to explore!
It's all about freedom!
Guys, stop filling his head with nonsense.
But it's all true! Right?!
C'mon, Boss, why not take him
on just one trip?
I'd second that.
Sure, but one of you stays behind.
Good chat, kid! Let's drink!
Weren't you on my side?!
Really, you're just too young, kid.
Maybe I'll give you a chance in about ten years!
Shanks, you big jerk! I'm not a little kid!
Hey, now. Simmer down.
Here, have some juice.
Oh! Thanks!
See?! You are just a kid!
No fair, Shanks!
I'm so sick of this!
Luffy, try to understand
where the boss is coming from.
The first mate!
The reality is,
he's the head of a pirate crew.
He knows better than anybody
how tough and dangerous pirating can be.
You get it? He's not
trying to dash your hopes.
No, I don't get it!
Shanks just likes making fun of me!
Look, an anchor!
See?!
I see you're having fun as usual.
Yeah, I just love teasing this kid.
Luffy, would you like something to eat too?
Yeah! Put it on my treasure tab!
The treasure tab again?
That's fraud, you know?
No, it's not!
I'll pay her back once I become
a pirate and find some treasure!
I'm counting on it.
Shanks.
What's up?
How much longer
are you gonna stay in this village?
Let's see...
After a couple more voyages,
we'll leave this village for good and head north.
A couple more voyages, huh?
So I gotta learn to swim before you leave!
Sure thing. Knock yourself out.
Excuse us.
So, these are "pirates."
Looks like a sorry bunch to me.
We're mountain bandits,
but we ain't here to bust up the place.
We'd like some booze.
My apologies. I just ran out of alcohol.
Then what are these pirates drinking? Water?
I'm afraid I served the last of it to them.
I feel bad. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this. It hasn't been opened yet.
Hey, wise guy. What do you take me for?
One bottle ain't even enough for a nightcap!
The floor's all wet!
Take a look.
My head's worth eight million belly.
I've killed fifty-six people,
all of ‘em comedians like you.
You'd better watch yourself.
But we're mountain folk and you're seafarers;
I doubt we'll see each other again.
Sorry about the mess, Makino.
Do you have a rag?
No! Leave that to me!
Seems you like to clean.
Maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
Later, cowards!
Captain, are you all right?
Yeah. No worries.
Talk about lame, Boss!
He got you good!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight back?!
You can't call yourself a pirate, or even a man,
if you laugh after something like that!
I get where you're coming from,
but he only got some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Hey, wait, Luffy.
I've had it! I don't wanna be a coward like you!
His arm stretched!
H-He didn't!
What's going on?!
It's gone!
– What?!
The Gum-Gum Fruit we stole from our enemy!
Luffy! Please tell me
you didn't eat a fruit like this!
I-I did. It tasted pretty bad.
That was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
It's a rare treasure of the sea
known as a devil fruit!
You gain a rubber body after eating it,
but you lose the ability to swim for life!
What?! No way!
You dumbass!
Gimme a fish, old fish shop guy!
Hey, Luffy!
I heard they sailed off without you again!
I don't mind!
Becoming a rubber man is way cooler
than going on some dumb trip.
It's been a while since the captain
and his crew set out to sea.
I bet you miss them.
No way! They're still not off the hook!
I can't believe I thought Shanks
and his crew were awesome pirates.
Really? I think it's much cooler to shrug it off
and laugh after someone humiliates you like that.
Makino, you just don't get it.
There are times when a man's gotta fight.
Maybe I don't get it.
Hate to intrude.
Those damn pirates ain't here today, huh?
We were in the area,
so we decided to drop by.
Why are you just standing there?!
Booze! Now!
Mayor, we have a problem!
What's wrong, Makino?
Luffy's in trouble with the mountain bandits!
Let go! Dammit!
Weird body ya got here...
Apologize already!
What kind of creature is he?
You dumb jerk!
Dammit! You're gonna pay!
He might fetch a good price.
How stubborn.
Brat!
Did I say something to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Get your foot off of me!
Let the boy go!
I beg you!
I have no intention of fighting you,
but I'm willing to pay.
Spare the boy's life!
Leave it to a senior citizen
to know the ways of the world.
But no.
It's too late for that now.
After all, he's pissed me off.
No...
I've had it up to here with this rubber runt!
You're the bad guys here, you mountain apes!
Forget selling him. Let's just kill him!
Luffy!
Please! Let him go!
No one came to greet us at the port.
So, this is why.
They're the mountain bandits from before.
Captain!
Luffy, I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols.
Shut up!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
You'd best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and you're dead meat, coward!
What are you, deaf?
I'll blow your head off!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
you've put your life on the line.
Huh? The hell do you mean?
I'm saying those aren't for threatening people.
N-Now you've done it!
These bastards fight dirty!
"Dirty"?
Cut the crap.
You think you're dealing with saints?
You're staring down a group of pirates!
Shut up! This is none of
your damn business anyway!
Listen, bandits.
It doesn't matter if I'm doused
with alcohol or covered in food,
most of the time, I'll just laugh it off.
But know this!
Hurt a friend of mine for any reason,
and you'll answer to me.
Shanks...
Answer to you, huh?!
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this. Shouldn't be a problem.
Come on! Bring it!
That burns!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
You'll need a whole battleship
if you wanna challenge us.
So strong!
Unbelievable...
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
You're a wanted man, though.
A smokescreen!
– Let me go! Let me go!
– Come with me, brat!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down! Luffy's gone!
What do we do, guys?!
Quit freakin' the hell out, Boss!
It won't take us long to find him!
I can't believe this guy...
I made a clean getaway!
I've got no more use for you.
You bastard!
So long!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum,
but I couldn't even hit them once!
Dammit! Dammit!
You see the looks on those pirates' faces?!
Pirates ain't nothin' but cowards.
Cut that out! Quit making fun
of Shanks and his crew!
Calm down, Luffy!
Stop making fun of Shanks and his crew!
Stupid kid.
Wh-What the hell?!
Help!
It's gonna eat me!
Shanks...
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino told me everything.
You stood up for us.
C'mon, don't cry! You're a man, right?
But... Shanks...
Your arm!
It's only an arm. No big deal.
I'm just glad you're not hurt.
Luffy finally understood the reason
Shanks never took him on a voyage:
the sea was dangerous, and he was powerless.
But more importantly,
he discovered Shanks' greatness.
He aspired to become a man like him one day.
Shanks, you're not coming back?
Nah. We were able to stay awhile,
but it's time to part ways.
Right. I'm not gonna ask you
to take me this time.
I've decided to become a pirate on my own!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'd never make it as a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours.
We'll find the world's greatest treasure,
and then I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Oh? You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Come bring it back to me someday
once you've become a great pirate!
He's got quite a future.
Yeah, he's so much like the kid I used to be.
Set sail!
The boy's adventure would begin
a decade later from this very port.
Ten Years Later
Well, Mayor, he's finally off.
He's disgracing our village
by becoming a pirate!
What a nice day to set sail!
What the...?
If it isn't our local sea monster.
You don't know who you're messing with.
Here's a technique that's ten years in the making!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
We'
A
re go
re go
That oughta teach you, damn fish!
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
Alright! Let's go!
are
on
the
cruise!
I'm gonna be...
We
are!
King of the Pirates!
We
are!