Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
[dramatic orchestral music]
[NARRATOR]
Wealth... Fame... Power...
Graphics
Datenshi
[NARRATOR]
Wealth... Fame... Power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
Soundtracking
Halee
attained this and everything else
the world had to offer.
Quality Control
fedew
Feeso
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Villager
fedew
Feeso
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Villager
Timing
Gab
PhosCity
Villager
Gab
PhosCity
Villager
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Phos
Villager
KaitouYahiko
Phos
Villager
Closed Captioning
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Translation
Funimation
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR]
These words lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
[whimsical orchestral music]
The Dawn of an Adventure
[NARRATOR]
This is a small seaport village.
For the past year or so, a pirate ship
has been anchored at the port.
A soft wind from the east blows gently
over this peaceful, sleepy place.
[SHANKS]
Luffy! Come on!
What are you doing up there?
[LUFFY]
Hmph!
[growls]
Monkey D. Luffy
Village Boy
I'm not kiddin' around, do you hear me?!
I'm really mad!
Watch, I'll prove it to ya!
[SHANKS laughs]
Yeah, go ahead, kid!
Not sure what you're planning to do, though.
[RED HAIR PIRATES scream]
[LUFFY]
Ow!
[SHANKS]
You idiot, what'd you do that for?!
All right, drink up!
[RED HAIR PIRATES cheering]
[ragtime piano music]
[RED HAIR PIRATE]
Let's drink to Luffy's courage
and our great journey on the sea!
Cheers!
Ha. Didn't hurt at all!
[SHANKS]
That's a lie if I've ever heard one.
I'm not lying!
And I'm not scared of gettin' hurt again, either!
You gotta take me with you
on your next voyage!
I wanna be a pirate like you!
[laughs] Yeah, right, as if
you could ever be a pirate!
"Red-Haired" Shanks
Pirate Captain
I don't think you're gonna fare
too well at sea if you sink like an anchor!
I'll be okay as long as I don't fall overboard!
And besides, I'm a really good fighter, too!
I've got lots of training!
I mean, when I punch people,
it's like firin' a pistol!
A pistol? If you say so.
Are you makin' fun of me?!
[RED HAIR PIRATE]
Luffy!
Don't be in such a sour mood, kiddo!
You're still young, you should be having fun!
And being a pirate's more fun than anything!
We get to travel across the endless sea.
Discoverin' new places all the time!
We're as free as can be!
I'd appreciate it if you clowns
didn't teach him that kind of thing.
But you know it's true, right?
Come on, Boss, we can take him on
one little voyage. What's the harm?
[RED HAIR PIRATE]
Yeah, he'll be okay!
[SHANKS]
Fine, but one of you gets left behind.
[ROUX]
Yeah, forget that! Let's get back to drinkin'!
[LUFFY]
Weren't you guys on my side?!
I'm just sayin', you're much too young
to try and strike out to sea.
You can ask me about it in ten years,
and maybe I'll reconsider.
Stupid Shanks! I'm not that little!
Geez. Calm down. Drink some juice, kid.
Ha! Yay, thank you! Ha!
Real pirates don't drink juice, big guy!
[LUFFY]
No, that's not fair, you tricked me!
[LUFFY groans]
Whatever, I'm tired now!
[BECKMAN]
Luffy.
You have to try to understand
how the boss feels.
Mr. First Mate!
Think about it. This guy is the captain
of a tough-as-nails pirate crew.
So he knows more than anybody how
dangerous this kind of life can be.
My point is, he told you
not to come along with us
because he didn't want to break your spirit.
You don't get it!
He's just makin' fun of me
'cause he thinks I'm a kid!
Hey, Anchor!
[LUFFY]
You see?!
You're having fun as always.
Yeah. I get such a kick out of
giving this kid a hard time.
Luffy, would you like to order
some food, too?
Mm-hmm!
Put it on my treasure tab, 'kay?
The treasure tab again?
You know that does qualify as stealing.
Nuh-uh!
Once I become a pirate
and find a bunch of treasure,
I'm gonna pay back every last bit!
[MAKINO giggles]
I know you will.
[LUFFY giggles]
[LUFFY]
Shanks!
[SHANKS]
Yeah. What?
[LUFFY]
How much longer are you gonna be here for?
I'm not too sure. I believe
the plan we decided on
was to go on a couple more voyages
then head out towards the north
after we're done with that.
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
Only a couple more trips, huh?
[MAKINO]
Huh?
Okay, then I can practice
my swimming while you're here!
[SHANKS]
That's a good idea. Knock yourself out.
[tense orchestral music]
[HIGUMA]
Excuse us.
So these are what pass for pirates here?
Looks awfully sad to me.
[footsteps continue]
You see, we're mountain bandits.
But... we didn't come here
to tear your place apart.
We'll just take some booze.
[nervously] I'm so sorry, sir, but we're actually
fresh out of alcohol for the moment.
[HIGUMA]
Huh? Those pirates seem
to be drinking, though.
Is that water?
[MAKINO]
No, that was the last bit
of what I had stocked up.
Well, this is a problem, isn't it?
It looks like my friends and I drank the place
dry before you gentlemen came in. Sorry.
[HIGUMA]
Huh?
You can have this one if you like.
It hasn't even been opened yet.
Hm...
[MAKINO gasps]
[menacing music]
[dripping]
[HIGUMA]
How dare you.
Can you not see who you're talking to?
You know damn well that won't
even be enough for a nightcap.
Aww...
Now the floor's all wet and sticky.
Look at this, pal.
I've got a bounty of
eight million berries on my head.
I've killed fifty-six people, and all of 'em
were mouthy fools like you.
If I were you, I'd watch my back.
But since we're in the mountains and you're
on the sea, maybe we won't meet again.
Huh?
Sorry about the mess, Makino.
Have you got a rag?
[MAKINO]
Oh, no, don't worry, I can take care of it.
Since you like to clean so much,
I think you might find
this mess more fulfilling.
[BANDITS chuckle]
[HIGUMA chuckles]
[BANDITS chuckling]
Guess I'll see you weaklings another day.
[HIGUMA laughs]
[MAKINO footsteps]
Are you all right, Captain Shanks?
[SHANKS]
Never been better, Makino.
[chuckles]
[PIRATES laughing]
[ROUX]
That fella really got you good!
[YASOPP]
Talk about a loser!
[laughing]
[LUFFY]
Why are you laughing?!
[MAKINO, SHANKS]
Huh?
You should've stood up to him, Shanks!
That wasn't cool at all!
If you can laugh over something like that,
then you're not a man, or a real pirate!
Look, Luffy, I know how you feel, kid.
But all the guy did was
spill a little booze on me.
It's not worth getting so upset about.
[LUFFY growls]
[SHANKS]
Hey, wait a second.
Leave me alone. You're just a coward!
[SHANKS]
Hm?
[LUFFY]
[RED HAIR PIRATES scream]
[rousing music]
Why's he stretchy?
Oh no, don't tell me...!
What the heck?!
[shocked] It's gone!
[RED HAIR PIRATES]
No way!
Yeah, the Gum-Gum Fruit we looted!
It was right in here!
Luffy, tell the truth.
Did you just eat something like this?!
[LUFFY]
Uh, yeah. It tasted gross though.
[SHANKS]
What have you done?!
The Gum-Gum Fruit is one of
the legendary devil fruits!
It makes your body turn into rubber.
This means that you've lost the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Huh?! That can't be!
You idiot!
Hey, fish guy! Can I have a fishy?
Luffy, it's you!
I heard you missed out on another
big adventure with the pirates.
That's okay!
My body's made outta rubber now.
This is more fun than goin'
on a voyage anyway! See?
[LUFFY chuckles]
The crew's been out at sea for a long time,
isn't that right, Luffy?
I bet you miss them.
No way! I'm still upset with those guys.
I thought Shanks and his crew
were cool pirates,
but it turns out they're all totally wimpy!
I don't know.
I think being able to laugh
after somebody humiliates you
like those bandits did is cool, too.
You don't understand, Makino.
Sometimes a man's gotta stand up and fight!
You're right, maybe I don't get it, huh?
[HIGUMA]
We're back for more.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[forboding orchestral music]
Looks like those damn pirates
aren't here today.
We were in the neighborhood,
so we thought we'd stop in for a drink.
[BANDITS chuckling]
[gasps]
What's the holdup, honey?
Bring the booze!
[worried gasps]
[MAKINO]
Mayor, please help!
What's the matter, Makino?
It's Luffy! He's in big trouble!
[BANDITS chuckling]
[LUFFY]
Let go of me or else, you sick monster!
[HIGUMA]
Well, this is interesting!
[grunting]
You're gonna pay for that!
This kid is a freak of nature.
[HIGUMA laughs]
[BANDITS laughing]
Say you're sorry for last time, right now!
Wonder how much money we could
get if we sold him off?
[yelling]
[HIGUMA]
Again, huh?
Fine!
Hm?!
[LUFFY]
Ahh!
I don't think I said anything
to offend you personally.
You think wrong! Now apologize!
Get your foot off me!
Let the boy go, I beg you!
[HIGUMA]
Huh?
[MAYOR WOOP SLAP]
He's a child! I don't intend to fight you,
and I'll even pay you to stop this.
Just let him live! That's all I ask!
Ah, a senior citizen.
Leave it to you to be reasonable.
[gasps]
[HIGUMA]
But you're outta luck.
[gasps]
The brat's already made me angry,
so not even your pitiful prayers
can save him now.
[MAYOR WOOP SLAP]
Please, no!
That rubber face of yours was
real entertaining for a sec,
but now all I want to do is bash it in.
You guys don't fight fair!
You're scum! Lemme go!
[HIGUMA]
Forget selling him. Let's just kill him!
[MAKINO]
Luffy!
Have mercy on him, sir!
[BANDITS chuckling]
[SHANKS]
Nobody was at the port to greet us.
[MAKINO, MAYOR WOOP SLAP gasp]
I figured something must be wrong.
The mountain bandits again?
Captain, you're here!
Hey, Luffy.
Didn't you say before that your punches
were as deadly as getting shot with a pistol?
[grunts] Shut up, okay?
You're still in town? Shove off, already.
[MAKINO gasps]
[HIGUMA]
You'd best leave before you get hurt.
Take one step closer and my friend
here's gonna blow your head clean off.
[LUFFY grunts]
Didn't you hear what the man said?
Do you feel like dying today, buddy?
[BANDITS laughing]
Well, now that you've drawn your pistol,
do you plan to actually use it?
What? I'm holdin' it, ain't I?
What I'm trying to tell you is that
guns aren't for making threats.
They're made for actions.
[BANDITS gasp]
No way, I don't believe it!
Yeah, these bastards fight dirty!
A little.
Oh, were you expecting saints?
Who the hell do you think
you're dealing with here?
In case it wasn't obvious,
you fellas have picked a fight
with a crew of pirates.
Shut your trap!
This ain't about you,
so take your crew and go!
[SHANKS]
Listen up, bandits.
If I'm sprayed with alcohol or doused
with food, hell, even if I'm spit on,
most of the time I'll laugh it off and forget it.
But...
Regardless of what
your reasoning may be,
if you hurt a friend of mine,
you can believe you're gonna pay for it.
[gasps] Is he for real?
[laughs] Oh, we are, are we?
[exciting music]
Go on, fellas! Show these
wimps a thing or two!
[BANDITS yelling]
[BECKMAN]
I'll handle this. Should be easy.
[yelling]
[yelps]
[BANDITS yelling]
[BECKMAN grunts]
[sounds of clashing]
[BANDITS scream]
Don't get too cocky. Stay focused.
If you wanted to fight us, you should've
brought a warship or something bigger.
This is so cool.
Amazing.
[gasps] No, hold on!
The kid was the one who
attacked us first, all right?
Either way, you're still
a wanted man, aren't ya?
[gasps]
[ROUX]
A smokescreen!
[LUFFY] Stop it! Let me go already!
[HIGUMA] Come with me!
[SHANKS]
Luffy!
Oh, crap, I let the bandit take him!
What are we gonna do?!
Calm down, Boss! There's
no use freakin' out over it!
We'll find him in no time, I swear!
Oh boy. Can't believe this guy.
[HIGUMA laughs]
Guess I made a clean getaway!
Sorry, got no need for you anymore.
[LUFFY grunting]
Ha! See ya, runt!
[LUFFY yelps]
Dammit! I suck!
These guys are worthless bandits,
but I still couldn't get one hit in!
I hate this! It's not fair!
[HIGUMA laughing]
Guys, did you see the looks on their faces?
All pirates are nothing but
cowards and weaklings.
[LUFFY]
Shut up!
Don't make fun of
them like that!
[MAKINO]
Luffy, no!
[HIGUMA]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Take back what you said
about Shanks and his crew!
[HIGUMA laughing]
[gurgling]
Ha. Stupid brat.
[menacing orchestral music]
[gasps] What the hell?!
[screams]
[gurgling] Help me!
[LORD OF THE COAST growls]
[LUFFY]
Here it comes!
Oh no!
[LUFFY's gurgling continues]
[LORD OF THE COAST yowls]
[LUFFY screaming]
Shanks, you found me!
[SHANKS]
Get lost.
[LORD OF THE COAST whimpering]
[LUFFY sobbing quietly]
[contemplative music]
[SHANKS]
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Makino told me about
how you stood up for us,
how you were willing to fight
and put yourself on the line.
Hold on, you can't cry.
You're a man now.
I know, but this is bad!
You lost your arm!
Oh, no need to worry about that.
I've got another one.
I'm just glad you're safe.
[LUFFY wailing]
[NARRATOR]
Luffy learned many important things that day:
the harshness of the sea,
his own powerlessness,
and most importantly,
the greatness of the man called Shanks.
That's when young Luffy
resolved with all his heart
he would become like him.
[LUFFY]
Shanks.
Are you really about to leave
the village for good?
[SHANKS]
Uh-huh. Yep, it's time for us to part ways.
I bet you'll miss me, wontcha?
Yeah.
But I'm not gonna beg to come with you,
'cause I'm gonna become
a pirate all on my own!
That's good, because I wouldn't
bring you with me anyways.
I mean you'll never make it as a pirate, kiddo!
Will, too! Just wait and see!
I'll round up a crew that's
every bit as good as yours,
and we'll find the world's greatest treasure.
And I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Oh?
Planning to outdo me, are ya?
Okay.
Uh...
If that's the case, I'll leave this here.
[sobbing]
[SHANKS]
It means more to me than anything.
Give it back someday.
After you become a great pirate.
Okay...
He really does have potential.
I know.
He reminds me of myself
back when I was a kid.
[SHANKS]
Set sail!
[NARRATOR]
One decade later,
Luffy's own pirate adventure
began at the very same port.
Ten Years Later
I can't believe Luffy's finally leaving.
Becoming a pirate is a great
dishonor to our village.
[LUFFY sighs]
Couldn't ask for a better day for this!
[LUFFY laughs]
[LUFFY gasps]
Hey, it's this big guy again.
You shouldn't've done that.
'Cause I've been training a lot
over the past ten years.
[roaring]
Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY]
Pistol!
So
[Vi
come
c Mi
a
gnog
board
na s
ingi
and
ng "
bring
We A
a
re!]
So
long
come
a
board
and
bring
a
long
[Vi
c Mi
gnog
all
na s
your
ingi
hopes
ng "
and
We A
dreams
re!]
all
your
hopes
and
dreams
To
geth
er
we
will
find
ev
To
'ry
thing
geth
er
we
will
find
ev
'ry
[chuckles]
thing
that
we're
look
ing
for
that
we're
look
ing
for
That oughta teach ya, ya stupid fish!
There's
al
ways
room
for
you
There's
al
ways
room
friend
friend
We
are,
we
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
we
It's time to get goin'!
are
on
the
cruise!
I'm setting out to become
We
are!
King of the Pirates!
We
are!