Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi   Girl-Krillin
KaitouYahiko
Karaoke
arch1t3cht
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Feeso   Gab
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Gab   Lance
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit
Zenef
Translation
arch1t3cht   Crunchyroll
Gaijin   PamkinPinguin
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Express to the Main Island
of Enies Lobby
It's been a while, Chief.
Eight years ago, he assaulted
government officials in Water Seven:
the fugitive Cutty Flam.
And the criminal responsible for an attack
on Marine battleships at Ohara in the West Blue:
Nico Robin.
We've brought them here without a hitch.
Both are behind those doors.
Welcome back,
Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa!
That's sexual harassment.
Just from saying your name?!
Long time no see, Lucci.
I see you look more arrogant than ever.
And I see you look dumber than ever, Jabra.
What'd you say?
Hold your horses.
We just got back.
He is correct. The two of you
must desist at once!
After all, this is a reunion
five years in the making!
Ow...!
Leave it to Fukuro to test us right away.
Six Powers: Assessment!
Suppose an armed guard
has a power level of ten.
Power Level 10
I will now reveal...
your power levels.
I will uncover your strengths.
First, Kalifa: Power level 630.
Blueno: Power level 820.
Kaku: Power level 2,200.
Lucci...
Power level 4,000!
You said 4,000?! Hey,
did you measure it properly?!
No one has a power level that high!
It's correct!
Everyone got stronger!
I already measured Jabra's and Kumadori's,
so now I know how we rank among ourselves.
Hey, Fukuro! Objection!
Lucci's one thing, but how the hell
am I weaker than Kaku?!
Kaku got stronger too!
Hey, don't let it go to your head, Kaku!
The assessment skill just
measures raw strength.
In an actual fight,
I'd also have devil fruit powers.
Don't go thinking you could ever beat me!
Think whatever you like.
I don't give a rat's ass about that stuff.
Well said.
Don't lend your ears to a stray dog.
What do you mean, "stray dog," Lucci?!
You mangy monster cat!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
Is it just me, or is Jabra
a bit touchier than usual?
Every guard on the island is talking about
how Jabra got rejected
by the waitress Gatherine yesterday.
That explains it.
H-Hey, hold on a sec!
How does everyone know about that?!
I blabbed about it to the guards
on the main island.
It was you!
Gatherine
Oh, please! This is only an issue because you
started with all that ranking nonsense!
Having mastered the Six Powers,
you have all far surpassed ordinary people.
Isn't a power level of 500 enough
to give you superhuman status?
Chief: Power level nine.
Less than one armed guard.
Zip it, you! As your chief,
it shouldn't matter anyway!
Besides, did you forget
about my special sword?!
I've always known that you've
lacked certain attributes, Chief.
H-H-H-Hey! You shouldn't be so blunt, Kalifa.
That's sexual harassment.
What?! Just by responding?!
Chief...
Wh-What is it?
That's sexual harassment!
Just existing?!
Kalifa! How rude of you!
Chief! A-Allow me to take responsibility
and commit ritual suicide immediately!
Seppuku!
Iron Body.
For shame... I cannot die.
Hurry up and die already!
Anyway, you all performed spectacularly
over the past five years.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This isn't really a reward
for your efforts or anything,
but I do have something I want to give you.
Well, I'll do that later.
In any case, I'd like to meet...
the "hope" of the entire world!
Go in already!
You too!
I'm just so excited!
I'm surprised to see you survived
that accident eight years ago,
Cutty Flam.
There's also...
one of the world's most dangerous,
most wanted women:
Nico Robin!
I feel fantastic! However...
it's unfortunate that
the world's citizens don't know
about the true value and magnitude
of the work accomplished today.
It'll be several years...
before anything about today
even comes to light.
I believe the justice doled out by those
old government geezers is too lenient!
Only through sacrifice
will we achieve our goal.
Our hard work will ensure peace
for all of humanity.
Killing some of the fools standing in our way
is a small sacrifice for world peace.
Fools like that fishman, who refused
to hand over a certain something.
As a rebel against justice,
of course he deserved death.
He definitely deserved it!
You're insane!
Mr. Tom lost his life
protecting those blueprints!
He died because of idiots like you!
Wh-What're you doing?!
Help me, guys! Hey!
Ow, ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Ow!
Kumadori!
Roger!
Hurry up and help me, hey! Hey!
Now... now... now...!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Whip!
Giant Scythe!
Bell!
Mallet!
Bazooka!
Gum-Gum...
Stamp!
Chief, main island reporting!
Chief Spandam! Please respond!
It's no use! I can't get through!
Is his receiver off the hook again...?
Not now!
Seriously, not at a critical time like this!
Hey, where did Straw Hat go?
He's right beneath you!
What?! Right beneath us?!
Get him already!
There! Down there!
Dammit! Boxed in!
Gum-Gum...
Volcano!
Th... The wall...! The wall is falling!
Get clear!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Watch out!
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
We need a plan of action!
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy is headed to the courthouse!
Courthouse, Main Island
Enies Lobby
Tighten our defenses! On the double!
Be quiet!
What's this ruckus?!
You woke me up!
Ch-Chief Justice!
"Three-Headed" Baskerville
Chief Justice, Enies Lobby
That's right! Lest you forget,
"Three-Headed" Baskerville
Chief Justice, Enies Lobby
I am the chief justice of Enies Lobby!
"Three-Headed" Baskerville
Chief Justice, Enies Lobby
On the left, I am the Left Baskerville!
On the right, I am the Right Baskerville!
And in the center, it is I,
Central Freeway!
– Say what?!
Ch-Chief Justice!
A pirate is going on a rampage
on the main island,
but the men are saying they can't
get in touch with Chief Spandam.
Please assume command!
A pirate, you say. Pirates are guilty!
Oh, come on. Let him off with a warning.
Then, let's compromise and give him...
the death penalty!
– Say what?!
There's trouble, Chief Justice!
We got a report that Straw Hat's comrades
took out Kashi at the island gate...
and that Oimo is losing too!
– What?! Don't let them breach the gate!
– Send 100 watchdogs immediately!
– Yes, sir!
Dammit! The five minutes are over!
Island Gate
Enies Lobby
This is bad! Hurry up
and clear the path for Rocketman!
You aren't passing through this gate!
We got the gate unlocked!
Now we gotta push open the doors!
What?! Ah, crud!
Alright! Good going!
Go!
No one's touching this gate!
Rope Action...
Top Knot!
Take this!
Whoa! That's a Galley-La foreman, alright!
What?! This puny rope...
Franky Family! Pull!
– Yeah!
Just leave it to us! Let's go,
Sodom and Gomorrah! Grab the rope!
Charge into the gate!
H-Hey! Hold on! Oimo's feeling dizzy!
Push the doors!
Look! The doors...!
The doors are opening!
What happened to Oimo?!
Just a little more!
They're through the gate!
Main Gate
H-H-H-Hey! Hey!
Hey...
Is that... a sea train?
What's going on?
What?! It's rushing straight toward us!
They're really gonna launch
onto the main island!
No way! They can't jump over that iron fence!
Get a move on! Don't let them charge in!
Close the gate!
Hey, granny!
Huh? What's up?
Change of plans!
Guys, looks like we're changing our plan.
The samurai man says everyone
needs to hold on tight to something.
"Hold on tight"?!
Hey, Swordsmoron! What's the big idea?!
They closed the main gate.
They what?!
What?! This is terrible!
We're gonna crash into the gate!
What'll we do?! What'll we do?!
Break away, Kokoro!
Don't worry.
There's a way.
Push that fence, frog!
– What?!
He can't...!
Any farther and we'll
run aground on the iron fence!
No way!
The sea train...
...is flying!
No! We're gonna die!
What?! We're gonna die?!
Nami, hurry into my arms!
We're gonna land in that gaping hole, you idiot!
Zoro! You've figured out our landing, right?!
Just leave it to...
luck.
– It's up to luck?!
Oimo is down!
A-Are you... the Straw Hats?!
That's right!
– We are?!
Whatever. It doesn't matter.
C'mon, shake a leg!
All right, guys! Press on as far as we can go!
– Yeah!
Paulie!
Dammit!
Who the hell are you?!
We're Enies Lobby's elite guards,
the Watchdogs of the Law,
Watchdogs for short!
Watchdogs of the Law
Elite Guards of Enies Lobby
Under orders from Chief Justice Baskerville,
we'll cast judgment on you
and bring you down at this gate!
Dammit! They send one guard
after another to block us!
Oimo! What're you doing?!
How could you let
pirates like them open the gate?!
Ow!
Oimo passed out!
– Not good! He's up and at 'em!
Oimo won't forgive you!
You're not gonna get away with this!
– What?!
Wh-Why the hell did Rocketman...
come from the sky?!
– Opening the gates was pointless?!
Wh-What just happened?!
Do you think they're okay
after crashing in like that?
Th-They aren't coming out...
Hey, what happened?!
Wh-Who are those two?!
Huh?
Should we have introduced ourselves?
That's stupid. Why should we have?
It's Roronoa's group!
– It's about time!
All according to plan...
Really?!