Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Feeso
Grug
Zenef
Feeso
Grug
Zenef
Feeso
Grug
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Timing
Halee
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
Linlin! I'll put you out of your misery
with my own hands!
Semlor...
No, Linlin!
Se...
Jorl!
m...
lor !
Chief Waterfall Beard!
Chief Jorl!
Semlor !
Hold Linlin!
Put out the fire in the village!
– Catch her already!
– Okay!
Don't hurt her!
Can you make some semlor ?
There's some for the festival
in the village storehouse!
Bring them now!
O-Okay!
– Mother, what are you doing?!
– It's dangerous!
Stay back!
Gebur...
Mother!
...tstag!
"Gerburtstag" - Birthday
Mother!
I shall give you a voice.
What's that?
Heed my command.
– There's a face in the fire!
– What?!
I'm scared...
It's like a demon!
Your name is Pandora!
I brought it!
Hurry up and feed her!
Semlor !
It's delicious! It's delicious!
Simmer down!
The fire...
is gone.
Hey, look!
How cute!
Hi, Mother!
Mother...
...worked a miracle!
No, it wasn't me.
The sun god calmed this disaster.
I'm so happy!
Punish her... She is not just a child...
If we don't do something now...
she'll bring even more disaster in the future!
– Chief Jorl!
– Quick, help him!
Chief Mountain Beard!
Linlin...
Please forgive her!
You're trying to stop me, Carmel?
Jorl has been my companion in battle for 300 years.
He's too old. I don't think he'll survive this time.
Being a warrior isn't about living long...
It's about how you die!
We have to bring it to an end...
We cannot forgive those
who defy Elbaf’s laws.
I understand!
But even if she can't be forgiven,
Linlin is a poor child who was abandoned.
She is now under the care
of the House of Lambs!
I cannot abandon her!
What will you do with her?
I will take her and leave this place!
Carmel!
Chief Mountain Beard!
You must kill Linlin!
Why should we pardon her
after she's done such a horrible thing?!
What has happened to your Elbaf pride?
Alright then, why don't you
get out of my sight now?!
Why?!
Hajrudin!
Let go of me! Let go!
What happened to Chief Waterfall Beard?
He died.
Doesn't she remember?
Jorl, the hero of the giants, died,
and between the devastation of Linlin and Carmel's miracle...
the events of that day...
spread far and wide through the few settlements of giants around the world.
With the orphans of the House of Lambs,
who couldn't stand to be apart from their mother,
along with the giants' new sworn enemy,
Charlotte Linlin, in tow,
Mother Carmel left Elbaf.
And then, they began life anew
at a reestablished House of Lambs.
It's done! Is this good enough?
That's all we need.
I'm sorry for asking these favors.
Without your help, there's no way we'd have a house
this far into the mountains.
Don't mention it. To be honest,
I don't wanna see Linlin's face,
but you're the Holy Mother
to us giants too, Carmel.
If you ever need us, say the word!
Thank you!
To put the worried children at ease,
Carmel began to smile even more.
Wait, wait!
A few days after leaving Elbaf,
things were just as they used to be...
No, Linlin's gonna kill me!
Wait, wait!
And the House of Lambs was filled
with the children's laughter once more.
Look after the house while I'm away.
I'll clean the bathroom!
I'll do the laundry!
When will you be back?
I'll be back once I finish buying our groceries.
Do you need anything?
Shortcake!
– A set of cards!
– Toy swords for samurai fighting!
Okay.
See you, Mother! Take care!
To the rest of the world,
the House of Lambs was a place...
where the pious mother would
miraculously reform troubled children
until they were ready for a good home...
You're right on time...
Of course. Have I ever stood you up?
Let's get to business.
There is a good girl.
I never thought you'd leave Elbaf...
I had to. I didn't want to give this girl up.
Think about it.
At just five years old, she was able
to destroy half of an Elbaf village.
But the price you're asking for is...
I know you can pay it.
If she were in the Navy, she could one day
be an admiral or even the fleet admiral.
If she were in Cipher Pol, she'd be
a great shield for the Celestial Dragons.
I've been in the kid-trafficking business for 50 years,
and this girl's the finest product I've ever had!
After pulling that stunt with the Navy 37 years ago,
I was able to live on Elbaf...
which got you guys the first-ever
giant recruit for the Navy... John Giant!
That was all thanks to me!
I run the House of Lambs nice and clean,
and those kids have no idea
that I've been selling the liveliest of them
to the government every two years.
Orphans make good spies, right?
They've got no history to trace!
All right! All right!
I'll get you your money!
Of course you will!
It ain't easy being the Holy Mother.
Mother Carmel
Orphan Seller
(Code Name: "Mountain Witch")
Mother Carmel
Orphan Seller
(Code Name: "Mountain Witch")
I think I'll take the chance to retire after this one,
so this'll be my last deal. I need you to pay me in full.
What do you all wanna sing today?
"Binks' Sake"!
Really? But that's a pirates' song.
That's right!
We're gonna be pirates someday!
Oh, that sounds cool!
♪ Making a delivery,
bringing it across the sea ♪
♪ Binks' sake in the hold
as we sail through the breeze ♪
♪ Far across the eye can see,
the sun is shining merrily ♪
♪ As the birds fly in the sky
as they sing out with glee ♪
You'll be sold to the government
before you get the chance to become pirates.
♪ Bid adieu to everyone,
so long to port renowned ♪
♪ Sailing on from dusk 'til dawn
and singing out as one ♪
♪ Cross the gold and silver waves,
changing into water sprays ♪
♪ Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea! ♪
One, two, three!
Happy birthday, Linlin!
"Happy birthday, Linlin".
Thank you, everyone!
We know how much you love semlor, Linlin.... So we made a croquembouche out of them!
I hope it's good!
It's called croquembouche ?
It looks delicious!
Let's have a tea party!
A tea party?
We'll spend time gracefully sitting around tables,
drinking tea, and eating sweets!
That sounds great!
I wanna have that! A tea party!
– Let's make tea.
– Join us, Mother!
Okay, okay.
Thank you!
Yay!
Alright, let's start!
– Eat as much as you want!
– Eat, eat!
Uh-huh! Thank you!
It's so delicious!
She eats so fast!
The tea party's fun!
I'm so happy! It's so delicious!
One day, Mother Carmel simply vanished.
And it happened on the very best birthday
that Linlin had ever had.
She was with her friends at the House of Lambs,
kids who'd been through the same hardships,
and her beloved, kindhearted mother.
Surrounded by all those smiles,
and eating her delicious, sweet birthday cake,
Linlin was unable to hold back her tears.
Eat as much as you like, Linlin.
I'll eat... I'll eat it all!
What a wonderful day it was...
She couldn't even see through her tears.
Hey, hey, don't rush, Linlin!
We made it for you!
It's all for you, Linlin!
Thank you!
Eat more!
Let's stay friends!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Let's stay together and have fun!
Yeah!
It's so delicious!
What a truly wonderful birthday.
Lick!
Oh, I'm so happy! I was eating so much,
that I even chewed off a bit of the table.
Thank you, everyone!
I'll never forget this day for the rest of my...
What?
Everyone?
Mother?
One day, Mother Carmel...
Where did they go?
...suddenly vanished.
Hmm? Huh?
Where are you?! Everyone!
Are you in the house?
Hey!
Everyone!
Linlin!
Oh, there you are!
What?
Don't leave me all alone...
Where are you, everyone?
Hey, Mother...
Why did you just vanish?
Where did you go,
Mother?!
Mama!
63 years ago, Mother Carmel
and the other children simply vanished.
Even Big Mom herself does not know
the truth of what happened,
but there were two people
who witnessed the whole thing...
Where did you go?
One was a warrior of Elbaf who was worried about the House of Lambs,
so he came to check on them.
M-Monster!
The giant went pale, took off running,
and never returned to the island.
Eventually, news of this day spread to Elbaf,
and then to all the giants in the world,
and from that point onward,
the name "Charlotte Linlin" became
so hated that
no giant would utter her name.
Where did you go?! Mother! Everyone!
Meanwhile, the other witness
was a failed pirate cook
who'd wound up living on the island
named Streusen.
He found it to be very entertaining.
He had the ability
to turn any object into food,
thanks to his Cook-Cook Fruit.
I've never seen a monster like that before.
Don't leave me alone...
At this rate, she's gonna die.
What a waste that'd be.
Where did you go, Mother?
Hey, what's the matter, little girl?
If you keep crying,
you're just going to get hungrier.
Say, little girl,
shall we talk about your dreams?
Who are you, old man?
Hey, don't come too close.
Hey, old man, have you seen Mother?
Do you know where everyone's gone?
I don't know,
but I bet they'll come back soon.
You think so?
Yeah, I'll stay with you until then.
I'm a good chef.
You won't go hungry with me around.
I'm hungry...
You can count on me.
See?
It was the meeting of these two
that led to the formation of the Big Mom Pirates.
Linlin!
Come to your senses!
They're going to shoot you!
So, at the tea party today,
if we break that picture in half,
what do you think will happen?
Mama will be devastated!
And no one there will be able to move
for more than five seconds.
Then, the KX launcher
will show its real strength...
and Emperor Big Mom will die!
You're doomed, Big Mom!
Mama!
Mother.
They're all trying to stop me.
People are happiest when they're equal.
But in today's world, a country like that
is nearly impossible to find.
That's why we should start our own country here!
It'll be a country where everyone is equal!
Country?!
That's right. A place where
all races can coexist in peace.
And where everyone
will be at the same eye level!
The same eye level? That sounds great!
Then everyone can be big like me!
Wow! How cool!
That's a beautiful dream, Mother!
Linlin!
Everyone, let's work hard together.
I'll do my best!
– Me too!
Yeah!
Let's create a country of dreams right here!
I'll do my best too, Mother!
You're a good girl, Linlin.
I am!
If there were countries like that,
the world would be a much more peaceful place.
Everyone would be able to find happiness.
Mother's dream was my dream!
Peace? Is that your dream, Linlin?
It is! I'm gonna build a country
that Mother would like!
Why don't you stop crying already?
Hey, hey, hey! I wanna see Mother's magic!
Magic?
Yeah, she was good at doing magic tricks.
I think she put out her hands like this...
Then...
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
What?! It's the trick that Mother used to do!
Why?!
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
How come I can do it?!
♪ Earth! ♪
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
♪ Flower, flower! Flower... ♪
What the...
Is that a devil fruit power?
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
♪ Tree! Tree! ♪
♪ Earth! ♪
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
♪ Tree! Tree! ♪
♪ Earth! ♪
♪ Flower, flower! ♪
Wow, I was able to do it too, Mother!
Thank you, Linlin! Let's sing together!
How interesting!
All right, I've decided.
I'm gonna set out to sea with her!
Nice! Nice!
A country where everyone is the same size...
and sits at the same eye level, and where everyone is equal.
All right, Linlin.
Let's build that country of dreams!
Count me in.
Uh-huh!
Hey, look at this wanted poster!
Fifty million just for a little kid?!
How is that possible?
A little girl destroyed the castle?!
The culprit is Charlotte Linlin!
Cipher Pol reported that she's dangerous!
She'll become a powerful force someday!
Catch her at any cost!
Yeah!
There she is!
Watch out, Linlin.
I'm eating sweets!
Don't interrupt!
Charlotte Linlin continued wreaking havoc
and became a worldwide threat seemingly overnight.
She's a pirate!
Run!
Bring me all the sweets you have!
Your Majesty!
Oh, no!
And then I'll guarantee you peace
and a country of dreams!
If you do as I say,
then everyone will be happy!
Those who disobey are just being selfish,
so I'll have to kill them!
Mother, I miss you...
I miss you!
Mother!
I'll make everyone big someday!
Then we'll sit at the table together again!
But there are still people who won't listen to me!
I'm so sad and can't stop crying!
Because the only existing portrait of Mother...
You're a good girl.
The one and only portrait of Mother
that was precious to me...
was broken by them!
I'll make them pay...
Those Straw Hat Pirates!
I'll never forgive them!
The plan has failed!
What?!
They failed!
Listen, since I can fly,
I'll plunge on to the site with a mirror to escape!
Once you finish,
dive into Caesar's mirror quickly!
Well, here comes my part!
Dammit!
She destroyed my launchers!
That monstrous hag!
She's definitely one of the Four Emperors!
Retreat, everyone!
Jump into the mirror!
What incredible wind pressure!
This is bad! We're stuck on the roof!
There's no way to escape!
And there's no way to win, either!
Rook: In Voller Größe!
What?!
Big Father!
Oh, cool!