Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Sewil
Graphics
AphantasticRabbit
Datenshi
Gabingus
PamkinPenguin
Pepperjack
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Gab
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit
panda :>
Poppy
Westfal
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
PamkinPinguin
rangicus
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The World's Supreme Authority
Speak of the devil...
You got business with me?
Yeah! Give back chestnut head's gold!
Gold?
You mean that geezer
Cricket's treasure?
Why should I give anything back?
As a pirate, I took that treasure.
As a pirate yourself,
you're in no position to complain!
Do too.
They're my friends,
so I'm taking it back.
I hate to ask, but can you fight?!
Do you even know
how to throw a punch?!
What can a coward
like you possibly do?!
N-No doubt about it!
That's him!
Hey, you're still holding onto that?
Tear it up and throw it away already!
But if this 100-million-belly
wanted poster is real,
then Bellamy doesn't even
hold a candle to this guy!
Ridiculous!
Just look at that kid!
Does he look like a threat to you?!
Even thirty million
is suspiciously high!
If you just stand there
in fear like this afternoon,
you ain't gonna plunder
anything from me, coward!
This afternoon was different.
Oh yeah? And what
made it different?!
This time, I'll shut that
smart-ass trap of yours for good!
It's collapsing!
I'll finish you off in an instant!
Spring...
Snipe!
How are you gonna
steal the gold back?!
You're nothing but talk,
you damn weakling!
You can't stand up to me,
and all you do is blather
on about dreams!
– He's coming this way!
– Run!
That didn't kill you, did it?
He got up!
It's too early to kick the bucket!
My show's just getting
to the good part!
Spring...
Hopper!
Bellamy disappeared!
That's the same way he killed
Roshio the Executioner!
They're your friends, huh?!
Come to think of it, that geezer and
those giant apes are just like you!
You're all natural-born morons
who believe in a tall tale
spun by some loser 400 years ago!
"The City of Gold"?
An island in the sky?!
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
You wanted to know if
I could throw a punch?
Get 'im, Bellamy! That moron doesn't
deserve to live in the real world!
So long, Straw Hat!
Hey... Quit kiddin' around, Bellamy...
C'mon! You're just joking, right?!
Say something!
Hey, Bellamy! Drop the act!
C'mon, get up! Get on with
the show like always, Bellamy!
You're a major rookie with
a 55-million-belly bounty!
That's right! Those two
from this afternoon...
have bounties way higher
than yours, Bellamy!
S-See! I told you...!
Chestnut head's gold. Give it back.
Man, they're tough!
They're so lively,
even after getting beaten up...
I know Chopper treated them,
but it's like they don't feel pain...
Why didn't you go with him?
Huh? What's with you?!
First it's "Don't fight!", then it's "Fight!"
It's "Don't go!", then it's "Go!"
No! I mean, they beat you up, too!
"Beat me up"?
They weren't really worth
the trouble, you know.
Fights that just end in pity are painful.
Huh? What kind of bunk is that?
Shut up and get lost!
You're being a pain in the ass!
I'm what?!
You're the one who never listens!
Why do I have to listen to you?!
Hey, now! Be careful there!
Are you guys insane?!
Stop giving orders!
This ship is our treasure!
What are you even talking about?!
Hey! I said stop!
You're the insane one here!
You guys are idiots!
I got it!
Th-That kid... It was a fluke!
Hey, you!
Hold it! I'm still here!
C'mon! Bring it on!
There's no way we can lose
to some starry-eyed morons!
What's wrong?! Hey, Straw Hat!
Where are you going?!
Where?
The sky!
The Previous Afternoon
An Island in the Grand Line
Captain? Captain!
What?!
Er... Is this really the right place?
The legendary cave
where Captain John,
the ruthless treasure hunter,
hid his fortune...
Yeah, that's right.
Keep going, but be careful!
Listen, treasure is often
protected by guards and traps.
If you let your guard down,
you could die!
We don't know what
kinds of monsters
or bloody traps from
the depths of hell could be here!
Now let's put in another
hard day's work on the tunnel!
– Okay, Boss!
"Boss"
Oh? You guys must be new recruits.
Oh yeah, nothing like
working up a sweat, eh, Boss?!
Well, a pickaxe is
a man's tool, right?!
It sure is! With our sweat
and hard work, we'll make a tunnel
"Boss"
that will bring smiles to people's faces!
That's right. And the booze
after work really hits the...
Why are you having
me do honest work?!
So, Captain Buggy,
Captain John's treasure wasn't there.
Mohji, you idiot!
Show some consideration!
It's obvious that the captain
got the wrong island.
Are you trying to make him
go red with embarrassment?!
Who are you saying has
a huge red nose?! Huh?!
By the way, Captain,
this is no time for fooling around.
What are we gonna do?
The Straw Hat guys are real pirates
on the Grand Line now.
Ha! Don't lose your head,
you flashy idiot!
We're leaving them alone for now.
Huh?! What do you mean?
You see, they say that
when a witch eats a kid,
first she fattens the kid up,
nice and chubby.
Get it?
In short, the higher those
Straw Hat guys' bounties get...
Oh, I see! When you beat them,
your bounty will become greater than theirs!
– Oh!
Yeah, exactly!
I see! That's amazing!
Captain, shall we throw a party?
Why not?!
This is no time for
horsing around, you guys.
If you can't find out where Luffy is,
how exactly do you plan to beat him?
Don't be so uptight, Alvida.
A little fun never hurt anyone!
Luffy, huh? If you're looking
for him, I'll tell you where he is.
See? He'll tell us where Luffy is.
Who the hell are you?!
Oh, sorry for interrupting your party.
I was summoned by
the aroma of delicious food.
My name is Ace. Nice to meet you.
Oh, no need to be so formal.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm asking you what you're doing here!
I don't care about your name!
What a flashily insolent attitude!
Captain! Captain,
this guy is... Fire Fist!
Fire Fist Ace!
He's the commander of
Whitebeard's Second Division!
Whitebeard?!
Oh? You guys know
Pops? That's coo–
– He fell asleep!
No!
And why not?! You can't deny
how amazing this opportunity is!
If we defeat Fire Fist Ace,
we'll become famous overnight!
I said no!
Listen closely and
remember this flashily!
No matter what, never mess
with the Whitebeard Pirates!
Whitebeard is a monster—
a living legend.
He's the only man to ever go toe-to-toe
with Roger, the King of the Pirates!
He's now, without a doubt,
the world's strongest pirate!
He's the man closest to that
secret treasure, the One Piece!
And above all, Whitebeard never
forgives the killing of one of his own.
Never! That's the kind of man he is.
You know an awful lot about him.
Of course...
Long ago... I met him in person,
here on the Grand Line.
Oh? You know Pops?
– He's awake!
Hey, you guys! Don't be shy!
It's a party, so let's have some fun!
Uhh... He's right! We were
having a party, right?!
Hey, you're quite the drinker!
Have some more!
Oh?! You guys have a lion?!
C'mon, jump through this fire hoop!
Okay, show him, Richie!
The Holy Land, Mary Geoise
What? Red Hair?!
Yes, his actions are alarming.
"Justice"
Though it's not as if he
himself is on the move.
Affirmative. It was indirect
action utilizing an envoy.
However, any contact between
Whitebeard and Red Hair is dangerous!
The Five Elders
Supreme Council of
the World Government
The Five Elders
Supreme Council of
the World Government
Yes, that is true.
But Red Hair is only
a threat when provoked;
he's not one to actively
effect change in the world.
Let us be patient and observe.
The Seven Warlords are our priority.
We must find
a successor for Crocodile.
Do not underestimate his loss.
The collapse of the three great powers
will fracture the world itself.
Balance must be maintained.
Yes, sir! That is why we have summoned
the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
but we are unsure how many
will actually show up.
They are pirates.
They do as they please...
Damn you, Crocodile.
You've put us in a dreadful situation.
We can no longer let the man who
defeated you remain unchecked...
Monkey D. Luffy...
Marine Headquarters to Mary Geoise.
Warlords Donquixote Doflamingo
and Bartholomew Kuma have arrived.
Donquixote Doflamingo
Warlord of the Sea
Former Bounty: 340 Million Belly
Donquixote Doflamingo
Warlord of the Sea
Former Bounty: 340 Million Belly
Bartholomew Kuma
Warlord of the Sea
Former Bounty: 296 Million Belly
Bartholomew Kuma
Warlord of the Sea
Former Bounty: 296 Million Belly
H-Hey! S-Stop! What are you doing?!
It's not me! My hands are
moving on their own!
Don't be stupid!
This is no time for jokes!
I'm not joking!
I can't control my body!
The hell you can't...! I can't breathe!
Knock it off! What do
you think you're doing?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
It's not me!
Stop it! Where you do think you are?!
"Master Tactician" Tsuru
Vice Admiral, Marine HQ
Hey...
Stop!
Doflamingo, is this your doing?!
Stop it at once!
Then start talking already,
or I'll end this lousy get-together!
H-Hey! Stop, you idiot!
"Justice"
Stop! Make him stop,
Doflamingo! You bastard!
Enough!
That's enough! Did you
come here to start a war?!
Sengoku "the Buddha"
Fleet Admiral, Marine HQ
(Marine Commander in Chief)
Sengoku "the Buddha"
Fleet Admiral, Marine HQ
(Marine Commander in Chief)
Oh, pardon my late welcome.
Thank you for coming, scum of the sea.
Oh, my. Listen to the big shot...
Let us begin. I doubt any more
will come even if we wait.
Two out of six is
better than I expected.
I bet.
I wasn't going to come either,
but business is booming on the island.
So I'm here out of sheer boredom.
I see. That's disconcerting to hear.
Nothing depresses us more
than a booming pirate industry.
Pretty blunt, aren't you!
Not very Buddha-like,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Such tedious squabbling.
Did I perhaps come
to the wrong place?
Hawk Eye!
Marine Headquarters
and the Seven Warlords...
A roundtable between these two
opposing forces seems pointless.
Oh, look who we have here.
Didn't think you'd show.
This is a surprise.
Why? I'm simply here to observe.
Some of the pirates involved
have caught my eye.
That is all.
In that case... May I join in
as an observer as well?
Well, I suppose I'm not
exactly an "observer"...
Who are you?!
How did you get in here?!
But my... What esteemed
company has gathered here...?
I've come in the hopes...
Huh?!
...that I might be allowed
to join your meeting...
if at all possible.
I do believe you have
stripped Crocodile of his title
and are now looking for a successor?
Are you... Laffitte?!
Laffitte?
Oh, you know my name?
I'm quite honored!
He's a well-known former sheriff
from the West Blue!
He was exiled for his brutal methods!
That was long ago.
Who I am is of no importance!
I've come to recommend a certain man
for the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
The Grand Line
Shanks... That name
brings back memories...
So this is a letter from him?
Yes. It's very important,
so he had me deliver it!
I see! Well done, then!
Well, I'm still just a newcomer
to the Red Hair Pirates...
Rockstar
Red Hair Pirates (Newcomer)
Bounty: 94 Million Belly
Rockstar
Red Hair Pirates (Newcomer)
Bounty: 94 Million Belly
But I was already a somewhat
infamous pirate before I even joined.
Hey, you guys! You've
heard of Rockstar, right?!
Nope. Never heard of him.
Anyway, the sea king tasted great...
Wait! What do you think you're–
Sending me a damn letter...
When did that kid decide
he's such a big shot?!
Hey! Hold on, now!
The chief said this was
an important letter!
Th-That was from Red Hair himself!
Are you insane?
And I'm Whitebeard!
Captain, that's probably
enough alcohol for now...
Don't be ridiculous!
What's wrong with drinking
something that I want?!
The chief said this
was an urgent letter!
I have a good idea what it's about:
Ace and Blackbeard.
Go tell that Red Hair brat
that if he wants to talk to me,
then he should come here himself,
and with some good booze, too!
Now get lost! I don't feel like
talking to snot-nosed punks.
Edward Newgate
The Great Pirate "Whitebeard"
Strongest Man in the World
Edward Newgate
The Great Pirate "Whitebeard"
Strongest Man in the World
That old-timer hasn't changed!
A Winter Island
This is no laughing matter, Chief!
Well, I figured this might happen.
Give me a little more time!
I've never been insulted
like this before!
Hey, you're not planning to do
anything, are you? Forget it.
I appreciate your help.
Head straight back now.
B-But, I have my pride...!
Your life is more
important than your pride.
There's nothing more you can do.
Sorry for all the trouble.
So, what are you gonna do, Chief?
We're going. Prepare to set sail!
To see Whitebeard?!
Yep, that's right!
Do you think the government
will turn a blind eye to this?
This isn't the time
to worry about that.
It's no big deal.
The government
probably won't stay quiet...
but if they're gonna get in our way,
we won't stay quiet, either!
Men! Prepare for battle!
Alright! Get the top-shelf booze ready!
Teach?
Yes. The captain of our pirate crew.
Never heard of him.
A stranger with no reputation
would be no threat to other pirates.
Yes, we realize that.
To that end, we are
carefully devising a plan,
so I ask for a little more time.
Interesting! C'mon!
Let 'em try, Sengoku!
We are the Blackbeard Pirates.
Please remember that name...
Hey, did you hear?!
Bellamy was defeated!
Whoa! By who?!
100 million...
From his haki, 30 million
seemed kinda low...
But this high...?
What's the plan, Captain?
Hey, you! Don't just
stand there gawking!
I'm mad as hell right now!
Shut your trap!
I've got no time for lightweights!
I've set my sights on marks
worth at least 100 million!
We're going to join
the big leagues now!
The hunt is on now!
Captain! Weren't we supposed to
meet up with Laffitte in this town?!
"Champion" Jesus Burgess
Helmsman, Blackbeard Pirates
Seems that's not happening!
That's fate for you!
Right, Augur?!
Marshall D. "Blackbeard" Teach
Captain, Blackbeard Pirates
"Supersonic" Van Augur
Marksman, Blackbeard Pirates
Precisely! Destiny always
measures a person's worth!
Doc Q "the Reaper"
Doctor, Blackbeard Pirates