Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Pepperjack         PhosCity
Zenef
Soundtracking                    Halee
Timing
Gab
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit   Lorphex
Muphen   panda :>   Westfal
Translation
Chloelyy
Crunchyroll
PamkinPinguin
Chloelyy
Crunchyroll
PamkinPinguin
Departing Shortly
Blue Station Entrance
Shipyard Island
Well, CP9 is coming soon.
Nico Robin, go on ahead and get on board.
Now!
Hey, you two! Hurry up and take her away!
– Yes, sir!
Government officials, Marines... and Robin.
Alright... How should I make my entrance?
None of you know
the darkness I carry within me.
She's definitely being
hauled in by the authorities.
But if she wanted to run, she could easily
take out those chumps on her own.
Does she have some kind of agenda?
Or is there a reason she can't run?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Robin my love!
My darling prince, I knew you'd come!
Could it be she's waiting for me to save her?
Corgi, sir!
CP9 has arrived!
– You bastard! Let me go!
– Please let me go!
You guys are freaking me out!
That's the Rob Lucci.
What a presence...
So that's CP9...
Hey, are you listening?!
Seriously, you're scaring me!
Let me go, you bastard!
Let me–
Hey, where are you taking me?!
You guys won't get away with this!
Just you wait!
I've got 8,000 men under my comman–
Usopp...!
Great work on your long mission, agents!
Lucci, sir, here's your coat.
You're going overboard.
Knock it off, all of you.
Y-Yes, sir! R-Right away!
This isn't a game.
Look sharp!
Everyone, get on the train!
Everyone, get on the sea train!
Prepare to depart for Enies Lobby!
I said let me g–
Who the hell are they?
In any case...
"Sorry I dragged you down till the end"?
He's a pain even after leaving the crew.
Ruins of the Galley-La Company HQ
A little farther to the right!
Spray water there!
Pump more water!
So, Robin doesn't hate us after all?!
That's right!
I'm so relieved!
What?! He turned into a tanuki!
He turned into a tanuki!
Hey, he turned into a tanuki!
That's why we need to find Luffy
and the others pronto to go save Robin!
Alright, let's go find them!
Where are they?
No clue! That's why we're looking for them!
Gotcha...
I'll give it my all!
Whoa! Now he's a gorilla!
Wait, you guys.
I don't care if you go after Nico Robin,
but the sea train for government personnel
will be departing at eleven o'clock.
Well...
if I had to guess, that's the train
they're going to take.
In other words...
so will Nico Robin.
What?
Following its departure, the sea train
will be suspended temporarily
since Aqua Laguna is coming soon.
Then... that means...
You can't sail out in this weather, so missing
the train means you're stuck on this island.
No way! This is bad! What time is it now?!
It's 10:30.
What?! We've only got thirty minutes left?!
Hey, can't you do something?
Stall the sea train for a while!
Well... Its destination is Enies Lobby,
which is off-limits if you're not a government official.
The engineer is a government agent,
so he won't listen to me.
Oh, no...!
Th-Then...
our only option is to head to the station
and convince Robin in person...
Chopper!
Huh?
I'll tell you what directions Luffy and Zoro
flew off to! Start looking there!
If you find them,
tell them to hurry to the station!
Okay, got it!
Hey... you guys.
You're okay, Mr. Paulie!
Give this girl and her friend a hand.
– What?!
Y-You want us to help them, Mr. Paulie?!
But these people tried to kill Mr. Iceburg!
We should tie these two up instead!
That's right!
Mr. Lucci and Mr. Kaku are still missing–
The Straw Hats are not the assassins!
They are innocent!
The real culprits tricked us
into falsely accusing them!
I have no clue who those masked men were,
but the Straw Hat Pirates fought them on our behalf!
As a matter of fact, Mr. Iceburg
and I would probably be dead if not for them.
Don't bother looking for Lucci or Kaku.
We might've seen the last of them.
What?! You know what happened to them?!
They moved back home.
No way! At a time like this?!
Forget it! Go find Straw Hat!
Hey, you! Hussy!
That again? Quit calling me that!
You're going to the station, right? Follow me.
Yeah...
Thanks...
Mr. Paulie, hold on!
Is what you just told us true?!
Quit your jabbering and make this right!
You wanna sully Galley-La's name?!
– N-No, foreman!
Our apologies!
– We're sorry!
Whatever you need, let us know!
Bring the yagaras out! Open the cage!
– Yeah!
They moved back home, huh?
They don't need to know the details.
It's bad enough
that they broke our trust, right?
Hey!
You guys!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, come back!
Everyone, please shout with me!
Roger! You guys got that?!
– Yeah!
Hey! Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, come back!
Turn into that canal!
That's a shortcut to the station!
We still have twenty minutes left...
Please don't go, Robin.
Sacrificing yourself for us...
As if we'd let that happen!
Yagara! Please! Go faster!
The last departure at eleven o'clock...
from Water Seven's
Blue Station to Enies Lobby...
Ouch!
Ow!
Stay here and be quiet.
Damn you! Would it kill
you morons to be more delicate?
Yeah, what he said! Morons!
Damn government dogs!
Huh? Hey now...
Due to the approaching storm surge,
the schedule has been moved up
and the train will be departing shortly.
Dammit! It's leaving already?
Looks like our mission is almost complete.
Refrain from making such
frivolous comments until we arrive.
Fool.
Pardon me.
You can't sail out in this weather, so missing
the train means you're stuck on this island.
Please! Make it in time!
Franky...
Are you safe?
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
Luffy!
Where are you?!
Hey! Where are you?!
Please come out!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, come back!
Luffy! They're gonna take Robin away!
Answer me!
Where are you?!
I wonder what Luffy and the others are doing...
Looks like no one will make it here in time.
I repeat. The last train will depart shortly.
Dammit!
Th-Those jerks!
They won't get away with this!
I'm stuck.
I can't believe I slipped at a time like this...!
Dammit!
I'm stuck.
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Come out!
We've gotta rescue Robin!
– Straw Hat!
– Roronoa!
Where are you guys?
What about this way?!
Hey!
Straw Hat!
Zoro!
Crap, no sign of them here.
Maybe they're in the Backstreets?
That may be the case,
but the area might already be flooded.
It'd be too dangerous to look there.
Dammit!
Straw Hat! Roronoa!
Lucci, sir!
The waves are getting too high,
so we're departing a bit early.
Is that an issue–
No.
Depart.
Yes, sir. Well, then...
I've lived on this island for five years...
but I don't feel even a shred
of regret leaving it behind.
Hey, wasn't that a steam whistle?!
Yeah. But it's strange.
It's not the departure time yet.
Then again, there are no public passengers.
The weather might be causing them
to depart ahead of schedule!
Hurry! That's the station, straight ahead!
Please stop, sea train!
Today's last departure
from Water Seven to Enies Lobby...
The train's leaving. Be seated.
...is now departing.
You made me live when I wanted to die.
That's your crime.
I have nowhere to go
and no home to return to.
So let me stay on this ship.
Mellorine! Mellorine! Mellorine!
Oh, I see... Then I guess
we have no choice. Welcome aboard.
– Luffy!
Don't worry.
She's not a bad person.
H-Hey, I think we're moving.
Damn government trash...!
We made it! Thank you, yagara!
Down the stairs past that entrance!
Got it!
Robin! Don't go!
Hey, you! Who are you?!
It's dangerous! Stay back!
Robin, get off the train!
It doesn't matter who we're up
against, we'll fight together!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Where are you guys?!
I can't... get out...!
Wait!
The train...!
Robin!
We were too late...
Seriously, what was that guy thinking?!
It doesn't matter.
That train is for government use only.
They'll catch him and that'll be that.
Huh?
That's Galley-La's... Paul–
Read the room!
Something is happening over there.
Train stations are places
of meetings and partings.
As station employees,
we should quietly watch over them, right?!
Oh, that's right.
Quietly, got that?
The train left pretty early, huh?
– What?!
Ah, yes.
All the passengers were on board, so–
Also...
the sea was getting choppier than anticipated.
The way things were headed,
it looked like Aqua Laguna was about to arrive,
so we moved up the departure time.
This place is dangerous, too.
You should evacuate to Shipyard Island soon.
That's right...
Y'know... Once the train departs,
there's no stopping it.
The truth hurts...
but this Enies Lobby place is...
Are you crying?
Well, um... I understand how you feel, but–
After that train!
She's pissed!
Those government morons!
They won't get away with this!
Hey, lend us a ship!
What's with you, all of a sudden?
A big, strong ship!
You want to sail in this weather?
You idiot!
Don't be rash! You don't know
how bad Aqua Laguna is!
We'll manage!
This isn't just any storm!
It's on another level!
The sea is about to get incredibly harsh!
If you set sail now,
you're as good as dead!
But if we don't, Robin is as good as dead!
That was way too close...
Th-Thank you...
Thank you very much, Mr. Paulie!
We almost got dragged into the sea.
Look at that.
The schedule board was torn apart
by the force of that wave.
Nothing like this has ever happened before.
What's with the power of this ebbing?
It's only just now approaching, but...
the speed and strength of this
Aqua Laguna's waves are abnormal.
Hey...
Will the sea train carrying Robin be all right?
It should make it through
the stormy area right before the surge hits.
If it clears that, the train will
make it through most of the big waves.
Excuse me, would you
be Nami by any chance?
An inconspicuous letter
was left in the station plaza.
From a friend, maybe?
A letter? From whom?
I'm surprised that you found a small note.
It was over here! Hard to miss it!
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
read this!
Nami, please
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
That buffoon...!
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Nami, please
read this!
What does it say?
Hmm... hold on a sec.
The first half is just
a pointless love letter, so...
She said it's a love letter.
The third man has appeared.
No...
Judging from the situation,
the third man is actually...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Here's the important part.
P.S.
I saw Robin board the eleven o'clock train,
so I'll get on, too.
What?!
Sanji got on the train?!
And... Usopp, too?!
Also, a big thug with a pompadour...?
That's gotta be Franky.
Right, there's no one else.
A fourth man...
And to think that the fifth man is Franky...
Poor Mr. Paulie...
Maybe it'd be better if he threw in the towel...
What's with you guys?!
Um... also, this was with that letter.
I should be able to find
a transponder snail on the sea train.
I'll touch base as soon as I can.
I got this baby transponder snail in town.
I want you to always keep it with you.
That's right.
Think of it as your dear, beloved San–
I see. So he'll call this one.
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Then he foresaw where
Nico Robin was going to be?
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
That's amazing!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
Yeah!
If you're not Nami,
don't. Dumbass.
For the time being, at least Sanji's with Robin.
We'll find a way to Enies Lobby, too!
Man...
I can't even have a smoke here.
Is that right?!
So Sanji went to the station after that?
Yep!
And Usopp is with them.
What a relief...
But anyway, no matter how
we follow the sea train,
we can't do anything
until we find Luffy and Zoro.
Okay, got it!
I'm certain which direction they flew.
Search those areas!
Everyone, please help us out!
Guys!
We're counting on you!
– Yeah!
Leave it to us!
Now, what's the best way to sneak in?
Whoa! What a crazy storm outside!
Collier Shoot!
Who are you?!
Hold it.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move!
I saw his kick.
He's no ordinary civilian!
Oh, please...
If you keep complimenting me...
you'll make me blush.
That wasn't a compliment!
He's mocking us!
Hey! Report to Agent Lucci
that we have a suspicious intruder!
Wait!
This isn't something we need
to bother CP9 with, is it?
No matter how violent the suspicious
man is, there's no need to fear,
because in this car–
Whoa! It's smoky!
CP6 Intelligence Agent, Jerry
Karate Island Native
...you've got me!
Jerry, sir!
I'm the champion of a South Blue island
that's famous for its karate.
That's right.
I'm a boxing champion!
Not a karate champion?
Save your jests until you've seen my punches.
That's cruel!
Jerry...
Aurora Flicker...
Jab!
J-Jerry, sir! Behind you!
He escaped?
Hey, kid!
Just because I'm tall, you don't think
this tiny car is a problem for me, do you?
Can't say someone's ever
warned me from between their legs...
My boxing actually works better
in narrow spaces!
Try my yoga style!
Yoga one, two!
One, two!
Your reach shortened!
Just what I wanted you to think.
Screw...
Drop Kick!
You're not even boxing anymore!
This is a waste of time.
Brochette!
From the very back, the one leading
the government officials in car seven is...
They get stronger from there.
The one who leads forty Marines
in car five is T-Bone,
a Marine Headquarters' captain
and a former knight.
Next up, in car four is Wanze,
a martial artist from Cipher Pol No. 7
who is also the head steward on this trip.
Finally, in car three we have Nero,
the newest member of CP9.
Anyway, though we are escorting criminals,
there's no possibility of a raid.
But just in case, we have military
power ready in each car, so...
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
We're on your side!
Come out!
Straw Hat, where are you?!
Foreman, it's hard to move, huh?
Take a break, will you?
Idiot! This is nothing.
Hurry up and find those two!
Yes, sir!
Has someone told
Mr. Iceburg what's going on?
Two men went to report to him.
Where are you going?
Mr. Iceburg...
Roronoa!
Straw Hat!
Answer if you hear us!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Where are you?!
Food... you say?
That's right. We need meat!
Lots of meat! Bring as much
as you can get! Hurry!
But why are we being bossed around like this?
No, we're not doing it for her.
We're doing this for Mr. Paulie, who's devoted
to her even after getting dumped!
Yeah!
Even so, that girl must be really hungry.
She's a growing girl, I bet!
Rain...
This is bad.
The wind was already making
it hard enough to smell...
Say, we've been yelling for a while,
but we haven't heard a peep back.
You don't think...
Don't talk like that! Just do your best!
Where are you guys? Luffy... Zoro...
That leopard guy couldn't
have taken you out, right?
We finally know why Robin left us.
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
Answer us!
Just wait, Robin.
We'll rescue you no matter what!
Hey, what's the matter?!
Oh, Mr. Paulie! Look over here!
The more the water ebbs,
the bigger the returning wave becomes.
If you see how the tide ebbs,
you can tell the scale of the storm surge.
I'm being blown away!
Now, if we try to see how much lower
the water level goes this year...
Look at that, Chimney.
Wow, that's crazy!
It's as though the sea has dried up.
Throughout my long life,
I've never seen anything like this.
Can the tide ebb this much?
I've never seen something like this before.
Just how big is this next wave about to be?
The Backstreets are gonna be
completely swallowed up.
There's no one left down there, right?
I hope not, or they're fish food!
The roar of the sea...
It stopped.
Oh?
Grandma! Look, look!
There's something over there!
You don't say?
There's something between two houses!
Hey! Look! Look! Look there!
Miss Kokoro!
Oh, you're that pirate girl.
Pirate lady!
Hey, look!
There's something over there!
Something over there?
Just what is it you're
going on about, Chimney?
Hold on...!
What's with this dried-up sea?!
Luffy...!
That straw hat...
Isn't that the next King of the Pirates?
Right?
That imbecile...!
H-Hey! Where are you going?!
Don't go down to the Backstreets!
Are you trying to get yourself killed?!
Aqua Laguna is already coming!
Come back!
This is bad!
That pirate woman went down the stairs!
Hey! Come back!
Don't go down there!