Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Gaijin
Mummy
Seize Straw Hat Luffy!
Here they come.
Imagine the haki...
flowing through my body.
You're mine!
Damn, that's not it!
Go to hell!
It's so weird.
I'm just not getting it.
This surface-level haki
won't bring down Kaido.
I've gotta get the haki
to flow into my enemies.
If I could get the haki to flow,
I could smash through even Kaido's thick skin.
Oops! I pushed too hard!
You've done it now!
Damn! That's just not it!
But...
I've still got a lot of sparring partners.
I won't stop until I master ryuo!
Sir Straw Hat sure is a persistent man.
Let's go, Chopperemon-san!
Okay.
We should help Olin-san!
What?!
No way! Don't worry about Olin!
I'm glad she's gone!
Luffytaro though...
We should help him, Kiku!
Why won't he run already?
Let's go!
Certainly!
Warden, should I throw the prisoners
in their cells before they get any ideas?
Good thinking.
Luffytaro is something else.
Yeah, he's a powerhouse.
This could be it...
The guards are stretched thin.
We could do it.
No need to worry.
Counter poison with poison.
Daifugo, get the weapon ready.
"The weapon" you say?
Got it...
Prisoners, listen carefully!
Your fellow prisoner Luffytaro is
out of control and making trouble.
You know what that means, right?
What is he up to?
Go do everything you can to restrain Luffytaro!
Huh? You've gotta be kidding.
There's no way they'll listen to you.
What?
Wh-Wh-Whaaat?!
Stop it!
I'm on your side!
Do you wanna escape or what?!
Well, we've had it with the guards!
It's true that your rampage
brought us some relief!
But escaping from here won't bring
Kaido and Orochi's reign to an end!
We fought to avenge
Lord Kozuki Oden's death!
But that pirate Kaido...
...slaughtered our families and friends
and beat us into submission!
Lord Yasuie's execution
brought back the fear and despair
of our past failure.
We leave here, and we've got
nowhere to go and nothing to eat.
There's no liberty anywhere in this country anymore!
That's right!
You might as well lay low here!
Don't be selfish!
You're the one being selfish!
Being a stranger from overseas, you can escape and rampage about as you like,
but don't get us involved!
Don't give us... any more false hope...
dammit!
You guys...
Are you all right?
Hey, hang in there!
Hey, this is no time for you
to be worrying about others.
Hot... It's so hot!
Help me...
Whoa!
What's wrong?!
What's this crap?!
I told you to worry about yourselves!
It's a contagious plague.
Touch it and you'll get it.
They're an example to the rest of ya!
Start acting strange,
and I'll shoot you with an infected round!
His Awesomeness Queen loves his inventions.
His interests lie in making
trick weapons and pathogens.
Oh, it's so hot.
Have one of
His Awesomeness Queen's...
excite rounds!
Straw Hat, did you really think
the prisoners would fight on your side?!
Too bad we've already broken their rebellious spirits!
Shut up!
You'll never hit me with that!
Look around, idiot!
It's gonna spread regardless of who I hit!
Hey, get away from me!
He'll infect you all!
It doesn't matter.
We'll meet our end here.
Damn! If only I could tell them everything,
they'd change their minds!
It's over, Straw Hat!
Hey, Straw Hat boy, just let
the fish outta the net already.
Let them know there is hope.
That we have this one last chance to bring down Kaido.
The voice is coming from the sealed cell.
He's a stubborn bastard.
Warden, wasn't some kind of beast in there?!
That's right, you guys never knew.
There was no beast locked in that cell.
We were told feeding that guy fish
from the factory runoff would kill him.
Lord Orochi gave that order 13 years ago,
intending to execute the bastard.
We couldn't disobey an order
from Lord Orochi, so we let him live.
We should have just
killed him from the start.
The man in that cell...
is one of the Nine Red Scabbards!
What?! Really?!
I thought they were all dead!
Kill him!
Make it look like an accident!
That laugh...
I have no doubt; that's Kawamatsu-san!
Hey!
Kawamatsu-san!
I am on my way!
There he is, the little dirtbag.
He's one of the legendary Nine Red Scabbards?!
I'll take the credit for the kill!
That really hurts!
What is that? A needle?!
No, it's a fishbone.
Uh... Uh-oh!
The intruder has escaped!
Kawamatsu!
Your handcuff keys and sword!
You're just in time, Raizo!
I've missed you, my beloved sword:
Sotomuso!
Gentlemen,
do you like sumo wrestling?
Kawamatsu-san,
help is coming!
Put some spirit into it!
I'm still in this!
Yagura Ryuo!
What the...?
First one to fly loses.
Your form is as good as ever, Kawamatsu.
That ability...
What a relief.
You bastard!
Like swimming in the rapids of a great river.
It is known as
Kappa Style:
Reprisal River!
Were those poisoned fish palatable?
They made me nauseous
and my bowels turn.
However, they kept me alive for 13 years!
This burden is but a gentle breeze
in light of my grief for my lord.
I have waited for this moment!
Kawamatsu the Kappa has joined the battle!
Kawamatsu-san!
Is that Kiku?!
You haven't changed a bit!
I'm so glad to see you alive!
Raizo, I feel the same.
Huh? Kiku?
When did you arrive?
What's going on?!
Who's that guy with the huge head?!
He's the intruder!
He stole the keys and sword from the tower!
What the hell are you waiting for?!
Seize them already!
Yes, sir!
What the hell did you come back for?!
Kawamatsu-san...
Are you okay, my friend?
I'm so sorry.
I've been nauseous for 13 years!
Prepare the excite rounds.
We will finish them off.
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Step away from Luffytaro-san!
Kiku! Raizo!
Whoa, old man!
Could you really be Boss Hyogoro?!
Yes, I am.
But more importantly, Kiku, Raizo,
tell them who you are!
You cannot inspire those who
have had their hearts broken
or those who have
faced defeat in battle
from behind a mask!
You are indeed
Boss Hyogoro.
You are absolutely correct.
We must first earn their trust.
We are nothing but ghosts
without revealing our identities.
It couldn't be... that face...
Isn't he the warrior thought
to have died at Oden Castle,
the most beautiful swordsman in Wano,
Kikunojo of the Lingering Snow?!
What?! You're a man?!
I am a woman at heart.
That mask is scary!
And that's...
Fukurokuju's rival ninja,
Raizo of the Mist!
And there's the samurai Yokozuna Kawamatsu,
the greatest sumo wrestler of all time!
That old man alongside them must be
the real Hyogoro the Flower!
So,
who the hell is Luffytaro?
Whatever, that's an amazing group!
What?! What about me?!
This has turned out just like Lord Orochi's ravings!
We've got to warn Kaido somehow!
No.
Now that you have seen us, you will need to stay silent.
Take them down!
Ninpo: Flower Shuriken!
Heavy Gong!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Eat this excite round!
What?!
We can't hit him with the excite rounds,
Vice Warden Daifugo!
Are you an idiot? I told you,
it doesn't matter who you hit!
Those bastards!
They're shooting the starving prisoners!
I can't let you use a virus as a weapon!
Hold it! We won't let you get
in Vice Warden Daifugo's way!
Let's go, Chopper!
All right!
Gum-Gum...
Heavy Stamp!
Leave our countrymen alone!
As he said!
She's a demon!
Kappa Style:
Yorikiri!
Ninpo: Lightning Shuriken!
Use these, Master Luffy's friend.
Friend?!
One of them should work.
Damn.
I've been shot.
It's hot! It's so hot!
Help me or it'll spread!
Stay away from me!
Ahh, hot, hot, hot!
Damn, those bastards are just
aiming at the prisoners!
Oh, that's right.
I forgot to mention one thing.
The disease's name.
A high fever spreads
from where the bullet hits.
Burning pain radiates throughout the body.
Ahh, it's hot!
Victims spew blood.
Then, they wander about in constant pain.
That pain infects others indiscriminately.
Help me...
No, don't touch me!
It hurts...
Let go!
Behold!
That's what becomes of the infected!
Help me...
They're like dried-up, rotten plants!
Help me!
Stay back. Don't come close.
That is...
His Awesomeness Queen's masterpiece!
The disease is called "mummy"!
Go!
You are now human weapons capable
of defeating enemies with a single touch!
We can't let it spread!
Everyone, you need to stop moving!
I'll handle this somehow!
I will cure every one of you!
Move along, prisoners.
Or do you wish to be considered rebels?!
Dammit!
They're not stopping.
In the end,
everyone in Udon is against us!
Get outta here.
If you hadn't come,
we'd have never met this fate!
Even if you're all... truly...
the Red Scabbard samurai...
who were thought to have died 20 years ago,
you'll never win!
Kaido,
that giant flying dragon,
the Beast Pirates—
no one can defeat them!
Look at us.
Just one of Kaido's subordinates created one weapon...
and brought this menace!
This hopeless threat!
That's right.
If you strangers hadn't come,
we'd have been able to maintain our daily routine here in Udon!
We'd have never had to go through this!
No, Luffytaro-san!
Don't touch them!
Stop! All of you!
You idiot! You infected yourself!
Is he stupid?!
Stop already!
You'll die!
Wh-What are you doing, Master Luffytaro?!
Sir Straw Hat!
What "menace"?!
What "hopeless threat"?!
This shitty disease
doesn't hurt me at all!
Liar!
Get away from them!
Luffy!
All the samurai that I know
are tough bastards!
But you guys...!
Your hearts have been shattered to pieces!
What the hell is your "daily routine"?!
Is your routine to do
as you're told, get your dango,
and live as they tell you?!
Wake up!
You're nothing
but slaves!
Big Bro and the others are okay!
Are they okay?!
What's wrong with me
coming from another country?!
What's wrong with a stranger
defending this land?!
I made a promise!
I promised... my friend...
who gave me her own food in Kuri!
I will make this a country
where everyone can eat their fill!
I'm gonna make this normal for you!
Before we leave this country,
we'll make it a place where you
can eat as much as you want!
Big Bro!
I'll keep that promise!
If I don't, this country
will remain hell!
I heard about Oden.
He was amazing!
But the day Kaido killed him 20 years ago,
this country stopped moving forward!
We came to defeat Kaido!
I don't need allies
who just get in my way!
So, now's the time for you to decide!
Are you with us?!
Or with Kaido?!
Are you serious?
You'd give us...
another chance?
He's won their hearts!
What a commanding presence!
We've got a problem.
He's gone and stirred their hearts.
But if I fire into that gaping hole,
they'll all panic,
flipping the situation to our favor.
I'll scatter 200 doses of the virus
using this excite shot!
Eat a big bowl of elephant snot!
No way, Warden! That's too much!
No, please don't!
Hey, Babanuki looks like he's
about to fire something over here.
What?!
It's too late!
Elephant Achoo!
What?!
What?! What?! What?!
I had to. I saw a pretty bad future.
Warden Babanuki!
Warden!
What a...
dependable man!
I'll leave the rest to you.
We'll handle it!
Hey, wait!
You better remember!
What happens if you defy the guards?!
First, we cut off both your arms!
We know. It doesn't matter.
We've already decided to revolt!
Thanks for everything, bastards!
Here we go!
All right!
Eight days until the final battle...
Without a word to the enemy's main army,
Udon has been conquered!
That was brilliant, Sir Straw Hat!
You've brought us quite the reinforcement,
Kin'emon!