One Piece
Wano Arc
Video Editing
Meggo
Timing
PhosCity
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
Gaijin
Shimotsuki Yasuie, the Daimyo of Hakumai
Flower Capital
How could she just die?!
Lady Komurasaki!
We need to see you again!
This isn't the oiran's procession
I wanted to watch.
Where are you taking Lady Komurasaki?!
She defied Lord Orochi.
She will receive a criminal's cremation
at Rasetsu Prison.
Ebisu Town
They caught Tonoyasu?!
What in the world is going on?!
To think Tonoyasu-san
was Ushimitsu Kozo!
Ushimitsu Kozo...
Night by night, the master thief
stole treasures from the rich
before distributing them
to the poor and the vulnerable.
A thief?!
That old fogey?
Ushimitsu Kozo...
The Flower Capital was abuzz with his name.
I don't get it.
Wasn't he some kind of saint?
Tonoyasu-san !
Why is everyone laughing?!
Your man is getting crucified!
Is Tonoyasu-san really Ushimitsu Kozo?!
Even if it were true,
it wouldn't matter.
I remember him!
It was that hair.
Tonoyasu is an alias.
Then just who is he?
Bakura Town
Kuri
It looks like something big
is going down in the Flower Capital.
Turn on the light-scroll snail.
Udon
You know him?
Y-Yes. I know him well.
That man...
He was Lord Oden's peer and one of the
daimyo who served the Kozuki Clan.
His true name was...
Shimotsuki...
Lord Yasuie!
Yasu the Hedgehog,
the daimyo of Hakumai.
He was a stern man who never smiled.
I didn't recognize him
because he was nothing like his old self!
Stop the execution!
I'm from Hakumai.
I'm glad you survived!
Release Lord Yasuie now!
You damn bureaucrats!
Prisoners' Quarters
Rasetsu Town
Flower Capital
Prisoners' Quarters
Rasetsu Town
Flower Capital
Lord Yasuie!
I guess they haven't forgotten me after all.
How delightful!
Hakumai
Wano
Hakumai is the only region
in Wano with an official port.
It brings both good and bad visitors.
Thus,
we must have an indomitable army.
Shimotsuki Yasuie
(Later Known as Tonoyasu)
Daimyo of Hakumai
I'd expect nothing less
from Wano's finest samurai.
Want a bite?
Are you mocking me, Oden?
Your loitering here is wearisome.
At least in name, you are the shogun's son.
They threw me out.
I'm not sure if they still consider me family.
Everyone's talking about it.
"Oden won't succeed
Kozuki Sukiyaki once he passes.
It'll be Shogun Yasuie."
You idiot!
Ow!
What was that for?!
Don't take these idle rumors to heart!
You're the one who'll lead the Kozuki Clan.
Lord Sukiyaki disowning you
was just tough love.
Why not show him what he wants?
Yasu-san,
I'd rather try my luck at sea.
Why isn't that allowed in this country?
This isolationist policy...
Damn these constraints!
Quiet!
Only a respectable warrior
is allowed selfish whims!
That hurts! Stop hitting me!
Who do you think I am?!
You're still a nobody.
Just some delinquent.
It's no use, my friends!
Orochi won't let me go.
But first, there are two things
for which I must apologize.
And I also have one thing to say
to that fool Orochi!
Toko!
Once I've said my piece, I'll cross
to the other side with a smile on my face.
Daddy!
I will now state the charges against the accused.
This man committed theft
in the capital last night.
Sinking to the dregs of society,
he now makes his living as a jester
in Ebisu Town. Once the daimyo of Hakumai,
he was known as Shimotsuki Yasuie.
For the grave crime of once
leading an army against Lord Orochi,
he has been sentenced to an ignominious death,
in sacrifice to Oiran Komurasaki.
Now, he has confessed...
to being Ushimitsu Kozo,
a known troublemaker in the land of Wano.
I lied about that!
What did you say?!
I figured I was going to die,
so I said that to draw attention to myself.
I'm sorry about lying.
I'm not the hero you thought I was.
Lord Yasuie!
Why would he lie about that?
The commotion around Komurasaki's funeral
has shifted its focus to Yasuie's execution.
Drake-san, the Ebisu townspeople
are barging into the Flower Capital!
What?!
That man appears to be
more important than we imagined.
Flower Capital
Entrance
You can't die, Yasu-san !
Yasu-san !
We'd be lost without your support!
You don't have permission to enter the city!
Go back to Ebisu Town, damn peasants!
Yasu-san !
There's unrest among the residents of Main Street!
Same in the Western Quarter!
One problem after another.
Lord Orochi's decision to broadcast the
execution via light-scroll snail may backfire.
Maintain vigilance throughout the city.
The lord shogun is incompetent, which means
his retainers have their work cut out for them.
Listen, my friends!
Behold, the lovely Flower Capital!
What a splendid land Wano is!
This landscape is the product of
generations of work by the Kozuki Clan
and the common people.
We should be proud!
Hurry!
Get a move on!
He's started spouting nonsense!
You have no right
to take credit for this beauty,
Kurozumi Orochi!
Can you hear me, Orochi?!
The vast forests, grasslands,
rivers,
and villages:
You stained it all with your greed-spawned sludge!
You're nothing but a vermin!
Damn you!
Holdem, you pissant!
How dare you set fire to my hideout!
Where are you?! Get out here!
Holdem!
What's going on?!
That's enough, Lord Yasuie!
You won't be able to take it back!
Now,
I have an apology for everyone.
Recently, a rebus has been
making the rounds.
The Kozuki name's been dead 20 years.
We no longer have the strength
to avenge them.
I was feeling remorse for the Kozuki Clan,
so I designed that rebus!
What?!
The image is meaningless.
It was
only a prank!
Really?!
What the hell's he sayin'?!
There you are, Ashura.
Oh, Kin'emon! Inuarashi!
This is big!
Look!
Lord Yasuie appears to have survived.
Yes, I just found out myself.
This is getting out of hand.
Oden died 20 years ago.
Orochi spoke to us,
the four remaining daimyo.
"Will you serve the Kurozumi?
Or will you fight us?"
How laughable!
You owed a great debt to Oden,
yet you usurped the shogunate
through a devious scheme!
Who would acknowledge you ?!
The daimyo and people from each region
immediately took up arms.
We were unfortunately routed
by the monster known as Kaido,
so Wano burned to the ground.
Fate being cruel,
I survived and hid away in Ebisu Town.
However, it'd be a shame to die of old age,
so I thought up the rebus stunt
and devised a plan worthy of a younger man.
I hope you can forgive me.
Nevertheless, Orochi's cowardice
surpassed all expectations.
He seems to have imprisoned innocent people
simply because of their moon tattoos.
What?!
Was Lord Orochi somehow deluded?
What should we do?!
We've arrested so many!
Lord Orochi has arrived!
You bastard, Yasuie!
I'm gonna fill you with lead!
There you are.
Long time no see, Orochi.
Any last words, Yasuie?!
Orochi! I suppose so.
Shall I recite the curse that has haunted you?
For a man of small stature
Ne'er in a lifetime
Has any hope to handle
What it takes to be Oden!
Well, that's it.
I wish you luck, Kin'emon
and the Red Scabbards.
And to you, Momonosuke,
the future shogun.
You have a clean slate for your plan.
I provided a new rendezvous point...
for our comrades imprisoned in Rasetsu.
There's nothing more I can give
with this life of mine.
Is he sacrificing his life
to give our operation a chance?
Lord Yasuie!
We are forever in your debt!
No matter how much
that coward Orochi hollers,
his soldiers will no longer be swayed.
A shogun shouldn't act with such fear.
Stop it! They'll hear you!
Daddy!
Yasu!
No one's been able to
take down Kaido for 20 years,
but now's our chance!
Cover your children's eyes!
The last daimyo to serve the Kozuki...
No... The neighborly man of Ebisu Town
is heading off to the great beyond!
Yasuie!
Let's have a song!
♪ Here I go! ♪
Fire!
Hurry to Onigashima!
Avenge our lord's death!
I await the good news in the afterlife!
Hakumai
Wano
Why would you want to steal
this much money?
Lord Oden was broke!
If you're gonna kill us,
just do it already!
You hedgehog!
Damn you, Oden.
You certainly know how to pick them.
Listen up!
I'm giving you the money
you tried to steal.
What?!
Please rethink this, Lord Yasuie!
We won't be able to sustain
Hakumai's finances!
You all can have this too.
It's yours.
Even more money?!
Don't screw with me!
Is this a trap?!
Do you love Oden?
Of course!
We owe that man our lives and then some!
– That's right!
– Absolutely!
I see.
Then take this money,
make yourselves presentable, learn some
manners, buy some books, and study!
Having a bunch of low-life retainers like you
would only disgrace Oden!
He's the man...
who'll be Wano's shogun someday!
Those who serve him
must be Wano's best samurai!
Protecting your lord is a must.
You all will be the city's...
no, the country's guardians!
Got it?!
Lord Yasuie!
Daddy!
Otoko,
please forgive me, Otoko.
For leaving you without a father.
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Dad!
That's enough! Hold your fire!
Yasu!
Yasu-san !
These are the scum from Ebisu Town!
Remove them from the capital!
Yasu-san !
Lord Yasuie!
Daddy!
Daaad!
Da-... Daddy?
Yasu!
Are you finally dead, Yasuie?!
Lord Yasuie...
What are they doing?!
What...
in the world?
Someone has died.
What the hell's so funny?!
My daddy is dead!
Why you little!
Please wait!
They're all... crying.
What do you mean?!
The people of Ebisu Town
are always laughing.
Even in times of pain or sorrow,
they cannot express how they feel.
With the exception of laughter,
all their emotions have been stolen.
They can no longer do anything but laugh.
It's the fault of Kaido and Orochi...
for bringing the fruit known as SMILE!