Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
This weather's great!
If we hold course, we should
see the Marine base soon!
Wow, Koby! You're incredible!
We're really gonna get there?
Of course!
Sailors should at least
be able to navigate the seas!
This is no time
to be laughing, Luffy.
He's being held prisoner there.
The infamous Pirate Hunter...
Roronoa Zoro!
The man slashes up his marks
like a bloodthirsty beast.
People say he's a demon
in human form!
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Gaijin
Pepperjack
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
Feeso
JT-421
Ravenfire
Zenef
Translation
arch1t3cht
DemonRin
Funimation
arch1t3cht
DemonRin
Funimation
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
We made it! The Marine town!
The Pirate King
and the Master Swordsman
C-C'mon, Luffy!
You're not serious about him
joining your crew, are you?
I haven't decided yet,
but if he's a good guy, then–
He was captured
because he's not a good guy!
Mmm! Yum!
Can you tell me if Zoro's at that base?
I think the name "Zoro"
might be taboo around here.
Let's see the base anyway.
You wanna be a Marine, right?
Y-Yes... But I'm not really ready yet...
Rumor has it a guy named
Captain Morgan is at this base, and–
What a funny town!
No, it's weird.
Zoro's name I get, but why are they
afraid of a Marine captain's name?
I suddenly have
a bad feeling about this...
You sure they weren't
just really excited?
That clearly wasn't it!
Alright! We're here!
I finally made it!
I guess this is where
we part ways, Luffy.
We didn't know each other long, but...
There we go!
Luffy! What in the world
are you doing?!
Now, where's this demon?!
He wouldn't be out in the open.
I'm sure he's in a cell or something.
Found him!
Perfect!
See! There he is!
I'm telling you! He wouldn't be out...
"Pirate Hunter" Roronoa Zoro
A b-black bandanna and a bellyband...
That's R-Roronoa Zoro!
It'll be easy to get him out
if we untie those ropes!
D-Don't be stupid!
If he got loose,
what do you think he'd do?!
I bet he'd try to kill you, Luffy!
Don't worry! I'm tough!
Is this guy for real?!
Hey, you two!
You're annoying.
Beat it!
Luffy! You're a goner
if he joins your crew!
Oh, no! Luffy, you have to stop her!
She'll be killed!
What?
You must be hungry!
I made you some onigiri.
You got a death wish,
kiddo? Go home!
Mister, you haven't eaten a thing
this whole time.
Here! It's my first time making them,
but I worked real hard!
I'm not hungry!
Now, stop bugging me and leave!
B-But...
I don't want them!
Don't make me kick your ass!
Picking on little girls?!
Helmeppo
Captain Morgan's Son
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro.
What's with that
weird guy down there?
Thank goodness!
He must be with the Marines!
That girl will be in good hands!
Oh? Well aren't those some tasty-looking onigiri?
Don't...!
It's too sweet!
You made them all sugary!
Onigiri are best with salt! Salt!
But I thought sweet
might taste better...
Take this! And this!
Stop it! Stop it!
H-How can he be so cruel?
I-I worked so hard
to m-make those...
Didn't you get the memo?
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
"Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
–Captain Morgan of the Marines."
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
- Captain Morgan of the Marines
MARINE
Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
MARINE
Those caught aiding
So, even the brats here know
how scary Daddy can be.
"Daddy"?
Then he's Captain Morgan's son!
You. Throw the kid over the wall.
Sir?!
I said, throw her over the wall!
Got a problem following orders?
Don't make me tell Daddy!
Y-Yes, sir... Right away!
No!
Th-Thanks...
Are you okay, Luffy?!
Are you all right?!
What a horrible guy...
Does anything hurt?
Damn you.
You sure are stubborn
about staying alive.
Yeah! I'm gonna
survive the whole month!
Well, good luck with that.
Only ten more days!
Assuming you live that long!
What drives someone
to be so cruel, Luffy?!
He's gone?!
I hear you're a bad guy.
What are you still doing here?
Getting put out here for all to see...
Are you really that strong?
What's it to you?!
If it were me, I'd probably
starve to death in three days!
Then you lack spirit.
I will live through this...
I swear it!
You're a pretty weird guy!
Wait!
Could you... get that for me?
You're gonna eat this?
It's more of a mud ball now.
Just shut up and give it here!
Told you so.
It was good.
Thanks for the food.
Really?!
Yeah! He ate every last bite!
I'm so glad!
But then, is Zoro really
as bad as they say?
He's not!
After all, he let himself
get tied to that cross in my place...
Huh? What do you mean?
It's all that Helmeppo's fault.
He's Captain Morgan's son...
Outta the way!
Make way for my precious,
adorable, little pooch!
Get in the way,
and you get executed!
No! Stop that!
Hey, you!
You got some kinda problem
with my adorable pooch?!
Rika! Stop that!
We'll get in trouble!
Oh, crap!
He's in for it now!
Helmeppo punches
and kicks him while he's tied up!
I... I...
So that's what's happening.
I'm hungry! Let's get a free meal!
Hey! Bring me a drink!
Oh, yes.
To alleviate my boredom,
I'll have Zoro executed tomorrow.
Save the date, everyone!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
Luffy! Please stop!
This guy's scum!
Y-You hit me!
I'm Captain Morgan's son, you know!
So what?!
When I tell Daddy, he'll execute you!
Fight me yourself!
Luffy! Calm down!
Do you want the Marines
as your enemy?!
I've made up my mind, Koby!
I'm... gonna get Zoro
to join my crew!
I am...
great!
Yes! You're exactly right,
Captain Morgan, sir!
Then why are the recent tributes
to me falling short?
W-Well, the citizens' wallets
do have their limits...
It's a matter of respect.
Wouldn't you agree?
Daddy!
I want you to kill someone for me!
You again? You've got
nothing but free time.
I'll untie you if you join my crew.
Say what?!
I'm looking for people
to join my pirate crew.
Forget it! I'm not desperate enough
to become an outlaw!
Screw that!
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
Pirates are despicable!
Who'd wanna be one?!
Oh, gimme a break!
You're already known
as an evil bounty hunter!
People can say whatever they want,
but I've never done anything I regret.
I will live through this...
and achieve my goal.
Oh? I see.
But I've already decided
that you're joining my crew!
Like it's up to you!
So you're a swordsman?
Yeah. But that idiot son
took my stuff...
I'll go get it back for you!
What?!
You'll get your sword
when you join my crew!
Don't screw with me!
He's going in all by himself?!
All right! Keep it steady!
Stand it up in one shot!
Daddy! Won't you go
and avenge me?!
That guy hit me in the face!
Not even you've done that!
Do you know why I've never
hit you before?
Do you?
Sure... It's because I'm–
Yes. Because you're...
"Axe-Hand" Morgan
Marine Captain
a hopeless son that's not even worth hitting!
Let's get one thing straight!
The only great one
around here is me! I'm great!
By the way, I heard a rat snuck
onto the crucifixion grounds.
I-I-I mean, there was that one runt,
but I saw to her punishme–
You killed her, I hope?!
N-No! I mean,
she was just a little kid...
You, there!
Go to town and execute her!
Y-You can't mean that, sir!
She's just a little girl!
I can't in good conscience...
Anyone who disobeys my orders
is a traitor, even little brats.
B-But... I can't do it!
Lieutenant!
Y-You didn't have to go that far!
I ascended to the rank of captain
with nothing but my own strength.
Listen up! In this world,
rank is everything!
Captain is the top rank on this base,
which makes me superior
to everyone here!
In other words, everything I do is just!
Right, you maggots?!
Yes, sir!
You're absolutely right!
We can execute the brat later.
Now watch! After years of
construction, it's finally complete!
The symbol of my authority!
Now, raise it up!
Display my greatness
at the apex of this base!
That's weird. There's no one here...
If I find the idiot son,
he can lead me to Zoro's sword.
Pull! Pull!
You there!
You bumped it, didn't you?!
I heard something up there...
I-I'm sorry, sir! I was careless!
I told you this statue embodies me!
The slightest scratch or speck of dirt
is the same as treason!
I'll check it out!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
Now you pay!
I jumped too far!
What is that?!
It flew up from below!
Got it!
Sorry...
Seize him! I'm going to kill him!
– Right away, sir!
Daddy! That's him! He punched me!
Oh! It's you!
I've been looking for you!
Come with me!
I need you to return something!
Let me go!
– Master Helmeppo!
After him! Don't let him escape!
Captain! Someone's
on the crucifixion grounds!
What?!
It's one traitor after another...
You need to escape, Zoro!
You'll be killed
for doing that, you know!
I can't stand by and watch
Marines act like this!
I want to be an honorable Marine!
Stop! I'm not running!
In just ten more days–
Your execution is tomorrow!
What?!
Helmeppo never intended
to honor your agreement!
So Luffy got angry and clocked him!
He did?
And now the Marines are after Luffy.
I won't ask you to be a pirate...
but please, help Luffy!
He's the only one who can save you.
And I think, right now, you're
the only one who can save him.
Stop right there!
Where's Zoro's sword?!
I-I'll tell you! I'll tell you!
Just stop dragging me!
Alright! Tell me!
In my room... We just passed it...
What? Why didn't you say so?!
Now we gotta go back.
Halt!
Release Master Helmeppo!
No.
Shoot if you want!
No! Don't!
Move it!
For the crime of treason against me,
I sentence the two of you to death!
This the room?!
Bingo!
But there are three!
Hey! Which sword is Zoro's?
Oh, he passed out.
Koby!
You've caused
quite a disturbance here.
You and that straw hat kid
are plotting a coup d'état, correct?
I've always fought alone.
Unlike a certain bastard who hides
behind his terrified flunkies!
Roronoa Zoro...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
You may be strong, but that's
meaningless before my authority!
Aim!
I...
can't afford to die here!
That's the match!
The winner is Kuina,
with 2,000 wins and 0 losses!
D-Damn it...
You're still weak, Zoro.
You're such a disappointment...
especially for a boy.
Hey! Zoro isn't weak!
He's the strongest guy here!
He can even beat grown-ups!
But he's weaker than me.
Even with two swords,
a weakling's still a weakling.
You whine like puppies.
You losers should keep quiet.
Another defeat, Zoro...
even after you've come so far.
Sensei!
Are you giving her secret training
'cause she's your daughter?!
Don't cheat!
No, no. Of course I'm not.
Zoro has indeed improved,
but Kuina has grown stronger as well.
Zoro?
Zoro...
I'm gonna wash my face.
Damn it!
Why can't I beat Kuina?!
Why?! Why?!
I'm gonna be the world's
greatest swordsman! So why?!
Zoro?!
What are you doing out here?
Right back at you! What are you
doing here at this hour?!
I'm here to challenge you
to our 2,001st duel!
I intend to make this our last fight!
I'm going to end this!
Fight me with a real sword!
You have one, right?!
Against me?
Sure.
My 2,001st win.
Damn it!
I hate this!
I'm the one who should be crying.
Huh?
When girls grow up,
they're naturally weaker than boys.
It won't be long before
even you catch up to me.
You're always saying you'll become
the world's greatest swordsman.
But my father said that dream's
impossible for me because I'm a girl.
I understand...
I understand that's how it is!
But... But it's frustrating!
You're lucky, Zoro.
You were born a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman too!
My breasts are even starting to grow.
If only... If only I had
been born a man...
How can you cry like that
after you beat me?!
It's not fair! You're my goal!
Zoro...
Boy this! Girl that!
Is that gonna be your excuse
when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
You're insulting all my
hard training up till now!
So enough of that crap!
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
It's a race to see who makes it!
You dummy. You're so weak...
– It's a promise!
Gotta get stronger!
Gotta hold more swords!
If two's not enough, then I'll use three!
What do you guys want?
Kuina...
Kuina's dead...
Apparently, she slipped
and fell down the storehouse steps.
The storehouse?
She was looking for a whetstone
to sharpen her beloved sword.
What would she need that for?
I don't know...
She was just a child too.
Who knows why anyone does anything...
No one could predict
something like this.
People are... such fragile things, Zoro.
Sensei...
That sword... Let me... have it.
Kuina's sword?
I'll get stronger
for the both of us now!
I'll get so strong,
my name will reach the heavens!
I'm gonna be
the world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her...
I...
Yes. It's yours.
I leave Kuina's spirit
and dreams... with you.
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
Fire!
What are you–
Luffy!
Straw Hat?!
No way...
That won't work!
I told you I was tough!
Wh-Who the hell... are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who's gonna be
King of the Pirates!