Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
What a day!
It's gorgeous!
As long as we can stay on this heading, we
should reach the Marine base in no time at all.
[LUFFY]
Wow, Koby! You're great out here.
You mean we're actually gonna reach
the place we originally set out for?
[KOBY]
Of course. It's nothing.
I'm just using the skills
that every sailor should have.
[LUFFY laughing]
You know, there's really
nothing to be so giggly about.
Because... at the Marine Base...
[sinister string music]
they're holding
the great Pirate Hunter...
Roronoa Zoro.
[KOBY]
This is the man who's
diced up his bounties
like an animal bent on carnage,
a blood-thirsty beast.
He's been called nothing less than a living,
breathing demon in human form.
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
PamkinPinguin
Quality Control
Pepperjack
Villager
Westfal
Zenef
Pepperjack
Villager
Westfal
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Villager
Timing
Camotoy
Villager
Closed Captioning
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
Funimation
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
We're here!
The Pirate King
and the Master Swordsman
The Marine base city!
[whimsical orchestral music]
Luffy, seriously,
you're out of your mind
if you think the right thing to
do is get this guy to join you.
Well, I haven't made up my mind yet.
I gotta see if he's a good guy!
He's imprisoned
because he's obviously not!
[LUFFY]
Hey, is that guy Zoro
around here somewhere?
[WOMAN gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD whimpering]
Maybe we shouldn't mention
the name "Zoro" here, okay?
Let's head to the base
and check it out.
You wanna be a Marine, right?
Well, of course I do, Luffy,
but I really don't think I'm ready just yet.
From what I've heard, the man in charge
of this base is named Captain Morgan.
[CROWD gasps]
[CROWD whimpering]
[LUFFY laughs]
This town is such a weird place.
[KOBY]
That was odd.
I mean, I understand if
they're scared of Zoro,
but why did they flip when
I mentioned the Marine captain's name?
I don't know. I've got
a bad feeling about this.
[LUFFY]
Maybe they were all just jumpin'
around for the fun of it.
And how would that make any sense?
[LUFFY]
This looks like the place.
I made it...
[cries]
This is where you
and I part ways, Luffy.
We didn't have long together, but...
[LUFFY grunts]
Where's the foothold?
[KOBY]
Get down from there!
What're you doing?! They'll see you!
Now where's this demon?
[KOBY]
They wouldn't
keep him out in the open.
He's probably tucked in
a prison cell below ground.
[LUFFY]
There he is!
I'm gonna get closer!
Koby, look!
[KOBY sighs]
I'm telling you he's not–
[gasp]
[sinister orchestral music]
"Pirate Hunter" Roronoa Zoro
That hood on his head...
and a haramaki...
It's Roronoa Zoro!
If we untie those ropes,
he can just walk away!
Oh, don't be such an idiot, Luffy!
There's no telling what a bandit
like him will do if you let him go!
He might just kill us both!
Don't worry, I'm strong.
I can protect us.
[KOBY]
He's lost his mind!
[ZORO]
Hey, you two!
[KOBY screams]
You're an eyesore.
Get lost.
[KOBY screams]
Luffy, trust me, there's no chance you'll
survive with someone like him on your crew!
[puzzling music]
[RIKA]
Shh.
[KOBY gasps]
[KOBY yelps]
Luffy, we gotta stop her
or she'll be killed,
either by the Marines
or the demon himself!
[ZORO]
What do you want?
I thought you might
be getting hungry now,
so I made you
a couple of rice balls.
[ZORO]
You got a death wish, kid?
Just scram.
[RIKA]
But you haven't eaten anything
the whole time you've been tied up.
Here!
I've never really made them before...
but I did my best,
so I think they're fine.
Listen, kid, I'm not hungry!
Now stop irritating me,
and get outta here!
[RIKA]
But–
Do not make me kick
your ass, little girl!
[HELMEPPO]
Now, now.
No one likes a bully.
[ZORO growls]
[HELMEPPO chuckles] Roronoa Zoro,
Helmeppo
Captain Morgan's Son
you seem to be handling this well.
Don't you agree?
Hey, look. Now there's
another weird guy.
That's great!
He must be with the Marines.
Now we know the girl will be safe.
Looky, some tasty rice balls.
[RIKA]
That's not for you!
[HELMEPPO screams]
Too sweet!
They're packed with sugar!
You're supposed to use
salt, you idiot! Salt!
But I...
I thought they'd taste better sweet.
[HELMEPPO]
Gimme that!
[HELMEPPO grunting]
[RIKA]
No! Stop!
[RIKA] I worked so hard!
[KOBY gasps]
That's just awful.
[HELMEPPO grunts, sighs]
[RIKA crying]
But I...
[sobs]
worked so hard to make those...
Too bad...
You must've not read
the notice that was posted.
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
"Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed."
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
Signed, Marine Captain Morgan.
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
- Marine Captain Morgan
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
in any way will be executed!
MARINE
Those who assist criminals
[RIKA gasps]
[HELMEPPO laughs]
It seems even
little brats fear my daddy.
His daddy?
So that guy's father
is Captain Morgan?
You!
Toss this kid out right now.
[MARINE gasps]
I said, throw her over the wall, soldier!
Now if you won't follow my orders,
I'll tell my father.
Yes, sir! I-I'll do it!
[RIKA whimpering]
No!
[RIKA screaming]
[energetic music]
Thanks, mister!
[KOBY]
Luffy! Are you two okay?!
What about you, little girl?
Are you all right?
I can't believe how
wretched a person he is.
Now where are you hurt? Anywhere?
[ZORO]
Damn you.
[HELMEPPO laughing]
You're just dead set on
staying alive, aren't you?
[ZORO]
That's right.
And I'm gonna make it through
the month without any problems.
[HELMEPPO]
Right... Good luck with that.
[HELMEPPO cackling]
Only ten days left!
[HELMEPPO]
Oh, you still assume you'll make it
to the end of those ten days.
[HELMEPPO cackles]
[KOBY]
How can that man be so cruel?
Luffy?
Uh! What the...?
Where did he go?!
[ZORO gasps]
[LUFFY]
So, I hear you're a bad guy.
[ZORO]
Are you still here?
[LUFFY]
You're stuck out here for
all the world to see and nothing.
Are you really all that strong?
[ZORO]
Mind your own business!
[LUFFY sighs]
If I were you, I'd probably
starve to death in three days.
[ZORO]
I've got more spirit
than you could ever have...
which is how I'm gonna
survive this ordeal.
This I swear.
Hah, what a weirdo!
[ZORO]
Wait, hold on.
Could you...
pick that up for me?
You're gonna eat this?
'Cause it's mostly a ball of mud.
Shut up and give it to me, now!
[ZORO coughing]
Should've listened to me.
[ZORO]
It was good.
Thanks for the food.
[RIKA]
Really?
That's right!
He ate every last
grain of rice there was.
That's great!
I wonder if Zoro was really as
evil as everyone thinks that he is.
He's not!
He's good... because...
he got himself punished... for us.
[LUFFY]
You're, uh... You're making no sense.
[RIKA]
Sorry...
It's that dumb Helmeppo.
[sinister orchestral music]
He's the son of Captain Morgan.
[HELMEPPO]
Step aside! Step aside!
Make way for my beautiful pet doggy!
Anyone who doesn't move,
I'll have executed!
[HELMEPPO laughs]
– [WOLF snarls]
– [CROWD screams]
[RIKA screams]
[MAN screams]
Stop it, you mean ol' thing!
You, little girl!
Is there some kind of problem with
how my beloved dog is behaving?
Rika, put it down!
You don't want to get us in trouble.
[HELMEPPO snickering]
[RIKA screaming]
[HELMEPPO screams, gasps]
[CROWD chatters]
[RIKA]
Helmeppo keeps punching and
kicking him while he's tied up.
He's being so unfair!
I don't...
I don't know how to help him!
I see why you're upset.
[RIKA cries]
[glass shatters]
I'm hungry.
Bring us whatever you got
and keep the check for yourself.
And bring me a bottle of your finest
moonshine or whatever crap you serve.
I'm trying to think of
something interesting to do
seeing as how I'm bored
out of my skull here.
I suppose I can execute Zoro.
[HELMEPPO cackling]
[energetic music]
You... You just hit me!
[KOBY] Luffy, no!
[HELMEPPO whimpering]
You can't hit him!
[LUFFY] This guy is scum!
You actually hit me!
I am Captain Morgan's son, you know!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, like I care!
You'll care after
he executes you for this!
Why don't you just
be a man and fight?!
Luffy, just ease off some!
Why are you trying to get
on the Marines' bad side?!
[LUFFY]
I've made up my mind.
[KOBY gasps]
Today...
Zoro joins my crew.
[MORGAN]
I am...
great!
[MARINE]
Yes, sir!
You are right, Captain Morgan, sir!
[MORGAN]
And yet, the taxes we collect don't even
compare to my sheer degree of greatness.
Yes, right, sir.
I guess that the citizens' wallets
just aren't very deep these days, sir.
[MORGAN]
The issue at hand here
is their level of respect for me.
Wouldn't you agree?
[HELMEPPO sobbing]
Daddy!
[MORGAN]
Hm?
There's someone outside
that I want you to slaughter,
and I want it done now!
[ZORO sighs]
Huh?
[scoffs] You again...
Don't you have things to do?
[LUFFY]
I'll untie you, but only if
you promise to join my crew.
[ZORO]
Your what?
[LUFFY]
I run a pirate crew, and I'm
looking for people to join up.
No way!
I'd never stoop to
joining up with a criminal.
Screw that business.
And what's wrong with being a pirate?
[ZORO]
They're despicable!
Like I'd ever wanna join up with one.
Oh, come on! Gimme a break.
Everyone already knows you as some
vicious bounty hunter always out for blood.
People can say whatever
they want about me,
but I've never done a single
thing in my life that I regret.
I will make it through this challenge.
And after that,
I'll accomplish what I want.
Yeah... That's great.
But I've already decided that
you're going to be on my crew.
What?! You can't do that!
I hear you're one of
the best swordsmen around.
[ZORO]
Well, I am!
But that idiot Captain's son
took mine away.
Guess I'll just have to
go get it back for you.
[ZORO] What?
So if you want your sword,
you're just gonna have to join my crew!
Now you're really pissing me off!
[LUFFY laughs]
Wait, he's actually
gonna bust in there alone?
[MARINES]
Heave ho! Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
That's it! Stop right there.
Now stand it up in one final pull!
Well, dad?
Are you gonna get revenge
on this guy or what?!
I mean he just outright
struck me in public!
You've never hit me before!
Why should he be able to?
[MORGAN]
Do you have any remote idea
as to why I've never hit you?
Well?
Uh... Is it because
you think I'm great?
[MORGAN]
No...
...it's because...
[HELMEPPO screams]
[menacing orchestral music]
"Axe-Hand" Morgan
Marine Captain
[MORGAN] ...you're a stupid fool...
who isn't even worth hitting.
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
[HELMEPPO yelping]
The only great one around here
is the man you call your father!
[HELMEPPO groans]
[MORGAN]
Which reminds me.
I heard a rat snuck into
the crucifixion yard.
[HELMEPPO gasps]
Yes. That's right, the little girl,
b-but I-I had her dealt with.
I hope that means killed.
No, I... I didn't kill her.
She's just a kid...
[MORGAN]
You there!
Go into town,
find this girl, and kill her!
But... sir! You can't be serious...
She's just a little girl, sir.
[MORGAN]
I don't care if she's a child or not!
Anyone who disobeys
my orders is a traitor!
[LIEUTENANT]
No, sir...
I can't do it.
[HELMEPPO screams]
[MARINES]
Lieutenant!
You... You killed him!
My strength was what I used
to rise to the rank of captain.
Listen!
In this world,
titles are what matter!
That means by being the captain of
this base and the highest ranking officer,
I am the most superior person
as far as the eye can see!
This means...
that I do everything right!
Am I correct, men?!
Sir! You are correct, sir!
[MORGAN]
Let's put killing the girl
on hold for now.
Observe, the greatest symbol
of my unending authority.
It took years to complete,
but here it is.
Now stand it up!
[MARINES] Heave ho!
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
Display my greatness at
the top of this base for all to see!
[LUFFY]
That's weird...
There's nobody here.
I gotta find that crazy idiot son
and get Zoro's sword back for him.
Huh?
[MARINES]
Heave ho! Heave ho!
[MORGAN]
Pull, men!
Harder!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
[MARINE yelps]
[MORGAN]
You there!
[MARINE yelps, whimpers]
[MORGAN]
You bumped it.
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Sounds like something's
goin' on up there.
I'm sorry, sir!
I was reckless! I didn't mean it!
[MORGAN]
I consider the
slightest scratch on this...
nothing less...
than a traitorous activity
that's punishable by death!
[energetic string music]
Guess I should check it out.
Gum Gum...
Rocket!
– [MORGAN yells]
– [MARINE whimpers]
[LUFFY]
Huh-hoo!
Wah... I jumped too far!
[MORGAN]
Huh?
What is that thing?!
It flew up from the ground!
– [LUFFY] Got it!
– [MARINES gasping]
[MARINES screaming]
[MARINES grunting]
[MORGAN gasps]
[HELMEPPO, MARINES scream]
[LUFFY]
Sorry about that.
[menacing orchestral music]
Seize him and hold him,
so I can kill him myself!
[MARINES]
Sir! Right away!
That's him! That's the guy!
He's the one who punched me, daddy!
[LUFFY] Hey, it's you!
[screaming]
I've been looking for you
all over the place.
You have something
that I really need to get back.
[HELMEPPO] Let me go!
[MARINES] Helmeppo!
[HELMEPPO] Someone help me!
[MORGAN]
Do not let that man escape!
[MARINE]
Captain!
There's someone in
the crucifixion yard!
What?!
I'm surrounded...
by traitors.
[KOBY]
You have to get out of here, Zoro.
That maniac's going to kill you
for what you're doin' right now!
[KOBY]
I can't stand to watch the Marines
behave like this anymore.
A true Marine should be honorable.
Look, kid, I can't leave!
I got ten days left.
And, then they're–
Well, not quite. They're gonna
execute you tomorrow.
They're what?
[apprehensive string music]
[KOBY]
Helmeppo never intended
to honor your agreement.
He planned on
killing you from the start.
Which made Luffy really angry,
so he just knocked him out.
He did?
Now that the Marines are mad,
they're dead set on catching Luffy.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna ask
you to become a pirate, though.
But I hope you'll help him.
You have a lot of
strength you can offer.
Luffy's the only person here who can
actually save you from execution.
And of course...
you're the only one here who can
save him from a very similar fate.
[MORGAN]
End of the line!
[energetic music]
[HELPMEPPO screaming]
Okay, so tell me where
Zoro's sword is.
[HELMEPPO]
I'll tell you! I promise!
Just please stop dragging
me across the carpet...
Fine, which way?
In my room.
We just passed it,
behind you on the left.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Now we gotta go all the way back.
[MARINE A]
Don't move!
[MARINE B]
Except for letting Helmeppo go!
No way.
But you can try
shooting me if you want.
[HELMEPPO]
No! Please don't shoot!
Don't! Get the hell outta the way!
[MORGAN]
For the crime of treason against me,
I sentence you both
to die where you stand.
[KOBY yelps]
This looks like yours.
[LUFFY]
Bingo!
Hold on. There are three here.
Hey, weirdo, which one
of these is Zoro's?
[HELMEPPO whimpering]
[LUFFY]
Guess he passed out.
[gasps]
Koby!
[menacing orchestral music]
[KOBY whimpering]
You've been pulling some
interesting moves around here.
What is this?
Some kind of poorly executed coup
you two planned with the straw hat?
[ZORO]
I've always fought alone
like a real man does.
Not like a coward...
who hides behind his
wall of expendable cronies.
[MORGAN]
Roronoa Zoro.
Don't you dare underestimate me.
You may be a strong fighter,
but under my authority,
you're just the rat we
throw out with the trash.
Take aim!
[ZORO]
No...
I can't afford to die here!
[INSTRUCTOR]
Match over! And the winner...
Kuina! With 2,000 total
wins and zero losses.
[ZORO groaning]
Damn it.
[KUINA]
You're weak, Zoro.
Nothing ever changes.
You know, for a boy, you're pathetic.
But, Zoro isn't weak at all.
He's one of the strongest
out of all the guys.
[STUDENT C]
He's even beaten grownups.
–[KUINA] But...
–[STUDENTS whimper]
[KUINA]
He's nowhere as strong as me.
Even with two swords,
a weakling is still a weakling.
You losers would do good to
remember that and keep quiet.
Your howling makes you look even
more pitiful than you already are.
[KOSHIRO]
You've grown so strong, Zoro.
And yet, you continue to lose
every match against Kuina.
[STUDENT]
Sensei!
Are you giving her special training?!
She might be your daughter,
but that's not fair!
You shouldn't cheat!
Calm down. I've done
nothing of the sort.
You see, Zoro has grown stronger.
But, Kuina has continued
to grow stronger as well.
[STUDENT A]
Zoro!
[STUDENT B]
Zoro...?
[ZORO]
I'm gonna go clean up.
[water splashing]
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO]
Damn it! Why can't I beat Kuina?!
Why?! Why?!
I'm going to be the
strongest swordsman in the world!
So why can't I beat her?!
[apprehensive music]
[KUINA]
Zoro?
It's late out. What are you doing?
Funny. I was gonna ask
you the same question.
What are you doing out so late?
I've come here to challenge you
to your 2,001st fight.
And it's gonna be the last fight
you and me will ever have.
This ends tonight.
Fight me with a real sword!
You do have one, don't you?
Real swords...?
You're on.
[energetic orchestral music]
[ZORO grunts]
[KUINA grunts]
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO screaming]
[KUINA]
Ah!
Win number 2,001.
[ZORO crying]
Damn it!
I hate it!
[mournful string music]
[ZORO crying]
[KUINA]
I'm the one who should be
crying out of frustration.
Not you.
When girls grow up,
its natural for us to develop
into physically weaker
beings than men.
Even you will catch up
to me soon enough.
I've always heard you say to me,
you're gonna be the world's
greatest swordsman.
When I told my father the same thing,
he said I could never be that.
And I know. I know that. But...
It's just so frustrating.
You're lucky Zoro,
being born as a man.
All I ever wanted was to be
the world's greatest swordsman.
My breasts have even
started to grow out now.
If only...
If I had just been born a man!
[ZORO growls]
[ZORO]
Don't fly off at the mouth,
whining like that after you beat me!
Because it's not fair!
You're my goal!
You know how this
makes me feel?!
Zoro...
[ZORO]
Boy this! Girl that!
Are you gonna keep up that same
kinda talk after I beat you some day?!
Like skill is irrelevant!
That's just an insult to all of the training
I've been pouring on every day!
So don't say that crap, would ya?!
Now promise me...!
Promise me that someday one of us
will be the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete and see
who gets there.
Dummy. You're so weak.
[KUINA, ZORO]
It's a promise.
[ZORO]
Gotta get stronger so
I can hold lots of swords.
If two's not enough, I'll use three!
[ZORO]
What do you guys want?
Huh?
[STUDENT]
Kuina...
Kuina is dead, Zoro.
[sorrowful music]
[MAN A]
They said she slipped
and fell down the storehouse steps.
[MAN B]
Storehouse?
[MAN A]
Looking for a sharpening stone
for her beloved sword.
[MAN B]
What would she need that for?
[MAN A]
I don't know.
[MAN B]
She was just a child, too.
[MAN A]
Who knows why
anyone does anything.
There's no way to rationalize it.
[MAN B]
Guess you never know what's waiting
for you around the next corner.
[KOSHIRO]
It may appear otherwise
to the blind eye,
but people are quite fragile things.
[soft music]
[ZORO sobbing]
[ZORO]
Sensei...
I ask that you let me have that sword.
[KOSHIRO]
Kuina's sword?
I'll get stronger!
Stronger than she
ever was, you hear me?!
Strong enough that my name
reaches up to the heavens!
I am going to be
the world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her.
I promised...
I did...
[ZORO sobbing]
[KOSHIRO]
The sword is yours.
[ZORO gasps]
I leave her spirit and her dreams...
in your hands.
[ZORO whimpering]
[ZORO wailing]
Gum Gum...
Rocket!
Fire!
What?!
Luffy, no!
[MORGAN]
Straw Hat!
[MARINES gasping]
[LUFFY]
Heh.
See ya!
[LUFFY laughing]
[monumental orchestral music]
That won't work on me!
Told ya I was strong!
What the...?!
Who the hell are you?
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
And I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!