Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Graphics
Datenshi
Girl-Krillin
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Feeso   Gab   Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack   Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
Gab
Lance
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit   EvoWarrior5
themuffinman   Zenef
Translation
arch1t3cht   Crunchyroll
Gaijin   PamkinPinguin   rangicus
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Unprecedented
Hey, Gomorrah!
Why are you slamming into the walls?!
What's wrong? Did you
finally reach your limit?
Th-That's not it! He can't see!
With his retinas damaged,
his eyesight is weakening!
What?! You can't see?!
It set off in a crazy dash!
Keep them encircled!
Stop the monster!
What're you doing?!
Fire the trench mortars already!
Stop, Gomorrah!
You're in no shape to keep going!
He says that he promised Sodom!
He told Sodom, "Leave the rest to me!
I'll carry everyone for the both of us!"
G-Gomorrah...
They were inside its stomach?
I can't eat anymore. I'm full.
Take 'em back home as emergency food.
Bro! There's trouble!
Some pirates beat up Sodom and Gomorrah!
You've got some nerve
messing with my underlings!
Hey, you're injured!
Don't dance, Sodom and Gomorrah!
There's a dead end ahead!
He'll die if he crashes into it!
Gomorroah! Stop! Don't rush around blindly!
Stop!
A dead end?
Do you see one?
Nope...
I don't see anything like that.
It's the courthouse, Gomorrah!
W-We made it! Gomorrah!
Reporting to all units!
The pirates' king bull broke through
the encirclement in Block D!
Courthouse
Tower of Justice
They've reached the courthouse plaza!
Courthouse
Tower of Justice
I repeat! The pirates...!
Look at this, Funkfreed.
It's a golden transponder snail.
As it gives you the authority
to exercise a buster call,
you can't carry this glittering transponder snail
without authority from at least a Marine admiral.
In order for me to exercise a buster call,
Aokiji temporarily entrusted it to me.
Just wait and see!
Once the revival of the weapon becomes reality,
I'll hold this power at all times,
and I'll no longer have to obtain an admiral's
special permission just to control troops.
With the push of this one button,
an entire island will be wiped out.
Authority is like a weapon too, huh?
Chief Spandam!
That scared me!
What's your problem?!
Knock first!
I almost pressed the button!
I-I'm sorry, but I was told
that this is an emergency.
There's a call from Enies Lobby's main island.
What?!
A call?! They should've
called this room directly!
Th– Hey! The receiver is off the hook!
Who keeps doing that?!
You just said that there's
an emergency or something, right?
Yes, sir.
Spanda!
Hey, Nico Robin!
Apparently there's an emergency report
from Enies Lobby's main island.
It's probably not a real emergency,
but you can guess what it's about, right?
After he fought so hard
to beat five of my guards,
just picture poor little Straw Hat Luffy
being stomped into the ground
by our strongest gatekeepers, Oimo and Kashi,
along with the rest of your friends.
Let's listen together and hear what became of the idiots
who rebelled against the World Government!
You're a real scumbag!
Shut up, you punk!
Hey, guard!
Yeah, this is Spandam.
Oh! Is that you, Chief?!
Finally! I have a report you need to hear!
Wh-Where do I start...?
Calm down, you idiot!
It's about the Straw Hats, isn't it?
What happened since
the last report? Oh! Better yet...
just summarize the key points
and make it loud and clear!
Yes, sir! The invaders–
You accidentally killed them?!
Well, that's their own fault for being so weak–
Approximately sixty pirate invaders...
have breached the courthouse plaza,
the innermost point on the main island!
Calling all units on Enies Lobby's main island!
All soldiers! Head to
the courthouse plaza at once!
You really pulled through, Gomorrah!
I promise, you and your bro's
efforts won't go to waste!
Let's give 'em hell, boys!
We'll rescue Big Bro Franky!
– Yeah!
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
Can you see Luffy?
No.
The rooftop's a little high for us
to scale the side of the building.
Right. It's not like we're made of rubber.
How many CP9 members did you see?
We only saw the big horn guy.
It's so surreal to think Robin and Franky
are up there with them in such a place.
That aside, we have to hurry to Luffy!
Robin is running out of time!
Hurry to the courthouse plaza!
The drawbridge isn't down yet! Corner them!
Whoa! That frog's awesome!
That's the flail that
knocked out Gomorrah! What a beast!
Over there! They're running away!
I saw three of 'em!
They're running now?
But they attacked first!
You idiot!
It's a waste of time chasing after
each enemy who runs away!
Shut up. I just went to check.
It wouldn't hurt to know what kind of
enemies we're up against, would it?
– Whoa! He brought him down!
What is this guy?!
He's gotta be one helluva strong guy
to swing that thing around!
Does he belong to a special
unit like the Watchdogs?
There may be more hiding!
Be careful.
Let's scoot. The guards are closing in.
Corner them!
They'll never get those
heavy stone doors to budge!
Finish them here in the plaza!
Come to think of it, these doors are huge.
How will we...
get them open...?
Get a move on!
I'm going in!
H-He cut through that thick stone!
Zambai!
We gotta split up and head to either side
to pull both of the drawbridge levers!
O-Okay! You got this!
Okay! This means we split into three teams!
We're gonna clean up the courthouse,
so a few of you will come with me!
Good luck to the rest of you! Now go!
Courthouse
Tower of Justice
Huh?
Also, the giant gatekeepers, Oimo and Kashi,
went over to the pirates' side!
They're speeding down the main road
toward the courthouse!
Out of the way!
Guard casualties have reached...
over 2,000!
N-Not five...?
And the one who beat 1,000 all on his own,
Captain Straw Hat Luffy, suddenly disappeared...
but we're searching for him as we speak!
This has to be unprecedented—the worst
catastrophe in the history of Enies Lobby!
Blueno...
What's he doing over there?
What's going on?
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
Baskerville! Chief Justice Baskerville!
Come in! It's me!
– Whoa! Chief Spandam!
Courthouse
On the left: the Left Baskerville!
On the right: the Right Baskerville!
And in the center, I am...
"Alone and Unafraid Along the Central Main Line"!
– Just who is that?!
Give me a status report!
I heard that the pirates have
already made it to the courthouse plaza!
Status?
Hm, status...
As for the status...
The plaza aside,
the inside of the courthouse...
– ...is in a terribly horrible state!
What?!
Ch-Chief Justice! I have a report!
The pirates cut through the giant stone doors
and entered the courthouse!
– I can see that already, you idiot!
I thought we'd see more enemies in here.
Looks like the way is clear,
but what the heck is that?
What?! His head...!
It's like the story of the guard dog from hell!
Berberus?!
You mean Cerberus!
Men! Order!
This is a sacred chamber of law!
We will now cast judgment
on your inevitable fate!
All right, guys!
Get to the rooftop to join up with Straw Hat!
Yokozuna and the rest of us
will hold off enemies at the doors!
We've got your back,
so just keep pushing forward!
Got it.
Hey, look at that.
The trial just started.
Their crime is as follows!
First, the act of stepping into Enies Lobby,
Just ignore it! Which way do we go?!
which belongs to the World Government, is...
Straight ahead! There are stairs on both sides!
Follow them to the top!
All right!
How rude!
They ignored our sacred trial!
Unforgivable! They dare
disrespect the Judicial Island?!
Damn you! Die!
Wh-What's going on? His swords
look like they're bending!
Charming Demon Sleepless Night...
Oni Giri!
Is he the one who cut open the door?
Okay, let's go.
The path's wide open!
Yep!
How is a guy who's this
strong not the captain?
Wait! Wait! Wait! Outta my way!
Reindeer! Swordsmoron!
Bro with the suit...
This is dangerous enemy territory!
I'll clear the path so Nami can
move forward! Outta my way!
Hey, watch it!
What?! Why is he starting a fight?!
You want a piece of me, bastard?!
Shut up! You cretins are
not to get in Nami's way!
Nami, this way! Follow only me!
Hey, we came to rescue Robin, right?
That's right, Robin is waiting
for me to rescue her!
Could she be crying right now
out of loneliness?!
Seriously...
We look away for one second, and Zoro's...!
What?!
Wait, Zoro! That's the wrong way!
I said the stairs! Why the hell would you think
to go that way?! What fantasy world are you in?!
Shut up! It was because
you didn't explain it well!
There's no way it was my fault!
Zoro, I'll try making some medicine...
to cure idiocy.
Idio– Hey!
Chopper...
Yeah?
Robin my love! I'm coming now!
Make sure it works on that guy too.
Um... Okay, will do.
I wonder if Big Bro will come out of this alive.
When the going gets tough,
they're the ones that get the job done...
probably... I'm sure... yeah...
This is a grave crime.
A crime of the highest magnitude!
Then, we'll compromise and choose...
the death penalty!
– Agreed!
– I'm the chief justice. Don't ignore me!
Chopper. Nami. Go on ahead.
I'll follow you after I take care of this guy.
You think you can defeat me?
What a cocky pirate!
I'll show you how terrifying I can...
Pull!
S-Stop it!
– Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
S-Stop...
We'll take you on, Cerberus!
Franky Family!
Let's go!
– Ah... yeah.
Luffy vs. Blueno
Courthouse Rooftop
My face door finally closed!
Naturally.
An opened door
is meant to close.
I am surprised you could
dodge my tempest kick.
Yeah... because it's not that hard.
That's regrettable.
You jerk!
He jumped!
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
Iron Body: Smash!
Gum-Gum...
Bullet!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick!
He is perfectly keeping up with me.
He altered my tempest kick's course.
He has unbelievable physical abilities!
This won't do.
I'm no good like this.
When I lost to Aokiji, I thought,
"If I run into guys this powerful
on the sea ahead,
I won't be able to protect my friends...
unless I get much stronger."
I want my friends by my side,
even if they're not all as strong as me.
I've got to be stronger...
or I'll lose them all.
Then... what will you do?
I came up with a way
to fight with all my might...
so that I won't lose anyone...
so that no one will be taken away from me.
What is he doing?
What is happening inside his body?!
And now...
you won't be able to keep up anymore.
What?
My techniques will all evolve to a new level.
Gear Second!