Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
The Town of Beginnings and Endings
You raised your price again?!
This is way too much
for what I'm getting!
Raise it again
and I'll cancel my subscription!
What's the big deal?
The paper doesn't cost that much.
It builds up when you
get it everyday!
You don't need to save up...
to buy your village from Arlong
anymore, remember?
So there's no need to be stingy.
You're so dumb!
Now that the village is free,
I can finally earn money for myself!
I'm gonna be a rich pirate,
who can dress up all the time!
Hey, simmer down!
I'm trying to concentrate on
developing my special Tabasco Star!
An eyeful of this
will make any bad guy-
C'mon! Just one!
Water! Water! Water!
No!
This is Nami's tangerine orchard!
I won't let anyone
lay a finger on it!
Nami! Nothing will get past
my loving protection!
Yeah. Thanks, Sanji.
She's got him wrapped
around her finger.
C'mon! Just one tangerine!
You're so mean, Sanji!
I said no!
Well, whatever!
I'm in too good a mood to fight!
The world sure is chaotic these days.
Another coup in Villa...
A flyer?
Navy HQ
Operated by the
World Government
So, they're too much for local branches to handle?
Correct. Before forming his pirate crew,
he bested Captain Axe-Hand Morgan,
and he's shown
no signs of slowing since.
Buggy the Clown,
15 million.
Pirate Commodore Don Krieg.
17 million.
Sawtooth Arlong of the
Fishman Pirates. 20 million.
Commander Brannew
Navy Headquarters
The average bounty in the East Blue
is 3 million belly, but these
notorious pirates, worth more than
10 million each, were taken down!
30 million as a starting
bounty is unprecedented,
but we believe it's necessary.
We must nip this evil in the bud now,
before it gets out of hand!
Agreed.
We're wanted criminals!
It says I'm worth 30 million belly!
Look! I'm gonna be seen around the
world! Girls might even fall for me!
What?! They included
Long Nose but left me out?!
Where are you?!
I don't even see you!
See!
It's just the back of your head.
That's nothing to brag about.
Don't be so sour! If you're a big enough threat,
you can get one of these without being a captain.
Really?!
Just keep tryin'!
Let's head for the Grand Line, men!
As always, you guys are missing how serious this is!
All of our lives are in danger now!
This is no time to be messing around in the East Blue...
30 million belly.
Navy HQ is sure to take action with a number that high...
and we'll be swarmed with strong bounty hunters.
This'll be beyond what we've faced before.
Mistress!
Mistress Kaya!
What's wrong, Merry?!
Take a look at this!
Usopp!
That's definitely
the back of Usopp's head!
Now that you mention it,
you're right...
Finally!
Luffy! You've taken
the first step toward your dream!
I'm Luffy! The man who's
gonna be king of the pirates!
See ya!
But the next time we meet,
we'll be on opposite sides!
We're finally approaching the Grand Line.
There's a famous settlement
on this island... Loguetown.
Loguetown?
It's known as the Town of Beginnings and Endings.
Its reputation precedes itself.
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
was born and executed in that town.
The town where the pirate king died.
Wanna check it out?
Yeah! I have to see it!
The man who got the One Piece—
everything the world has to offer—
was born and executed there!
Anyone who wants to flee,
should do so now!
This bastion of peace will not...
tolerate any weakness during this age of piracy!
The people that fall prey to villains need us! We are justice!
No matter what kind of evil roams the seas,
we marines must be prepared to fend
it off without mercy!
In the name of absolute justice!
"Justice"
Yes, sir!
Wow! What a huge town!
Pirates stop here on
their way to the Grand Line.
So it has everything you could need!
Alright!
I'm gonna get some gear
for our next great adventure!
Looks like I can stock up
on fresh ingredients.
Fresh women, too!
There's something I wanna buy, too.
Oh? How are you gonna do that?
Aren't you broke?!
Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
Huh?
I'm gonna see where the
pirate king was executed!
Hey, wait! We haven't decided
where we're meeting up yet!
Man, that guy.
The king of the pirates was
born here and died here!
He might've walked down this very street!
Yahoo!
Damn, these are expensive!
Too expensive!
Lend you money?
No problem!
Just remember, you'll
hafta pay me 300% interest!
I'm not giving that greedy women another belly.
But I can't enter the Grand Line
with just one sword...
What do I do?
"Monster"?! That's quite rude!
Shut it! Our boss is
behind bars because of him!
You should have taken that as a lesson!
No way! We ain't satisfied leaving things be!
We're gonna drag
your corpse to him as payback!
Very well. I will fight you.
Will you now, girlie?!
Don't make us laugh!
What can a girl possibly do?!
Die!
Yeah!
She did it!
That's one strong lady!
You're amazing!
I can't tell if she's strong or lucky!
My glasses! Where are my glasses!
My glasses...
Hey. You looking for these?
S-Sorry for the trouble!
Thank you!
How's this?
Oh! You look wonderful, miss!
It's so elegant, miss!
And this?
Elemental, miss!
This one?
Electrifying!
How's this one?
Elegiac!
Will you be purchasing all of these?
Nah, I don't want 'em.
They're too extravagant for my taste.
Come again!
Oh! A top-quality aperitif!
Oh! Two champagne-like bubbly beauties!
The whole town's like a buffet!
Damn, I can't decide
what to go for first!
I think I just found the main dish!
"Love-Love Pirates"
Awesome! What is this place?!
It's like a collector's dream!
Welcome!
Everything here once belonged to famous pirates...
who returned alive from the Grand Line!
They are incredibly valuable.
All these items were used during
adventures on the Grand Line?!
That's correct!
We only do business
with the bravest sea warriors here,
so it'll be a pleasure to serve a gentleman such as yourself!
What do you say? This was Gold Roger's favorite gun!
What?! Gold Roger's?!
Yes!
Are you interested, sir?
S-Show me everything!
My pleasure!
Where are we going exactly?!
You broke my glasses.
I told you.
I'll pay you back... somehow.
You don't look like
you have any money!
Something about you just seems off!
T-True, I don't have any now, but...
Those shadows under your eyes!
You look like you haven't eaten for days!
Is your mother sick?!
Or maybe your wife ran out leaving you to raise all five kids alone?!
L-Listen, you!
I don't need the details!
Just come with me!
T-The Navy?
Here.
If you work for the Navy, you'll never
need to worry about money!
Screw that! Why would I wanna be a marine?!
You're just going to take off?!
I'm trying to do you a favor here!
Look, you!
Chief Petty Officer!
It's time for training!
Later! Please work hard, okay?
Chief Petty Officer?!
Damn it!
I'm gettin' nowhere like this!
Even three-mop style is the best!
Let me try again!
You! What are you doing here?!
I knew it!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Why the heck are you cleaning?
Intel says you've joined
Monkey D. Luffy's crew!
You're under arrest!
Well... now what?
What happened here?!
It seems someone attacked them!
There's no trace of the assailant!
"For your glasses."
Man, that freaked me out...
Dammit! She looks
way too much like Kuina!
Not to mention she's a swordsman, too...
Anything's possible I guess,
but I doubt I'll ever see her again.
I'd like some swords.
Yes, yes! Welcome! Examine
anything that catches your eye!
Ipponmatsu
Weapons Merchant
Our shop's been in business for 200 years!
I have 100,000 belly.
Sell me two swords.
Eh? Two for only 100,000?
Damn, he's a bum.
50,000 a sword'll only
get you some dull blades.
I'll make do with whatever.
This is all the money I got.
You'll make do with whatever?
Hmph! What a novice!
That sword on his waist!
Could it be?!
H-Hey there. L-Lemme see
that sword of y-y-yours!
Why're you stammering like that?!
J-Just let me see!
Weirdo.
T-This really is it!
C-Calm down! This is a big chance!
An absolute novice just waltzed
in with a named blade!
You need to play it cool!
Say, this isn't a bad sword!
What do you say? I'll take it off you for 200,000 belly.
Then you'll have 300,000 total!
You could get three nice blades
at 100,000 apiece!
Huh?! What're you talking about?!
A-Alright! I-I'll
make it 250,000! No, 300,000!
500,000?
Look. Raise the price all
you want, this sword isn't-
Alright, then! I'll buy it
from you for 650,000 belly!
Fine, you damn haggler!
How does 800,000 belly sound?!
Hello!
Did you finish polishing Shigure?
Thank goodness! You're all right!
Someone went on a rampage
at the naval outpost earlier.
You were missing so I was worried!
How dense can she be?
Thank goodness! That's such a relief.
But the fact you're safe and sound...
means that you must've left earlier, abandoning my kind offer!
Here, take your money back.
I can't accept money
from someone that cold.
Besides, I already bought some new glasses!
Isn't that katana the Wado Ichimonji?
It really is Wado Ichimonji!
Wado?!
Don't say it! Don't say it!
What a beautiful temper line!
It's one of the twenty-one excellent wazamono blades!
See! Look at this! It's worth
no less than 10 million belly!
But what are you doing
with such a legendary sword?
Damn you! You had to go and run your mouth!
I should sue for obstruction of business!
O-Obstruction of business?
I'm sorry! Did I say something wrong?
You're here for Shigure, right?!
I'm done polishing it!
Take it and get the hell out!
Why did you run straight into those?!
I-I'm sorry.
That clutz saved you!
It's a shame that a clueless guy like you...
is running around with a named blade without realizing its value.
All the swords in that
barrel are 50,000 belly apiece!
Just pick whatever two you want!
What's he so mad about?
You must really like swords,
to want to carry three of them!
It reminds me of that one bounty hunter!
A bounty hunter?
He's infamous! His name is Roronoa!
I hear the name a lot.
Right. He's a swordsman renowned
all throughout the East Blue,
but he's a ruthless brute!
Using swordsmanship for something as petty as bounty-hunting?!
Why're the forces of evil so strong in this era?
All the famous sword masters
are pirates or bounty hunters.
And almost all of the world's
named blades are in their hands.
It's a real shame.
I dunno. Everyone has
their own circumstances, right?
You have to do what you can to survive.
Well, with Shigure in my hands,
I'm going to hone
my swordsmanship...
and someday I'll retrieve all the named blades...
from the criminals of the world!
The twelve supreme wazamonos,
the twenty-one excellent wazamonos,
and the fifty great wazamonos.
I'll risk my life for them!
You gonna take this katana, too?
Wado Ichimonji, was it?
No, it's not like I want
the named blades for myself.
I'm just saying I don't want them in the hands of criminals.
This sword...
That sword! I think it's...
I thought so! Kitetsu III!
It's Kitetsu III!
Its predecessor, Kitetsu II,
is an excellent wazamono,
and Kitetsu I before that
is listed as a supreme wazamono!
Mister! Is this sword
really only 50,000 belly?!
Y-Yeah...
Incredible!
It's a great wazamono, you know!
Buy that one!
You have to buy that one!
It normally goes
for one million belly!
It's an absolute no-brainer!
N-No! I can't sell it!
That's right! Selling this for
50,000 belly is clearly a mistake!
No, that's not what I mean!
It's cursed...
You knew?!
No. I can tell.
From their first incarnation,
every Kitetsu has been outstanding, but each one of them carries a curse!
Many famous master swordsmen
have met their tragic ends
after taking up a Kitetsu katana.
These days, there ain't a single
person who'll use a Kitetsu.
Because they'll end your life before you know it!
I just wanna get rid of the thing,
but I'm afraid it'll curse me...
I-I'm sorry! I had no idea it
was such a terrifying sword!
I should've minded my own business!
It's perfect! I'll take it!
A-Are you a moron?!
I can't sell it!
If you die because of it,
it'd be like I killed you myself!
You're the moron!
Just get the sale!
Honey!
Let's test it out.
My luck, or this thing's curse?
We'll find out which is stronger.
You can't be serious!
Stop! It's sharp enough to take your arm off!
I'll take it.
Hey. Could you pick another one for me?
S-Sure...
H-Hold it!
This blade has an uneven finish...
and a black lacquered sheath!
The great wazamono Yubashiri!
My shop may not be much,
but this is the finest sword I own!
I can't afford it.
I already told you, I got no money.
Forget the money. And I don't
need any for the Kitetsu, either.
I'm sorry for trying
to cheat you earlier.
It's been a while since I've looked into
the eyes of a true swordsman.
They say a sword chooses its wielder anyway.
I'll be praying for your good fortune!
I definitely feel more
at ease with three swords.
Oh, what's this?
I can't believe a miser like you gave a treasure like that away!
What's wrong with a man
entrusting his dreams to another?!
Just take out the damn trash!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I was so frightened...
I still can't stand up...
What's that?
Lemme see.
Hawk Eye!
What're you doing here?!
Calm down.
I have no qualms with you.
Where is your boss?
Camping out on an island like this...
How carefree.
B-B-Boss!
I-It's Hawk Eye!
Hey there, Hawk Eye.
What a surprise...
You caught me at a bad time...
Are you here to challenge me?
I have no intention
of settling our duel;
now that you're missing your left arm.
I encountered an interesting pirate,
he reminded me of a story you told me once.
It was about a boy
from some small village.
You don't mean!
So you've made it, Luffy!
Captain "Red-Haired" Shanks
Red Hair Pirates
In that case, Hawk Eye...
I can't just let you leave.
Isn't that right, Hawk Eye?!
Right! Now drink up!
It's time to celebrate!
I thought you had a hangover?
Don't sweat it!
There's always room to make a toast!
C'mon now! C'mon now!
Just chug it straight down!
That's the way!
Let's drink! Down the hatch!
Yeah!
But, wait! Boss!
You said you felt sick 'cause you drank too much before!
You dolt! How could I not drink
on a joyous day like today!
The sun's still up.
Don't sweat it!
Let's party!
Hey! Luffy's a wanted man now!
Good for him!
This village might become known for being the home of a famous pirate!
That'd be great!
Quiet, you miscreants!
Mayor!
What's so good about a criminal
hailing from our village?!
A toast!
Honestly! Every last one of them!
Come on, Mayor! Luffy looks so happy here!
A pirate's a pirate!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Sure, but it's his dream.
Can it really be that bad?
His dream... or fate?