Two years have passed since the war between
Marine Headquarters, the Seven Warlords,
and the Whitebeard Pirates.
On the deserted island northwest
of the Isle of Women, Luscaina.
Luffy!
Yeah! I'm coming!
I can't believe it.
It's been two years already.
Hey!
Watch it. She's my friend.
Luffy, the ship is ready
to set sail whenever you are!
Okay, thanks!
That's amazing.
He's the boss of the island now.
Thing is, we became friends,
so eating them went out the window.
They do look tasty though.
It's okay, Luffy.
All your favorite foods are on the ship.
I think I'd be a good wife
since I'm thoughtful like that.
I'm not getting married,
but thank you for the food!
I can't help loving that harsh side of you!
Rayleigh left six months ago.
He must be waiting to meet you on Sabaody.
He was done teaching me the basics
in the first year and a half.
It's time I say goodbye
to you guys and the island.
Alright...
Let's go!
Video Editing
Gigglebot
Galaxy 9000
iconsumekidneys
Gigglebot
Galaxy 9000
iconsumekidneys
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Zenef
Graphics
Datenshi
Soundtracking
Halee
Timing
PhosCity
Subtitle Editing
JT-421
Translation
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Gaijin
Ibfinity
Rokitoki
arch1t3cht
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Gaijin
Ibfinity
Rokitoki
Ten-Odd Days Later at a Bar
Two Years Later
Did you know that
Marine Headquarters moved?
What? It was?
Yeah, they switched places
with the G-1 Branch,
sandwiching the Red Line on either side.
That's how determined
Sengoku's successor is.
After all, he set up their headquarters
in the sea with the Four Emperors.
But thanks to the switch,
headquarters has less sway here,
so there are more lawless areas on the island.
Hmm, no wonder it seems rougher
here than two years ago.
Hey, did you see this?!
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
I can't believe the Straw Hats
have resurfaced!
For real. They've been quiet for two years,
so we thought they were dead.
URGENT:
CREW NEEDED
They're even recruiting!
URGENT:
CREW NEEDED
Pirates who survived the first half
of the Grand Line keep showing up.
He's enlisting them to expand his crew
before running wild in the New World!
Sounds exciting!
Maybe I should join too!
No way!
There are people with bounties
over 100 million on the island now.
They definitely ain't taking you!
What?!
Sabaody Park, Grove 33
The Sabao Dome, a Concert Hall
Hey, don't say that!
Can't you do anything about it?
Tickets are sold out!
What else would you expect?!
We're talking about the superstar Soul King Brook's world tour!
This island is the tour's final stop!
The place is already packed!
Manager!
I'll put on a great show today!
Yes, that'd be nice!
Your TD is doing very well
and has sold over a million copies!
You certainly are the king of soul music!
Listen to the crowd!
Soul King! Soul King! Soul King! Soul King!
Manager,
before the concert,
I have something important to say.
What is it?
Come on, baby!
Yeah!
We are...
Bone!
Bone! Bone! Bone!
♪ Bone to be wild! ♪
I can't believe it... How selfish can he be?!
Hey, give me a transponder snail!
I'm not gonna let you
get away with this, Brook!
Let's make today the greatest anniversary!
Women! Real ones!
Ah, there's no doubt!
There are actual ladies in front of me!
Here, on this island, are the real ladies
I've been dreaming of, night after night.
Viva Sabaody!
I need a lady!
Sanjikins!
We'll leave you here.
I don't want to part,
but I'm sure we'll meet again!
I never want to see you again!
Thank you for the ride! Say "hi" to Ivan! Bye!
The man, Sanji,
has just come back from hell!
You know what they say?
Boys can't help being mean to girls they like.
It's true. It happened to me.
I won't ever forget him!
Wait for me, Nami my sweet, Robin my love!
Huh? Did I hear wrong?
A 55-million-belly bounty?
Check the poster again!
Captain Monkey D. Luffy
"Straw Hat Pirates"
It says, "No bounties under 70 million."
We ain't dealing with no captains worth less than that.
How'd you guys even get here in one piece?
Dammit!
Get lost, scum.
Don't you know I'm
the son of Dragon the Revolutionary?!
Navigator Nami
We don't need no dead weight!
Shipwright Franky
We're an exclusive pirate crew!
We're in another league.
Marksman Sogeking
Don't think just anyone can join us.
Get lost.
Straw Hat Luffy is merciless.
Well yeah, he's already achieved so much.
Hey, Franky, how many people we got so far?
A hundred or so.
Three whole pirate crews have joined up.
Ten of them have bounties.
That's good.
And two of those are high-profile rookies.
Wet-Haired Caribou
and Blood Spatter Coribou.
Both are known for killing Marines.
These brothers are captains with bounties
of 210 million and 190 million.
We'll get some use out of 'em!
Let's get more followers!
Old man, we need another round!
Y-Yes!
Hurry up!
Oh? And you, woman,
you've been there for quite a while.
Stop drinking all alone and come join us!
She's a beauty.
Not on your life. I'm waiting for a guy.
What?
She turned him down.
Hey, hey, you better say yes!
He's Straw Hat Luffy!
Remember?
He's the crazy pirate who burst
into the Summit War two years ago!
You've heard of him, right?!
Waiting for a guy?
Gotta be some wimp who'd wail and beg
for mercy after hearing Captain Luffy's name!
Get over here already!
I'll only say it once!
You and I are not a good match,
so I'm not drinking with you.
What?
Do you understand, Straw Hat... who?
Huh?
Did you say "who"?!
I'm Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, you'd better apologize!
You're in danger!
Huh?
You've got a lot of nerve!
Let me handle it.
Hey, you! You're a funny girl.
So I'll make it easier for you.
Are you gonna drink with Captain Luffy?
Or are you gonna die?
For your information, I have a bounty too.
I'm Cat Burglar Nami!
Don't mess with me!
Lethal Green Star:
Devil!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
The hell is this?
Help me, Captain!
Get away from me, you dumbass!
What is that plant?
Say, young lady, do you wanna drink with me?
Usopp, long time no see!
I can't believe it! You've gotten so strong!
You've blossomed a bunch yourself!
What?! She was waiting for that young punk?!
Did you do that?
Yes, I did!
That's my new weapon: pop green!
It's not like I've been gazing at the sea,
doing nothing for two years.
I'm sorry, but...
I no longer belong to the weak trio
with you and Chopper.
I became a warrior
who isn't fazed by anything!
Hey, dude! Did you do this to us?
What?! Sogeking?! Why?!
Usopp, forget about them!
Let's go somewhere else.
Plus, I need a favor.
Wait, you guys!
Huh, Luffy?!
Let's go!
Hey, ma'am, you haven't paid yet!
Keep the change!
Shit! They made us look bad!
Go get 'em!
Dammit!
Huh?! What are these black bubbles?!
What the hell?
A cloud?!
Wh-What happened?!
So I got my hands on some new technology...
Really? You were in the sky?
Find those two and kill them!
Marineford
(Former Marine HQ)
I have a report! At the Sabaody Archipelago...
What? The Straw Hats?!
Yes, sir! Reports say that they're
recruiting new crew members.
Report this to headquarters.
If he's really alive, that's bad news.
Gather the troops on the double!
And intensify the search
on Sabaody Archipelago!
Did I lose them?
URGENT:
CREW NEEDED
Brook's concert?
URGENT:
CREW NEEDED
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
What is going on?
"Soul King"?
Shakky's Rip-off Bar, Grove 13
Wh-What?!
That swordsmoron was the first one here?!
I can't believe it!
Our next voyage will be rough.
Franky came second, about 10 days ago,
and immediately went to see the ship.
The Sunny is safe, right?
Of course. Not a scratch on her,
and the coating's already done.
That's good.
He did a good job.
There's no regret for honorable wounds!
Yes! A year to heal!
I didn't know you had such
a strong sense of duty.
Thank you, Duval.
What, you think I'm handsome?
I returned your favor, young master!
Whether it was raining or windy,
dangerous pirates were after your ship.
But I fought day after day
with cuts and bruises!
Those were painful times!
Boss Duval!
Even so, how did you get hurt so badly?
Well, fall for me...
I mean, listen to me, young master.
That's because the Marines finally...
And Nami was the third...
Nami my sweet!
Where is she?!
She went out shopping to kill time.
What about my story?!
Nami's shopping! Nami's shopping!
Usopp arrived fourth a few
days ago and went to town.
Chopper arrived fifth yesterday.
Brook came here today for a concert.
A concert?
And then you came.
So seven members including you have
already arrived on the archipelago.
We haven't seen Nico Robin or Luffy yet.
It's extremely difficult just
to get to this island.
You all are quite impressive.
It's nice you'll be able to reunite.
Yeah.
That aside, I can't believe you trained Luffy.
He must be incredibly strong now.
I haven't seen him in six months.
I'm excited to see his progress.
Progress...
I wonder what kind of
"progress" Nami has made!
Hey, are you alright?
Hey, Zoro! Sanji! Robin!
We finally meet again,
but you're acting weird!
Zoro and Sanji, you guys have grown
so close over the past two years.
But why aren't you talking to me?
Hey, it's still following us.
Oh, you're being shy, you bastards!
That tanuki knows a bit
too much about us.
I've been thinking about that too...
Could it be? Look at this.
Zoro, Sanji, Robin & Chopper
"Straw Hat Pirates"
Don't tell me it's...!
The real Cotton Candy Lover Chopper,
a 50-belly bounty!
So it's their pet!
You guys changed a little. But I don't mind.
They must've dumped it on the island before they died, and now it's a stray.
So it's following us because
it thinks its masters are back.
Then let's ditch that fox
and take this one instead.
If the pet is identical to the poster,
we'll look more authentic.
We're gonna keep it?
What does it eat?
Cotton candy!
We don't have that.
We don't need you anymore! Go away!
Come here, Chopper.
It's a cucumber.
Scary! Robin, you're scary!
Now's our chance!
Oh, Robin!
What? Hey, Nico Robin!
Who are they?
This is really bad! Robin was abducted!
They're kidnappers!
Hey, shouldn't we report this to Captain Luffy?
What?! Have you guys seen Luffy already?
You're right!
They must have new members by now too!
Yeah, we'd better rescue Robin already, huh?
Lead the way!
This is Sabaody! We caught Nico Robin!
With some fox creature
that won't let go of her.
I better hurry up.
They might all be here by now.
Hey, you alright?! Hey!
He's horrible!
He shot her out of the blue!
Terrible!
Hey, stay with me!
Why did you do that?!
What did we do to you?!
I said, "sorry," didn't I?!
I mistook her for someone else!
Sorry. I was looking for
a couple that look just like you.
A long-haired woman and a long-nosed man.
You mistook her and shot her on the spot?!
My god! Straw Hat Luffy is horrible!
Huh? Don't tell me that you
got a problem with me?!
Looks like you do.
Don't blame me! It's their fault!
Hey, stay with me! You alright?!
Find those two, you guys!
We can't just let them get away!
Kill them... to make an example!
Oh, did I run into you? Sorry!
Bye!
What's wrong with him?
Doesn't he know who Straw Hat Luffy is?
H-He's a dead man walking!
Wait just a minute!
Huh?
That's Sabaody Archipelago in the distance.
Luffy, we have to say goodbye here.
We can't let them find out about our relationship.
Uh-huh.
Put this on...
like this!
I don't need that! It's too much!
Is that so?
But in case something happens...
Uh-huh.
You have to be careful.
Make sure you hide your face.
The world thinks you're dead, but...
people still know what
you look like from two years ago.
If you cause trouble,
you won't be able to set sail.
I got it.
And in the backpack, I put
500 changes of clothes, 1,000 lunches,
handkerchiefs and tissues, five years' worth of towels,
three years' worth of water and snacks, silverware, toothbrushes, soap,
hand creams, three years' worth
of bug bite ointment, and...
That's way too much!
Oh?
I wish you a safe reunion with your crew.
Yeah. Thank you for everything!
Good luck!
I've heard Sabaody
has become perilous these days.
Yes. That's why the Marines are paying
a lot of attention to what goes on there.
Take extra care!
Will do.
If you need us, the Kuja Pirates
will always come to help you!
Please keep that in mind.
And could you do me a favor?
What? I'm not gonna marry you.
No, I just want you to leave
without saying goodbye.
Oh, I've never said that to anyone, anyway.
I wanna see you again.
Alright, I'm off!
See you!
Take care, Luffy!
See ya!
He said he wants to see me again!
Is this what they call...
a proposal?!
Nyo, it's nyot!
Hancock told me not to cause any trouble.
Hey, you ran into me on purpose, didn't ya?
Th-That guy is screwed!
Sunny !
Sorry to keep you waiting for two years.
I'm glad you're okay!
We've got an absolute babe here!
You're our super archaeologist...
Robin, aren't you?!
You haven't changed at all, Franky!
Of course I've changed, silly!
Witness the romantic masculinity jam-packed in my body!
Feast your eyes on this fantastic,
one-of-a-kind transformation!
I'm beyond human understanding now!
Yeah, it's probably hard
to see you as a mere human now.
Hey, hey, you sayin' I'm perverted?
What a great compliment!
Is this the coating?
It's like jelly.
That's right! Rayleigh sure knows his stuff!
Now we can dive into the depths!
What technology!
I just saw Rayleigh and the others.
So you went to the bar.
What number were you?
Eighth.
Everybody's here except Luffy.
I see. We'll begin a new voyage soon.
I've got the ship in tip-top condition.
The new weapons are ready, too!
I can't wait.
By the way, where are the others?
Usopp and Sanji were here earlier.
Usopp left to buy fuel,
and Sanji went shopping for food.
I see. Actually, on my way here...
I found this.
Did you know about this?
Who is Soul King?
Oh, about Brook.
Yeah, I knew about it.
I've seen his TDs everywhere.
He's in the spotlight now.
From the dark, silent, foggy sea,
propelled into the bright lights of the stage,
cheered on by legions of fans.
He might not...
want to be a pirate again.
The Sabao Dome, Grove 33
♪ Soul King is mysterious... ♪
♪ He's nothing but bones! ♪
♪ Afro on the skull! Girls love the contrast! ♪
♪ Girls love the contrast! ♪
♪ Wanna make her weak in the knees? ♪
♪ Got milk! Got milk! ♪
♪ You need more calcium than protein! ♪
♪ Ah-ahhh...! ♪
Why don't you say something?
Did you run into me knowing who I was?
You see? You made me look like a chump.
You humiliated me in public.
We're talking me here.
I'm an elite pirate with a 400-million bounty!
Plant your knees on the grass, right now,
and beg for your life!
Hey, fisherman, sell me some fish
at your best price!
Huh? Is nobody here?
Hey, are you the owner?
What's the matter?
He's gone!
The green-haired man!
Green-haired? What happened?
I did something horrible!
It happened just now...
Old man, I wanna fish.
Huh?
Wha...?
Young man, you don't look like
the fishing type.
I promised to meet my friends on this island.
But I got here first,
and I haven't seen any of them yet.
So I don't have anything to do.
Can you take me out
on your fishing boat?
Sure, I'll take you out on that boat,
so why don't you wait for me on board?
That's what I told him.
Green hair, three swords, and a bellyband?
Yeah, and he has a deep scar on his eye.
You know him?
A scar on his eye?
Was it this guy?
Oh yeah, this is the guy! Is he your friend?
Well, let's say an acquaintance.
I told him to get on the fishing boat.
That's for sure.
But when I got back here...
No, young man, that's not it!
That's a pirate ship!
You guys! We're setting sail for the New World
that we've been dreaming of!
W-Wake up, young man!
You're on the wrong ship!
So I think he's heading
for Fishman Island like that.
That idiot!
I thought it was unlike him to show up first.
I knew he'd do something like this!
He was on a pirate ship!
He might be dead by now!
No, no, it's okay.
It's not your fault at all.
He won't die.
We're lucky we know where he's heading.
That aside, can I have some fish?
Well, but...
Hey, what's that?!
Look at the water! Something is surfacing!
What is it?
It's huge!
It's a galleon!
Was it poorly coated
and crushed by the water pressure?
Or attacked by sea kings?
It looks like it's been
cut clean in half!
Don't be crazy!
What could cut a ship this big?
You bastard!
How dare you ruin our dream
of going to the New World?!
A twist of fate!
You should blame your own cursed fate that
brought a plague onto your ship.
So self-righteous!
Look!
Somebody's on the ship!
Oh, he's back.
Could've stayed gone for all I care.
I got on...
the wrong ship.