Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Quality Control
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
Villager
Zenef
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
Villager
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Villager
Timing
Closed Captioning
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Camotoy
Villager
Zenef
Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
Funimation
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
They Call Him "Straw Hat" Luffy
[thud]
– [SAILOR A] Huh?
– [SAILOR B] Huh?
[SAILOR grunts]
Ugh. I missed again.
[SAILOR A laughs]
Strike three, pal.
[SAILOR C]
I'd be embarrassed.
You suck!
Hm?
[SAILOR B grunts]
It's heavier than I thought it'd be!
Maybe it's filled with beer!
[SAILOR A grunts]
Well, I think it's our beer now.
[whimpering]
[menacing orchestral music]
Ship off the starboard bow!
[SAILORS A & B]
Huh?
[SAILOR C]
And they're flying a pirate flag!
We've got a pirate ship in pursuit!
Enemy raid! Enemy raid!
[SAILOR A & B scream]
[cannon fire]
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[ALVIDA]
Koby!
Yes, ma'am?
Cabin Boy Koby
[ALVIDA] Who is the most beautiful
of all on these seas?
[KOBY] Uh...
Well, uh, That would be the captain
of our ship, Lady Alvida, of course.
[ALVIDA chuckles]
[laughing]
The Lady Pirate, "Iron Club" Alvida
Good answer.
That means a lot to me.
It's been a while...
We're finally gonna see a little action.
That's right!
So make it count!
Hit 'em with all you got, boys!
[PIRATES cheering]
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[PIRATES grunt]
Here we go!
Time to show them
the terror of Iron Club Alvida,
Lady Pirate of the Seas!
[PIRATES yelling]
[yelling continues]
[whimpering]
Koby! What are you doing?!
I'm not... real good at this stuff.
[scoffs] You're telling me.
Maybe it's 'cause you're too busy
back-talking me all the time.
Oh no! Not the club!
Anything but the club!
Please!
Then get your ass in gear!
[screams]
[sobbing]
[ALVIDA] Move it, you brat!
[KOBY gasps]
[ALVIDA yelling]
[screaming]
[ALVIDA groans]
[PIRATES laughing]
We're not gonna
take your lives, we swear...
But we will take
everything else you got on ya.
[ALVIDA]
And anyone who fights back will be eating
their dinner off the bottom of the ocean.
[KOBY]
Uh, hello...?
I really hope there's no one in here.
[sighs] That's a relief...
Hm?
[KOBY]
Wow, that's one big barrel.
I wonder what's inside of it.
[KOBY groaning]
[apprehensive music]
It's our favorite coward.
You trying to hide in here
and duck out on all the action again?
No way!
I was just trying to haul this
big barrel of beer over to you guys!
[laughs]
Why don't you let us
lighten your load?
[PIRATE B]
I was just startin' to get thirsty.
You can't!
Lady Alvida will kill us
if she ever found out!
She won't if you keep your trap shut.
Right.. boy?
Yeah... Right.
[laughs nervously] Okay.
This sucker's heavy.
[PIRATE B]
Hah, perfect.
[PIRATE A]
I'll open her the old fashioned way.
[PIRATE A growls]
[growling continues]
[LUFFY yelling]
[ALL scream]
[triumphant orchestral music]
[LUFFY]
I...
slept...
so...
great...!
[thunk]
Hm?
Who's that?
Who the hell are you guys?
Who the hell are you?!
Your friend will catch cold
sleeping like that.
You're the one who knocked him out!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Hold up!
Are you messing with us when you know
good and well that we're vicious pirates?! Huh?!
– [KOBY gasps]
– [LUFFY] I'm starving.
[LUFFY]
You got any food?
I'm talking to you!
[growls] You damn kid!
[PIRATES yelling]
[KOBY screams]
[LUFFY] Hm?
[PIRATES growl] Die!
[KOBY whimpers]
[metal clangs]
[PIRATES gasp]
[KOBY whimpers, gasps]
What is wrong with you two?
[PIRATE C]
Wh-Who are you?!
[LUFFY]
Me? Oh...
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
Hi! [laughs]
[PIRATES screaming]
So... what just happened?
You got me.
[gasps] Quick! You've gotta run!
If those guys come back here with
their buddies, then they'll kill you on the spot!
I don't care about that. I'm hungry.
How can you just blow
this off like that?!
There are hundreds
of them up on deck
and they're waiting for
the opportunity to kill anything!
[LUFFY grunting]
[KOBY straining]
[KOBY mumbling]
You're going the wrong way!
No! Wait!
[LUFFY growling]
[shrieks]
[laughs]
It's a gold mine!
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
[KOBY]
Who's knows...
[LUFFY laughs]
[KOBY]
Maybe we'll be safe in here
as long as no one else gets hungry.
[LUFFY]
Ooh, which one should I take first?
This box looks promising!
[LUFFY]
Apples! Excellent! [laughs]
Heh, tasty!
[KOBY]
Uh... Hey! My name's Koby!
You're Luffy. Is that right?
That was pretty neat when you
jumped out of that barrel back there.
These are awesome!
[KOBY laughs nervously]
[LUFFY]
So are we on a pirate ship or what?
[KOBY]
No...
It's a passenger ship
that's being raided by pirates,
pirates under the command
of Lady Alvida.
[LUFFY]
Aw, who cares anyway?
What I wanna know is if
there are any boats on board.
[KOBY]
I think there are a few.
[LUFFY]
Great! 'Cause mine got sucked
into some big whirlpool.
[KOBY]
That one outside? No way!
No one could have survived that.
[laughs] Yeah! I gotta say,
it was a big surprise!
[laughs nervously]
[LUFFY]
So are you one of the pirates
or one of the passengers?
[KOBY gasps]
It was on a fateful day, long ago...
That day...
I stepped out onto
a small fishing boat
on the outskirts of town
to go catch my dinner.
[KOBY]
Huh?
[whimpers]
[KOBY]
Turned out that particular boat
was actually headed for a pirate ship.
That was two years ago.
In exchange for them letting me live,
I'm forced to live
the life of a cabin boy.
[LUFFY]
You're pretty stupid, you know that?
[KOBY]
Gee, thanks for your honesty.
[LUFFY]
If you hate it, then leave.
[KOBY]
Are you kidding?! I can't do that!
No way! Nuh-uh! Not a chance!
Just the thought of Alvida finding me
scares me so bad, I wanna throw up!
[laughing] You're a moron
and a coward!
[laughing] I hate people like you!
– [LUFFY laughing]
– [KOBY sobs]
[menacing orchestral music]
All right, quit your
lollygagging around, boys!
We gotta load up everything
before the Marines get here.
I catch anyone dawdling, and they'll
get a real mouthful of my iron club!
[PIRATES screaming]
[BOTH]
Captain!
[ALVIDA growls]
[PIRATE B & C]
This is bad!
[ALVIDA]
Yeah...? Then out with it!
[PIRATE C]
It came from inside the barrel!
[PIRATE B]
Such a horrible monster!
[ALVIDA growls]
Huh?
[PIRATES whimper]
[ALVIDA grunts]
Who are you...
[PIRATES scream]
[ALVIDA]
...calling a monster?!
[PIRATE A screaming]
Uh... we weren't... talkin'...
about... you, my lady.
Some guy was hiding in a barrel!
He could be a bounty hunter!
What?!
Yeah, you're right.
If I had the courage,
I could drift alone in a barrel
and be rid of these pirates.
I actually have my own dreams.
Someday... I'd like
to live out all of them.
So, what about you, Luffy?
What was it that first got you
to set sail on these seas?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[laughs] Well, I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
[gasping]
The King?!
Yep.
Are you serious?!
Yeah!
But... But that would mean
that you're a pirate, too!
Right.
Your crew?
Don't have one yet,
but I'm lookin' for 'em.
[KOBY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[yelps] King of the Pirates
is a title given to one
who obtains everything
this world has to offer!
You're talking about seeking the great
treasure of wealth, fame, and power!
The treasure that you
seek is the One Piece!
Yeah!
Yeah?! That's it?!
Pirates from all over the world are
looking for that treasure, ya know?!
Yeah? So?
No way! It's impossible,
impossible, impossible!
There's no way anyone like you could ever
reach the pinnacle during this Great Pirate Age!
There's just too many out there
that are meaner and better!
[KOBY]
Ow... Why did you hit me?
'Cause I felt like it.
[KOBY groans]
Oh, well... I'm used to that stuff...
My shipmates smack me
around a lot...
all the time, in fact.
[LUFFY]
It's not about if I can.
[KOBY]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
I'm doing this 'cause I want to.
I decided long ago that
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
If I have to die fighting
for that... then I die.
[KOBY gasping]
All right...
Now that my belly's full, I'm gonna
go get me a brand new boat.
They might even just give me
one if I ask nice enough.
Maybe they're generous people.
[KOBY]
I guess I never thought of it like that.
[soft piano music]
If I put my mind to it,
if I'm prepared to die for it,
could I do something like that?
Like what?
Do you think...?
Do you think I could
ever join the Marines?
[LUFFY]
Marines?
Yes! Catching bad guys is
the only thing I've ever wanted to do!
It's been my dream
since I was a child!
Do you think I can do it?
[LUFFY]
How should I know that?
[KOBY]
Then I'm gonna do it!
I'm not gonna get stuck here
as a cabin boy for the rest of my life!
I'll break out, then I'll turn right
around, and catch Alvida myself!
[KOBY screaming]
[menacing music]
[ALVIDA]
Who is that you
plan on catching, Koby?
And you actually think
this twig is gonna help you?
Well?
[KOBY whimpering]
[ALVIDA] Answer me!
[ALVIDA growls]
[KOBY whimpering]
[ALVIDA chuckles]
My guess is that you're
not Zoro, the Pirate Hunter.
[KOBY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Zoro?
[ALVIDA]
Koby!
[shrieks]
[ALVIDA]
Who is most beautiful of all
on these seas?
[KOBY stammers]
Well... I... Um...
G-Give me a sec... I know this...
Hey, Koby, who's the fat lady?
[PIRATES whimpering]
Oh no...
Not good...
[ALVIDA growling]
You...
runt!
[KOBY whimpers]
[LUFFY]
Let's go.
[KOBY]
Huh?
[KOBY screaming]
[energetic orchestral music]
[PIRATES gasping]
[LUFFY laughs]
[PIRATE growling]
Missed me!
[LUFFY laughs]
[KOBY sighs]
[screams]
[LUFFY]
It's not fair to attack from behind.
[PIRATES screaming]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[screams] And it's even more not fair
to gang up on a guy!
[PIRATES screaming]
Gotcha!
[LUFFY]
Gum...
[ALVIDA growls]
[LUFFY]
Rocket!
[gasping]
– [PIRATES moaning]
– [footsteps]
[KOBY]
Luffy...
What are you?
[LUFFY]
Oh...
[laughs] I'm a rubber man.
So you're... made of rubber...?
I...
[gasps]
[KOBY screams]
So, you've eaten of the devil fruits.
Yeah. I ate the Gum-Gum one.
[apprehensive string music]
Ah-ha...
I heard rumors they existed,
but I'd never seen any evidence
of them before today.
You're more skilled than
the average deck swabber.
Are you a bounty hunter?
[LUFFY]
I'm a pirate!
Pirate? Ha!
All by yourself on these waters?
[LUFFY]
Today, it's just me.
But I'll find my crew tomorrow
or next week or something.
I need... ten guys.
[ALVIDA]
Hah!
That would make us enemies.
Am I right?
[whispers] Uh, Luffy? Let's go.
But why?
You saw how powerful her club is.
And of all the villainous cheats in all
these waters, she's easily the most...
I decided long ago that I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates.
If I have to die fighting
for that... then I die.
Go on...
Tell me...
[KOBY whimpering]
You're the most...
ugliest thing on the sea!
[ALVIDA growling]
[KOBY whimpering]
[laughing]
What'd you say?!
[laughing continues]
[KOBY]
I'm leaving and I'm gonna
join the Marines!
Then I'm gonna spend the rest of my
life beating up dirty pirates like you!
[ALVIDA]
Do you have any clue what you're
saying to me right now?!
[KOBY]
Of course I do!
And I'm gonna do what I want,
and no one's gonna stop me!
And when I join the Marines,
I'm gonna join them!
And I'm gonna catch
your lousy ass first!
You're dead, kid!
[ALVIDA yelling]
[KOBY]
No regrets! No regrets!
I did it! I said what I wanted to
and I fought for my dream!
Well said! [laughs]
[yells]
Heh. That won't work.
What?!
[LUFFY]
I'm rubber!
Gum...
Hah!
...Pistol!
[ALVIDA screaming]
[PIRATE A]
The sky's so pretty and blue out here.
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Hey, you!
[PIRATES]
Yes?!
Go find a boat and give it to Koby.
He's leaving your ship
to join the Marines.
You're not gonna stop him.
[PIRATES]
Uh... Yeah, sure!
[KOBY gasps]
Thanks, Luffy.
[BOTH screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[KOBY]
Look! It's the Marines!
[LUFFY]
Ooh!
Perfect timing!
Head over there
and tell 'em you wanna join.
[KOBY]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
But I'm a pirate, so I'm outta here!
No, wait! You can't be serious!
I approach them like this, they'll just
capture me like another pirate!
[KOBY]
We actually managed to get away!
[sighs] What fun!
[laughing]
So, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
If you're searching for
the elusive One Piece,
then you have to be headed
for the Grand Line, right?
[LUFFY]
Mm-hmm.
You know, the people I've talked to
call that place the pirate graveyard.
Right. And that's why I need
an extra-strong crew.
You guys mentioned
some pirate hunter.
So what's he like, Koby?
Oh, you mean Zoro?
Last I heard was that he's being
held prisoner at some Marine base.
Oh, well...
A weakling, huh?
No, you're so wrong!
He's as violent as a demon,
and three times as horrifying!
Why are you asking
about him anyway?
[giggles] I figure if he's good enough,
I'd ask him to join my crew!
[KOBY]
Chasing him down
is just plain reckless!
[LUFFY]
You never know! He might jump
at the chance to join me!
[KOBY]
He's a bad enough guy
that the Marines caught him!
No way! Not a chance!
Forget it! No, no–
[thud]
Ow!
[groans] Why'd you hit me?
[LUFFY]
'Cause I felt like it.