Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Fedew
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Zenef
Graphics: Datenshi
Karaoke
PhosCity
Timing
Gab
Subtitle Editing
Camotoy
Pollychan
Soundtracking
Halee
Typesetting
Gab
PhosCity
Translation
Crunchyroll
Liisa-Pekka
PamkinPinguin
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Six Vegapunks
You can run, but you can't hide!
Hakugan, take charge of the Polar Tang!
Okay!
Shachi! Penguin!
Into the sea!
You got it!
Re-Room!
What's this?
Amputate!
That's not what I heard it could do!
Is it an awakened technique?!
Alright! Fall!
Not yet!
You son of a bitch!
Quake Crush!
Damn that monster!
My goodness!
Stronger, are you dead?
I see...
You were a good boy.
Eat this!
What are those?!
Get away!
Apple bombs!
Huh?
Don't mess with guys from
the North Blue's frozen ports!
You don't stand a chance against us at sea!
Your ship's as good as sunk!
Prepare to attack!
– Yeah!
Jean Bart! Three o'clock!
A sniper!
Protect the captain!
I'm on it!
Oops...
His defense is strong.
K-Room!
That doesn't even tickle!
Shock Wille!
See, that's what happens
when you charge in recklessly...
Warp.
Commodore, shall we return to the ship?
Don't be stupid!
We finish what we start.
Understood.
Warp.
Blackbeard is here!
Are all your officers devil fruit users?
That just means they're all weak to the sea!
The perks of devil fruits
are well worth the drawbacks!
Room!
Takt!
K-Room!
They're attacking from below!
They're tryin' to sink us!
How can they be this good in the water?!
Look out!
We're just getting attacked a little.
It'll stop shaking soon.
Because our commodore is the strongest!
If Mama's still alive...
you won't be talking like that for long.
Charlotte Pudding
Big Mom Pirates
The guy we're fighting right now
is the one who killed her!
Times ain't gonna change if
the old legends are still ruling the roost!
On Cacao Island,
in the Whole Cake Island archipelago,
two intruders have come to
Pudding's home, Chocolat Town.
Their goal was to abduct Pudding.
Those intruders were...
the Blackbeard Pirates' Van Augur...
and...
Kuzan.
I know what you people
are trying to make me do.
I won't let that happen.
Black Vortex!
Emperor Blackbeard and Trafalgar Law
just clashed at Winner Island in the New World!
Once again, I have to wait
and see what happens.
Being fleet admiral is frustrating...
Future Island, Egghead
The pacifista stopped all of a sudden.
Now, Bonney...
Luffy, 70 Years Old
(In One Possible Future)
you could have disguised me as a better age...
Look, I get how you feel, but...
if you won't even let us beat up the ones
that aren't actually your dad, we'll be–
Be nice, Luffy!
Sorry, Bonney.
We've just been through a lot
with those pacifista, is all.
Also... turn me back to how I was, please...
Oh, boy...
Since they're clones of someone
who was originally a human,
it stands to reason that he'd have a family.
Don't take this the wrong way, Bonney.
To my knowledge, Kuma was once
the wicked king of Sorbet.
He became a pirate after
his people drove him out.
Then, after joining the Revolutionary Army,
the Marines arrested him
and gave him a life sentence.
But due to Vegapunk's fascination
with his physique and potential,
he was allowed to return to sea
as one of the Seven Warlords...
on the condition that he submits himself
to body augmentation and cloning.
Is that right?
The Warlord and cloning stuff I get.
But being made a cyborg?!
It's basically a death sentence!
No one would accept it
if they knew what it meant!
You're right...
Still, that's a lot of conditions
for a life sentence.
Just how awful were the crimes
Kuma the Tyrant committed...?
My father was not a tyrant!
He hated the World Government!
He would never work with them!
They must've modified him by force!
Hey, are you trying to kill us?!
That was way too close!
By the way, was that...
A beam saber?!
Awesome!
This is a scrap heap...
It must be full of Vegapunk's junk.
I can use this...
Anyway, this is...
murder in the name of science!
My father said his people are special.
But so what?!
That doesn't give them
the right to experiment on him!
That doesn't give them the right to kill him!
You said it!
A special people?
Bonney...
Could you turn me back, too?
We're flying!
Team Sunny
The robot is actually flying!
Cool!
This here Vegaforce-01 is propelled
by the jets on its back,
and floats with an anti-gravity unit.
"Anti-gravity"?!
The island A.C. system makes this possible,
but someday it might be all over the globe!
Whoa! Check out this city!
I've never seen buildings like these.
Let's climb higher!
Look, a monster!
Cool!
And a giant robot?!
How many are there?!
Those fish are flying!
Is it because of the anti-gravity device?
What a futuristic city!
Darn tootin'!
On this island, the future is now!
This is Future Island, Egghead!
Above the clouds is
the laboratory level, the Labophase!
And down below is
the factory level, the Fabriophase!
The workers and researchers live there.
I hear your captain is down
there causing a hullabaloo.
Good to know he's okay.
Here we are!
Labophase
Future Island, Egghead
I can hardly wait!
Hey Zoro, aren't you coming?!
And you, Brook?!
I'll watch the ship.
Me, too.
I don't trust that woman.
Man, this jackass...
Oh, Lilith! Just ignore that Moss Head nobody!
What is it?
Try it.
Try what?
It's like the sky island!
Right?!
Really?!
What the heck?!
So cool!
This is so nostalgic!
Oh, really?
First time for me!
What the heck is this?!
Did Vegapunk make this too?!
Yep! You're spot on!
By precisely conditioning the island's air,
I modified the density of pyrobroin
and moisture in the condensation nuclei,
recreating the island clouds
and sea clouds of the sky islands!
My guess wasn't that spot on...
This here's the entrance to the lab!
Cool!
Flashy!
Before you enter, change into lab suits!
That right there is a trancos, a changing room!
Welcome.
Please select your preferred attire.
My preferred attire...
What the hell is this?!
Try that lever on the dom shoes there.
They'll fit any old foot!
These, right?
They look heavy...
So light!
And cute!
You look great in that, Robin!
It's perfect!
These could squeeze the life right out of you!
Why do you say morbid stuff like this...?
These future outfits have me all hyped!
Way to go, Vegapunk!
They fit perfectly even on my body!
Super!
Mine's just a regular aloha shirt!
Well, Nami and Robin
look super cute, so who cares?!
I've never seen fashion like this!
Yours is great, Robin! You look tough!
Yeah?
How do I look?
You look like a perv in anything!
You're too kind!
Geniuses can even see their own future...
What are you talking about, Vegapunk?
I think...
I'm going to die soon.
Enough with the jokes!
That's not funny.
I just wanted you to know that...
Dragon.
Shouldn't you have gone with them?
This is a government island.
Who's gonna bust them out
if they get caught?
I thought that might be the case.
Care for some tea?
Sure. Thanks.
My good sirs!
You're still here?
N-Now wait just a minute!
I know I said I'd get off
anywhere that wasn't Wano...
But not here, my good sirs!
This is a government island!
I heard you helped out our captain. Thanks.
Now scram.
I'll make them pay for this!
At the Lab
That looks like fun!
All right!
This is radical!
The stairs are moving!
They're coming right out of the ground!
What's the mechanism?
What powers it?
Fire's what runs this island!
You can convert fire into any form of energy.
Are there a lot of resources here?
I've been researching what things burn best.
If there was only a flame that wouldn't
go out, I could even make a sun!
A sun?!
Huh?!
That's a wall!
Hey, open up!
What's the holdup? Come on through!
Don't let your peepers trick you.
Lilith! Lilith!
What's wrong, Edison?
Lilith, my sweet!
I can't hear anything now–
His neck! His head!
Don't worry.
If his head were cut off,
there'd be blood everywhere.
Thanks for the commentary!
It wasn't scary at all!
Sanji! Are you alright?!
Yeah.
You can just walk through.
Doesn't look like it...
Alright.
What?!
I'll go, too.
H-Hey...
Excuse me.
I went through...
Why?
Why did they make it so confusing?
Huh?
What?! The door's just iron on this side!
How does it work?!
Lilith's gone!
Hey!
Walk right on ahead!
Huh? Who's that?
My name's Vegapunk Edison!
Another Vegapunk?!
Glad you could join us.
Step right this way!
Just a little more.
I wonder what's ahead.
Time to look for the treasure of the future!
What's "the treasure of the future"?
Something like flowers made of gemstones!
I can't tell if that's childish or old-fashioned...
Future Kick!
Someone's there!
Huh?
Hey! Why?!
Jinbe?!
He's too young.
He looks different, as well.
Possibility one: It's Jinbe's child!
Possibility two: Jinbe was turned into a child!
No...
Possibility three: He's Jinbe's doppelganger!
He has wings...
and a weird vibe...
Hey! Who are you?!
He looks like a kid, but he's as big as Jinbe!
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Possibility four!
It's a pacifista!
It was a set-up!
I knew the government
wouldn't be so hospitable!
Stop, Jinbe!
He's not reacting to that name.
So he's a clone of Jinbe?
That doesn't make it easier!
And I'm not about to start beating up a kid!
He's a power user?!
What's going on?!
What do you wanna do, Nami?!
Do you wanna fight?!
Wait, Zeus!
Hey! Hold on a sec!
That power belongs to...
Nami!
Hey! Stop!
Jinbe...
You bastard! Let go of Nami!
Damn you!
Vegapunk's work or not,
I'll make you pay!
Alright! Death penalty it is!
Even if you are...
the real Jinbe!
I concur.
What you just did is unforgivable!
Gigante Fleur!
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
Spank!
Get away, Robin!
He uses fishman karate, too?!
Lethal Green Star!
Skull Bombgrass!
Even though I know it's not Jinbe,
it just doesn't feel right!
Did it work?!
Yeah, I think so!
He's gone!
He's gone?!
Why?!
I hit him, didn't I?!
Hey!
Let go of me!
Usopp!
Sanji, leave it to me!
Usopp, don't move!
Damn you! Let go of me!
I said don't move!
That energy...
What in tarnation...?
Radical...
Dodge it, S-Shark!
Beam!
He used a darn laser beam!
Who is this feller?!
It packs one helluva punch, too!
That was a close one!
Edison
the Visionary
The seraphim is just a young'un!
He ain't ready for a laser
experiment just yet!
Damn right!
How much does he think one seraphim costs?!
Should I rip this numbskull's head off?!
That's evil!
Don't show pirates even a lick of mercy!
I'm gonna bury them right here!
That's really evil!
S-Shark, beat the devil outta them!
Give 'em a good thrashing!
That's enough!
I wasn't gonna go that far!
Eureka! I just came up with a new invention!
Really now?
I'll take care of this, then!
I'll leave the rest to you...
Pythagoras!
Excuse me?!
Of course!
You don't get interesting
battle data like this every day!
I've got to draw up some blueprints!
So busy, so busy!
I'd even take help from a cat at this point!
Wonderful!
Excellent!
The seraphim's attack patterns
are developing as he grows!
Could this support my theory that experiences
are stored in one's hereditary elements?
Come on!
Really give it to 'em!
S-Shark!
This could be the solution to
the accelerated growth issue!
Heart rate over 90 BPM!
Green blood is flowing faster!
Show 'em what you're made of!
York the Greedy
The more I write...
the more my stomach growls!
There's no stoppin' these ideas!
I ain't got time to eat!
I need you to chow down for me, York!
Okay!
That's the ticket! My noggin
is soakin' up the nutrients!
I've got even more ideas!
Eat! Eat! York!
Another helping for you, Dr. York.
Nuh-uh, not enough!
Get me more!
Yes, doctor! Right away!
Yummy!
Her current BMI is over 600!
I don't want any more!
That's it, S-Shark!
The battle data keeps updating!
Oh no, not now...!
Ow, ow... I'm calling a temporary truce!
I can't miss this opportunity
to monitor his growth!
I gotta go to the bathroom,
but I can't waste any time!
Much better!
Digestion Punch!
That's it! Time to experiment!
Please bring me all materials
relating to devil fruits!
Deliver everything to Dr. Pythagoras!
Prep for Dr. Edison's experiment!
To simulation room 88!
Nap time.
That's Dr. York's fourth
snack, dump, nap cycle today!
Are you serious?!
That's enough, seraphim.
Stand down.
Edison, Lilith, Pythagoras!
I think you've had enough.
Oh, what a shame...
Consarn it!
Ouch!
Why's that scoundrel butting in?!
We were just getting to the good part!
Eureka!
Did that guy come to rescue us?
No way, he's just as shady
as the rest of them!
He's probably a colleague of Lilith's.
So this guy must be...
I am Dr. Vegapunk Shaka.
Shaka the Just
Another one?!
What's with you guys?!
You must be the Straw Hat Pirates.
We are! Now tell us what's
wrong with these shoes!
They're stuck to the floor!
Dom shoes can easily be controlled
by the magnets in the laboratory.
So resistance is futile, then.
We can't trust pirates.
There was also a female Vegapunk,
and another that was talking over the speakers...
Yeah...
I am Vegapunk as well.
I don't get it!
How many of you guys are there?!
Maybe I'm Vegapunk, too...
What?!
Like hell you are!
Does this island look like
the future to all of you?
Yeah, it's amazing!
It's not just any future!
There were those mechanical sea beasts!
Plus, the Vegaforce-01
and the island A.C. system, too!
It's a hell of a future!
And I've never seen a city like that...
I wanna snoop around
and see how everything works!
Don't be so cold!
Let's be pals, Vega!
Even my technology is still so far behind...
This island is from the past.
What?!
What do you mean "from the past"?!
What if I were to tell you...
that 900 years ago, there was
an advanced kingdom like Egghead...?
Would you believe me?
Nine hundred years ago?!
What are you talking about?!
It's real!
Look, Chopper!
It's not a holo-holo!
It's really there!
It's made of iron!
What is this?!
It's pretty beat-up.
Did it use to work?
That would require futuristic technology.
Isn't it too old?
I wanna ride it!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's go, Chopper!