Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Amazon Lily
The Isle of Women
Calm Belt
Amazon Lily
The Isle of Women
Calm Belt
Amazon Lily
The Isle of Women
Calm Belt
The Matter Involving Captain Koby
For centuries, our law has strictly
forbidden men from entering.
We've nyever been invaded by men like this.
Part of the mountain was destroyed,
and the town suffered heavy damage.
If I remain here, the Marines will return.
Where should I go?
At a time like this...
I wanna marry Luffy...
You always want that.
A Few Weeks Ago
We've breached the gate!
The mast!
Keep attacking!
Sink them along with their ships!
Deploy the new pacifista—
the seraphim—to the front lines!
Ensure the cameras are recording!
Got it!
Vice Admiral Yamakaji
Marine Headquarters
No sign of Hancock yet...
Vice Admiral Yamakaji
Marine Headquarters
Warship spotted off the stern!
Behind us! Pirates!
Who is it?!
Emperor Blackbeard's crew is here!
Seaquake!
The sea kings will notice!
Who's that?!
We can't fight a child!
That's one strong kid!
And don't you think she...?
I've come for you, Pirate Empress!
I won't let the Marines
have your devil fruit power!
Hancock... That beautiful face...
I wanna take her head
and make it my treasure.
Do what you like after I've taken her power!
C'mon!
Shouldn't we take her alive
and have fun with her?
Halt, Blackbeard Pirates!
Vice Admiral Yamakaji!
Give us the order to attack
Emperor Blackbeard!
Wait for word from headquarters!
What?!
I have no business with you guys!
Show yourself...
Boa Hancock!
Blackbeard!
I guess it was inevitable that pirates
would try to capture the former Warlords!
Damn!
There's no end in sight!
Watch out!
I'm gonna die!
Let's go.
We've got to do something
about this situation first...
Hancock!
We, the Marines, would
prefer to avoid bloodshed!
If you allow us to take you into custody,
you have my word we will withdraw!
Don't be so cocky, Koby the Hero!
Leave him to us, Big Sis!
Preposterous.
No one can capture me.
I do not bow to anyone!
Wait!
No, Big Sis!
Commodore Teach!
Nothing's working against hi–
Hey, now...
You all let one brat take you out?!
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me...
White hair.
Brown skin.
Black wings?!
"PX"?!
Don't tell me...
he's a pacifista?!
Damn!
This brat is a pacifista?
What's going on here?!
This brat...
is something else!
Black Hole!
Hey, this doesn't look good...
– Hubba-hubba!
Wow!
Hancock!
The Blackbeard Pirates, too?!
Slave Arrow!
This is bad...
We've got to go stop her, Helmeppo...
Helmeppo!
Vice Admiral Yamakaji!
Pacifista! Wait!
You'll shatter everyone who was petrified!
Pacifista!
This is an order! Stop!
So that's Koby!
Perfume...
I can't dodge it!
Black Vortex!
How's that, Boa Hancock?
My darkness absorbs devil fruit powers.
Emperor Marshall D. "Blackbeard" Teach
Bounty:    3.996 Billion
Former Warlord "Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock
Bounty:    1.659 Billion
Snake Princess!
Her devil fruit power has been nullified!
Unhand me...
you filth.
Well, there's the Pirate Empress
we all know and love!
Good grief...
All my stupid crew members
have been turned to stone!
How should I proceed?
Just as I thought, she's unimaginably tough!
Boa Hancock!
I've come for your power!
This power is nothing without my beauty.
If you kill me, your people
will remain petrified.
The next user cannot undo it.
We're getting nowhere.
Koby the Hero!
You did me a solid during
the Rocky Port Incident!
Thanks to you, I was able
to take down Ochoku,
and take his place as the boss of Pirate Island!
So, Hero!
If I take my hand off this wench,
do you think she'll turn
my men back, just like that?
She needs to change back our Marines, too!
If you all agree to leave quietly…
I'll do it!
No.
You're lying!
If I unhand you, you'll petrify us.
And that'll be it.
Am I wrong?
Frankly, it's hard to think of a man...
who wouldn't fall victim
to that technique of yours.
What should I do?
I guess I should just kill you!
Please, wait!
Those losses would be too great!
I knew the Marines would lay siege here...
but to think it would reshape
the very island itself...
D-Dark King Rayleigh!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Hancock.
Rayleigh...
Hey.
Whitebeard's little apprentice!
I know it's childish to say this,
but I just don't like you!
What?!
That's the Silvers Rayleigh?!
Hancock.
Undo your petrification.
I'll keep watch until the end.
Nobody will try anything foolish.
Everyone will leave this island!
Present Day
I'm really glad...
that you're alive.
Thank you, Rayleigh.
"Dark King" Silvers Rayleigh
Right Hand of the Pirate King
Advances in technology
can create new menaces.
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Shakuyaku
Former Captain of the Kuja Pirates
Empress of Amazon Lily Two Generations Ago
Because of Vegapunk's
seastone paddle ships...
the Calm Belts are no longer safe.
The Marine siege.
The introduction of these nyew weapons.
Blackbeard's raid.
I thought we were doomed...
Frankly, I was only able to save you
due to the particulars of the situation.
I've gotten old.
Nowadays, I don't think I could
beat Blackbeard in a fight head-on.
So the Marines thought those new weapons...
could replace you guys, the Seven Warlords...
In the end, those two...
...got away without even a scratch!
But the strange thing is...
one of them looked just like our
big sister when she was a child.
Aye aye. Proceeding directly
to the port of Egghead.
About Captain Koby's kidnapping…
CAPTAIN KOBY
900!TR;5BpG.!
8anLI.bMGWJw!
6E"5;SImhTns!
d5kx7OaccIsH!
yM20zy"7n.X6W
T:NiCEujA:lAw
oM9wZFnCplEfY
s6qT'RlHdt'yE
CAPTAIN KOBY
CAPTAIN
qpx
twIUY
18Hfi1uu
SHuTQ8s9jd!
P3szTjF0ir7?Ei
OBC
lNC8e
0e3iD:zx
StuaH9AeAg'
u9MF6It?IZV1"b
CAPTAIN
Ih:
R.wVd
F?KXnUad
bZVWZa'3Pg!
EhHI,ApJ"Es7OT
S0K
V4dhU
,R"z9Yqs
LP:v9uMMNBw
,,.T4JFnozqho'
CAPTAIN
xFM
E.gGB
CyRhTwmk
11"xdubbn.!
PCpMpAFqGCsn"J
a18
CUv"P
bXKfmq6O
rI16;?9M7;L
mqRDAgv4rQSnfp
CAPTAIN
YBV
0QeOU
Xl"?lJI"
trNVnNKTQi!
'?7!'npDDPFGCt
"G;
6:q4:
orU4S4E'
m.NZCNMNkew
D0J2Mczktd1Hpd
CAPTAIN
b3P
i?nr0
hWvb9jxF
0f?Bl5F8f3!
VON4t7v6BO!caM
vIT
m2,.7
emaqHeh2
w!.w1yv?65h
z1NZU94a2;M;dI
CAPTAIN
.4d
lu.:z
S171HH9t
MWGH.TQ.vD!
:yeusWste:JZRb
q.r
FX3D'
6hWOkEb6
W6gIxqQPDdT
h4wW'Nr8CBH.o,
CAPTAIN
ott
i:bu!
negmUkRc
i71uaXIgRj!
P6Sd!qLBT;bvbh
Tid
EaPYa
,nmwfjLv
Nu0z,26KU.J
97de'OtOeXcGLq
CAPTAIN
g!N
MHi.0
AnF?:hc2
pidNRYWY"q!
q19c;5u?ddmpU3
FkN
Bxg!l
lbjQ7bxj
o??NHfsBmhz
UCxSTXBL0UAqyZ
CAPTAIN
t1D
lE1.x
JDbr9mrv
I6MJg?srHN!
dZALl!StHYPabW
vH6
cm4u7
4yqtw0jI
tZHMb"x1pNV
bEU1AHGDW6"9Xz
CAPTAIN
ZG5
t1HG7
m8wDm6;b
TGY:cpROpc!
;!jx90YQnlQxH,
?xI
QH8uQ
vy'ZqT3J
:VbEoCCEuM:
e4IZU:iNITTdUk
CAPTAIN
6hW
i,VW4
1Ew.yFdm
kALwadzsCY!
OgQBl"?WQ!NyN0
yWY
1w;xN
T9RPTO8K
,e:ZqBOwZt3
1IDy6ObQbgN8Ne
CAPTAIN
T7j
oe6hB
i7Ajls'V
dznWQas?J,!
tYt;D3Q2LMn9Ik
DkE
T5HJ2
ONdsvBrq
ZvBWXWRb'IH
lxMx"gQTy4n0uL
CAPTAIN
Ok9
Kp78Y
pU0efm,g
mw?lfO0Xax!
17'Ig"o"MKVouO
vy?
3;",8
!n3KpT,c
KZSqwvB0'EQ
,Q9'L?Xo"U:a3H
CAPTAIN
MaL
.7JEX
iOOxcZ!5
eDehQcLBGZ!
nzD2g8jSfvaKcT
k7j
3BdNt
nPEt"SAj
qRm:5G8DVSY
zT"E74KcVW':L9
CAPTAIN
z:W
fROCD
l?LAm3AF
3v'RcHTy3M!
5l5gk4l?LMuxp:
WBQ
cKaVF
YNJwp6lH
UI1?HZFazDR
BDbDY4Gi;ZnwYw
CAPTAIN
ol6
Y0VKU
Wyk',zCO
oSVL:s8LuI!
nma8Dr1YxdKkYp
u2F
2z9ED
zzHjzKjR
2hPaalWJqO3
STq'mQ62B4lWKG
CAPTAIN
Zs6
,YzmC
REvb5:L;
hw,p1Nwhu.!
j'qHa6B1DEUTwR
LvW
kfv,3
z"w!LoZJ
i;F!0NXUS?:
g6ccc5a!TJPdvn
CAPTAIN
8'4
EkbIy
mbKvZt,w
v0Gox1O;aQ!
z3z:18F872Z87Y
5jP
ei3rC
y3t31uVs
vbgJFFVb'uK
mhLwcBrVvDyTtY
CAPTAIN
B6Z
86bD;
P,tY!1g0
Qwq7s0Tpea!
0M',;9x8ghd3d?
uCm
7F414
V7QjnRE:
CO1f0Q!L8Lv
1;RTQkZHZ1jUcW
CAPTAIN
V;6
C1SEl
6vUdqKdD
o:FMFCzWS:!
9Gk2M7aB5lYSzP
!MK
LXh:9
R?r7GP6J
w9mbxPSbWo8
6aCNR8MnUcTkJE
CAPTAIN KOBY
Fh7F'a3'YxAllapPl!
hs9Oaqr;YFZ.Wxl
pfIxb3BAjfOa4s:rh!
"TIq"JfoZ7gJ?ZDCie2!
R46NG47Z.60hdm8bBy
I1hVLKsAaoQl10A
R5;VpEGu?k2MJmwAvv
SrcJ2YAGx1KKc7rYSF0O
CAPTAIN KOBY
MC49oENTC3BJcHmL0!
:.UfHUNIHOPEy1K
juSLZdSvQDmVXUsFH!
Bd,,bUQ6Q3auK!8o:8"!
V:f,RNN5QYyH5ysz4S
bX6?kNN2W;,ulb;
okEya"DltkFpd6XRaf
Kih05wD:?mXm3tiynI8N
CAPTAIN KOBY
J7Dh3CKetoK3ck6?8!
Mw'dxh7zaADeT2F
nIXKy02RpVMRUn8L"!
".biJ!QzT1Flg9.B1RH!
9!rL3nVuI'g4yRZY.0
"Y0:h024HRqT.1g
?BXy1O7TPyk708TSik
T5NMjh1fXY3'Rsh5ZXzS
CAPTAIN KOBY
"r:cM58OmKb5CTp2H!
X!a!rVMMQ"hGTp!
DH's7JM9TU9YZcpa2!
.kQHMNPRL;8c:KB!Xst!
qgB7!lzzi3k6PlkBbB
f4P3'qRFl2'Fs!o
T4zrn6rclt0UOW:hny
tzs3WNFKW;5ah?C7lcC1
CAPTAIN KOBY
Yhuep:nNA5GTtRsqi!
oNnjkE,Wwjd;0Gx
T:nBrhP3oyb1YCs,3!
d:rmx5wbTNWDlxM.lGE!
lpreim0NYMxtIxJuOe
!NkJxaTKds8VaxF
64:nnK22?hDJ7gN2m4
mgNKn16zqN3Gk:IcoOlt
CAPTAIN KOBY
EZB';huEc:YD4"!K:!
tU0do!H"mBDNPRn
g2Niq!VvrLJP2qa0;!
SZ,qEnzgY.!Qef,QNdN!
GLUfpnDYH'Z'wn6K:k
Yiw';C4.2IBN,XF
zhN:Y2FE5wO'LiO'ld
iy6TxnzsNPajEYRON7NP
CAPTAIN KOBY
OdHTqoMCcx10ajvjq!
MjEycupxXeqqi14
G,STztR,Ygr!tS"n7!
FNSu'tkVY'm9,hE5p!s!
KErO2Xw"MRcQZveLJ9
AA79sbqiHS;Wm!"
OA92qQ9dn50rVxDXgs
JNQ.k!IFkPo,E'tOBwP.
CAPTAIN KOBY
G;0aqc0zC8vUKh?Ro!
edGpu'FdOooC,Xh
rbdsH7q:d"Xd7!o0X!
IX?t;c540'PVzD6tz0I!
8gfgn5p7nFJoqg"Ct;
:jll0y0zccUhxQv
NiU!1zP1o,NwIGDiT?
"?,nqsEPR2!ohlB7gDOL
CAPTAIN KOBY
u?On,FSyXsWTyAOQ5!
.,:XYoB!pkgwdbg
gdneP1h!XUrTv9YNl!
3!1y7!!:;mmb"y,Ak,N!
Cw0RkOH,oCAp;yURcH
6hJx;S?U;UeXMcC
rtk;LEezmgJCl50N'G
UFP'6ph7yn6luykfTQNY
CAPTAIN KOBY
f1K3LdgpEXRBSlPMJ!
MFM2'TEgtCg;qS;
A32pUXsCWotInqsx;!
lBcdLRyCcqA"3h560gO!
KnebMGoZo1qax"R5X;
EkCnZBfahEli1aQ
iCowM17:641.5z4Uh:
nQyM9??3gwfIod52rdgi
CAPTAIN KOBY
Y98mbFalV"hR"xoOt!
Mk:aKXoik!rA9rW
W0bCGl3LY7lRHRnxK!
KPRgWP8.ItR;bMxqN"9!
zCK4vJq6zNP?crolzX
zmPU3u07Ke0HS:t
l0p;cMMaNCVEkaZOY9
CPRiWQq3Og78RN,CNwue
CAPTAIN KOBY
dUF8zU!OJb;POTnv1!
TQE5XAXquQGYntH
M91D0Tnk6Y;H3BhsZ!
'"piYvW,kZ23V.Xn3i;!
RtYC7fQPs,LRqp'lic
HVLoCVV9svpgI7v
CtJVh"VOU3uLtmZPRI
LI,g1hDtJ2!7PHwYXIkC
CAPTAIN KOBY
c!XZ0p;NR'MsNh0cp!
c!'AKVJ'TK,MW.l
b3vOZeyxFM.OP'K66!
gQKUmaVASc0P.YCka7q!
j:LAN!wN0wgVN3PhIW
mZEMh:WYtJMyery
KzF4pL3fnsQLb3xAbW
'rXxz2e4Sf8g8vuGI6Se
CAPTAIN KOBY
f?H.RL4SP!qMPQT76!
Ea?MxWJUMKWLL6G
qXzIsBoXHCIZ:eZwT!
qZz!IzkOarnUtqQA6.R!
Q2WEiNf:cerbYY5J7a
23V,ASShvwKNXC!
SX;AIlwdD6nVXytzlI
5"qehJpZCSPU57r?daYF
CAPTAIN KOBY
Ts33qgMBl8U45ySXx!
W.G!E'NJyPaES5d
Rjm!CCcci!MAhHTm1!
hjQ8,P!!"U7.9v0zJZC!
;WM.rx1W'797PW41vD
WTSAv0N,zuUKxYw
Bnzooop?7b38,WaS9e
c4hZc36RkK.prheKm6xC
CAPTAIN KOBY
0:EVkglpf1FSM'zD4!
wNyrx,MSsNJL;Ra
EzL'xPVWeJ0Ml1ry4!
yfF9u?mY'DUh59gIThX!
Dy4?.b67bt:4rMvXb7
'Nwqzb"93NEA6Wq
rVnFXn5Q.McJehxoE4
IcH;?s9Sq!oBaJUy?H!?
CAPTAIN KOBY
xw.9m?tMu4iwz33P"!
y?7dCe3FJO4.LU9
Ag9o8RO"dyM8C33TC!
jZa;m!U'D9aesD.dNY8!
HU;Fc0zktRB2ErKxG1
FBxK?lsNw64ITKE
ryluNVd7AgDbP3OBC8
TAD0WgJ13M9YuNoJN7mZ
CAPTAIN KOBY
SSiUWIFb?5SYk"cu7!
:UbcjPKExxi9BYv
HDxkK"RXqjcbhk0jq!
Em8Y;5,XfDpjDfOPm7"!
0:3NWk1:YBgJk3Kt4a
vcOZz8UJAbfgBc8
8udt1es9chUR:iGx38
O0nrMWpQRyznHV:SWyYl
CAPTAIN KOBY
AK1k:Bd;:'J'I7"N"!
TJHeec.SZToU43Z
oWfhUQfdop4PSmWOU!
;:;vYDN:fC7XV'OjIX5!
Et;qFo3So9NvBfSNbT
5US59O17BJnWvoi
UQv7q9.VY:uxV6Lw'W
FnF3XoNPa'y.GBXfO6.A
CAPTAIN KOBY
FSAspQLnWfb9NuBQz!
.:'t8XK:;F4RLgm
rhA.;yEIwy"OUJtEU!
vSuVJ6qYdbTiLqWbWSy!
cQ2YnEGZQoEiNNGIqy
BSb2H,f5T4F"6RH
e;OYSGcSYqhEL;SdEr
!Tyh5mQu:Z85"mHmr'C;
WAEhu:9Tetst7Es79!
b,"V4WS5h"YFTYg
CvDlz3K6DPe0LyXmv!
sPpxTs17;gRYaQ1!Mdt!
Rtf;lO5b2aCPad"ZO4
b;"NcmUTOkZP5La
m'biO1LRY0aOuHkLa8
26;BI5rRtFhZVFCbVLZ1
CAPTAIN KOBY
dM1?oq7nRl;AqfVUj!
cS5q!.ervTNYB:M
QK!RAsNjcMKtXjsOX!
vUB.8r;0pCUCGnoHcxU!
1OCa,6iY,5Ui6KvaWh
!!tBBXJb8"NfA!D
?JophYNDxmrBkFIRT0
G8:7GMfdCmx8EykvrYfp
CAPTAIN KOBY
PfXji?:kzB,3GqyE,!
P:!7,GD2L,vOZQn
oPfeR0ZchdoWIs"Q8!
LK8.3d8uRMj87o6K:hx!
108wa:4?.w3yTfDIz8
4elOnedrnSf;X'j
rhr0P"Ty."JwsrdN3X
LOCp9Jsnw.MPIMw0b6Q"
CAPTAIN KOBY
f.P,tk;L.VHVjcMVW!
RHkko,IiUyo1?ez
uFc1qFaT2A:eEA1fm!
vEyfgF2;zajnO"UiwR'!
EjH3H98MYi4y"9MrA3
dsf6Y6ej32.A,An
php7qeAp2UZtqtNzwm
8fk1jD36tZWVDO6XrcpR
CAPTAIN KOBY
C64cJleXId.gjSDJ'!
nbAQ.RH5RK.?6dG
VfJypR?K6CR'Jq7L:!
Tb.wPGUNtdUDqjbjUbX!
;QY1OkaD.n85qd36G?
zx"2nSw6:2H6Bis
kJ"QiXldv?m5L94;UW
P5eiWteNZgluWPvXsSaF
CAPTAIN KOBY
3D1cuTKwOY6vDrLhv!
fBN5PRyHLX4xTkF
wBl4mw5RikQKGtdvO!
9fPn4nZMcZIH6gf,Ka:!
E.HYe7TNb:jN4yp5O?
eLNvFiufsGFMJfl
B1T5u3:RMF;OPvSjg8
VK'GuB2fJAfQ:'A,cH7V
CAPTAIN KOBY
bnmT5oy0C.wyFPxRq!
JK0FTL0Q6eD4Sqw
3jjhC?7cKgoLDfaW6!
AOd?dajjWV0,xhD3lAV!
Os?RbJNznc9LVseHDi
uPNVQqgfiHNnY!.
6FpF6;JU5z7xlC:L9"
GmR5.zohb!kwTJ29bpFe
CAPTAIN KOBY
4mDfbk"!zfsmSMoGR!
7AH2KJ:dTVJ'naI
0piZK4EENqEN'hS6X!
PFjjLkSlz'EtnfpaqIt!
,M!LmmxQ0LffEZXsPq
4UY'wr33rTxcU1S
LJC99r9zN9lN'j15gJ
.Xq0vFUJA:7syM8o'iNw
.zpHeVu4E5":n;;fo!
elgV?sEnLD:TI5J
fmxbG1nrwTpozW,Iy!
t.ficrO:;LWJB90c0OB!
vtTXaqIOphuQMWqF'9
na8"pozKNk'ye0x
NRfppa?"qFBZ'cZ4Qd
9YCHNLT;KfNaI9EbRQro
CAPTAIN KOBY
vzpg"hSTJs5,qr0EM!
oqx5;vM,44nHWbF
iZk3kC7RDXnZLBuTl!
vC3bpf.K0sNuBR83Y1r!
DNW7JyyPmy9qDSc?Mr
Vb:j,mQAF8.jnFk
n?mmfOOyS;iIZgY99n
ek0AtdnrTUNQ7J"eqX2e
CAPTAIN KOBY
u;eRxCq4Phb48w1fL!
3kYEAwxGy7DKPPc
.ng6Oi89XTIO07eTq!
L9"ud7JqDB0hj9;5uI7!
VO.IB,eTi5Qa5:0WqQ
!E3Gx1,5W0R3gKu
Qi7J9QmWZ!a6eZcXo!
idyyLH':JEU;8M!0.p3"
Captain Koby, the hero
of the Rocky Port Incident,
CAPTAIN KOBY
JuP2iU:bGcIz2f?67!
2.WvzoxITn9,zAm
5qnN3,PxzXnNN8La"!
FuULpRSkA2E.F,1hOkv!
pY1mXX!8zRJGMJ!5SP
eWZW5aXIUF!BvX8
PYYNwhx8oJDNNoVG8z
c'rghM.?yDf1K5epHb,w
CAPTAIN KOBY
A0,"bH;f6NokAlEG.!
0T,D'MqXw?RR7aB
8wpSrOcX"B;tKH0vc!
JyRLUvosC0CrQhF1vTU!
XEngJFnyuN3:zEdwxM
2w,RzqOY0HcKKrp
4134HBDNv:qX5nJ;qP
,LS7oz;6?hnQlEcnVzq;
CAPTAIN KOBY
T6J;R:wkJVBIahVT:!
C6PB?nCBaV4D3cW
DqabLw7FQ,mzQ'NxD!
vbbizhNkFXg8kVSUhzP!
6N0Qtt;F9VuyElapZR
!OR"TDlgcwGHG;g
Uq;:nPWubgAcp:NUTx
d.8:G3NPcsTyNu',2k1s
CAPTAIN KOBY
7BV0coBXvJ!2w9SG2!
V!SEWGN6C;bCB.d
Mi3xpwhe48kfMUJcL!
aoSkpVKQV4F?3t.qBji!
31,Bmf0a?.j;0O:ciC
pS2!.jNg0T;6ebA
tMs57hJnalMQ3ZOb5R
p1774z.K9'X?lh6LuH;N
CAPTAIN KOBY
gg3UA?MGCQMIBWn0"!
GRGwvXgT?JhnDg1
dJyL?jq,Lb"pW:ED4!
Bwx4'KzDHpyX2TwTJoF!
H4S:ee0evOq3dH?6gJ
DRdyC7qYegfDX.z
Z5b'TPwa,iQC9UOXIz
x3a?Y3NRoTLcGu1duPkv
CAPTAIN KOBY
cweYxcuPG31c0:V:z!
;v;f0EP:HKWkjW'
IBW;zEdCAw1r,;dK"!
SSg.qN3AMuAD,IRQBx4!
ighEnj.1fSNcWYb1RY
.,Qy!H8LAOeh.sZ
K31pi2haBR0'zDcfAV
Ehhk1N8VcNQEsb8JBfd2
CAPTAIN KOBY
5.G57pqbPEtsJP'iK!
wLryhiRmxHHUFb8
xqzkZhjjvu4nzfvsc!
cYmJ9Q0DQ3cZQQC7pZN!
IA,Q.a!:!07lEG'UGt
.8WLllis"gSG?HG
e8QtSsQOcj'PBe:EIp
ADTq"Vh1yX6tvDaybRN.
CAPTAIN KOBY
yp9UooHkcGYgoQN1n!
f6JtSdj74YwFMRc
?Sqm!36FUFAQkki1f!
HfFdpcthbUnt1?1cwdi!
Ax;8,"t;pGZBssNHOJ
!ozBxkz0tl5FglZ
6kzxaMKstBOO92fisZ
ptJmJwEuCbQW'RH,46Ap
CAPTAIN KOBY
AGVHZ?;SNPw;?PyeP!
E0M!63L9epVeS!5
!ViUT;Ke5GtxmTrkB!
IZe3e.OiO!V"aoPyx4W!
AZjaXUoUNRGmWfUh6p
uW4KX0g;uDikQVw
qyHY3zM.DSpdgtPHmf
8vF02L8Bx7luj:xCXVfF
CAPTAIN KOBY
SQWJ?Ey4XR0lF5bv"!
fOZEqjMair".4wp
9d4uWHm:XJFkeWbM8!
MZyfMYuR?yf'LTp"GhU!
b44sx3K3.TT4!bliup
LUgIMjhnzLQqCd6
JxtCrbSYB'nxQZA4P!
j32,hF4au1Bb"enM7ONz
CAPTAIN KOBY
upcYhZ8onXJ.xZWxd!
Sj8;7RQS,HdEqt:
pLcvkaB'crybZ,IWp!
QVyh5eR?BlyxBffwE,g!
os:UeLE7h?ZLV,QSkx
5nEVXZJ1'F6Cfny
yzT6Mu6OSJ!QgsMZb.
I8HUs9fJdqqs"mPiRU2b
CAPTAIN KOBY
Ny!.OOyUBJxc?3C5?!
DQKqcvWr!IqpVY4
"R0cwUeMEl:4p!yHY!
;Xly0B8tJ3.6MDV97AQ!
NIo48ajKr72pVt4v,t
c5ytGm??a.s,.AR
wrJtDhqrgOu2iSps5a
xGRXduLRrvRMK:VcZcmx
CAPTAIN KOBY
4vm1!CP?oNEzLNe9M!
Z;?nScC9'q"dig6
xKA2S784GH1vem3xP!
j,n3N7SDKu6kV'LFWEu!
tXLSy9UQ7Nu3UNAXvn
s!RN7"Jp.hG"0O2
jtbz0:rhTLu!aq548C
V6J3NE6b20fJkAzRIPlE
CAPTAIN KOBY
OCJgrOYBiZ!?SF0YY!
'rlBsSa:V8?JGjX
CnmAi9PswXm,y:9Eh!
3pnkFustPAc2q,U1ofV!
!gC88W8lchiboXkEkD
WZk3H'BpuYkNNfL
X0x7f.1N?3;Y;vDh6H
b9uWuLEUJYiR7Q2i0BSX
CAPTAIN KOBY
m6WZqzUUB85hv.deD!
5'IxY59uZ:JQpc;
WH.Eczu,IZ5RjSh77!
.B"P.XnOXGfYCoikwaA!
oqgeo.EAUcTHMit,2E
,ny9my2LyX?l4L'
csTG7'7iC,?pIcOB1s
rmsG?1pWNqaiV'DKI8GD
CAPTAIN KOBY
R6"auGNDW1lD.Xez?!
ql9A?3.VjlCZtL5
gdj,o;HZ:kK8H0pca!
CcuDmHjwIshC6Ttbfyn!
MwTq7vNp7OAncLrqKV
FDA6FbZy:Y"pJqR
7U4mG1W:EY,9:pYc7E
BGBq8ix,kHr3o.U3tFAW
CAPTAIN KOBY
OHBHKLxTLEgJrflMX!
2UT6r0H47UVtwvw
Aa'!7F5J.1BLQok5n!
xvwP?GcDHXY;rWD"JeA!
QRTOSRg0nujP1zJ2yK
KZWn8Z5iZIovvSr
3M1IqMHaRFjLBOdOlT
",.TNw'RBP1tcyW31yFn
CAPTAIN KOBY
zG33jOa3M0sgewqc3!
Vn8vX6b2jK!tDXe
:z0Nvy3aS6,RXoElu!
:8,n'5BWYvxCEAmTdyB!
uwH0efDh?X3Ozbidhn
,vF9LZGshSQqFtY
0:2Nzeu1hN5'CNrbZ?
Eo5cFTO.xd!y78gvqCWq
bokqn?PS?lUYBZoS.!
UMl84Hnl6CT:DYE
kkCvWlz7uRN!zGn,H!
hrdXmBPP6KByj1R;E'I!
RTxhRmBCB,nHlgGDu1
AeSOCh56;t5PN;T
OSvxJXQ?TmNKWgEVem
w5q10FMLH8iyC9izo54E
CAPTAIN KOBY
CLDn'WDIgp9epm.t;!
4eu8F,96g7eD9tS
yl0KD35WHdtAb,pt;!
nGh0efKdngcZXfZ:Ls0!
XUlAyR4EczaVG..m;Y
IUMddwsHEB?qA2E
xwpOamJiVDPr!.gQiP
KTI2?mMUcsz2h21uA2?K
CAPTAIN KOBY
APp3JIgHQ8XEbm;ve!
bJINcRIFn4e7Nx3
"bpukpbUwv;E3S3.Q!
Oe:dFJuTrcD5q:6H3O:!
sLtx.:xgSvfA29WgfW
TVqNH!NMUjmmNYW
CY9lKs!'bxtOR7eCOj
w8dnjYGkV7"pn;L29yMC
CAPTAIN KOBY
IzD;t8x;lD!KB;1DK!
fJ1kU82z?L32:64
k,OJ!hp;?xCvdO:fb!
bsS8Z4!?5;MVrsmayqo!
GgWXyHG6;IWGNfWizf
O;8cGwnKBU7:X1'
Gsce9uzV!MwdUN3l1v
pAfmmrTZF2NN2t!:kvV:
CAPTAIN KOBY
MQyTdJpQcpcdgvBiT!
.TKMsTVwqMW84dm
jrT.7eudkvX,,wY4t!
9IYxpoQ'.csFequ8?'6!
MtrQPin3OoJ:!Fyfi9
s38?s0489UdqKzZ
XBz1uxPlog'O8bqBMy
Cfn1:cy97!ZquXKYiw2k
CAPTAIN KOBY
;s03"mlWv7eap9cgo!
"fzFsgL2h9oZF7H
hCJ7JJA5R9s'Om1cs!
wtg3oKcd1rBdc8hwA9y!
gMmg;hRNKQQ5.qOnWg
QghGF?'zEvQ14yA
Ub5;Ml7PtEaPTY05rx
vtQkl'O:vjKxiruGPM7;
CAPTAIN KOBY
gCSD:RVLhf,ahgptO!
a8P:?7RdTy3bJP'
rwiheDIH84'b'r8Cr!
rDPDAh9a9cdCh7l4khe!
rajTo2cyl;Nj9LIOgD
UtOfGC'7".7'z5w
9oer'jmnB53n'T0HsU
jncT6l9jyt1QqtpgWB2p
CAPTAIN KOBY
I,hefgB;9oF?gyxjl!
lM5Kma!bPomi,Jv
WH9kZm!jTL8HF7mob!
,'FBeHO?:AUWbF4zWby!
PS8SBUq5mmbIYsYOpp
UmcPxoRoLCibSPZ
ppNT7XMFe7"4YclqU.
G7Nxrfu9SQ'Vn''N9:Zd
CAPTAIN KOBY
qY.RTIPl"5viDAY14!
tdNril:q!1Jfvgq
B!0WSwD,HVdMww1t1!
k?1T66Vfg,JQcWx!MsH!
pd894!'gyKeBwH7i'l
qaNET;8nZdM:LC.
mDzYgKZgmdxafD:MNU
uECiu0qFkw,uAePqwgDE
CAPTAIN KOBY
wP7.DtIvkLaA7RTJP!
g"5'KT;R73Kn32z
Qieb?88TT!5LTbmBv!
Lg8:OxjIuX?dtQxwsEN!
RqFW1P0i72h;qfAGh,
EuoPKvhUV7wu1WW
'QzaZtL,PoNawip!HP
GglS5y3'MjWcYL1fssNw
CAPTAIN KOBY
nQjL2aNzC0dcvt:Z2!
1eyaGf9R9co,AMd
FIBbTkcU3oX2A01?7!
L0nGtOL7:txkzsH1Q0"!
rox.AaNsheu7zwOFOz
GNtIlcY6Ka1xTl.
CgzwvsXM8G8dL!uh?X
EXJF2I,yZsGGqDtBczwb
CAPTAIN KOBY
hkpZ.Teth1RzM4IP!!
daUo4fmcs4iwepx
rD2.CxJGXA3P6GObl!
VQBQR?yeRv:hpcmb7I1!
kWN.jXiMzzrlCcnsGc
o1pF2xVue.6,4"R
FtjXCpihNmoGx?7Qc:
EdR!Y!tVj83Tj:S0o'."
CAPTAIN KOBY
grKS8v8TX?F,26PO9!
MIYgVKnMpYAFPlF
h96MYEEgF,DjZ:b1B!
kB'Ftstc?2JuWROLD01!
JunP,:,JGJKpviwrbL
ycMWCXbfDh!ov9"
oQHFArk0;uOCNQc9Sa
kFWu"Fbw;NwsQbslDB"A
CAPTAIN KOBY
Fv!zQUfyO5H:XJFn6!
KXfA:orxLRMwMp.
g3'v1Zmnyqbe'OqDG!
7h6fNO7D0SjrpKb1xES!
.'32zUuaLxNWAwFmdb
j8?3Gz;aY2O1qC"
N8Pu!RN1BvoeHbQOam
jN.aNJ57!Y!r!XDO4"US
CAPTAIN KOBY
nR2ioQBHONa9;pHLx!
5XMTOoofxOGc0ME
sOTcHiEzWrnMjTJG0!
w62DIQ1zpF6qRGuHXa'!
vGX:OfKioN5c949qje
Td:T4mUi4wcUTuk
wTjeeIuGujeB,YAvTT
HoqOZymOZ'fEJeoaKmx0
vK2u05BOOiy.8TEn4!
!2QswzacsKT!Pfv
QcbgQFeFE7b3yCCST!
oJJsxS3"kizgiQwN,r;!
'w8.5Q!u?;uyw:"s2z
0kvhlVqsbTN3p"s
NS8DVfHraWaHAaruy"
7VUo7AifVpPxmT!N.fY4
CAPTAIN KOBY
wVT.49:T45yUItuDU!
x!NJMthTlkPutdY
aMTU7CS3wx'GWKr5:!
lR7CzeP8Krwpf7!KRp'!
!'zUWa6cptl9yNpJ'9
IxNMZ0rQL2mD30T
c914YBKo6c1:yruLUv
7O6sqKgxfx"7RL:SekWt
CAPTAIN KOBY
k21IGN6TGFwJJWUy1!
exrdanaDS5Av1t,
cj2V;xIcqR:8;0lcb!
0RjI6KqbixcrbNx:Wgq!
vE69cNIAOXNr2L1mx9
hSx04,4ZmYS6.6:
70E0ExRXv1l5r!c02p
HO:nopA4P?zU,NslVzvd
CAPTAIN KOBY
Q9VhqNz3q!"g862fL!
N!eQqoNex0hMWMM
Er7TQ3uR2jVP:e0EL!
vx3!Wks8W4z:ZNWz?1F!
fTpzONEza.aFcmer,z
NZzqvQNG2z.9kLf
JPf;M7ccJZpHBzPTMB
!.ZIB:R?n1D3ZNseBfIh
CAPTAIN KOBY
SsKkZXSJ54O"QUCD7!
gqY:5cL"M4jdT::
QY6,eRD?JxptqVvdE!
!Sr20dKGRG,OcEaWJvh!
bYgrhQaQFop"S8u,GN
vyiGq"D9rGMHO3K
eDsDsH0dVluO..PYaz
sUHXK0mO5pFzggC;"Ki7
CAPTAIN KOBY
L83lT?76?AyS7ZImD!
uumX"G5IN.F2yJ!
Xc.Q;54yTT2gC!9PP!
2xyhjUqT0LH7jY?Fx4"!
Aro6R?UPMh67rKkRqY
1xEN828uNFEenuy
v,qjCpPJCWzALKAyPx
Zy0Zl?jNF1b31cG:vPt8
CAPTAIN KOBY
mLEdFU"MBaUYj4bGy!
9yTnuZI.JD6IKC?
Y25fBms?VIPAT40z9!
KL2"SB;gsdpF,Ze0lWW!
inYY,"!n:3W96YkT1W
JKb".Cw'THMLpZX
!VS!j27IZKsq82RYoD
lwIYBBH8.Q!p8cUl3Yx3
CAPTAIN KOBY
GQ,YaaxqomN2bIwID!
'9gCgM;eUBCwyz2
gZ,ap8fjwTJokPLd!!
TiDpOuBaV69KIGfpcto!
4f5j'mDe7rN6LUhYcX
MnZbCKm;AA"Aw'h
KtQl3I258g1qVE9poR
6nawth4N2AeQVYZjMUil
CAPTAIN KOBY
ra8P.hG6kHJ"lSuQA!
5V"72?L!r"F8MeI
eS.e0T0!q,7!uoTP5!
yHTMsQ8B6VW5n0.iRIo!
tUx3;.CT?Oo27LwXkm
r!2.YjKc9hpHizj
ogx4Vf1gpDvN;P9YK'
?BXgOhm7XRDnjCCXr!fs
CAPTAIN KOBY
c?"x'cEDJ,Kf3A4.:!
uUDuDArdrN3v;.U
fDQ8Zbhec:Fp.Fb!m!
ZLXT16pfceVflm1qp.A!
slj:edJz?kfgdS7eHK
GDlvSI;TMNrotRo
P7WPEZFdBcou7wdPqX
xlGOB;R!Pw4GNpa48j3r
CAPTAIN KOBY
DC7;nwR;ROiHDuG96!
gUUE1LnM8Jz4H8E
6Q6hsNCi;8oS.nmPw!
Hr3U1!pv8,dRS.gK53D!
e:hd;PIg:HQXozO,9P
f9WctExl8sEA'r;
,eYY2N;rUe':lJiIGq
q,sx3d.gYh7Ub9h5LCb;
CAPTAIN KOBY
xKopE46kbiPiLa8A;!
?'y592'1JAxhBQM
eveSbzJpOzpTkhSvO!
qaEdg:18XOflh4ew2SP!
NdHNJZJU:'e,e2u;ho
'u8JPi21mclTQmU
yfOAfSHOZtAbecqXTT
6,:gvqT,X8X.:5sK,5'M
CAPTAIN KOBY
SL,b;Q'8JVX'arXv!!
t9btOg27deqOeut
9Mn!f7hi;iwZYAl2Z!
iXgkATQdhYt4x'XeL6S!
tWxIeg!LO:8NQlklZ0
L'5zoAN9HOcUDco
TGx7OclDRUnb3drX75
4SqBrFuYH'kxV'Xzezn1
CAPTAIN KOBY
hmH4v4;?wbiku9Tdc!
0DgoMhme0or"0Yb
zfXSO6vX2q9Lws7Mv!
!'u3l'F9rZlPTw?izeW!
hnMU6Xc,:cN"aX8DEO
!6AxEoH'6H8tAHx
,1j2VGnu?7ELQ1Bode
NddXAmfS:5J,7eVc9.Jq
CAPTAIN KOBY
u"ZGq!E5e0FvT!Zc6!
q4klke2Z74DTK:!
oBrBNR1dlarN6whaD!
ft1DTgV7Hkd1M,FovXM!
mR6ry.BJR1:NF70DND
7ax9.Sb;WEY?x4X
:n1vNI;heXiN6N:iUJ
:zTV'B6DE!g'Ge?.kQXW
CAPTAIN KOBY
xXXbH5xSiEL;WYY'w!
EMRMz4y2i2o""bv
vued;aCvNk0rVc:7T!
cdJ4lwbGoXC6qXnMy.S!
FM!YYywCFoq9T4Qqpb
HN6yInlf,ibXPC?
S,lgrNTRNABp5FL:D3
zll5dd3VoKqstrsCQGrM
CAPTAIN KOBY
W7K:,im"STKXhm!GZ!
e6HTHeFaFV60sqX
b!wD42hX'0c;!GMfB!
19nG8:!VfPP.ZXV'"k"!
m8K8k9ILDs8G;vCWcu
CAyyJVpH2UKYc26
Z02mb1j"kcLWr6izXy
.ejN5;nzI;F41ks!MoW5
CAPTAIN KOBY
31XEt9er.2M9S6YId!
3eOV,A8LbZO7zTy
MGL??4dy5wPq3Ce,j!
?SBFgBwz7,mfIXA"XG2!
QhQV"f8nJ6hlVt;hAn
5UVBtqRtXVrW7fe
a79xrI!jeQ"6SFGhy!
'5MXTNnUfkpbC;0Y;qhC
CAPTAIN KOBY
LDiWMPnSd3BsbqmJ8!
tzsjc,1Ch'Q'VmQ
scjVkOLarFAL7GKcw!
7!,06"Elg'VVR;fMf8D!
DGxiDp"ebn9v1?Zhrj
:kOPE9JVILA"J7d
a5B7BPh:VmP.fM4gWo
g;JI:hO"r8cgdOU:CrQv
d0HzRhGCk8sin65r"!
la'KPDpo1nRtVlY
8,ZdIXs2wlSU1S.IL!
5RxpenfeQwssaCc6LDs!
GCcb2Rk8mjZ,mYnY3N
Ux1r1yxSGNd2xfn
sRhWgIF62fwn,k72Km
JCh,SzKewCnk8hm7Pbwt
CAPTAIN KOBY
?"64PziYk0'VD;e0'!
ylfH:tWJ.:z2?tk
,fx.lnh,IYQ.LGQ6g!
TIxdxQ3cmWc82q6g00C!
jhh2,qBbYbDcI9,Eio
ppm4Qw"?'fMGSL1
.8OArsO3bI37nG"gq8
bl1?.MWJipZyVlYgYf:s
CAPTAIN KOBY
kuh'k'eElhHx2E4XH!
kEDpiAvw4o6hduh
ZRn;:wxwgmmsy!3NT!
bYwU7UrqrPLmjwt?nrh!
.MEvMB'"jbWeXbx8Gl
aIygl"573wyHGXb
!FsnEvz:o6V3skiNm!
W.n7OCNZlga'N!?GwLnQ
CAPTAIN KOBY
5?T,EGbQ:gM"?,1PJ!
6!4GI;EtVs8RGgo
lJYi2ugpcFD.ywjXp!
uBBrpuvsA.,3Mj9xh.6!
wLSBe:azJkXF1lDFWx
gU7l8GfRX;SZImR
Oo,xc22iMV6So"WAbS
6.GYEwV,KZm;G'xTO8U,
CAPTAIN KOBY
bwAB:3,J"GtFbRrIb!
ONje:IOO'!:dK"P
Jv'ItLc!hSQtdgzp5!
s2!wo7tFA"V2QcN0AuC!
f?k9N4spnT!'XfGh.'
cN1D?Z',paWrf;g
rzJVy9W4'a3y0ZGrLr
04'Fgq5xMmOb,4NlYGJ1
A5mQpkpLap'"KKvv:!
2UtgP!WLZnaaiFB
hdkSGXa807.5dWJKh!
ivNQISjBX?0iJs:QWmO!
dRLU1EjLzgxyo.KhTv
Gg3vu!aJfmJ'Owu
UzNBFVHs7ThpIsagNk
AFN,YnoYudgje1cA8Gv!
CAPTAIN KOBY
UsBtR?leWj?x4XShL!
mVGN66,B,LKg'1'
VKjv!4M,vTDJIILSv!
eyMG4r'rWc!8qy'MUXR!
W.VAc6WfauOPeBvPf4
cHpNM'XG6MaU2a"
954?Z6DajLyyLc?,S0
oLL7i6fNqYj4bc7.U2pn
CAPTAIN KOBY
oSzn0yWQJEn"9tspc!
h2B'"mTi95Qd5oQ
,pyBp89EuIWvgyeyf!
;zJW8UJnBwE?4'2Ef7N!
6bGDk4qY1EjwPVL:sU
x6NI"?x2!8meFXz
JBCW:t46"vUeinTJuk
ZVqlm,CgG54!1x'worN2
CAPTAIN KOBY
FpriExlOkduK8z'G0!
jkC;W"Iy'QSibU7
PxiN:MROwvevHmBhX!
b5:Y5mCTZnsjWnHgZEL!
YVqpecK.rS8lrrijd:
va,m!4zYaBqk'My
n0UNGOYyb5x;B9W.0Z
jhWmZEJPj1wyTb:tQUjD
CAPTAIN KOBY
..O1F;,'nqIFALBZy!
2;Oa1r3NfWMo6H'
6MixKiQTt8c,qvq1R!
tsO'W'EJihoxekY,N9E!
e0DUcRuaD,tdnM:nIA
oKUQq2gNJp40fQ3
PZUD4ij8R!KW;bowFL
JFu'r,MXWZvnX6C?N1'A
CAPTAIN KOBY
72.SI9DKi?.ytnx74!
;yCvcP"PmBY4noz
jYYGMn59aNCpmN6,9!
,krg0kswwmIEtmsjI2a!
2;R99fsZF"2EroVdrj
sSswf67DUVBMv25
.Aa0,lB:dNRlVNJxNZ
u25:2ebK9?HiChMZXg":
CAPTAIN KOBY
5ump9TSXfyFrDZScN!
gM31SK?5J1T23YN
17Z?m5bJx!u"tr:iV!
iewjJgl3Kt0vf3PJS6j!
.kYrHUkXqm6E8HCuNs
PSX1c6LWRCDi4AN
wDegW6rO3QYWsZ8qzE
Ui1FHMg'YYXG5fqDchAO
CAPTAIN KOBY
zO.BczFBFx7CT7d'b!
RKeH7dF?5!osvEO
D:MkdF?U58''c9JnZ!
?FiMKIHCfeIQxUKa7Gn!
T"yCr6cqKc!piHMiCQ
otPF.gC4Eg9Z?v6
Dteg61yl7ga:bUTe5E
dV7NAbLwi9qf2,O:i,gQ
2Mvyo8WG?EJ"OWca:!
HRCiiATSlddpkd,
7Vb7FFTEZgE!MLvYZ!
8ZV78mtx4Rnq?lDgk1Y!
Y.5Gh6QFC4Dx";53PG
"BNS..!e1BwVzS3
v.aH;"Lj:CQZSNkqQh
xqJiME8"l:YfkjMUdayP
CAPTAIN KOBY
!nSKL!;7t3u6StyzR!
2PUqgPn5?f!wSHU
nEnzNaDo4BzQaCG;R!
xTi?q5ecaOWbxHstQGg!
VWGOUCzEe9LbfykrnO
7?RJTY7j:KfoOrH
Z8ZmNWCYL7SZe4zN4V
l.RJNa:,gbxL5..Vucht
CAPTAIN KOBY
!DBFzTHHm,LEFtjOw!
Lm,TUuRsZh".!Vs
AOVsI939izMT9WkTU!
'rB"oF89Jl56Xdw?T:g!
OrtZVvytJNWVBcaAl1
EwXA'JybGx5tV?s
ub3eenOg;tYar!PQpL
pvrcTMwtfJb;bMdF;R4q
CAPTAIN KOBY
xyJd,TcH26'wMqFyI!
WI"fikj'7q"xgsx
Z3phvajAyxkpbX,oU!
P,fpFICQz0RyNo9Caoy!
9.N5hS:oQUhp;0aR"!
cq"kZ2SQZ.fqSR0
vyuEXpQO.FXVoECKhJ
Ys".huwDj90VN09cN;:M
CAPTAIN KOBY
Zu6kVS10et,KB?'vK!
?veV;!e9hlNCb68
TEUxaOwo2doJQRM6k!
B3J:GL4322fL"TuD7i4!
eewKB"DWIK5Tm9cA;l
B3WJeNrmfQNHPTe
zarm,Wl0,:O?.bhYAh
qJ7x7ZmMR4tLfJyuMb42
CAPTAIN KOBY
ZN6x7nVB;idfXR;;J!
q6JzUx59M42dZaH
2ILP4;?ETypz"OqMx!
3YV477,YzitS2M3pUWK!
ZNgatHiIEX5F8V"MEy
JiJpEZ:ApfEHq'i
EJQaw7rdmUl.t2UI5v
1vU,2U7lfsRKBzSMf9IR
CAPTAIN KOBY
:b1gEY2HPberK?x:4!
hQAEEr?1lclefri
"7DvsIeMjQ1mNNuxE!
eaq2w8ZWbmLXR51Ny;R!
GSCIhycbKfCwtww8ws
MU0E0Y"kQR,7iU?
GtMQN6MZpoYRNN0OnF
yC.mYf9fiVs:9QyNb:Qe
CAPTAIN KOBY
VPTAh,ayu9imSQIG'!
RW.A.AF"OAt683s
yfu6Q7ty7"Doc7Coi!
,f0M5K5M3rgEAH4xIS9!
666hHSp;fppOIdA1'B
Z7t,KKu,AzzJQc.
11ru0R0vd7SfQcE2rY
U"La?hxIlqdgoJ,IO'CE
CAPTAIN KOBY
h?qgCtFBM"OG5kM!g!
c6jAP.LQ7X22oO;
Br,e7kJRkbTis'i9b!
z.GK5NeiJZ!EQam25zK!
T3XMQfkJ.8;u7'CKf:
sp9,uK7FxCmjBa1
UcsaxBusIJ9.SMR:H!
Ip0g0Nuzmtz40x:'p6F.
CAPTAIN KOBY
2Z8D?zgt:NPCrwOvK!
wDpeD5RPHv?xh;K
71VYz0VL7TwYMYb!C!
zOjC8jvJIL6MMpg!hsG!
aRxjdmtP0NfC'd3.S?
qdysWxUgW!8.HDR
qbP0UVz''dblNu3u!y
AfcwYgKWm9L?veo,6eGr
CAPTAIN KOBY
LTkiEy4jFs.hDKZxR!
lh1b3F8a1bARtZB
DVj3g6grwgu7:ecvS!
LsV'7E,XOPjPGe:tgyg!
njr8mUJAY3j8"93uSy
NOS.P9Vcz:u3KLE
snZAMduP5c.W!m2RoE
X,TJ,Z.v2'BP9AwItjTS
CAPTAIN KOBY
OD.XL6vYgBNrYO2MH!
0cdVq30;ixqpIp'
R5'5K;bPhq"DStg;y!
qbxIUnK1kxF;sZ7f6E8!
R2o5ClgwVtNoWRMhrE
gj.t6kMO6uKP8CE
i;F9'uv'PnczwS38Bz
49yP2'zbBq;xG,QxxN53
CAPTAIN KOBY
9kGV?p81uzMMgHX;1!
22Cp5eVGo6:e5,c
M8.Ck;V,Z'8PYhs:t!
DXI!39Pq3KJ2FRmU;4w!
IK6O13!ljXYz.0,wIY
4gh6yji4Yu31A!8
8.dHjuwNdVI45dFwbs
7G6UQ8lSS.l!!Yfbuar3
CAPTAIN KOBY
z:j,o7npGLajLWOV0!
nQz6anCCZo1wk!r
qO5vNgTD2cKm,EeaV!
CT!FeDZJNHKbOI4xyAq!
9b"uNtrPMdmW'5w.7h
bY5vzlvdz0KEwqL
PeiONKMNi;OoABBgHO
7SKXCQblNr0EmC5Zk5oH
CAPTAIN KOBY
!!tYWAqgGzPZenDVd!
k36rjj7LtNvTD,2
iDeBfYcbziBA46gxK!
sbN7x0LV.v8o4Z5zwoi!
h2,qs6s'!fOCqd,F.U
o6t"?WiHMNO9Yyo
EW5I4uE3GFbTG9?Nhk
RwN8oeA"h;ERV.!:93;v
CAPTAIN KOBY
4ClGLjgw8qA6ZdfCN!
NB?0EndiJjCKTY8
D8vT0J,54"hjf8'?3!
jGTOI'?s.ETay033Hhq!
:xhl6AJj";MQ;jjdNx
Nb31o:OFqaX51dQ
sVb!IBIBFIu4hwXg8'
GKIbtQKs2'?xH".N;dcT
CAPTAIN KOBY
QT;u6;OWKuH34i!Vj!
NHnEdTjIXH!4EcE
SoW1V,DcpagE.TQl.!
4p!?za1jZOQBS:9Tw7j!
HPuPA:nmtPmNCW48Ou
Nod:nZOFaxsqS8T
sFAtEWw3;FkZvYVq3A
,x:WOdIv8M14tsx0eQzX
CAPTAIN KOBY
;XMSbzfiSsWzSTEgM!
13.1FDR;g5dL7aK
"E0pyN1Ul7rA1ILr8!
9!2IajDheQZ?bb2'gZi!
Q!s1fPS1??ZoP'S96R
K'rSB?1h55RGLtH
rNpthN1dW?Oe;CX0hp
!w8dNAzEVsJRo2ctqpoC
CAPTAIN KOBY
j6dhhYD9b2Uv'lSKn!
G22jBp:M9pereiW
1.Bh4:V'";xWgG'pp!
lAKgj4RtRGSVE9WrKh4!
.ZTVo43L"s?5dubM"5
h9nll"ioj'T3orX
NF.I;kfnowOYGxC'1s
smny;jSY3E9pt;l7"pd7
CAPTAIN KOBY
O7cBhnw3g,SZ7p.xi!
Wu!"ZsR"2hBK5h?
bcwrsi2":9GqTbfXC!
N,'7pq0b5arb9SUjRH2!
VeR,R5C1L,TN2Y"xP0
?yw5VKxSDI3xPDj
kEx!98'Z9e3TCVJ3zw
N65FoTsDVpaJX4T7fuOe
CAPTAIN KOBY
IOiK':U9MP8HP1nk,!
L,tjzgvGKvUBTRD
'pCwuAFmzaIPq4eFQ!
hxx'h!..gM6.oGPeN5c!
BV4A?n'0GOLRV8Nbmn
b.wT3uosB?l3E5o
bIquVBB0cdS,V"rbyI
mBhdD6LMDinMks9ENS3S
CAPTAIN KOBY
U361CN1JGtBGcbiXB!
34k!K?ZynvXh::S
j5BB87huJFg;NTcGM!
7g.tIwUx,14S3DhZs3s!
gkl"IN2KW6z8QKwiAG
t3hOVqKnYr.0VR6
16BL3mTVuhq4NInwxL
QvQmu5R7WTA.Pq,WMIwS
CAPTAIN KOBY
LDHLj'mXH3hW0w2a4!
Jd51x?Iemxed5QJ
udrap;GTnl10aLy7P!
WJkYbroM9zJ2HSzXC0s!
!mNVimP'a'Kb8kzVlU
Uz5K6ZXXnmyIE6V
ABsI14jttyzJF5Qdr9
q8sOUjcZmMTkPFM1TeM4
CAPTAIN KOBY
LmdCjSUhwkE56"cl7!
cygIXwiuFq9hGE6
i72nWvD1qWv.aw.pY!
Hh."sBp?rWe:vs5buN6!
ogyH9KxsU?6djXU4N"
?!.2gXAfSz1wBl1
7FFzZK9fa?8pKFV4Uv
1vph:e5ZsCzQaf9Y1NK2
was taken captive by
Emperor Blackbeard's group.
MYJO'kRlRVCatKTbR!
WKj8vGu2cugawPg
3H2oXo4C.H2PxYRCX!
Nn!B'OepRLiYce.Okes!
OzBsoPJhmJJmx1GQ;B
YIy1tXg3EJOcaLg
fCtQH!9XzjmRrAYtq4
NZvJ'9"Z47H100V.lMaV
CAPTAIN KOBY
x?0JG8TO5pomt.jfQ!
B3tnCGHM?iih0'f
L.37GzK5VHEmb,SPF!
lF8imb8OB5ZBQpciHaa!
X9JErPO2;ItA"sKmcU
l5Yp0sBifdOfo99
mrdL:y0Gqavfpa04,i
fal!Fnu"xgkLjMOR3ADE
CAPTAIN KOBY
wlQ89l'R,5YTgm,nx!
4uXn.wTCegWdj9Z
67pdebF;3PIHL:1ZL!
SZwVb7lp7E3x9i,0KE7!
WIZFMwkNh0DtunO,?i
9zOFRHYz;w4IEje
4xzug9YHItMyuIk9K7
YO3r"":mlda'Mn3V2BwV
CAPTAIN KOBY
9r9bqYLffT.fvd4;r!
Gs3NnQ'9RKzTR4U
C?5:7KxTcJxTCHh3o!
rLXxfLFyo8kKjikKDEK!
HIXlt7tr"vU'u,LG62
F:hNdMP9N3lrGOi
,XSx9J,4"ZZTjbrDR7
kk?rQB82.GaVVMPcQpNX
CAPTAIN KOBY
4MTx'ELGxa5;aCPxv!
7mnE,BfsFnw.Biw
IPk:p."!Jcf:!SHQV!
q'Uk3335JBqtSG,n5ZJ!
4Lv"ZtX?NCq!s!PVs1
p!9YPWGqA5tcgyM
UlNC2j3mqmx,f1SKo.
5IpcF78kSQzl?rWAGcjp
CAPTAIN KOBY
gWV36cR8i6,EL,J2i!
iP?2uliiPVbq.1v
LifS1glJEoflAxXVu!
;v1Ga14"TCnPTGsKURn!
X84YAqJ1Kx,3Bf:JIO
DYBGz1Bmwr!G2OY
tpiiM;jJ.lQMg.ed,5
y.5wsOmbK1!a.",IVawp
CAPTAIN KOBY
pznEw5?;Nkdor.c'b!
,xtTEGLRiJRkb5:
evOZQBLc,8vvTHXcC!
2O75"Fi:K9aTI'fH!8C!
;KnK6A7ZNnZ.aplUD.
4gzG7?xo8;x"0By
FKf;OmEfr4R7mc8Buu
LTy;k"hQZePke8R;Sw6b
CAPTAIN KOBY
9D17pQhDBZIuhfV0R!
'YtEPE1ulB4w?c:
!HxWs2OlW6brjAp7C!
Mb!wTvKCby3rjqaJcq'!
F!8u9h71gGrm6v!q2s
ZiEEAyNk4!gyR7G
mIV9Ac:SAX7kf;dsHk
'i.G;JJd6.LkESIS84g9
CAPTAIN KOBY
pw4badRR6D9ddFWmy!
u3ASkSZNuuhGHFN
ogp6ME8gne,!Gbv3E!
vkhHS6aW8fMmhs31GbF!
tFCPoC9JfJLg'mMPgL
1OQtGmgNn;1o2'N
T'vb!j4kHcL1CgKu8S
CDbpbu09,NGvO?xIsQ9N
CAPTAIN KOBY
LGGmQprY?;hr78810!
,t;PyXf!JKtM6AK
UhhSCW6uXKZ6xvz0D!
W!FFcSi46t83crbcR5A!
:9.:E?"!pSwf:R0Cxr
ghu".XpyP2v6MFQ
0h5,2cqrSHn9ez!Fta
052u?JKXUZkMXNMcKkI;
CAPTAIN KOBY
Tujl9q4n:hxqQ"Khf!
QWLJuMZngsm?FPa
1I'qwoXZS5cX,X0O,!
qbuxnvuAy;hNFmkkx3N!
ezMF"gkdrjpprj1q;D
pmn:B.04JW;OaHO
aIRGE2Nc"k1uXTryeD
o!8UWT3Dp;tNlcCPO4Nq
CAPTAIN KOBY
IU2cQMv4.Kf0K'YWc!
Jr7C94XBYgyRvk:
uJ"q"6t2NKTTEC1Uj!
KOt7j!:ylxQHN6e7Gvs!
8WYIzvqBkJgTF3hGfC
soTdGLh0"fqep4;
Aha,k39JNfJG"ro,GV
8R!YziPgnoQQNVCyRLfM
CAPTAIN KOBY
2uULHzHln9NVtSw65!
6z,8YWDYVi;TzfQ
v;qDNxpG8l22fgjbt!
tySBBn:71APRD?V;R';!
YC5E2qlj"FNYKg!.:B
FgOW5.VCg3IWOuB
485wNAr90eW4kN;Rax
cWhebL'n8,7G9zjuqM?N
CAPTAIN KOBY
CKNSQEaDXV:ecHIEG!
haIgrufgFT4eWe.
"OYwjTgIFZPm.EQ4v!
!IeZ72!xQWN;C,ed:JU!
?8N3trn3ox3o;CvX.k
tauAGnbvo8;dV4P
JXgsyDQLkgyw1;YeLp
DC4y?.CLFNNuX5gd?KXG
CAPTAIN KOBY
7SmFd375L"aH1m':u!
RQC9AsMI.iYUV94
C02ja7jPByjZVK6pV!
:ljIg";PpSsCHyiLSbm!
n''iDu30svILoP;KX9
!Q9TexnU4hplLH5
bg9vH?";."Mtv7!s!K
0zk:hGjKGabL'2q89g4?
CAPTAIN KOBY
X?oT4udWfL'9gqF?u!
ckH:8O5Qov1L?WY
C:T0POApBmy!;'mgn!
Vbh!.D64.lpH'BZuIV8!
v'ptU'O:GNMDxAfUT.
pIQkg5GFOyR4qgI
Fk0i.XFNcCMpjWx5vj
l,:DtQY!.'mNb5czVl!m
CAPTAIN KOBY
jkwiljFIhUmVNvbXI!
DRQau98LRUUfaj0
Om05d:;,7DJ!Uq0Rn!
I7qSxV20utfFO9sLsXf!
MhGCexgUQUOfNLiSRK
nw?2MhjMBvqBuUa
GLeE5g6Y73l8n0Hfke
vnyfO'jqRTIC1nL4B!Yz
CAPTAIN KOBY
fbRwfKtF6Rn?y,C2.!
g6D;2OJBs0FsA8z
FOcjvfXUS:.:f0Ybl!
b2WnEGROvcqnNkoUs,x!
HOkD16x4azwT,ubmcM
6Z!JT:HL.fseRkH
xGBfxqURU0Rykg8IrR
RpBdAN'"ZQY7N7N2kRB;
CAPTAIN KOBY
1nlJ"R6XFBXQ.B0R1!
Txa65j2EcbyxCu?
2adc56A3s3Tc6wEgu!
O4UHkcrEsac?'o.WV2L!
3;.2SHIZhzyP'9D,yL
XRuGSWLBZnazqWR
J5?AV3Gut05wBpTO?k
ifuIvMipAuLIS9!kOpFT
CAPTAIN KOBY
r.'INIuPaGld9p2qj!
QRHWreKG2Go6L1D
S:D.ei'r"U5N7XWsu!
h48fVkGecc6iddepfpa!
b;obNgpuctoHwpSyj"
P5DyMf!3n1sxOEs
6?;bciOrtP;NoC8rjj
sFemJSGiK,Hy3Ge6ZLT8
CAPTAIN KOBY
Z.dDVdsNW67PiA:UU!
:Bo1diKTuFnO!pM
wYNCgrUoUlYLugwsH!
HWTgxM0uFdAB,0k0.g'!
5dQW:cBNc?YnT9Op'R
du'wDd8!lk2KthO
CWNVe"S9Xx"?zOCcLn
?cVLC5ouGDX6LJNRaTLY
CAPTAIN KOBY
JntxWdeVTJR4NDx;q!
04RXw2?xRV2T?99
j1RZ0;wOqvtJM5PKn!
TBbnPBr9LzJWubByM'F!
hvbe:16YCL!eNz1bQF
TjuO3D3d9HwTfQ2
!?Uhf'OwGl:,BtKT!A
1JRbEt6dH1Mo1dLxavd0
CAPTAIN KOBY
8jTed0Iiy.vPeR.iJ!
NJ2jy,yFUJm,GAU
W!fxa9t?x0Ay7x'ei!
1!E6dY;xPmLTPv4jFxa!
h:tI7.?!iwOWw'uysO
NdvxhuKzIBRhg8q
OxD64;Pwa6j!8p1EBM
hELbmDGSs?Y;BnSJmEvi
CAPTAIN KOBY
?oyHSddhrFNv":On"!
HjOOdDyD"Z?bRAz
vI6,UpuwS08!cRsOU!
faFvZCb;AThC5qbB1Pi!
RShipUlVf'NOf1CikR
fGmiqKCTLcs?s0p
Fj"abOx"98".WgnKrV
eM,.dytHD;nu!ktNA"j!
CAPTAIN KOBY
:C"hUwd?hrsY!fEk7!
Yg:fjIzfNgwX2ob
St,c3,USoyB6zPP,J!
ao0va?IfzjAoG1sd"k,!
;E7';'en8QShz2NcS2
ufHL"?2YN7;cSi?
Gpc'zaZhmQIaD7mHP;
gAco9ww0pHAZLU'3cv"t
CAPTAIN KOBY
"'GXgI9xJpE?PxIv!!
U6KCp1j"!6gfpAo
lyHt7ydW.;kwg8uyJ!
?uy4L3,bT:nNc3DAekG!
6nw..w9vC'4qUHBQx:
wQcXKC9HbJ?mn"Z
Z72b9IAZ1PXfKuFymY
dZzJp:D!sB4N!7.S,lA'
CAPTAIN KOBY
2YSC.,R:KGoT!5rAv!
uUHyUKfzPLTTZ3m
6TMdaV.D5V9MLvL?:!
EA:nPtWpbNG9?vHEaie!
dvsd'4Il0N.!6JzdAB
hZglu"6?bN5M7C:
fdMPe;Ofee0U":D:Cp
WRyoUaF.rNVqw6Ddz?E8
CAPTAIN KOBY
wPP4EpvHbl,s"mejm!
u:Rth!APh?mcATe
kTGW1drOv,Ha?KBoa!
Cm6i,PEjYVff0YXidku!
TPSNe1FhpCd':cKafm
dS6TGJ1bkksRmnl
wFrp30dG,WEhcT0iOP
:dzjzZHLcx6mS3VQ!1,F
CAPTAIN KOBY
YtZ2gNSmI!ojjeu8x!
j'ULl;nJlfkSoAe
"pOpcjsz?h7hj!dVD!
zEfdq9H"T4.xEe6s,k7!
wm8"FNokbBh'6cztfj
ui?eZyNPG;hHRtv
:qwHNghooT7M4mJYhC
uusi9t6Jco?Fcmh.s8,9
CAPTAIN KOBY
"MhkBYBD4y.vvllUx!
7FpgdbsVCHrBHYE
!h"3"ohxfgInP4T3M!
,rx2aryvT4cF,CrLTl'!
?!Dc?mAHC1zbZ6ha5N
RFIfG?os6Y1BkNK
Zfj1?XqsDu!4mpYA,4
Ib19DEMRragva9UDpbOP
CAPTAIN KOBY
ylWjtfXdHxLtzQV:Q!
JdeIGvfHl;?X;tK
Y9ylsyVLv.n.c"5QW!
Lxxva9YG,1ucduDPPwR!
uvYQXbVnututF'LCGL
.uVrRXBkOjEKA:I
lJuKgx""0Nimw1MGfQ
RLmM0euS.O.NicqyTRXq
CAPTAIN KOBY
Oo9wH1Ivk?YN3u,ha!
tIDTmHawoy9HY4S
mtCGCY?NjS44FgkR!!
'G0VbFeAMLPi?1J0G8E!
9,pKuvSvpW,NhonTGg
LCatDxsga2l5AXH
H2ZZNJ2NEQ0;:RWf'm
Poj8kLZ6RmvtlkpGycHC
eyG6j2MBHz6wzXWHd!
7SrRSbxeuTmoeMC
O7x'2lE5r9.k;Ypqt!
BpyrhoayV.7Vr:zeVs;!
o5w1MURigOVu?M4:i7
h!ZepRQ9o8in9'j
LBMVAQb1VSgnQyCsSg
slm!IZCaavzcIE'7jVvr
CAPTAIN KOBY
6h:S8Ko1Pj7TVxLWk!
2DEKwPoGPjTBn;w
.pdigW5xsNVbG48Am!
W!cNbLfHwC0:lZEc0tz!
IBQ6mvyGrIy"TLp2:S
c04'V8hC?P;t3vf
XCQAT90h4Ng,hDBhvm
aL;N:A1TEv8L3,nUy0QC
m1vq!jRnM9PQUTDO7!
,mJ5MTI!:ndLnbj
'L7M6Q?uJFTMRxN.G!
oaEUjnjFNSXUL.P:V.j!
XF'Xxsjy47zEFH5It;
.09DrEQZ"VAkHYR
nPsDFzYt4ay,?JN!c?
'?;;ujiUNMWXa5L125r1
CAPTAIN KOBY
"iius9nTi9Vyk39"?!
71'Qpr34R82WRyz
qPirNaKT?3UhLxUtd!
abZ02R;,YbLLPfy6WkO!
tUfs7sY'.ysK8:n!A0
Sq'T2Zipm.D32Vw
uTBNNfIErprsDUj7Kl
:yAUy!zvu8D1Z1Z9.6pk
CAPTAIN KOBY
'7Cs7r:zltqn6JSGk!
8:TjJ;q6h7BfBHQ
BRGnxycxUTa61C?aM!
gPXknwn?pjStVlju;uV!
X24!y?XBRTR8R.GX"L
HM.?jVw!zg7mkH4
ibBxtmzdTAO1tO,Pq1
jqOhz1v5JTHiHmgp;'nQ
;rYlMm!'7.sdrIKb5!
Yu8SP6K5YSAO1ha
1wDLhlBLpe,7jaJYf!
0jYevueteYLFIMTH"nQ!
fuA8nfs36Df?,hFm'R
Bb39Rr?4JrJ7??2
X0Sjalg1Ay3TyXsFrh
xjECQXZgDG0;x?Kut6!8
CAPTAIN KOBY
4zriEjT2knN.gyIzl!
GhZAFZWfnCDR0Hn
S!Du1oRB4QI4QPTkS!
1Gpw6!C,.Omb3P833yh!
fh'Zn8qVYrNeUCtguh
lmOZeeDFRpeiJ5s
bMnxKnaAmyr,piofeC
4gGaN0SQmwEdqDRM3aj9
CAPTAIN KOBY
;2P.8VYlUmQgGCUKK!
1A;0X!BkdokJGK9
"QLZd06"waut:Qwhr!
oSJiuB'WkSh"Zzfvylx!
GF9aS23giNFZ6Ctt!b
5e3XlCMmwOA0Pec
gqOWvJ"n3bK"pj2.ng
0vDs8Wm;jtl4CCQ:kKCB
CAPTAIN KOBY
UHiYokYoEqbiMm85q!
hR99cEv44'YfnMo
k8pEyQHqJbD5QU1N!!
uHNa0Jh.zK8QDVKICS;!
M!KSa1GgyqVOmlKgBQ
Zx1P9:'gWjUwfk8
"YV8JoqWDokg'5CNbN
bPN9'3.UuE4n'.hZWsC!
CAPTAIN KOBY
J9YQERSlGu3c:2V;Q!
xyVDixQHTjl8S,8
AF6wrKkNpgO0Qf"x6!
Gj!x"9aePGup'xb8N2O!
fnEOM4AQesMAJm0uzT
OW5P8mtHF4LY1vd
ZnLKYEsNd47HhPoIx2
i3H,kQsY!uMVG1XWNpjE
CAPTAIN KOBY
g:KnGDsU74!Vi.m?A!
AVxnwPIkk0?.0qa
GFUu16nfqMQg2'eo:!
io1DLsYusK'YrTAOUMs!
;79CQkRLQmAgPs11yB
.Bv0FfY'u,HU?m5
?H4GjD;gZlQBUFTbk9
H;D!?xtxg,hBhb8'6?q7
CAPTAIN KOBY
QqSZdMKLoGCryrhZJ!
A'ETTd?hNFxb9'W
Lj6.ERh?XeEyOvXp:!
JnFnY"ocAa'z'SG,.iV!
4WTGpYzQk!T:E48R,y
qCz!noCzNySggK?
'xha.m,q4a5s5"CuWy
I90upZZ,1sxM.p7sYtb.
CAPTAIN KOBY
RnuseKOh?Yhf4;muH!
VJNldZRRlfOj;Fu
x."IAdfz5.EhYA.Un!
C.IwxvqO!;A86AaCrnr!
j8pNhA:AEM1WJmutbu
KCN6f50gsokmNkw
KL8lwGh9,Hplj!vOHm
w7ePrpgvwQfO6;wV4mRg
CAPTAIN KOBY
C:W,LLH7X.8p9rFS6!
'YJpA"Cz3q;GC2l
rP05C7Bp1at5SaDeO!
AT8ERRzpguw:2eOOuUb!
K7QoH1N6kYR.JlPCyh
mK"l!Vb;'vt39'?
1:sveRSUlK'zBb31vo
,9K'YReWw6;FwX2eo5fP
CAPTAIN KOBY
8Hq7O8Vbwgq!caM7W!
LvGHB;y1VuySu.L
H.ShGArkvUzHI:8rg!
;P5?kolB'9?B2MS"Mg'!
wxureR33z41g1Qk7'z
RmFXbz0E3hqZQf2
sHw.xU9Qe:RYeE3OFD
;jktLoNqtDH,mi7eQDuV
CAPTAIN KOBY
nPZD,0aP5Kt"yy3Oi!
Locxtu9YBQru1jH
xmi7g:heFqZhp5aYs!
dL.S13b!Qd0aPNqjb2P!
h".bj7nCeQ1xLn8'91
NsE"duVtCTEbf'c
nWjKQHtE2S3HZgCEcb
j0q994i;fT'mrNAFXnX8
CAPTAIN KOBY
5PITMq3RxsevCyMn'!
hngFcIKKM6Z0X0,
nlfONc3':xEuQ;DQ6!
98Y7ynrkRLthkOdzyRo!
k.A1qIpx'Bc898P?:b
qLA0SEpEy"DQkCp
"xPlNBdkhpOm5TKQG'
mh.SVvtZRIR?G!bojaD!
CAPTAIN KOBY
8cRhkzYni6'edD.F3!
97SbC6ZJ3FS.kg5
J;dBsnzZuWD.wA8Qt!
6lyAe"a'NJ49:?M.jaA!
ndDHS5re42Wu0hrIjK
6mB?ETAGY,2UmfY
VrA,6VXpeO1o;?gvoW
Lg?NPgmdN!BQiK!FeZbz
CAPTAIN KOBY
xki7xS8,x!K9a1?6a!
0dAlha,VhA8:Kz'
eyX1nY8YjZq60bO6S!
7xwX6uNysr,cWFoaXLH!
NbJogU:d7;JbSaOjVt
on8SgOO,dzQUUNH
UB:T?hIEBjUXvCQDSu
t50hjkNOtdpnHxFcihVl
CAPTAIN KOBY
L8b"p!HFWz3BvVmnq!
aK?bI,chk?2!"Kd
OIBfqtQ,Sx.ICIk:s!
xpSXsuWPS3x;pWw;1oN!
7l1uR?9z:wj3KT'dr7
zxMfy998jTqTVAd
93MXxySH"yRRrDxcG1
Bu6K19gPgxBI8FNTAzNB
CAPTAIN KOBY
nLiFBZEN,J!vujDtC!
LQS.yblnS4MJLCw
:0fPhjrr1cxTduHy4!
0a2T7B,Tl5030sJH8dP!
trRXX"vNuWHz2I?WBJ
A:vt3aUNKrKP224
Y,SJoOyKoknKKs9Az4
x?WrjxcB2H;1TvpvQhAT
CAPTAIN KOBY
2itZlSuM2S7yUOV5o!
,W4I;7T3O2xlWdA
SmwvUoKdjtO8S9Oms!
Z7CU8tgt8ibh"MNMGPT!
8fAKq,sn1,aAJ;hHJz
2UaTgFbF"kg1qwQ
EWG!:TDqDV'lkpcqn0
iRUpdw!X0fVBQ4NLTlAo
CAPTAIN KOBY
mw.6nK0fyy9W8Er3y!
1:.LK6nvFALli"Z
xkqxs7:rn?hOiLPIB!
9Ekly;n..z"0wSykL!5!
eM!C0:DC;ec6oVMs8d
'5pOujE0fwq9I28
Qde?bRnnZM:,RHSr"Q
lhmUGLt"qJQE4AK!!YjC
CAPTAIN KOBY
6rCiWDH15tWHRuvs5!
Tv1YCPJRqDz"NIP
fF5,pEatXJF'u6TLM!
vlFiCggN7.GQd,sI,wg!
tm8XrMbOLyh0fgP0R.
n9'EwwHj3pxkN3Q
IVX50syw8y!kvUuEUb
MJsIm8"NWLw4dy3"9IZ4
CAPTAIN KOBY
y6XbM'VFv:ulTIq3b!
xa91GUQazD2BvIL
lyFcFKwg9myo?!WTM!
n!vUzHv0QiuZH6IAMlc!
!dwDNMqNpeiAtcfTAF
frhIYlFK?gsM:!7
MCEJIpQTTLh?xnITle
QLfpn;JGXq'!,0YbnO1O
CAPTAIN KOBY
FEa,Sdf.f6VVUPrTS!
KZ6Isx'2Phs5e3!
9"3h5llQYmQICm4dN!
J.I!FMxm,minOHDmvuh!
FMLCApp8rVG6nxOG7c
71Jv4EuGgU'9hOH
v,8eRKxI!YCIuaPQNu
Zvu:YGp2w3;bj"BS3jz0
ZZoblIe'WmHwcba!o!
4:Hf9iYvdn'R;z3
;RYBQac0m0X?HoXfD!
tM?xqToatTzaNxQzd?H!
amguo2jjMhOTUCl0dj
8M!SZq5P1!s;.JZ
BxNnV:j1jo676jDs!l
VSXi"kS2kbT"Nw5nO4vd
CAPTAIN KOBY
E9!uw0Rr;u4O2i!r1!
zr9FQa:SlTRmyHL
1LheXZKIXR2P7lJDX!
8gXxf5;.Xo5QzspJfQ3!
2fmDoiQy5EaiIlhS3G
aVyiM7U?xr"d2K8
jqpepIsKYZJ'5KsoQV
4Mg0OnKHHrqWsuDYAQQT
CAPTAIN KOBY
k'9xHdr,H5MlvYBSB!
erZb3:xET;KHK!P
PBrR48PaNd2gLCHi2!
hk.T'ibtBsX?n!d,M:"!
Pn"Dx5U"3A7o'YlesZ
"'r5!Z7G0i:AZ4M
TH1P6X0JNAOnt8,PXD
A:mSpRaGpQy5ZEizYA6N
CAPTAIN KOBY
CVdgLMRZ18LU:v.au!
2qM9!FVPR!zUx;r
4f3Mc"4TbBFqQywUV!
CCUSL.xJYSLkRNba4ii!
8Zw;HVDMDWNe?VtsIt
d7Zd8,ugEf,M"dg
?Rg7nhtGvwuEO1mfHP
O9anXJZwDzi?ZNiFa,A,
CAPTAIN KOBY
9Iw:mk9eH3K9zPxuC!
g!IR"ksZ7R;eUJ;
12.u1MSq,Nm9beDtV!
,Ns:osvcQ8trS:IEkfn!
T51tJp3RaEqwsK!2'T
cX'RZ9SgDBhfyE;
yeC:IIrgKNZ2WE2u"'
cNHBSicr7J1sRBFEJc7Y
CAPTAIN KOBY
VUsbvvz2xAP.81bTv!
EhOVYGxQjTYjo7n
OisA0,wF?S;2?NxCj!
ctKHMs73n4B?H;i0G2F!
nKLUgk;5imnad13mHG
JOCdDGEgZB8r'0X
;J54rljs?h'kwNUaLv
kcZCwUBovxAtPvl,Pddf
466LpHueU1yN1D0SP!
gKz,3oM28ZB3j3N
94z"AaKWpxwRCQif,!
gMRgzfczzYk7Ptdd2tO!
3y7y2oGg0;ANWHD6tT
O9:ENs6bAjd;NRN
hWB".SC:Ys6OoyRA0x
DlJ93zkO8rJekMeVmQ2?
CAPTAIN KOBY
Y't;Hkjo9;K:t?X9T!
9n4dcYJJqXkPw,f
Zso0"O8GQE3Ti:IIh!
cqiv'wa9dcL4M?508pV!
PKv;wEJmBbl!GFcJ.n
hcP3t;zJrtXsElx
STTdXM.shApzjuxiti
wablm!ZIsq3C?L,4w,dL
CAPTAIN KOBY
'PA4'?xNhMotwf1g0!
?Me9eDSmm.!Zjlb
qQExa0",yH7f!brnC!
C:SSD8tKzW64S!zJyON!
:lgXZ3SN00pwFaaX'T
BX:kliQm07!h7QC
qUQdE,Wkm'NSoCLuta
GAS8NGESfq8q2K08W5Nt
CAPTAIN KOBY
nX4ZI5sRlL:ZX3O9j!
Pj4nb?isRUV;'Zq
O553LTng9O?CAfpC,!
zeux7nwpjbPZKsz9s?R!
"e53lDNUpBoQa:Xwqy
aQBJxM.GkjybB9K
t1cbPPUBdkpjfdegoY
WR,m"yXJ.QAAj'cSCEGK
CAPTAIN KOBY
hpiEQQZl8r7GIm73v!
NMQPchgsS3e::a'
OI2m"Sqrdp.gPG6nV!
BZUJ;GB,2X?L,c"k:ZX!
sYmtpgquaYCPnX?"mR
NXy93Meyt4dHBKm
!PO,;J8ewse0R?N"zt
U"cnGzDp:k;TUm"cB2s0
muqGtlM6zkzSRLhZh!
'YP6C.htMXS0?FZ
tQyqiWxzWiPhhjyBa!
Vs5B79gA;CvW2uI6jBt!
GU82zSWNvpaBXH"TpN
e;!!8ULHU4Lm:nO
owR25xzh;BYeI5!wn9
lSBbt2!UmYb:sFaXwJNl
CAPTAIN KOBY
Tiqe6mitKfQHQF8IV!
jZ'fSZ13f,RvtBW
q5QxviKIzh8R?R"jN!
.:Z!B"teg!LGHSBKL!A!
y9?A!1rOX6?u:Zj.jc
SEQOabJU''qlMk;
zfBCO"r5GVM7;c5ZNI
0'Fb.NnaC:;;;1BzR99A
CAPTAIN KOBY
ll8gfl3sVlnyr?DiF!
JekcBNdrElBCYE7
AK"K0;CL?6h:fdVJG!
ZHS3KHjgC3q"3yT4upR!
:eblYBZBOywYrHPnoe
j'2?WNdu.NmIbb,
HJtosfmzxuI97TsY.g
TaXP.wG?wIScuedQspN.
CAPTAIN KOBY
pri2LiVtO2o,nR,CR!
"uAkyu5hMEfWHDw
jQyTSyOzzQ.a;amjm!
Ps,nC"C8i?ut1q25jn9!
,LTBj1Y2RIaS9cBoo2
dwLsugF.I82s?sP
!GR3,ed26Fmg"0v9eo
?slGJj!wl916S6z!toiR
CAPTAIN KOBY
ISkKTCPr"xxfIB.gM!
2U1h97aXxqQXQK"
1Idd3yqyzyx3n;1q8!
2TPqAdeynyziEsIEfet!
RBgqNHdgvk!?4z;K;b
6t8Vd76UvI17M2V
qkgIlhi8Q'R7CRiE1E
cG!rj4dW,'4okIfcOy5Q
CAPTAIN KOBY
j2S4.A6bAV7Lg;rZm!
cXkN':XKxcN8joY
ZSkk7:JQApmGhXpKF!
pRN:r3TrP!!ui6497QU!
AEbmStBNkJiYtkShs.
gf.NH4EKMjNz8k:
RzyTGRK4GE!tP1hbzf
JqN?1wH6?hj4Oxjx60R7
CAPTAIN KOBY
S6csuiH?o7NaOe'b7!
n42bSsMCavt'J?:
MqbNeu2dwyJZaUJ1j!
Cqm1g9Sp3?werQ'Xpq0!
iYAe7DUy7JN,S8aQFp
UO:Z36GUUuqkvNG
wunNRas0PLnn?!mg.b
'aavPWptMGnhMIE"LwBN
CAPTAIN KOBY
ltThc50TOpGOyXEr6!
vHvAN99CilSWdEk
eTkC;::v1'YSpigf!!
zqatK57mCS"Q4FBuBSy!
yXFO7tuzjrkIYN;fU?
wqzSNf"bBAthjR6
8J:MvxS'6'ygCxHKnk
.l2'y2U99UA8W4G:IVzm
CAPTAIN KOBY
ypH1s!QMXFyR28W?5!
?:?EXcei4EYu4f,
rpn.PROCWpxILcPba!
d!;t;I"3tgF1r4T!2WB!
EDmrmcL:nSlZ4CEP,.
jKY;6v8nn.f3f4n
cfybE9Msu.7kz:qk6i
rQTsctAlxt?Smb4',,Qy
CAPTAIN KOBY
q0oKuRBKcVs2ZO0lh!
WDd'OShKrz.pnFf
ufzODTO70e7kJ.WRj!
U0YVusnAU?ifa82d8Tc!
RFZWn:'KNl2FM?4X?S
JDqG8B"Z:vyQTnI
J"HW6OTdblu2h?9bGI
O9T5P.VpPNGwNEtdDY:J
CAPTAIN KOBY
QnW;FVSWxj7?OjXMp!
S9OUa6yT8r3M?28
bLEgYDxf.9?lEnXNd!
Yg?ZsXhxyjWKXKNjIu5!
!Ttxo,Xliy:RSbUdke
EHJ1X70A9Zcnnq2
Hg5FCSglJYup.9ENgX
:01m9Vv,kB,A5UNI'JH7
CAPTAIN KOBY
wz5GmC"jDy1gZvDUP!
PA4kPCSZaSDRImw
l8"3;RlyLL1fy,NWn!
0ZiHMPrYBk,g!PLR30p!
EjNtvN5Nwt;RbSYjhJ
xxBJ1drK4dj:2wA
:eGJuO9mEQlUE1NANB
7WwJCT6:YqO1MG4cjAjL
CAPTAIN KOBY
;zt3:ztKjWlVPEU6E!
hE77GXvLpsEem9V
LM;rTBQbaWV'E:v:4!
LgoPJVeg1Lwd,1QePTm!
,AN27NA,kO0SBFu.Q:
nrDFdyCQRPGknVO
0el"ENN7SFl,4CsAha
q!HPlpDvVINvL2McRJ3!
CAPTAIN KOBY
k,HSBD.xofvnzh,nR!
IaEcDy;LZYtfDr'
VKks5u4Z??Iz;TKZC!
fX'UQ.KQLBuOCjNsQsZ!
AtYrduEhePXpU2tmmn
hODZ'bHaYwd"8PJ
l"E.!JWeYH6dnHW7Of
gR;Yf;2AjNl79DNMidLa
CAPTAIN KOBY
RfeoAM8Q,cfJ5OB8H!
7HjZ;;IpgrID?AG
;1hoAX;l3;C;N8:jW!
aoIHm1z1V'EXiVJHUQP!
4AXb8.66MquixWoCzg
eeuDLdGthoUmJfb
lWX6A9j;d.q2N0DYp9
1fhbSErz6:cZlh5MfXOk
CAPTAIN KOBY
EcmuOQyqSN.rg71ge!
i?bglzVLB7txuDr
iBxBm96hwFljKqfYC!
d93GBHel3H4MGf1;nzE!
v5FrTRHi2N?R9PR"lq
lIx3ky7FpOVacDH
kasMgYhIcXsgQ4vL0R
A28yNgPnbXcQMrkNJYKp
His status is unknown.
CAPTAIN KOBY
6I0FnrW5x2d5eUgeZ!
7hX5FXQfm5B,;y6
v6;OrOH2,1bramT0q!
,pfNHSVzCvutBVZ1n?D!
p4,iCeYakgfq7aB6pn
.l2"xNRj4JQxFJK
8KQ1MPySKFH7HrSUaX
gSUNwqAHwlPM7jTT6'L;
CAPTAIN KOBY
?xt2HZc:N8sc6TXU5!
7D3wslz87iuV1pG
13AP!cKrOvsq!u,0,!
LoLRR.A;eUb8AdSTwSF!
cT;Y4Lg7N4r,IQDz'd
"hkKUh?r!IaUx7E
92"rc6iSXHqtPD24;m
WlbaynX;VLGr!bFK1643
CAPTAIN KOBY
QE??FUe:Un5S.Ct.Z!
lZfC:g;20DGwTJG
muqWIqPAR!?bkVVOe!
ngdh'PrjJuY2"25J0Mn!
"pC5o8?"eW??Kvt'Fz
;gQHFIuUI3qz:r.
xL6ALTAhbl4,a7j'0Y
2jMm3,H7YbD.XGc6gPLR
CAPTAIN KOBY
IgS"TwRiMKM?T.A1a!
qfY:,f7'I8!DnUY
tFD,J2.oxx?AT6k5b!
kM:RBHkiPf0lq294M:R!
6NVNSm"CG8HZtR2MtM
pYVeJyZ3.buIFsU
9cI;3ZDSW?;'!;Y:B"
:E7ZQ2nqvSqZl;kvbtb4
CAPTAIN KOBY
Hjjk3YCLf1,MIFeo:!
vm:g,2JsPNGvtPp
0OJZxmoQ5U7sn'MJc!
!qf3nVh9!"zP:.xd8ZA!
kYzxROPH20,lQjqwyK
lDdluLtmYNwYTO1
R8ciHdq"lPyX,EK1S2
ljGPcqotDgi"HEg7VRY1
EYHTBXKwMM6p.l'ci!
I,3zLJwAw:FL7Kf
CPj47ZhiVl:Bpvhzg!
0S"LbH"PZy9D'7OwF:Y!
5Xyw3JY,CxiF4rs2Od
tFdB0XOj9wvNpGP
W8EToh?wzltJy2xWrY
Bt4pvrjdmw4dtjBCe7?f
CAPTAIN KOBY
4nO!PsYLTAmJF8Ch1!
JnxasYX0gcf!1,6
J4'dd9Zm9np.9Yp6w!
o2w,v;UxAHJbk6or!zx!
AW8n9RjFulCaKVTMu;
NrhhL'RukzzQEAZ
xs0Ucr:mjAvIPQlPSz
FwreAE8GimH,,qpUwWUj
CAPTAIN KOBY
!l;LemNPOGtp7xFH.!
sxWLI'fPGJg8O1?
G1nJzZwE9GHIpwXj3!
"5dLDa4"Tv;qTC9:0T"!
E;?5'lN.1jTM8"uAuL
uIJe5;Qkg2qZGpv
!yFyATWxRK61Z:8I;F
CzIZ3:p,YY6Wr?Q,slPz
CAPTAIN KOBY
KEidwS;ATu;?Zdg7r!
JOJpyYPggzTkXmv
;YRVOE:hIWedrHWgV!
1iem"DtUzysFY4OjM7"!
5Hic5by7nPh6m;mccu
G2EVffbeM.,!B0T
t:eBsQ74IHd;Fzj1Lh
KkILq56YRT"W8k2unPTR
CAPTAIN KOBY
qB4?sOW:4TiYFfhop!
.0QZDh7;0Yof5T,
b!2Q"lp1!'ndRA!.!!
5PmRZdBvSvzDTlmrZeo!
muaJNfQD1q2FjO?gKy
.X8LyF7,W,YQVro
zCIH1'D4bNrVWNBUdj
q83Jl:pv5ho6.4iJ'j7s
:PPn3oTls8WmFj."Y!
SkUwStaYMjkGxs9
L88B5olOuoCBCCjKA!
Cr?lrJiPhwk?J.'uULQ!
pROvw',dJRvPjmzyrl
pCbXtTmshZt;.3W
iF9alS,mkSawvcVia"
pB24axOv8BirAcyJEFCf
CAPTAIN KOBY
fuCEN1qa.Mz8LZVXd!
Ggs.p!:oiMImxjT
S.Qpx7icqn.FV:IpC!
6Afe94wHq2lgFKxSWRI!
xfuuNcdtD9:,UCg"TV
!iOjpApxh03TxWN
DIkmlRXBo3EtEU'BO0
iqMQJlntRDiHjZo?lbeq
CAPTAIN KOBY
NRYRVlZ8aeYvSYQxX!
RgupMUBTO4W?ppI
qm3:nAtD9kcBj:em5!
QFG"3Fx4z99AFIjhfqo!
NNGV0aE;kN2A8Kqy8F
pQvgR.et;Ia!Rn6
1adQOJ.rA;2D3Ja4Lx
I7kx?ZLFAcbD1WJAEUpg
CAPTAIN KOBY
bJB"Z2F3Tl8x4LpL8!
"IepSs4IsH5;U.v
'xHv8fou'uqIL8Is;!
t0GgrS?K.B8HrnCqK6Y!
'ZwX9HH,JkfHyECLOL
u6XEaVVqdSh.i?6
7UCW6aIdR!ORB8GeV:
geN3:sTK9ECp.ku3DK5.
CAPTAIN KOBY
nhlmDla6DcuKStlab!
kS9WJ5NyFyu"5SR
i0sLsIHW.33Pclm,E!
.TNeUKM022FVIxpwWAn!
Jh,155;6g'lC!4Y"J"
"Gbsl.NMBuUD"d5
EwLiC17P"iaX?Aewyg
rkNQS3eUaiivSTLk,6vq
Y1hVAgrcowJXb1ze.!
dF;;QhWq1GA"aH?
1BOeMvz';vRXVH6K6!
hlH0fzFBWoDQtEneDTx!
XmZjQELNnP.HDxTTUj
oOLnIWktQfXF,sZ
Aj23"w?fK;1pKgLSV5
l,"eCNhMmZj.gOk4.lnU
CAPTAIN KOBY
9IQ9":UGIaUW3hxao!
P!jwvIYZajq!eVn
P,I;lgOWMYVwVQezC!
86id7ADC3jBj.78w2De!
Kz3N79zf,WUVW?wqzu
Ikh34amc3:Q2Mbk
dT1q"lg!,Nqjsq4JsT
AK.NhhRzrJOZGuZ.pqO!
CAPTAIN KOBY
C5c98E48Tc:80381R!
iC;xN2DXa'NuDdp
k;mM;!ZGFqc9t9jvO!
8sAaa6:hWnGadTSffiz!
mqeWHl52YFvJs?;eU"
zF0fNtRJcgNcs1C
kG75k4WQ"XqvtsJD,D
!9C!4RyS5nrYqS6uy21q
CAPTAIN KOBY
Fu3;Z1eiJDPY9gycm!
;L9YfX7t"'g9M'e
dWAAiAH5FjlaqJFJa!
fTl.Ep"evkppHtcXX:I!
s!cTnn"bjZwGv'0HKp
pH6:TOHCHUUod,Q
MxOTmaiPNOqJxXP3Af
ard':2jJ'E;,OxfK'xac
CAPTAIN KOBY
E:q,mC:ST'Q;RTzcZ!
Y"V0wqhBDv;ofXA
q0FjD8eG,2TI18jJH!
BmF:jHaKk2I'jBYOfiM!
PSMKv6BDgUsbjtoHIv
s2GKQuSYhYw8CHb
l1ZUt3P6kDou.xQoLo
7v'6BwD"wQQ.q"d;Vz7k
CAPTAIN KOBY
E!Of54Rv'6p4OBW7Z!
PiFowj37oYnGodP
Ee8Refw3CQw?6y3ZY!
3I9kxVmk'"Z:1u0Wa6c!
8Z.QNHmTXlUAge5jj.
6x,CX6:9DRVmhlo
g1"BE6peWULgf:tngF
RmJLb7xCyZQCaDYDw4oX
3b,j9Yt9Qqzs2RF0g!
!5H'k7akChat2Uq
y82ZMQQIugV;77D9W!
jsg2!rtWJwk9'8DKc6F!
RI2utz!cH99eUNBaQF
:!q8B20zxwcL0qU
wcQ9u"wzkthBj1kIPb
hK5fH1DXi,"SymYP9TPx
CAPTAIN KOBY
?TQkaYuy7DuXWmBsp!
dP,fqLrkWgL'jsd
9OVJY7ASmIGg7FvBH!
YJ;HP5q!0t4Gsqj"RqB!
,88'go36WZo94:T5R5
DQLZmHo8zVik,3V
SoTqHzUS,tm"sNwme'
tCC4t6M?9B2;H78u9RBO
?liFf1N8'wf'IqYuC!
cIJLm:CI9SPEqWA
J?xqgni:'9HDHm:S2!
uh1xJyMzcfRGhY7ox8K!
Sw9kCjNO7Ku5n;VFGw
xO2,KH,nFC"h;gX
ymzlpdQeLLa7gOFzbb
5anZIkJ59a2fWM5Z"7zb
CAPTAIN KOBY
1v;gpwXLJc0ebypD0!
YncWdxtm5:2ht1p
I;XNO;6"U";gy!75R!
yo'.YU4'm?MIOxOhkap!
MNJV0Hu?EPyUr66n0n
o'3FB06i:'VJdMi
a,:NONJ6ZE3HO.t0ic
QO7s;g?D!.6ZD5'.uQUd
CAPTAIN KOBY
Eykp.fcystFt,QREg!
fSlwzQW5;oAQ;7m
sHjOk2m5WoP;1EHGr!
dhs!Y?,jXDf9.tbzNGb!
TRjzX?rhq;,waiaKdY
rV:2xC,46m,Eh9c
ui.gH'CG"kl8NdgJb8
l2CSkvoCynk1H"LoNpi?
CAPTAIN KOBY
3xb5ElZNM1wHjAKj8!
fF6T!75Tsp6'Nnz
F1LKg'RvtV9VS667c!
B'Jx?3uZAgnWrPEPw3z!
Qo3x7"GNqZnEMXpoPW
8Jqj87:XG2,EN5F
FZYOYeKfEt,qXxd,7L
c":Cjc'GKIUqAm3:2!vz
CAPTAIN KOBY
!JzkxJ2Z'lx,l3at?!
Ad5jBDaBYKJZkLq
6SJ4FN90nPI:eZ4.R!
Ia"SgO9xUJdxe4IHIEj!
2zlkCs;0.M;07g2nYM
R?DDL,VMEEh8:8t
J3aYDN;;pYLE7gb"dN
Qou69c?wQ8A"AJ0FrLlE
CAPTAIN KOBY
Yd,;a4zaMA.yWZ6zb!
7IHklLYLrmA,aJC
zZ93.7vfNWu5Doa4r!
0ySZTAMdJpT18SL'r0w!
EtRC5,5?iFdcE,YvQn
!eBuYJct'9WiNKH
J8PKKL;!NiGvLVR8GS
l:xbb"ArA99rp"sh8XvK
CAPTAIN KOBY
nDzsH"mHU1pHJMxar!
5dhkKrAAmYa6WhP
"zlG:vfhFI80worV0!
GFec2fRWeS3ebXnSRsV!
gQUDfYD6Yf,et6vGLt
Igr7ODJHE80qcQU
Wb3aOAKa1mMzm'gar4
w3Ey1Y.oDg2i5NUNjOgF
CAPTAIN KOBY
ThJ'T6YSu2rembvhA!
jXnXZ5wS6skstl:
:.fzSA,3zVwJ,yA'8!
Elmq?EQqRHmmrh!rJ,d!
"xYq;ZXRng,lLZTjuj
57npuO,!omepRXP
C:9qt?LAwUWvGX?bBQ
ujLtmpzsqw"5HzVsMcBo
CAPTAIN KOBY
MSd6T:VK,oMhRGEN1!
c"wgbTUh'fo!;Px
6b1fssF!Cw1u,Ly't!
aQLH8vW:M"ZKU50aF6e!
b4ecbj4XboNUoQiNzT
b5Ugh0,gtTg;ukj
s'XQeTY:dZ44KkEIEt
sP01k6A"3nFJudHe?aet
CAPTAIN KOBY
NjPim!efvKZ"D,R9J!
3daE34z"L5I;tOV
P6CUMtYyHlncx?O:W!
.fA,t88;kd3Q5KBHc,h!
Ng',k.Ool?bw5USARj
wcqRwZm;?O?RyZE
0x:f'Gcl,Qa!kkXBcS
DNtQ?EteeNCaP7pbno1s
CAPTAIN KOBY
M,ejjNLEyprOVHv8k!
H172a1cIIwxCBg8
RyDu9WAD.N!Wwgz7t!
RFEQ?4KmPRfzv9Mv5x1!
LhCW2NsKAXgs:7zyW9
vi'cK4kG,;3iig;
qateZNOOVNnckLarc6
7BXc;w7x;c3gwkT?k6!6
CAPTAIN KOBY
G47uSxEzv8SjMBpup!
lUHI,Nm,G06A2mm
JFzIrwB.K0R!n80TK!
OOmSLGtPncDMN9sNXRe!
ki3fwZ03;A3yKJNyrJ
xlLfVNYE9Tv;B!'
hF.e!A,j5g7ECiZNzL
f,GXu!;Y80F2NQlNbjal
CAPTAIN KOBY
FSpsq!mIVPsaMwo'M!
UYX8DITvVr7YAWE
JNTKQWSGWrTNZrPP7!
29rhjmx'8"qK'uvtemW!
u8jR.zGl;Rjz35"!AR
.nvf49QEm22Ia.q
aNYjE.4d8l3N152.4j
2REdd'Ue3Ya9bmIoM6;U
CAPTAIN KOBY
krL5n!,.,ojMhQpcT!
,?9kTsqyRqxOD1u
M4V3a6kJT5dF6v3KF!
sHegPmud4yJ'tCfRW3l!
2'fOZV"'asjK;Hk8RL
Z;;za924;OaeM8J
MiwWOYQF3Wb:GC,loS
6tUctAwYvNFNrMEmpj;e
CAPTAIN KOBY
4VK87nO';Sx63r6oZ!
cclNV;RJM7j7:;l
YZYtCdBgfr!13AjRY!
N.ZI1vw;mtIzvhHJRXF!
p7m,Dkx7T6U"bRA,l5
"aZNf?lYyZUdXeu
!a8n"qt?!:giC7rDsZ
Np0hy;FD4eCXMp!qLKeC
CAPTAIN KOBY
AN5bnk??bWdTcb?dL!
i3U;VwyryC0g2IN
jNREAoTSwMSgO2JXA!
WwsYfPbq;'mrJsNNFL;!
1N.kgyiKXgyEJecMHX
C1wSdgsy6Bt,::N
rNn!Q4Wzq8YR6kEa4M
qjjfEyeAzab.zXNNdpUJ
CAPTAIN KOBY
EB"WMmGgrNHC.DDVO!
kWjg?Uw"xXP1EOi
0OIq'fxMUfB?VWEJ:!
:W.mch.WnFQ"AXTLOD;!
G!2jiAx9gNJ?4vvnRT
CEi9kl'M4Pp8X'L
0GGtZqHbAq8;ss6z'A
rtC5ia0?F9"83.WIalOq
CAPTAIN KOBY
?tnE;Q.KOh?Ulgy"N!
X,i6mJM2b"'Mjyy
l0xtPB!!HZQk0PATh!
Prl7Ng'GCFpaq6fVgtd!
8'Sno8jWtA9:6LjqNX
ZHClrPqS0tFhbx'
hWFSudIGor8sJ4kGYe
'z2iNl?l62caK:Jz7o0k
CAPTAIN KOBY
8?W0:7E?b:OC:S3cO!
okD,tMym7pHbY:F
UxfjUfSDGIoAk'S:k!
sIf.Oy8kMQPbG'XnG,Z!
bHmDMXIamFsQuv7!EJ
hQbS32uKkJDjIFO
uLJVAqwkV6mI1AbKRL
VCcIUMvOJgnxq9JoHVvm
cEawBHQYcCdZ!8,FR!
Sw3f9"!eHd6k23d
z3"pSMPoDiCG0kcb4!
g;"lfXMivh;BAKEGhs!!
LXotLRY76ilI3wwuHh
O'p'3:n7MQq7SSy
z0M,RzCmvJ.hqwlP!e
LuGcccfj8CCBhoUYu'ja
CAPTAIN KOBY
Tsga9Nm2T3OF8hz.x!
:zZcvf2i!DrnpFR
ysQ0MxIt5Dncc!izf!
OQWdv0MSuVKmaKRLAJ9!
SiggzNYWk05!C.3N8n
!x2DRDty56Q4Sp4
FFp;2be3Fu;BD,z;iq
Sgx"WiZzjDimawHwwc3X
CAPTAIN KOBY
5MvPfTybErczV?mSg!
sLimqnZK'sdSe:n
N0ln5pd1HGJKxTI?Z!
e:IYb?Qs;:iwp:7tGFU!
QX0g"bLZ"oZz5zPeKq
rp!ad5Tmqnx02UM
NJB66LsOAPRm"Y01Ss
b1R:,d:kB!mq398FtrRq
CAPTAIN KOBY
fAwDWqhVOlUPCW"zw!
K'sO0f1b!G4Obja
8mixN7P,j9,si77.U!
O'!cQ;ntmP;GJR0PKs'!
bIoc?3WCuFbBeKSV3W
,qehL:e'Q:1kXuL
d0yfNJNvxEYTS1vmxn
gDUPro:0C1.zYiCQXW4G
CAPTAIN KOBY
CiS4HmxlxDXWygVoS!
'gRCnSP.wSXUveK
4!7"H,qMR7H"BZWS7!
KyzsaEtmZLn'EnvSXqd!
4nH2.Yj?R3IAdk"NGX
QHKsHI2Jo.q8rlY
HeLFNtxKG.,b8BFcCb
CKGUrvvq?UbJAL:2yKgb
?kSCy7YfSYE8WowXv!
eDdKMvXZ1:sCO!?
I5;8G?d?8n2e;s'Dk!
'jlReM;6:OB!44DDpMW!
4di4,,R3wsBFiZm.6c
Y0m6;QoMdGUX3Yg
fhokD6fcXnYp!htCWp
xvf;VjtsZyKysW?Oqnww
CAPTAIN KOBY
Rxv,A:'fBdrOgXoka!
hAbuofBR;6Yipmy
,B:U6QciSkphFBPSm!
NqhAmvkFovgZ"FRyd4Y!
LOqRjZ0zqwu3O0YBEb
p:VU2kU!3;SqUQ6
8puT9RhDot8u5k58Lq
NnGD3C0RJeF;'bbti?tz
UOEljmqeQxy5IY!vB!
F0"SR?9O8G0H?AZ
?23?pbs:VhGHR9atM!
ihpfbnYa"aGLUL,.l'I!
lyVrlPVqgV0Feurd1z
6?Ut2veKRBrsy;G
sVBROFLIS!d;;sAccm
W3DFnAbZnx7LF.uoT2m3
CAPTAIN KOBY
il"dYfK'5wV6dVsXy!
wQMpuuWGxu6"Vql
Tm'5Io!N;AYv4e.6g!
A.oi6:YrC4JTIx8Qhau!
Cj:mVzstGWvyDYoZo;
IrSz.g.mvftgO!x
?RQWZ,BNqP2pODEotM
Ik,59foeOqgAxZO!zYS'
CAPTAIN KOBY
TcnNAVDhvD0Izy7pu!
39mV"oXEEWsvmAt
f5hRrAP8YeMQotWGO!
.rBjmziB7rRvLeAP?yi!
C?,NxOEXhaCeE7Qbk4
5.s5q6:Vp1.oMYd
Ivyltq"YDBPATj'55w
vKX,NiHMTINVnRppn,Ak
CAPTAIN KOBY
f:ifSIPUKqEeeMCCR!
5un"aXGP0TZ"Omh
rJ4,tn98m?wAdA?X'!
W,FG3,F0i!Bo?"mz;Z?!
sYl;3a;Rsmig840Km2
Yidi6Myw:?1UtQd
SwSPNR'JMQ10qKfQUz
8dPis:5'!:""sWjFPih1
CAPTAIN KOBY
4jUPau;IN9ONLqZhu!
0oXcSLdR?sTdR0u
pw"D5awVveVV2mqoV!
U;zOy"nn;gLgs:?xyq!!
gi,aCo36NmeNZ48KS3
9w8w6jQvmm!w!Tk
15WaWlX;RbBO45:GfZ
v:GmK6ISgmPyvJL4lZEN
CAPTAIN KOBY
,;tmjv9LgfzamVpPo!
C2Kjkz3RJ?3;FQh
U3JpWXw!WrKtlQG4d!
LWWryL747YG,ZskX4wq!
O:Ze;03iT4rxI0agCo
GIeAZD66qivRQ1S
74F5f2:y,mIkkP6rMI
,Qc:7xDiKJgLWmk;o1w7
hJIi.7zF5jMiQ4::;!
,Grrp1kY7ITEJCm
I"d0rS7AImbTHc;:I!
6?tKw8Wsgr:!d7P1elP!
1Ul4OKe.EzGAhuFxBE
tg"fp;Lo6PxkAGL
pfbWfOX:9"VQ:0CwCE
o'yViT;5gB9hLJt'0J03
CAPTAIN KOBY
D2JcJvGOPYuvS;vJ1!
'iu6zNvtCd?G:26
o6'zAGo:.upeX;Vod!
4'3rX8fbHFufyBvAr5!!
O?ihpNx'puLK7aR33T
oMjywN0h:J4PWpx
87!t:46JX,Z0ClFGjq
0XhbwIvVnlta8xh?6,Je
CAPTAIN KOBY
;JsPrgzQLoEpYktRS!
2Gsd!mKU!NOxR'g
yYH'Z,ac'N?E7!6fW!
:0NdRcc5z,PG3,oHf1c!
oTPIaAUGVbUv,c!gDo
ZB45Jt0,2N1qt4K
nRoA8'wnaNe"G9lJOW
MoN:JiKdpBRef79gbovx
CAPTAIN KOBY
P"VQLhw93fX'eYiTv!
:;y6fdk4?'8Rt;S
1Ho.HYPaD7NvMw85O!
yhQf3Qk"L4ThD5jK?Z9!
ctqthYzgtp7z9id?CI
wuz0:H92!2AIjYf
CtBUYKwGQ6NY"sdiWm
;GOi1JFf7sIHfDksYKjK
CAPTAIN KOBY
ZRkEnSELaNLUsn:yc!
65tjlqZ'Nn5oZDi
y,jX:e0C:r9k2F3E,!
y,5n1AbJHuVXkn?8k,V!
4Zq54E?NdNjrFAKZxf
?OdhW9KCN1fAHk9
P'ywv"o::u99vs2myJ
uEKy"O.n4xdIUIZ6yz0X
CAPTAIN KOBY
757VYYgHwhK'7"Ydz!
U0oA'GqXsFA?Sg:
,.8dhOmPY'5KpfD8X!
YZK0FIHxr6f4GbyDMj0!
mXYYx0wTaSl'C1Wt?X
tUNNuOx"jw1J2Vk
qFUhRWMy"e7BZOzdlZ
FQ?28IEaSBVyOV'ZQUnO
CAPTAIN KOBY
WmnapchKA0ov35RRK!
OxC"QnHJuh0ua9P
.1PrDDl3sTI'ZEj8?!
;FlmsIlJBX;29I748F!!
jSec9O:ulz'27gx6N4
7jTGfq84Y8rTtIp
NDA1bdoDjqR1n"eC,a
.smGn0T;;r!ZbsFcYbDC
CAPTAIN KOBY
R1c9fSQW:d6hdB:?x!
JGERbLUXVblT;zd
T,V'LGYV,60U9zMPH!
s,G?d0ZzXmxJwwu:k;G!
SrJtFX!B7;8;eqS5M9
U1YCB"V05Edxq.R
jsXcZdt!CTWwLuVoBv
hhxQV5"!wEJWHAw..r7e
CAPTAIN KOBY
sDsCUsalmvv3p?GSD!
1PLLVGkNcledxc,
!L,2Z2TeDO:BUHfzu!
tG81jMnn0eexGAiBdBh!
8GTn"7r1iTBZweZx3c
czr.rgUN3.dn.Zc
8TS?,.KpLcdtYtMYDK
hOxYn7'mYmqun2xcrken
CAPTAIN KOBY
WKpHgEE6JY,SjWGZ4!
Z.nwqmdGnO'A1EW
m9lXl;AbqevNzKmjC!
t,k5Kaka.WzMCYqlQb9!
oJq:xwC1aQ2TK,Hg"X
'so4EwZV9b2fCVo
b,VQh6L?eCDNOOirfY
76ny'X;aKIZO8kS8bA73
CAPTAIN KOBY
vBdinl!YVKUT?74Z?!
.:h,vyRd2XAD,:,
o8'HqEs,tcFzfaV9Z!
kIhVeuNRpRKjCI"wATl!
T"b";Hep3!ZSnEYxpH
,"B4jVwwZvm6D0z
6zVz?UBX58kp:WFoeB
8v0NSuNTqR7WhNPR2SDc
CAPTAIN KOBY
wyumIOLFOTpcQnWcp!
:iv,sGeqMku'UUs
",vWZWCN0ebdIWtrC!
3l?6lNDx2ohLSoAOs'7!
9TcMCh4p;4CzxiMDch
5Vs6;lgUfL!q0fY
5AK!S8fNV75UqasW?A
NIOkLN.RhNMzcq9"!tgw
CAPTAIN KOBY
Q;7:Pbgs,VQCA51P!!
xi0dW:FXX,bUX4G
Ac3Y,UXRjxuH"CZNn!
OTMWaQP:kGB.cKB;nHh!
KV:p0Ud2s2wy?86InS
JBGkE93mYH4hJMa
uRIhFygqEn.r3coN2v
fKLCS1K9gUeIod'3yNAb
CAPTAIN KOBY
GbnGvLLy!IhstYlV3!
EgVmwRyVvR"5lr5
;aio:JfMVzq0mTyxO!
8fQQb'6rV5dVkXn9:RX!
sh0q.g1SRJi80nQd!K
WXc67ux4I7GBjBh
NDmUc.5b7Kb;HCV8tI
'K0YahukEM5!tdlpJXop
CAPTAIN KOBY
BGzp"Of?Zt84WADpV!
sQQzM:nJWMurksU
MQ2,mV!9fLVCeU5En!
nTUU6KcELxBdfK5rKl4!
rvy3;cp8TTqyVy7S5H
UxetAZt7Z"gGNwJ
eX!H8niq!qovDtG0nm
SdeFWKSE?kyunJgAue8N
CAPTAIN KOBY
LOellIyujq3OC8"Py!
1ZWR'7"3SzZWGN!
apw5iVV:.hNSC2ITc!
T0QvQD"jP'j8?8l4UQ3!
aiYjSbrug;BoX!dsc2
L7SrOpD;j"9XUNL
bDlYV'J'ANN62?wQUI
hCfBRXrFZYRX!sX'bZmM
CAPTAIN KOBY
N2W;N1sV?NGFJHojF!
8QVMeNji;cpf"a;
zFpzCE5uVRz6OLUFw!
;zbCmfF!C3l!y2.QOTG!
NR6ZN6"zaNdy"KUBmb
e"HANNNvImvq'Qu
i"U2Ewv:LTBY7G8lvP
U,lCO.RgjbrZeUi6!qda
CAPTAIN KOBY
?8!a3o.CvqT;m,!0s!
RrXa57bCkMRZ2hb
9h8hxtYEkxKfuDRZS!
H,D96lJ?E2G16XEd!Ju!
xAajs?oK6c:nx5BUdk
xB7IGzj:nVciOuy
040gezB2gr5Brp"3?V
kgO4"3Q3BLFV"2ik!GhC
CAPTAIN KOBY
KJ9euM1w?xSJy3a8;!
nTM6.4mv2kg;77'
QF:dDfXqA5bOhySh,!
KrVzso,B7WBIP!zJdzb!
Wy?;K!,9MGZdpw;3uv
s"6nUfYG9763LZh
xtrE7;.hefHa838am;
5Afof:VpM4Y7vGgrMw'l
There's no way that's true!
He would never kill Vivi's dad!
Sabo would never do something like that!
Of course.
I agree with you.
The Revolutionary Army's
enemies are the world nobles.
Not the kings!
"Revolutionary Army Declares
War on Celestial Dragons"...
"Chief of Staff Sabo Assassinates
King Cobra of Arabasta"?!
"Disappearance of Arabasta's
Royal Daughter, Princess Vivi"?!
Where are you and how are
you feeling, my darling Vivi?!
Please be safe!
Set sail for Arabasta!
Now!
King Cobra is already dead.
What would be the point?
And Vivi disappeared in
Mary Geoise, of all places.
Then...
we're going to Mary Geoise!
What?
What?! Are they going to Mary Geoise?
I'm in trouble...
I can't really hear them!
That's our enemies' stronghold, idiot!
Do you plan to take on Marine Headquarters?!
Damn right!
What, are you scared, Zoro?!
I'm just saying we have no leads!
Calm down!
Vivi's father is dead?!
He was so nice to us
even though we're pirates...!
I'd like to thank you...
from the bottom of my heart as a father
and as a resident of this land.
Thank you very much.
Yeah! No other king is that kind!
Vivi!
I'm so worried!
This must be so hard for her!
I can't help but worry!
Vivi!
– Vivi!
It seems like the last Reverie
was quite tumultuous.
I've never heard a single shady rumor about
the Kingdom of Arabasta's government.
The Revolutionary Army's
chief of staff, Sabo...
We met that big brother of yours
in Dressrosa, didn't we, Luffy?
I can't take it! I'm worried about Vivi!
Where is she?!
Me, too! Alright! Let's go rescue her!
Let's go!
– Yeah!
That's enough, you guys!
Luffy!
What did you say...
when Ace was in trouble?
Ace has his own adventures.
You trusted him to pull through
on his own until he actually needed help.
Are you underestimating Vivi?
She can take care of herself!
When the time comes for us to step in,
we'll give one hell of a fight!
We can't do anything now,
so stop making a fuss!
All we can do is make a fuss,
so let us make a fuss!
This guy's an oni!
You Onigashima!
Green Kaido!
Green Mom!
Shitty Moss Head!
– Boo!
– Boo! Boo! Boo!
Shut up, number four.
Again with this?!
It's not so easy being above you!
Since when are you above me?!
Always have been and always will be!
While we were in Wano,
so many incidents have occurred,
and they're developing rapidly...
The abolition of the Warlords...
sent those elite pirates back to sea.
And that led to...
the foundation of Cross Guild,
and Buggy the Bombastic Clown's
ascension as a new Emperor!
That last one's gotta be a mistake!
Maybe it is and maybe it isn't.
Thanks!
Luffy.
There are a few other names in here
that have connections to you...
Do you want to hear?
I'll leave it to you.
Just tell me the important ones!
All right.
Let's do that.
You've already got a lot on your mind.
Sabo is innocent!
He...
grew up in a strict home,
so he just wants to set everyone free!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country and live freely!
I wanna see the world out there
and write a book about it!
Seafaring is the one thing I do love to study!
Let's get even stronger
and become pirates someday!
That was my plan anyway!
You don't have to tell me!
When I'm a pirate, I'll beat up everyone
and become the biggest, baddest one of all!
That's the only way I'll prove that I lived!
It doesn't matter if the whole world
rejects or despises me,
I'll become a great pirate and show them all!
I won't run from anyone!
I won't lose to anyone!
Whether I'm feared or hated or whatever,
my name will be known all over!
We made an oath.
The three of us, including Ace!
I got it!
Alright!
I'm gonna...
What did you just say?
What?
That's so funny!
Hey! No, no, no... No way!
I love it!
That's great!
Hey, Chopper. Examine his head!
No way!
That's impossible!
Maybe it's possible once
I'm King of the Pirates!
No one would think something like that...
Huh?
Didn't I tell you?
Any of you?
Well, I don't care if you didn't...
Because that's impossible!
I guess I only told Shanks, Ace, and Sabo.
What did they say?
They just laughed.
Shanks laughed himself to tears.
That's what I want at the end of my dream.
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Quality Control
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Villager
Zenef
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Villager
Zenef
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Villager
Zenef
Graphics
Datenshi
Maktree
PhosCity
Datenshi
Maktree
PhosCity
Datenshi
Maktree
PhosCity
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Typesetting
Gab
PhosCity
(Mou
Soundtracking
Halee
(Mou
Subtitle Editing
Lorphex
Poppy
Westfal
Lorphex
Poppy
Westfal
Lorphex
Poppy
Westfal
Translation
Crunchyroll
PamkinPenguin
ssho