Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Those are our Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go, always, be the best
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
We got to carry on Hard knock days
The State of the War
Pica-sama's head's come off, and he's stopped moving!
What happened?!
Now's our chance!
I will take down Doflamingo!
I will!
No, I will!
They're coming again!
Stop them!  Don't let them reach the palace!
I-It's hopeless. The Colosseum fighters won't stop.
Look at them go!
I can't believe they're still resisting the young master.
They're crazy -in.
Indeed.  Fujitora and his Navy grunts are right outside the palace.
G, for Navy Grunts!
So it was the Straw Hats that stopped Pica after all.
There are four different enemies approaching the palace right now.
Alright, here I am!
Transform!
The Smile factory!
Now it's time to smash the factory gates!
Radical Beam!
Not that your attack could even scratch the factory, but...
I came to settle things with you, just to be safe.
You still wanna fight?!
That's what men do, kiddo.
Senor!
Please, Kyros! Come out and surrender!
If you don't come out, we'll come for you!
We don't want the money, but the slaughter won't stop until everyone's dead!
We have no choice! We want to put an end to this nightmare!
I wish to end this battle as quickly as possible.
I will not blame you for your judgment, but you've reminded me of why I must keep going!
Fire!  Don't let him escape!
I, too, have something I must do!
Huh?! Luffy-senpai ain't here!
Of course he isn't.
You knew?!
Luffy can't stay still in one place for five minutes.
Freedom!
I'd expect no less from the Pirate King!
Robin-san, they're still coming after us.
Once we reach the top, we've won!
We have to take the net down once we're done with it.
You did it!
Pardon me.
Big Sis!
King Riku, what is that stone monster?
Why is the palace over there?
I found it.
Viola-san!
Viola!
I found it, Father.
The key to Trafalgar Law's handcuffs.
I finally found it using my Clairvoyance.
We have to get it to him somehow.
Wait, Viola!  Why are you so concerned about them?
They're pirates!
That's right. They are the outlaws who will tear down the peaceful façade of this country!
Father, I'm betting everything on them, on the Straw Hat Pirates.
The pirate Doflamingo, who was given the rank of Warlord by the World Government,
has reigned over this country and caused us all so much pain.
I don't want any help from the World Government or the Navy, who pretend to be so righteous!
They can't hear...
The voices of the victims...
The enraged screams of this country.
The people in charge only ever hear what they want to hear.
At least the Straw Hats have passion behind their words, and they act according to their hearts!
I'll beat the crap out of Doflamingo!
So stay with my crewmates.
King Riku. King Riku!
Look at this man.
Aren't you the five-star?
That's right!  He is God Usopp, also known as Usoland!
This man fought without regard for his own safety...
And broke the spell on the toys that had endured for ten years!
He is our hero!
Usoland!
Usoland! Usoland!
And Luffyland is that superhero's captain!
King Riku, the Usolanders, aka the Straw Hat Pirates, are this country's shining star of hope!
Even if they are pirates, we will trust them to the very end!
Viola-san, I'll take that key to Lucy.
Rebecca?!
I can't wait around here. Please let me go.
Rebecca...
Alright, great idea! Go to Luffy-senpai!
Of course, I'm coming along! Leave it to me!
Rebecca, if you go down there, you'll be hunted down as an outlaw in Doflamingo's game.
It won't be easy for you.
I'll be fine.
In that case, you could go via the rooftops!
Kabu-san and I will accompany you, so don't worry!
Via the rooftops?!
That's right! Inhel, I can leave the factory to you, right?
Of course!
According to our reconnaissance unit, Fraland is currently fighting Señor Pink.
We will help Fraland to free our captured friends and Princess Mancherie!
Good.
Then I'll see you later!
Everyone, there's no time to relax! Let's meet up back here at the royal grounds!
Now let's go!
Straw Hat Luffy... What a strange man.
Doflamingo!
How odd!
Ah! It's so odd!
How could those idiots from the Colosseum climb all the way up here?!
I thought there were thousands of marines down there!
I thought so too -in!
Vice Admiral Bastille and Navy HQ Admiral Fujitora, too!
How did they make their way through?!
Hey!  Is this all the Donquixote Family's got?!
We'll reach their boss soon!
I have a report!
Straw Hat Luffy has made it to the first l-
Rubber Gatling!
Outta my way!
We can't... c-compete with him...
Straw Hat!
They're dropping like flies!
T-The Colosseum fighters are coming up too!
Straw Hat!
I see them, Dellinger!
The marines are being stalled.
What?!
Is there no way to have you move aside?
That's right.
The Straw Hat Pirates and those warriors who support them...
I can't let anyone who's trying to hurt them...
Go any farther!
Is it the Revolutionary Army's job to protect pirates?
Yes, it is.
As a member of the Revolutionary Army, I won't let you through.
No, I got it wrong.
As a brother, I can't let you pass!
Oh?
And precisely whose brother might you be?
You bastard!
That won't hurt me.
I have the power of the Mera Mera Fruit.
Are you kidding me?!
The Navy can't be defeated by a single member of the Revolutionary Army!
Wait!  Don't do it!
Fire!
I said "Don't!"
This guy's fingers are freakishly strong!
They're claws!
Step back!
You guys can't beat him!
My fingers are...
Dragon claws!
The claws that rip apart those bigoted people in power!
He broke Vice-Admiral Bastille's Shark-Cleaver!
Why, you...
These claws can...
crush human skulls like an egg!
I have a problem.
Since that bird cage thing is in the way, my meteor's going to be sliced, isn't it?
Run!
It's a meteorite!
Oops! What a fine mess!
It's all over the place...
I hope no civilians got hurt.
When you plan to bring down a meteorite, let us know, Isshou-san!
Oh, I'm sorry!  I brought one down!
Before you do it!
Do you know the position you're in?
I still haven't gotten used to my own power...
So I tried to ward it off.
Vice Admiral Bastille!
Vice Admiral!
You said you had to do this "as a brother" earlier, did you not?
Yeah.
The previous owner of the Mera Mera Fruit, Fire Fist Ace, who died at Marineford,
claimed that he was Straw Hat's adopted brother.
You mean you're his brother too?
We exchanged cups of brotherhood.
We're tied by an unbreakable bond.
What a troublesome bunch of brothers.
What kind of brothers are they?!
Straw Hat's brothers...
One of them was one of Whitebeard's commanders,
And the other one is the Revolutionary Army's second-in-command?!
Remember this...
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
I'll throw my rank aside and come to his aid, no matter where in the world we are.
I never...
Newspaper: Ace is dead
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
...want to go through that again!
I guess there's no point in asking you any more questions.
You don't care anyway, do you?
I don't have any sake to go along with your stories.
I will...
protect Luffy!
New Royal Palace
First Step
Go! Go! Go!
That's the Reaper of the Colosseum!
Bring the bull down and get him bucked off, then he'll just be a prize in the game!
Don't underestimate Ucy!
Ucy! Go! Go!
He's the Reaper! Bow down!
Outta the way!
We're gonna go straight to the palace!
Ah!  Cabbage!
Straw Hat!  I'll be going on ahead of you!
Damn! I thought I was taking a shortcut!
You gotta run faster, Ucy!
Damn, everybody's catching up!
It's Hajrudin!
Outta my way! I have no business with you small fry!
I gotta keep moving!
Oh, no! They're gonna get ahead of me!
Shoot, shoot!
Here they come, again!
Don't wimp out! Shoot the bull!
We're gonna fall!
Stop messing with Straw Hat Luffy! You idiots!
Ra-Ra-Ra-Rampage!
Who's that?
Hey, don't be so cold.
I was a contender in Block C, same as you.
Assassins From Mogaro, Funk Brothers
Older Brother: Kelly (Fused With Younger Brother Bobby)
I'm Kelly Funk!
You were?
Hey, hey, hey!
We were saved by God Usopp like the others!
I found a shortcut to reach the higher levels.
You can make it straight to the Sunflower Field,
right in front of the Palace!
What? Really?!
I wanna help you!
Alright! We're gonna overtake Cabbage and the others in one spurt!
Hey, Straw Hatter!
When can I get rid of these handcuffs?
With these Sea Stone shackles, I might as well be going there just to get killed by Doflamingo.
Well, it'll work itself out! Let's just go!
How can you be so sure?!
Go back to the plateau where we were before, then!
Huh? Why?
I'll look for the key!
This fight's gonna be win or die!
See? There's a shortcut!
Now, go ahead, Straw Hat. We'll guard the entrance!
Alright, thanks!
Ucy, let's go!
Take care.
Good job, Kelly Funk!
Make sure to guard the entrance! Thanks a lot!
They fell... What did they want, after all?
All right!  Don't worry and keep going, Ucy!
Straight to the Sunflower Field!
S-Straw Hat-san...
M-May you be victorious!
Your Snail Phone...
Answer it.
Hello?
This is Luffy!
The man who'll become the Pirate King!
Luffy. It's me.
Robin!
We're still at the plateau you were at before.
Where are you?
We're at the first level of the other plateau and heading for the Sunflower Field.
The Sunflower Field is on the fourth level.
Viola found the key to Traf-kun's handcuffs.
Oh yeah?!
Nicoer, get it to me as soon as possible!
What should I do?!
Hello, this is Leo of the Dwarf Tribe.
We're gonna escort Rebecca-sama, the rooster-human and Robiland there at super high speed!
Let's meet up at the Sunflower Field on the fourth level.
What? How will you guys catch up with us?
I'll explain later! See you at the Sunflower Field!
See?  I told you it's gonna be alright!
It's just a coincidence!
All right!  Ucy, run!
Stop! He's going in the water!
What?! It's a dead end!
Go back! Hurry!
Ucy! Don't panic!
Somebody's coming.
This is just a slanted water well.
There's no shortcut in here.
It's you!
Editing: Sewil
Timing: Datenshi
QC: Mr Luffy,
Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking: Halee
Doflamingo!