Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
Translation & initial syncing
Vegapunk Fansubs
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
Syncing
Galaxy 9000
Sync-checking
Sewil
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Feeso
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Video editing
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
Raw provider
SOFCJ-Raws
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Clash!
The Titanic Battle Against Zombie 900!
They don't have a wanted poster.
Which means the ones remaining are...
That straw hat from before...
An orange woman...
And a cool hero.
I'm missing three people.
Where could they be?
She's awake.
Stop!
Perona-sama.
I hate cockroaches! Get them off!
Please calm down!
Not cockroaches!
There's no such thing!
Where am I?
The enemy is no longer here.
You were unconscious.
What happened?
And to you of all people.
What happened to the mansion?!
Was this the pirates' doing?!
The pirates caused a lot of trouble, but...
These are the traces of Oars' mindless rampage.
Oars?
And, according to our reports, Oars annihilated all the Zombie Generals.
The ultimate army?!
Is Oars out of control?!
Well, that's-
Guys!
Brothers!
Woman!
O-Oars?
B-By the way, it seems Hogback-sama got trampled...
What?!
No woman here?
Woman!
Woman?
This is bad, I have to get out of here!
Thriller Bark is being destroyed by Oars and the pirates!
Quickly! Gather the provisions and treasures!
Once you've put them on their pirate ship, we're outta here!
Their?
The Straw Hats'!
We will escape on their ship!
Quickly!
Yes, immediately!
Meanwhile, in an empty room.
Now, the vow kiss.
What?!
W-W-W-Wait!
What's this?!
No! Stop!
You're awake?
Give up, then!
Once I kiss you, you will become my wife.
I said no! You invisible, perverted beast!
I still wanna go on adventures!
Be quiet and accept it!
You will become the Graveyard King's wife! The Graveyard Queen!
No! What is that?!
Curse you, Namizou!
Lo-
Lola!
Namizou...
You!
How could you betray me?
That speech back then about supporting me was nothing but a lie!
What support?! You were trying to steal Ab-sama from me!
What kind of friend are you?!
W-Wait a minute, Lola!
I was unconscious all this time.
I don't know what's-
A wedding dress?
Why am I wearing this?
It's beautiful.
It's not beautiful, you traitor!
Wait! This is a misunderstanding!
Dammit, Lola!
Not only did you interrupt my wedding, but you are trying to harm my bride!
Shut up and marry me!
Hell no!
Ab-sama, you have no idea, do you?
This woman's real name is Namizou!
And she is actually a man!
What?!
That's impossible!
I did say that...
But, at the bathroom I certainly...
Disappear, Namizou!
Stop, Lola!
Hey, stop already, Lola!
Is she missing...?!
Namizou.
Lola.
Escape, Namizou.
I'll keep him busy.
I'm here to save you, my friend!
Lola!
Ab-sama!
Now that you know the truth, Absalom, forget about her and marry me instead!
Lola...
My bride is escaping!
I am your bride!
There's no doubt she's a woman, Lola.
Get out of my way!
Lola!
Meddling zombie...
You made me waste my strength.
Very smart...
You stopped running.
Either way...
You can't get away from me.
I'm an invisible man.
Thunder Charge!
How dare you!
I'm here to save you, my friend!
How dare you hurt Lola!
That's it! Come straight into my arms!
Swing Arm!
It won't hurt you anyway!
I'm aware of that!
How come?
Back on the bridge, he didn't feel it.
Figures... He already exerted himself when he fought that man.
That must be it.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I won!
I must have hit a weak spot!
Lola!
Are you alright?
Hang in there!
Thank you for coming to save me!
Why are you thanking me, Namizou?
We're friends.
But... Back then, I was scared of you, so I lied...
I'm sorry.
I'm actually a woman.
Silly you.
I knew.
Lola.
More importantly! Ab-sama is off-guard right now!
You shall be my husband now, Absalom!
Are you here?!
Come out, Straw Hat!
Woman!
Cool hero!
What was his name?
Let's see...
I'm sure it was Ross.
No, you got it wrong.
It ended with... "rs".
Fuse.
Whoa, that's a wild guess.
Uars?
Something's still missing...
Oars.
That's it!
Excuse me... I'm sorry, but my body...
Yeah, don't worry.
Can you still move?
Yes.
Then step aside.
Hey, Oars!
If you have Luffy's shadow inside of you...
Then you should already know that you should never...
underestimate your crewmates' strength.
You're a sturdy bunch, little pirates.
I have a proposal for you all...
How about we flip this guy over?
I see.
That would certainly be nice.
W-Wait a minute!
F-Flip over?!
This huge thing?!
However, with this enormous size, Luffy's attacks are more impressive.
But he doesn't look like a "Pirate King" in the least.
How shall we strike?
There are countless ways to do it.
He must have a weakness.
When you're catching a big fish, the most common tactic is to weaken it bit by bit.
If that's the plan, then I am...
Too scared.
I'll squash you!
Here he comes!
Rubber...
Butt Slam!
What kind of attack is that!?
Scatter!
Scythe!
Bastard.
In that case, I will show you...
Our combined power!
You two!
Let's do it!
Tactics Fifteen!
What?!
No way...
Are we gonna use "that" here?!
Zoro!
Curly!
Stand by!
Just hold my legs!
What is he up to?
Here we go!
Pirates Docking 6...
Giant Robot Warrior...
Big Emperor!
Wait a minute, Franky!
The left arm hasn't docked yet!
What?!
Hey, what're you waiting for, Nico Robin?!
Hurry up and dock onto my left arm!
Robin, hurry!
Come, Robin!
Do it like me!
For a person, that's shameful.
Why did you stop?
Why're you shocked as well?!
I was starting to get excited.
Do it!
The docking!
How absurd! I can't believe they made me do such a thing.
No, forget it happened.
Robin, if you had joined, we would've completed the Robot Warrior, Big Emperor!
I never thought you'd betray us! Never!
Luffy would have done it!
Don't ever ask me again...
to do your docking.
Payback time, you bastard!
Franky!
I'm gonna borrow this huge thing!
You! That's my Heavy Nunchaku!
It can't be helped,
I'll lend it to you!
You bastard.
I have to hurry and go re-rescue Nami-san!
You?
Robin!
Once I reach his left arm, you take care of the joint!
Understood.
Perona-sama!
The fridge is already full!
Nothing else will fit.
There's still the pantry, isn't there?
Roger.
Hurry with the treasure!
Load the rest of it!
Roger!
Take this!
Deadly Special Oil Star!
Tri
ple
Shot!
Hey, curly eyebrow!
Throw me!
Carrying such huge thing...?
It's okay if you can't handle it!
Bastard!
Of course I can, idiot!
Armée de l'Air...
Air Army
Power Shoot!
Great Sword Strike!
Cien Fleur...
One Hundred Flowers
Big Tree!
W-What?
D-Dangerous... I'm falling! I'm falling!
Behold!
My super instant-made mid-air stairs!
Franky Skywalk!
But... this foothold won't last much longer!
Let's go already, Chopper!
Ok!
Super...
Frapper...
Gong!
Regardless of size, the human body always has the same weak spots.
Hitting your jaw will shake your brain a bit.
Now your only support is that single leg...
Monster Luffy.
Anti-Manner...
Kick...
Course!
Completely flipped that monster over.
Alright! Go down!
One down.
Hey, hey! This doesn't look like a mansion anymore.
What are those moves?!
Acrobatics?!
C-Could it be that...
Someone flipped him over?
C'mon, use your head.
Not even an army of one thousand men would be capable of such a thing.
I'll be fine, Namizou.
You go ahead and escape.
Let me explain the current situation.
Lola...
That friend of yours, Strawhat Luffy...
The Special Zombie who holds his shadow is rampaging all over the island.
It's the zombie we saw at that freezer room.
How troublesome!
How are we gonna take Luffy's shadow back from that monster?!
But...
There's no way I'm going back empty-handed after going through this nightmare!
There it is!
And it's not locked!
Why, you bastards...
I've had enough of you!
I will crush you all!
I just followed Moriah-sama for fun anyway.
Of course I'm not gonna stick around if my life is on the line.
Now, hurry up, all of you!
We need to get outta here as soon as possible!
Yes.
Alright! Load the remaining provisions!
Who are you?
You're not a zombie, are you?
What're you doing here?
Such a huge body...
You look just like a bear.
A Bear huh?
Now that's the right answer.
Is Moriah...
around here?