Scattered Evasion!
Now fall and prepare to have your brain splattered!
Mid-Air Spinning Big-Top!
How did ya' like that, ya' big sea gorilla!
Wha-?! It didn't work?!
That's dangerous!
S-Stop punching me!
S-Seems like you're a little stronger now...
Man, these guys're tough!
What're these animals?
They're the Wrestlers of the Sea, the Blue Gorillas!
Or just Blugori.
Don't let your guard down! There's still four more of 'em...
You have already beaten them up!
But we don't have time to fight all these guys...
He's amazing! He beat the Blugori!
Hey, what are you?!
Please, open the lock for us!
What is it?
Wasn't there just one prisoner on the loose?
I'm pretty sure it was just one...
Maybe I'm seeing things, but I could've sworn I saw two shadows...
Anyway, five Blugori are down in front of Shared Cell 10.
Five? There's no way!
There aren't any Level One prisoners who can beat the Blugori!
What?!?!?!?!
You wanna save Ace?!
Yup.
Quiet!
You're the one who were shouting...
Hey, C'mon! Get the key to the cage...
That's enough out of you!
Shut up!
You know Ace?
Sure.
Unlike you, that brother of yours was a gentleman.
After that, we had a blast, and wound up drinking buddies...
It's a shame what's happened to him.
The nerve to lay a hand on Whitebeard's crew... The Navy sure is stupid.
I wanna go to that Level Five place.
That's where Ace is, right?
Think I care?! If you wanna go, then go by yourself.
Think we're friends or something?!
No way I'm going somewhere that dangerous.
See ya.
If you ain't leaving, I'll just escape on my own.
Even with over a dozen warships out there?
You really think you can get out?
A d-dozen?
I get it.
They're preparing for Whitebeard's attacks...
Perhaps this is a bad time to leave.
Guess I could kill some time down here, then.
Oh well. I'll just ask someone else.
Please give us the key!
No, there's no way!
It just can't be!
Could it be...?!
See ya. Good luck escaping.
There's no mistaking it.
Hey, wait, Straw Hat!
What the hell?!
There they are! Up there!
They found us!
Why'd you have to shout?!
That bracelet of yours sure is nice!
Give it to me!
What're you talking about?
I got this from Nami!
I'll tell ya how to get to where Ace is!
Seriously?
Sure. Will you give me that bracelet?
Yeah, if you'll help. Okay.
All right!
Then first, let's lose these guys!
Carry my feet with you!
Feet?
Run, Straw Hat!
Explanation of Buggy The Clown's Bara Bara Fruit Power.
He's able to split up his body and control each part separately.
However, his control is limited to a small field,
and his feet must remain on the ground while he's using his power.
What a stroke of luck this is!
Captain! Captain!
What?
Are you sure this is the spot?
The legendary cave Captain John dug out in order to hide his great treasure,
that he cruelly protected in the past?
Yeah, this is the place. Keep moving.
Right.
Listen up!
The treasures are guarded,
so if you let your guard down, you might not live that long!
Will we encounter monsters that would attack us,
or traps that you would see in Hell?
Right, let's do our best digging today, too!
Yes, Chief!
Oh? Are you the new guys?
Man, working up a sweat sure is great!
Indeed! And our sweat will eventually create a tunnel and become the people's smiles!
Yeah, yeah! After hard work, sake tastes a little better too!
What are you making me do here?!
Afterward, we went to and from on the Grand Line, searching for the treasure,
but we never found a single bit.
I was arrested here after I messed up flashily and broke into a Navy base...
Then I was thrown into this prison.
But it seems my luck hasn't run out just yet!
Keep running as fast as you can, Straw Hat!
I'll take you to Level Two!
Level Two? That's not it!
I wanna go to Level Five!
That's why I'm taking you there!
You can't just go straight to Level Five!
Listen up. The first undersea floor of Impel Down, where we are, is Level One.
As you descend into Level Two, Level Three, and below,
the prisoners will become more and more vicious.
I was sent all the way to Level Four and exposed to the Inferno,
but I don't know anything about the floors beneath that.
If I remember it right, Level Five is where the nastiest criminals with bounties above 100 million are kept.
But some of the prisoners say there's another level below that one, too!
They say it holds the villains so evil that they had to be erased from history itself!
It's just a rumor, but Ace might be down there.
Anyway, I can't take you any deeper than Level Four.
Really? You're a nice guy now?
Of course! I mean, you're giving me the Treasure Mark that'll lead me to Captain John's treasure!
I...I told him!
You're in here 'cause you're weak, right?
Don't be nosy! Leave me alone!
H-He didn't notice!
Good thing this guy's slow.
I see. So this bracelet is some sort of treasure-map-thingy, huh?
I had no idea!
You were paying attention then, dammit!
Well, now I have no choice!
Then I'll just let you have it right now.
You're... giving it to me knowing how valuable it is?
Sure. Saving Ace is more important to me anyway.
B-But if you give it to me now, I might just fly off and leave you here!
You could, but you said you'd show me the way, didn't you?
Don't look at me with honest eyes like that!
I'm just a cheap, worthless scumbag, ya know!
You can't just take my word!
The map to the treasure of my dreams...
Captain John's Treasure Mark.
I accept your offering!
I owe you one, Straw Hat!
Now, how do I get away from this guy?
Hm? So we'll get there faster if we break that wall?
Right! I'll handle it!
That's not...!
Who are these guys?!
That's Buggy the Clown, who escaped from his cell, and...
Who's that?! There are two of them!
This is the surveillance room!
Which means, breaking out of here would be a really bad idea!
Stop! Straw Ha-ugh...
What the hell is this place?!
A forest inside the prison?
A red forest?
There's lots of people down there, too!
Those're the prisoners!
This ain't no ordinary forest!
The blades on the trees are razor sharp.
They're the Sabertrees!
And the grass sticking up from the floor...
is the Needlegrass, which pierces your body like spikes!
Chased by poisonous spiders and jailers,
the prisoners run around getting cut by the leaves and the grass,
staining them with their blood!
Their punishment is being sliced up and covered in blood...
That is Level One, Crimson Hell!
This is what Impel Down is like!
Impel Down, the Underwater Prison  -  Level 1
Crimson Hell
Save me!
It hurts!
This really IS Hell!
Did Ace have to go through this too?
I Got it! We can just keep falling like this!
Why?! We'll get cut up!
I won't get cut!
Just shut up and hold on!
Straw Hat! My feet!
Throw my feet down there!
Feet?
Right!
W-What is that?
That was close!
As long as I've got my feet on the ground, we'll be fine!
We don't need a staircase from this floor to the next!
We won't need an access key, either!
I just remembered, there's an escape route readied for anyone who wants to escape from the pain!
There's an escape route in Hell?
Take a look! This is it!
A hole?
It's pitch-black!
This is an escape route, but there's nobody who tries to escape through here.
You wanna know why, Straw Hat?
Because this escape route leads to Level Two!
It's connected to an even more terrifying Hell than this one!
There might be some who try to run from Hell and back up to the surface,
but there's nobody who'd be dumb enough to jump from the surface and into Hell!
I get it! This makes things a lot easier!
We've just gotta jump in, right?
Yes, but once we reach the bottom, we'll be in...
HEY! HEY!
This hole sure is deep! What's down there?
He has no self-control at all.
Ain't he afraid of anything?
Ah well...
If I run now, he won't follow me, after all!
I got away from 'im!
I finally got the marker for the treasure of my dreams!
Who'd want to lead the way in here?
See ya, Straw Hat!
Just go to Level Three or Level Four or whatever by yourself, and die!
You dumbass Blugori!
I'm a scatter man. I won't get sliced up even if you cut me!
My feet...?
You're kidding!
This is the surveillance room!
There really was another one!
The two of them are falling toward Level Two!
Please confirm!
Understood!
Impel Down, the Underwater Prison  -  Level 2
Demonic Beast Floor
W-What? The monsters are agitated for some reason.
T-Think they're hungry?
I don't have the energy to be scared anymore...
Sooner or later, we all become their fodder...
HUGE! IT'S AN ACCURSED BEAST!!
This man, he's...
Dammit! The rumors were true after all!
We're gonna die!
I never even wanted to come to Level Two!
I was plannin' to leave you behind and make a break for it!
Did you say something, Buggy?
Hey, what the hell is that?!
I think it's the rarest of mutants!
A snake hatched from a chicken's egg: a Basilisk!
Guard
Beast
Those things come from chickens?!
YOU KIDDIN' ME? THAT'S WHY IT'S CALLED A MONSTER!
Up on the surface, it'd just attack and eat people, so they had it brought down here as a guard.
What're you doing?!
I don't have time for this!
Right, just bring it on!
It is quite hot.
Yes, like the Assistant Warden told you earlier,
the Warden resides in Level Four, the Inferno.
There's an enormous fire surrounding this room.
We've arrived.
Where's the Warden?
Warden Magellan has diarrhea and spends about ten hours a day in the bathroom calming his stomach.
He spends another eight hours sleeping,
and taking his lunch and breaks into account,
he works about four hours a day.
And he still manages to keep his position as Warden?
He's quite reliable when it counts.
Sorry to have kept you waiting. Here he comes.
I forgot to mention, the Warden ate the Doku Doku Fruit.
Doku = Poison
He's a poison man.
A poison man?
Please be careful.
Thank you for your hard work!
Welcome back from your noble task, Warden!!
As always, that was one hell of a battle.
You must be visitors.
I am the Warden, Magellan.
Impel Down Warden, Magellan
(Poison human who ate the Doku Doku Fruit)
Ah, so bright! Such a bright room!
I'd like to be in a darker, more confined room!
If I could, I'd keep my heart confined too!
Don't be ridiculous!
Warden, Vice Admiral Momonga and the Warlord Boa Hancock-dono are here to see you.
We're in a hurry, Warden Magellan.
Oh, I apologize.
Bit of a problem with runny stool.
I suppose the poison-soup I had for lunch did not agree with me.
Well, whaddya expect? It was poison!
I'm a poison-man, so poisons are my favorite!
Besides, don't they say "poison quells poison"?
It's quelling it so well you've got diarrhea, then?
My, you're as poison-tongued as ever, Hannyabal.
Retire already, so I can take your post, plea-
Oh, whoops! I meant hurry and take them to Fire Fist Ace, please!
Too cruel! Your mistake was just too cruel!
I have such a heartless subordinate!
Take these.
H-Hey! B-Be careful when you exhale!
Your breath is poisonous, ya know...
Why are you laughing?!
Serves you right, foolish subordinate.
Your breath and your attitude are both poisonous!
What, exactly, were you attempting to have me inhale?!
Such insolence!
Ow! Such a beauty! I'm in love!
I'm so jealous...
Assistant Warden.
That's the Warden's seat.
It'll be mine eventually.
We're in a hurry!
Yes, this is the Warden speaking.
Why are YOU answering?!
Woe is me! I'm dying! God dammit!
I always wanted to be Warden...!
Prepare the antidote for the Assistant Warden.
Yes!
What?!
Intruders in MY Impel Down?!
Impossible!
Someone broke into Impel Down, which has never been breached since its founding?!
This is a horrible crisis!
The Warden's responsibility!
Could he have been spotted?!
Transfer all live camera feeds to me now!
Warden...
I would like to go see the prisoner as soon as possible.
Right, let's go! Going right now!
W-Warden! This is a major incident, you know!
That's odd...
I've lost contact with Warden Magellan.
In any case, hurry up and report this to all floors and Navy HQ!
I don't know how he got here or what he wants,
but the guy who's been running around Level Two with Buggy the Clown...
is without a doubt the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy!
We can't get in touch with the monitoring room on Level Two!
What?!
Level Two monitoring room! Did something happen?
Respond, monitoring room!
Right!
His hand just became huge!
What was that you did just now?!
It's Gear Third...
Seems we beat it somehow...
Right, I'm back to normal!
Let's hurry to Level Three!
The Gods have come to free us from Hell!
Amazing, they beat that monster!
They defeated the Basilisk!
You did it!
You guys're awesome!
What's more, you knocked it into the monitoring room!
Unbelievable! You guys're GODS!
I dunno who you are, but thanks!
Mind getting the keys for us?
The keys for the cages and handcuffs!
They've landed over there!
Is that...?
Let's keep going!
Don't be impatient.
I'm in a hurry!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Why is he here?!
No, I suppose him being out of his cage means that he MUST be trying to buy back his freedom!
I can take advantage of this, and use it as a chance to win back my freedom!
It would appear the God of Good Fortune has not yet abandoned me!
Want this, you guys?!
YEAH!
Of course we want it!
Hurry up and give it to us!
Is that the attitude you should have when asking someone a favor?
We're sorry!
Alright, I'll give them to you!
You should be grateful to me, the great Captain Buggy-sama!
Alright! It's open!
Be grateful, you fools!
Now, say the name of the man who freed you!
Captain Buggy!
We'll never forget what you did for us!
You're our savior, Captain Buggy!
That's it! Carve that name into your hearts!
Now unlock all the cages!
It was an accident that I fell down here,
but if I cause a riot, it'll be easier for me to escape!
Are you satisfied now?
Let go of me!
Now you've gotta help me out!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Hurry up and show me the way!
Is there a hole to take us down like before?
I don't know how to get to Level Three!
There's no way I'd remember all the
passageways in this maze of a prison!
Thanks, Captain Buggy!
Now we're free too!
Cut it out, Straw Hat!
What're you saying?!
You told me you'd guide me to Level Four!
That was a lie! A lie!
I just lied to get the treasure!
Now all the prisoners are gonna mess this floor up good!
You lied to me?!
What's up with you guys?!
Wasn't this your big chance to escape?!
Uh, looks like we got a little ahead of ourselves...
We don't have a chance here.
Not as long as the boss of this floor is here...
Yeah, we're better off inside the cells.
Right, Straw Hat! I'll tell you how to get to Level Three.
HEY! DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY YOU DIDN'T KNOW, YOU BIG NOSE?!
WHO'RE YOU CALLING A BIG NOSE?!
If you are having problems finding your way on this floor, how about I lend you a hand?
Who's that?
It has been a preciously long time, Straw Hat Luffy.
It seems that, thanks to you, I have become a free man.
I am a man who always repays his debts.
Who're you?
Oh, that "3" means...
You're the guy who was on the giants' island!
Three!
It's MISTER Three!
Prisoner Number D-0464
Origin: Baroque Works Agent
Mr. 3
Nobody's...
getting away!
I can't even scratch myself...
You got beaten up pretty badly, huh, boss?
It ain't my body that's in pain...
Ace-san...
the pain...
It lies in my heart, for being unable to do what's right!
Pirate of the Royal Seven Oceanic Warlords
First Son of the Sea, Jinbe
(Whale Shark Fishman,
Bounty: 250 million belly)
Jinbei...
As things are, I cannot accept death!
So what if they take my position as a Warlord of the Sea away?
I don't need it!
If only I could prevent this battle,
I would gladly give my life.