Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing         Sewil
Raw provider      GS-Raws
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Underground:
Inside the
Officers' Tower
With this fake grape made from tatababasco, we'll knock Sugar unconscious.
Captain
What is it?
This is...
There was a fly.
He shot down a fly.
I'll make sure Operation SOP succeeds.
You may be able to hit a fly, but not me.
I'm too fast.
He's so fast, I can't see him!
He might be able to do this.
I'll have you return our captured comrades.
Go for it, Leo!
I know you can do it!
Please, make it.
Wait, Leo!
Robiland?
The Underground Trade Port
We haven't gotten any new workers this past year.
I know.
Shing Flower
"Elegant Sunflower"
They haven't shown themselves in the palace either.
Who's slacking off?!
Artificial Devil Fruit
Smile Factory
I-I wasn't slacking!
They must have noticed that five hundred of their people have gone missing.
Yet they never see the bad in people. The Tontattans sure are dense...
I mean, pure-hearted.
Then why aren't they showing themselves?
Who knows.
Well, if we can't get any new workers, we'll just
have to make the most of the five hundred we have.
Get moving! Whip of Love!
Hey!
These Smiles aren't ripe yet!
Are you alright?
I thought you Tontattans could grow any plant.
W-Well yes, but the Smiles aren't natural...
No excuses!
Please let my brother take a break.
The food today was spoiled, so he...
You're complaining about the food too now?!
Don't you want to cure your ailing Princess Mansherry?
W-We do!
Then keep producing Smiles!
They're essential for the medicine that can cure her.
Less than ten percent of the crops you produce each season are usable.
Work harder and make the process more effective!
Could you let us see Princess Mansherry?
No.
Why?
If you catch her disease...
... it'd make us all cry!
You Tontattans are our invaluable partners!
S-Sanshita-san!
We'll do everything we can!
Please look after our princess!
Of course!
How can they believe such a blatant lie?
W-What are you doing, Robiland?!
I'm sorry. But if you'd just charged in like that, you would have been killed.
I looked at that fly's corpse.
He hit it perfectly between the eyes, despite its size.
Trébol's dynamic visual acuity is exceptional.
It's far too dangerous to go after Sugar while he's still guarding her.
So what are you going to do, Robiland?
Over here.
Hey, what's with this crate?!
It's a swarm of pink bees!
I have news, Trébol-sama!
There's a commotion in port four from Captain Eves' crew.
They're demanding to talk to a commander about the deal.
They must be really brave
if they're not scared of Joker's name.
Hey, did the guard change?
The usual guard is out for lunch right now!
This is an emergency!
Several of our people have been injured!
Please help us!
Injured? I'm coming.
Hey, hey!
Trébol-sama! You're outside?
Strengthen the security on the four doors to the Commanders' Tower.
Yes, Sir!
And inform me right away if something happens.
Uh... Yes, Sir!
Trébol-sama!
We appreciate your hard work!
Hey, hey!
Where is it? Where's the fight?
Port four.
What? You won't fight, Usoland?
It would be easy for me to handle this, but...
Doing nothing can't harm me.
... by watching over you, I will give you confidence!
Confidence?
Don't worry! If anything goes wrong, I'll save you!
That's so reassuring.
Who's there?
Give up, Sugar!
We've come to retrieve our comrades being held in the factory!
And we'll knock you unconscious!
Unconscious?
I don't know anything about your comrades.
What?!
Really?
Really.
Okay then.
It's not okay! Don't let her trick you!
T-That was close! Give back our comrades!
Who told you all this? You're clearly too dumb to realize that you're being tricked.
I had been wondering why the Tontattans
haven't been seen in the palace for the past year.
So it was because someone has been deceiving you.
Silence!
Hold her down and force her mouth open!
How insulting. It feels like
you're underestimating me...
Little Black Bears!
Time to make the contract.
Oh no! She turned us into toys!
Obey my orders until you die.
Have we all been forgotten?!
What?
A bunch of toys showed up out of nowhere.
What were we just doing?
Slaughter all the intruders in the Commanders' Tower!
I can't resist her orders!
Slaughter all of them... Even me?!
Don't! I don't want to fight!
Those must be Sugar's subordinates!
I can't believe she had more backup aside from Trébol!
Leo! It's me, Flapper!
Take down the enemy soldiers!
No! No! No!
Nooo!
Trébol, come back! It's a trap!
Trébol!
A trap?
Hey, you!
Look at that, Trébol-sama!
The pirates are causing a commotion. We can't deal with them!
Hey, hey, you!
What's the problem?
Trébol-sama!
Hey, what's up?
Well, it's not really a problem...
Just, a bunch of bees that were in the cargo.
There's no problem with the deal.
That woman!
Hey, hey, wait, wait!
You!
Hey, who are you? Hey!
She disappeared! Hey! Hey!
But wait... That face...
Was she one of the Straw Hats?!
How'd she get here?
Trébol!
Why are they after Sugar?
Get back here! You've been tricked!
Die, you imbecile!
Now I'm mad!
Sticky Chain!
Sticky Stick...
Meteor!
T-Trébol-sama has gone mad!
The Commander's Tower has been crushed!
Usopp, Usopp, get a hold of yourself.
Thank goodness.
Rob-
W-What happened?
A duck suddenly fell from the ceiling.
Leo and the others have been captured.
There are others, as well, right?
Right, right?
What are their names?
I'll never talk!
That's right, don't tell them!
Let's get out of here while we can, Robin.
See, the other guy is my friend.
I think his name was...
Oh, you mean Usoland?
Hey!
You idiot, he's not my friend.
Dammit, you tricked me.
Is the one-legged soldier one of your people too?
I-I won't talk.
We already know.
If you already know then there's no point in hiding it.
He's our comrade.
I knew it.
Dammit.
I'm starting to connect all the dots.
Even if you figure it all out, it's over for you.
We will get our friends back!
That sticky stuff is also combustible.
What's going on now!?
Trébol-sama!
Leo, Leo!
Let's get out...
I mean, you have to get out of here.
You guys can't go any further.
You don't stand a chance against Trébol.
We... can't do that.
I must... hurry and complete... Operation SOP...
And then the captain will...
beat Doflamingo for us.
The captain is waiting for us!
I have to hurry.
The Royal Palace,
1F Lift
Captain!
This morning
in Dressrosa.
Doflamingo-sama is stepping down as a Warlord?
Is he going to abdicate as well?
He's just a pirate now!
Now he'll be hunted by the Navy!
We're gonna be free!
Captain, did you see the newspaper?
Now our comrades will come back, right?
We won't have to fight after all!
What a relie-
No, it was a false report.
No way!
I'm so glad it was a mistake!
There's no way someone as great as him would just leave the throne.
Doflamingo-sama!
I'm gonna enter today's tournament and get the Mera Mera Fruit.
And then I'm gonna kill Doflamingo!
Rebecca, keep calm.
I understand your anger.
I feel the same way...
but don't do anything rash.
We will be the ones to fight.
Everything's prepared.
No, I won't wait!
We've been plunged from heaven to hell.
Everyone's at their limits.
Their wills have been broken!
Can we merely await the day of our execution?
If you win a thousand matches you can be set free?
That isn't even hope!
It's a wall of despair!
The legendary gladiator with three thousand wins, Kyros?
Everyone knows that statue is a lie.
Kyros is some ideal warrior the dying prisoners dreamt up.
A statue full of wishes that they
can succeed and get out of here.
Rather than putting my hopes in a stupid dream,
I'll take a chance on today's tournament!
As if there's a chance!
You can't possibly win.
You'll just be throwing your life away! I refuse to let you enter!
You're so hot-headed!
You're only sixteen!
Do you think yourself an adult, Rebecca?!
You're still a child!
Listen to what I say!
Quit talking like you're my father!
You're the one getting heated up.
What plan?!
There's no way you can beat Doflamingo!
You're just a one-legged toy!
Indeed...
You're right.
No, wait!
I may have said too much.
But please, don't enter.
I didn't mean it.
Soldier-san, wait!
Wait! Soldier-san!
I was afraid that you'd die and got scared!
I'm sorry!
Wait, Soldier-san!
Soldier-san!
Oh my!
Rebecca, who has never initiated an attack, has begun attacking!
What's with that sword?
There's no edge.
This is an arena for killing.
If you're not gonna cut someone, then get cut yourself.
That'll get the audience riled up.
Lock!
A direct hit!
The undefeated woman was completely helpless!
Diamante!
Dammit!
Hey, Musclemelon!
It's Bartolomeo.
Protect that girl.
Rebecca, do you know how your mother Scarlett died?
I'll go get us something to eat.
The way that toy soldier was crying was truly pathetic.
I'm sorry,
I couldn't protect your mother!
Royal Palace 1F
Outside the lift
These tremors...
It must be Pica.
Why is he thrashing about?
We won't let you follow them!
Are you okay, Captain?
T-Thanks.
We have to hurry.
Wait, they'll die!
Let go of me, you damn gnomes!
Look ahead, captain!
We were prepared for it from the start.
Don't be stupid!
If you don't make it then what's gonna happen?
Even if Leo and the others complete Operation SOP, if we don't beat Doflamingo, nothing will change!
You're the only one who can kill Doflamingo, Captain!
Underground Trading Port
The Officers' Tower
Who's your captain, Leo?
Why are you betting everything on him?
It's just a one-legged toy!
When new toys are turned, they are bound
by a contract that blocks their will to resist.
Huh? What's that?!
But in the case of our captain, the first toy who was ever created in this country...
Sugar made the mistake of
not forcing a contract on him.
Due to that single mistake ten years ago, he is the only toy able to defy the Donquixote Family.
That's why the captain has been fighting on his own for ten years.
If it weren't for him, the toys could only cry themselves to sleep.
We Tontattans wouldn't have noticed a thing.
We'd have all been turned into their slaves.
If we ignore his screams, then there's no saving this country!
He is worth betting everything on!
No one remembers him now...
but long ago, everyone knew his name.
Back when he was a big human, his name was...
Kyros!
The strongest gladiator in the Colosseum's history!
He is our captain!