Translation
FUNimation
Raws
cloaknsmoke
Soundtracking
Halee
Editing
Feeso
Alasta
Infoboxes/title card
BernieCrane
Timing
Sewil
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
Quality checking
Galaxy 9000
Alasta
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
The Navy isn't following us!
Did Captain Usopp
scare the pants off them?
Amazing! Amazing! Just as you'd
expect from our navigator!
Well done, Nami-san. To think you
detected such a wind beforehand...
What's wrong, Zoro?
You've had a serious look
on your face for a while.
Well, I hope it's just my imagination.
What is?
I feel like this ship hasn't
been moving at all for a while.
What?
Come to think of it, the sail
isn't catching any wind at all...
Reverse Mountain
Ah!
What's wrong, Nami?
Nami... -san...?
Dammit...!
We've entered the Calm Belt!
Charm Belt?
What the heck is that?
Calm Belt! It's an area of sea
where nothing moves a muscle!
You guys, enough chit chat!
Fold the sails and start paddling now!
Put the ship back on its earlier path!
What're you panicking about?
Paddling? This is a sailboat.
He's right.
Just do what I say!
We're in big trouble!
Well, the sea is quiet.
Yeah.
All right, fine! Then I'll
explain it for you! Listen up!
Since we rushed and ran away,
we came further south than we planned!
Then did we enter the Grand Line?
If it was that easy, anyone could enter!
Look. The Grand Line is
running between two sea areas!
Do you get it?
The area on both sides of
it are called the Calm Belt.
The reason is unknown, but in these areas there's no wind and no current.
They're an area of sea with complete calm.
No wonder there hasn't been any wind.
We can't do anything
if the ship doesn't move.
We can just wait until
the wind starts blowing.
Like I said, once you're in this area,
wind never blows no matter how long you wait!
And, that's not all!
There's another reason that
people call this area dangerous!
Here they are!!
They're huge!!
The Calm Belt is the
nest of the Sea Kings.
Moreover, the ones here are super huge!
They're another reason why people
can't cross the Calm Belt.
F-For the time being, no one move.
They'll probably go back
into the sea eventually.
Then we'll paddle hard using our oars.
Are you serious?!
Idiot!
Sorry.
He's gonna sneeze!
Ahh...
All right! We're going back!
We really are flying!!
Looks like we're back
in the area we came from.
I don't see any sign of the Navy, either.
Ahhh... I thought I was a goner.
Nami-san! I have a report of love!
I see big rain clouds up ahead!
There's a storm under 'em!
Looks like we're back on our original course...
We should be seeing the
Red Line at any time now...
Look at this!
I'd heard the rumors about it,
and it's drawn on this map, too!
If it really is true, then the entrance
to the Grand Line is a mountain!
A mountain?
--We gotta crash into a mountain?
--You can't be serious.
I didn't believe it myself,
but the map has canals
that lead to the mountain.
That might mean we have to go up it!
Neat!
What're you talking about?!
Even if there are canals or whatever,
a ship can't climb up a mountain!
But that's what the map says!
Yeah! Nami-san would never
say anything that's wrong!
You stole that map from Buggy, right?
Can we really trust it?
H-hey! Someone help with the rudder!
--Sanji-kun! Give Usopp a hand!
--It won't budge!
--I can't think with all his shouting!
--It won't move! Someone help!
Yes, Nami-san!
Okay!
D-doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!
Eh?! Usopp! What did you just say?
"D-doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!"
Current...
--That's it!
--That's what?
They really do go up the mountain!
Are you still saying that stuff?!
Look here!
See? The guiding light was
definitely pointing to here
on the Red Line... Reverse Mountain!
Hey! Little help over here!
See these canals here?
If major currents from the four oceans
all flow toward this mountain...
Then the four currents would go up
these canals, collide at the top,
and then flow into the Grand Line!
Reverse Mountain is a "winter island,"
So any currents that collide into the Red Line
will plummet from the surface into the depths.
If we screw up and miss
the entrance to the canal...
...the Going Merry will run smack
into the Red Line's rock face...
...and get wrecked!
And then we'd be at the bottom
of the ocean. Understand?
So, basically, it's a mystery mountain!
Well, maybe you don't get it...
Nami-san! You're so amazing!
I've never heard of ships
going over mountains before.
I've heard some stuff before!
Stories about the mystery mountain?
No.
I heard that half of everyone
who heads to the Grand Line
dies before entering it...
I knew getting in wouldn't be easy.
Hey! I see the mystery mountain!
W-what?!
T-that's insanely huge!
The entrance to the Grand Line...
So that's the Red Line, huh?!
I-I-I can't see the top
because of the clouds!
We're getting sucked in!
--Hold the rudder good!
--We're on it!
Just do it!
Nami! Is that the canal entrance?
Most likely!
This can't be for real!
The damn ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
We gotta make our way through
those water gates just right!
Otherwise the ship'll be busted into pieces!
W-we're getting off course!
More to the right! Right! Right!
The right?! Go starboard!
C-come on, now!
The rudder!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Luffy!
Grab on!
We made it!
Now it's just a straight shot to the summit!
Hey! I wanna see! I wanna see!
A-awesome!
We're in the clouds!
We're above the clouds now!
Look! The summit! It's the summit!
Yahoo!
I see it!
This is the greatest sea
in the world! The Grand Line!
The One Piece is up ahead, somewhere!
Go!
Whoa!! This is great!!
Did you just hear something?
Isn't it the wind?
There must be lots of unusual landforms!
What's that?
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
A mountain?! That can't be!
But it's really there!
Who cares?! Go!!
After passing the Twin Capes up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
Hm?
Oh crap!!
It's not a mountain!!
It's a black wall!!
No, it's not!!
Then, what is it?!
I-i-i-it's a whale!!
Wh-wh-wh-what're we gonna do?!
Shall we fight?
Idiot! There's no way we can fight that!
B-b-b-b-but, our path is blocked!
What're we gonna do?!
Hold on a sec!
If it looks like a wall from this close,
then where are its eyes?!
That's right! It's possible
that he may not have noticed us!
But unless we do something,
we'll run into it!
Hey! We can get through on the left!
Port! Hard to port!
But the rudder is broken!
Do something!
I'll help, too!
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
Luffy...? Hey, what're you doing?!
It doesn't work! The ship doesn't turn!
Dammit!
Don't give up!
Cannon?!
All right! Did it stop?
Ah... We're screwed...
This might be it...
My special seat...!
Let's get out of here before it's too late!!
What the heck is going on?!
Did he not notice the cannon
attack because his body's too big?!
Or is he just slow?!
Who knows?! Anyway,
let's get out of here now!
Ahhhhh! My ears hurt!
Paddle! Just paddle!!
We have to get away from him!
You...! What the hell did
you do to my special seat?!
Dumbass!!
How was that?! Bring it on, you bastard!
Shut up already, you idiot!
Wh-what?
--Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!!
What am I gonna do?
They've all been eaten...
Hey you! Spit them out!
Give everyone back to me!
Spit them out!
I'm saying give them back!
You...! You...! You jerk!
You're diving into the water,
aren't you?! Stop it!
Hey! I'm telling you to stop! Hey!
Please wait! Give my friends back!
Hey! I said stop it!
We're gonna go on adventures together!
They're precious to me!
Give them back!!
Huh?
What do you think...?
What do I think...?
How should I think...?
H-h-h-h-how...
I was sure that we were
swallowed by the whale...
Is this a dream?
Yeah, it's probably a dream.
Then, what're the island
and house doing there?
They must be illusions.
Then this is...
a Great King Squid!!
Looks like there's at least someone there.
I hope it's really a person...
I've had enough. I wanna go home.
Luffy went somewhere, too.
What's gonna happen to us?
What the heck is this?
Why is there a door and
a passageway in a whale?
A ship...
Sh-sh-sh-shall we fire the cannon
at that island?!
No, hold on a sec...
Someone's coming out...
--Ah?! It's a flower!
--A flower?
Oh, never mind. It's a person.
What is he?
That old man killed a
Great King Squid with a single hit...
Was he just fishing...
or did he do it to save us...?
Say something, you jerk!
I-if you wanna fight,
we'll fight, you bastard!
We've got cannons!
You'd better not, or someone will die.
Oh? Just who're you saying will die?
Me.
You?!
Well, calm down.
He's mocking us. That bastard...
Hey, old man. Tell us where
we are and who you are.
When asking someone a question,
isn't it proper manner
to give your name first?
Hm? Yeah, good point. Sorry.
--My name is Roronoa...
--My name is Crocus.
I'm the lighthouse keeper
of the Twin Capes.
I'm 71 years old and a Gemini.
--Can I cut him?!
--My blood type is AB.
--Now, calm down.
You're asking where we are?
How dare you run your mouth when
you barged into my private resort?
Does it look like we're in a rat's belly?
S-so we were eaten by a whale after all...
But is this really inside a whale's stomach?
Wait a sec! What's gonna happen to us?!
I don't wanna be digested!
Would you cut that out?!
Don't you guys have any appreciation for a running gag?
That was a gag?!
The exit is over there.
We can get out?!
Hold on a sec! Why's there
an exit in a whale's belly?!
Why's the door in the sky?!
Wait... Look at it carefully...
This sky... Those seagulls...
They're all painted! It's all a painting
inside of the whale's stomach!
Call it a doctor's playful mind.
You bastard! What the hell
are you doing here?!
That's enough. Leave him alone.
Nami! There's an exit so
let's get out of here already.
Yeah.
What's going on?!
It's started...
Look!
That's not an island! It's a ship.
On top of that, it's made of iron!
Of course! It's because
this sea is gastric acid!
I guess that means that wooden ships
would melt if they stayed here long.
Hey! What's started?! Tell us!
This whale has...
Laboon has started hitting
his head against the Red Line.
What?!
Come to think of it, this whale had
terrible scars on his forehead.
He was also howling at the sky...
What does that mean?
He's suffering!
I see! So that's what that
geezer's trying to do!
Likely... He's probably trying to
kill the whale from inside his body!
Now...
What a vicious way to kill it...!
Now that the mystery is solved,
it's time to hurry up and get out.
If we take our time here,
we'll be digested.
We have nothing to say
about his whale hunting
nor are we under obligation
to save the whale.
Let's get out of here.
Ahh! Dammit! With the
waves surging like this,
I don't know if we can
even reach the doors...
We have no other choice but
to paddle! Take the ores!
Let's leave quickly!
I'm worried about Luffy.
He's outside!
I saw him fly out of the mouth!
That old man jumped in!
Huh? What's he gonna do?
He's gonna be digested.
What?! What's going on?! Huh? Why?!
Dizzy... Dizzy... I'm dizzy...!
What is it this time?
The sea? A river? A channel?
Okay. We've succeeded
in infiltrating this far.
Listen, Miss Wednesday.
Behind those doors is the stomach and
that geezer is likely to be there.
We must eliminate him.
Everything is for the whale.
Mysterious Woman
Miss Wednesday
Mysterious Man
Mr. 9
Yes, Mr. 9. This whale is a
precious sweet honey to our town.
Hey! The geezer came out!
Forget about him.
More importantly,
how do we open these doors?
Okay, Miss Wednesday?
We'll open the doors with
"Three, two, one, baby!"
Don't let down your guard.
Roger, Mr. 9. I'm ready any time.
I can't stop!!
What is this voice, Mr. 9?
I don't know, Miss Wednesday.
Those guys're...
Ahh!
Huh?
This isn't good, Miss Wednesday!
It's a sea of gastric acid below us!
Luffy?
Hey! So everyone's okay?
In any case, help me!
Aside from Luffy...
there're two weirdoes...
Hey! That old man disappeared!
Don't bother! For now, let's save Luffy!
Stop it, Laboon.
Don't hurt yourself any more.
There's only a little sedative left.
I have to make some more...
That wall divides the world's oceans.
Even if you hit it until you die,
it won't break, Laboon.
It's calmed down.
The whale is quiet now.
Seems like it. Now...
We did save you guys for the
time being, but who are you?
Mr. 9, they're pirates.
I-I know, Miss Wednesday.
B-but if we talk to them,
they should understand... perhaps...
You thugs're still around?!
--Huh?
--Don't make me say this yet again!
I won't let you lay a finger
on Laboon as long as I'm alive!
He's back.
Who's that pops?
Huh?
Even if you say so, we can't leave.
Taking down this whale is our mission.
We won't let you interfere with
our whale hunting this time!
We'll open an air vent in
his stomach! Let's go, baby!
Roger!
Ah! Bastards!
That pops jumped
straight into the bullets...!
Could it be...
that he protected the whale?!
Stop this pointless resistance!
If you want to protect the
whale that badly, go right ahead.
We'll turn it into food for our town!
What's going on?
Huh?
I just... felt like hitting them.
I thank you for saving me... but why?
I wasn't trying to save you.
I just didn't like them for some reason.
Huh?
--Say, who are these guys?
--Hey, Luffy! What're you doing?
--What're you doing inside this whale?
--Stop it! Hey, Luffy! Stop it!
--They're thugs from a nearby town.
--They're after whale meat.
--What're you trying to do?
--It belongs to someone else.
--If they capture Laboon,
it can feed the townspeople
for at least 2-3 years, so...
Laboon?
It's the name of this whale.
It's the world's largest whale,
called the Island Whale,
which live only in the West Blue.
I won't let them have him as food.
There's a reason he keeps
hitting himself on the Red Line
and howling towards Reverse Mountain.
I'll tell you... Laboon's story...
One day, while I was on duty
as the lighthouse keeper as usual,
some good-natured pirates
came down Reverse Mountain
and entered the Grand Line.
And a small whale came in as well,
as if following them.
That was Laboon.
The Island Whale lives
only in the West Blue,
and it's the world's largest whale.
The pirates had been traveling
with Laboon all that time,
but they left him in the West Blue since
the Grand Line is extremely dangerous.
Although they thought they did,
he followed them.
Island Whales usually
travel together as a group,
but I suspect Laboon felt that
he was a member of that pirate group.
Since their ship had broken down,
they stayed at the cape for several months.
So we became quite good friends.
Because of that,
on the day of their departure...
I have a favor to ask, since I trust you.
Could you take care of him for 2-3 years?
We'll go around the world
and definitely come back here.
Well then, we're setting off now...
Guys! We're setting sail! Hoist the anchor!
Yeah!
Laboon!
Laboon! Wait for us!
We'll come back here for sure...!
For sure!!
That was 50 long years ago...
50 years...!
Laboon has been waiting
for those guys for 50 years?
Is that why he continues to howl
at the wall, hitting himself on it?
Yeah...