Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
Translation & initial timing
Vegapunk Fansubs
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Feeso
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Video editing
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
Raw provider
SOFCJ-Raws
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Combination of Brains and Brawn!
Oars and Moriah vs. the Straw Hats!
Brook... you can move again?
You saved me. Thanks a lot.
Certainly, I was seriously injured.
And as I bravely dragged my body to the kitchen in my quest for salt...
I discovered a bottle of delicious milk and drank it, giving these results!
There's no way for calcium to be that effective!
Milk can heal broken bones!
Liar!
Well, at any rate... we've obtained a large amount of salt at the very last minute.
The way to the kitchen is blocked now.
The salt that Brook has brought is our last hope.
We're short on time.
We have to fight!
If we make that monster swallow the salt,
And then beat Moriah immediately afterwards, we can win.
You should be grateful that I came out to fight!
Also, I'd be extremely careful if I were you.
I'm not here without a reason!
I'll make you experience your worst nightmare!
Allow me to join your fight, as I promise to fight with all my might!
I can't think of any other way to repay the great favor of recovering my shadow!
I shall...!
Creak...
Don't push yourself.
Just hang on to that salt.
I'll show you something special.
My anti-monster rounds.
Gotta take the initiative.
The last one was too small for you.
Franky, I'm counting on you!
Deadly Special Oil Star!
Of course! Got it!
Transform!
Super Size... Fire Bird Star!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
How shameful.
Don't panic, Oars.
Heat and pain were hindrances in your human era.
Such things have no effect on zombies.
Calm down and get rid of those flames.
This is our chance, Zoro!
Alright!
Three Swords Style...
Great Buddha Slash!
Eat this!
Jenga Cannon!
You bastard!
They're coming this way!
Veinte Fleur!
Twenty Flowers
Stop it, you idiot!
Damn it!
He used it against us!
Hey, are you alright?!
New Weapon... Kuwagata!
Kuwagata: stag beetle
Is everything ready, Usopp?!
Y-Yeah, but building this was quite absurd!
I don't even know what'll happen.
No need to worry, you idiot.
I feel especially super this week!
Then, get on!
You bet!
Give it all you got!
Here goes!
Deadly Ironman Meteor!
Now that's what I call super!
Say your prayers!
This is a special mortar designed to bring down Sea Kings!
I'll make a hole in that face of yours!
Take this, Moriah!
What impressive agility!
I tend to forget we're actually fighting Luffy here!
Franky!
Not done yet, Oars.
He's still breathing.
Finish him off!
Yes.
Hey, he's gonna do it again!
Stop, he can't even move!
Thunderbolt...!
Huh? That cloud!
Tempo!
Lightning!
This attack is...!
It worked!
He's down!
It's the Clima-Tact!
Is Nami-san alright?!
What was that flash just now?!
Lightning?!
So suddenly?!
Oars was hit by a bolt of lightning!
Most likely!
There she is!
It's Nami-san!
Nami-san!
Hey, stop yelling my name! He'll notice me, you know!
I'm so glad! I'm so glad!
I'm so glad Nami-san is okay!
Thank goodness!
Please forgive my incompetence!
Nami-san!
Why doesn't he shut up?
Woman...
I told you!
Rubber...
W-What?! What?!
Don't tell me it's gonna stretch!
It won't reach her.
This is our chance!
Go help Franky!
Pistol!
I-It stretched!
Why?!
It stretched.
No wonder I always had that feeling.
That's impossible!
Nami!
Nami-san!
I see her!
Nami is safe!
Thank goodness.
Robin saved her!
That came out of nowhere.
Are you alright, Nami?
Thank you so much... for helping me.
This is definitely no good!
Why the hell did his arm stretch?!
There's only one rubber man in the world!
Moriah... He's behind all this.
Rubber...
Whip!
Now he's nothing but a monstrous Luffy!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm in a hurry right now!
What do you want?!
Yes, we know you are.
We're aware you have no time to lose.
Just give us a minute!
You're our only hope.
We've been looking for you!
We're the Risky Brothers, henchmen of Lola the Proposer, Captain of the Rolling Pirates.
You want to defeat Gekko Moriah, don't you?
Don't you?
We know the secret to Moriah's ability.
It'll grant you insurmountable power!
So please beat him for us.
Secret? Power?
What do you say?
That's why I'm asking you: what's on your mind?!
Allow me to introduce her.
The Captain of the Rolling Pirates, Lola the Proposer.
Her current total of proposals is 4,443.
My! I like you.
Marry me.
No.
He rejected her!
That's the 4,444th person who's rejected her!
Anyway, we're part of the group of victims that have been stripped off their shadows...
And are doomed to wander the forest.
I also had my shadow stolen, so I have no time to lose!
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
In any case, there's never been so much chaos in Thriller Bark before!
Moriah's three servants have been obliterated and there's barely anything left of his mansion.
Yeah, we all have been very excited since you came.
But... rumor has it that the enemy's trump card, the Special Zombie, has been awakened!
We receive information via our Victim Network.
We've been without shadow for three years now!
We don't wanna keep living like this!
If you manage to defeat Moriah, we can all have our shadows back!
Then again, we're in trouble!
Do you know Moriah's current location?
Inside his belly!
He's inside that monster's belly!
What?! He was eaten?!
That's not it.
He's riding in his belly.
Basically, unless you defeat the special zombie which has your shadow, you won't be able to reach Moriah.
He's fighting your friends in the mansion's courtyard.
What?!
Damn it!
Then I have no time to lose!
I told you to wait!
Save the sluggish explanations for later!
Showing him an example is faster!
An example of the shadows' secret we've discovered!
Yes!
Move it! Move it!
Here it comes!
A shadow?
Yes, a shadow!
Shadows that are released upon feeding a zombie with salt can be grabbed with your bare hands!
Here goes!
W-What's all this?!
You're stabbing me with a shadow!
Hang in there.
Stop!
I'm losing consciousness...
Alright!
It's in!
Well?
Are you back to your senses?
Yeah.
Can you use a sword?
Not... in the very least.
W-What happened?!
The shadow which entered your body just now... is that of a skilled marine swordsman.
All the power the shadow possesses is added to your own!
Furthermore, you can keep adding shadows as long as you hold on to your senses!
Amazing, isn't it?!
We can take advantage of Moriah's ability to dramatically increase your strength!
We've caught plenty of shadows.
However; if you don't have a strong mind and easily go unconscious, all the power will be wasted.
How come you have that many shadows?
In order to find our shadows, we've been desperately purifying zombie after zombie.
But we only found shadows of people we didn't know.
So we started capturing them instead.
Listen, be sure to remember this.
When a shadow is put into a corpse, that corpse becomes a zombie, but...
When it's put into a human with a soul and mind of its own, it can't settle down.
Your power-up will last 10 minutes, at best.
After that, the shadow will go back to its original owner.
Do you understand?
It's a 10 minute match.
All the shadows we've risked our lives to capture, will be given to you!
That many?!
The fog has already cleared. That means we only have 20 minutes of night left to strike.
Anyway, we've gotta hurry.
Hold on to your senses!
You should be able to handle 20 or 30 shadows!
Our limit is 2 or 3, at most.
Go ahead!
W-Wait a minute!
Isn't it too soon-
T-This man...!
What kind of mind does he possess?!
I can't believe my eyes...
He absorbed 100 shadows straight!
Unbelievable!
As expected from our ray of hope!
H-Hey!
How are you feeling?
Are you still you?
Straw Hat Luffy!
Yeah.
It's me.
The power keeps... overflowing!
Somehow... you...
You've changed...
You were a bit smaller before.
I'd never imagined this kid would be this strong.
The thirst for battle...
Is burning inside me!
You're ready to go!
Now, there's no time!
Show that accursed Moriah what nightmares are all about!
You're our last ray of hope!
Nightmare Luffy!
Just you wait!
Moriah!
Wait a minute!
You're going the wrong way!
Rubber...
Here he comes!
Bell!
I feel better now that I can stretch.
Spear!
Damn, what's going on?!
His attack power has greatly increased!
Why can Oars' body stretch without having a devil fruit's power?!
What did you do, Moriah?!
Yes! The real nightmare starts now!
Behold the Shadow power!
Shadow Revolution!
R-Revolution?
Shadows are bound to follow the body's orders.
That's common sense.
Body and shadow will always share the same form.
That is an inviolable rule.
However, right now...
Oars' shadow, which should be serving its body, is being manipulated by my own shadow.
Can you tell what is happening?
I can change the shape of Oars' shadow at will.
However, body and shadow must have the same shape.
In order for body and shadow to be the same, the body is forced to obey the shadow and change with it.
A shadow revolution!
In other words, by reversing common sense,
Moriah forced Oars' shadow to stretch, and thus the body was forced to stretch as well.
So... it's not like Oars has turned into a rubber man...
He has become a monster that can turn into anything!
How convenient, for such a big monster!
Yeah, now it won't be easy to get near him.
Soon you'll realize it's worse than rubber!
If I make his shadow round,
Oars will do the same!
Oars Ball!
Take this!
Run away!
Hey, hey! Wait a second, Master!
Stop messing with my fight!
Sorry for that.
I didn't mean to spoil your fun.
I'm here to give you a hand and nothing more.
Now, Oars, make sure to crush them one by one.
It's dangerous to get too close, Zoro!
Hey, where's Luffy anyway?!
Moriah tricked him into going somewhere else.
He better be alright!
How come?
He's a real idiot for sure.
What should I do?
I wonder if I should tell everyone, in this situation,
that there is another Warlord of the Sea on the island.
So the situation is: We got to beat Luffy's zombie first, then Moriah or else we won't recover our shadows?
Is it that kind of situation?
Yes, it's as you say.
No way!
It'll be morning anytime now!
That's what the enemy wants!
We have no choice!
Excuse me.
Skeleton, you were here all along?
I have a...
I have a favor to ask you!
Please listen!
Everyone, thank you very much!
It's a simple request.
Are you sure about this, Brook?!
You saw what happened to Franky, didn't you?!
I'm not responsible if anything happens!
Get ready, as this is very powerful!
Dark Cloud Tempo...
Please, go ahead!
To think I have to use Kuwagata again!
There's nothing more painful than an unpaid debt!
Don't hold back! Give it all you got!
Alright! Get going!
Here I go!
Slalom Vine!
Such a great shock that my bones can be seen!
Then again, bones are all I have left!
Here I come!
Like an arrow of lightning!
Lighting Bone Sword...
Gavotte Bon Avant!
Bon Avant: Leap Forward
Awesome!
He went right through him!
My shoulder was pierced!
He's off-guard!
Let's strike again!
M-Mission...
accomplished.
Nice job, bones!
Two Swords Style...
Double Slash...
Tower Climb!
You!
No, first of all...
I'll finish off this skeleton!
Rubber...
I-Is he going to...?
Battle Axe!
Brook!
Deadly...
Atlas Comet!
It's no use!
Not good.
Usopp, fight!
Fight...
Hey, hey wait!
You're next, nose bastard!
Rubber...
Bazooka!
I'm dead!
It won't stretch.
Why?
Ochenta Fleur...
Eighty Flower
Cuatro Manos!
Four Hands
What's with these hands?!
I can't move!
Yes, I thought I'd have you stop your shadow manipulation.