Video Editing
Meggo
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
Soundtracking
Halee
obtained everything
the world had to offer.
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Raiyan
Zenef
His final words lured all sorts of adventurers to the sea.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Galaxy 9000
PhosCity
My treasure?
It's yours, if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
Galaxy 9000
Zenef
Everything is right where I left it!
Translation
Gaijin
FUNimation
Raws
Df68
Now pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
あ
re go
ri
り
ing
tta
った
った
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
shin
針
しん
なん
じゅう
use
jyuu
滞
たい
shin
針
しん
なん
te
て
jyuu
渋
じゅう
tai
滞
たい
って
って
it's
でん
じゃ
tsu
な
ja
い!
でん
じゃ
na
な
i!
い!
th
en
it's
っか
っか
いい!
いい!
った
った
ット
イン
ット
イン
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Pirate Commodore Don Krieg
You're a pirate?
Yep!
So why did you fire a cannonball
at our restaurant again?
That was an accident!
A self-defense, stray shot!
A what now?
Whatever. Just don't try
any funny business here.
The owner was once a cook
in an infamous pirate crew.
Ah... So the boss man was a pirate!
This restaurant is
that old fart's treasure.
And the cooks who admire and flock to him
are hot-headed pirate types.
Well, they're a perfect fit
for a place that pirates frequent.
Yeah, this restaurant is pretty wild.
Well, that's the norm here.
Some people come here just to see
the cooks and pirates going at it.
But it freaks out the waiters,
and all of them quit.
Ah, I see... That's why the boss man
wants to keep me here for a year.
Hey, join our crew.
I refuse.
I've got my reasons for staying here.
No! I refuse!
W-What do you mean?!
I refuse your refusal!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together.
H-Hey! At least listen to my reason!
Okay, what's the reason?
None of your business!
Huh?
You just told me to listen!
I mean you should respect my damn opinion!
I'll fillet you like a salmon,
you dirty straw-hat bastard!
What'd you say?!
Make fun of this hat, and I'll knock you into next week, you jerk!
Sorry to interrupt, but...
– But what?!
I'm Gin of the Krieg Pirates.
Gin
Pirate-at-Arms
Krieg Pirates
Gin
Pirate-at-Arms
Krieg Pirates
You're a pirate too, right?
What's your goal?
My goal? One Piece.
That means I'm going
to the Grand Line.
Since you're looking for a cook, you must not have much of a crew yet.
Yep. He's number five.
Why are you counting me?!
You seem like a nice guy,
so let me warn you.
Don't even dream
of going to the Grand Line.
You're still young.
No need to rush into things.
The Grand Line is just a tiny fraction
of the world's oceans.
There are much safer waters
out there for a pirate.
I see... Do you know a lot
about the Grand Line?
No... I don't know anything...
I don't understand anything about it...
Which is exactly why it terrifies me...
For one of Krieg's men,
you sure sound like a wimp.
Hm? Who's Krieg?
Galley
Sea Restaurant
Hors d'oeuvres for table three!
No waiters; take it out yourself!
Is it really okay, though, Patty?
Is what okay?
I hear that guy you beat up
in the restaurant earlier
is one of the Krieg Pirates.
Oh yeah, I heard.
Don Krieg's the most powerful,
vile pirate in these waters.
That's right.
Hm?
After all, he's the head
of an armada, commanding
50 pirate captains
with their own vessels.
He's a monster incarnate...
So, what's the big deal?
I heard he commands an unparalleled force of over 5,000 pirates.
If that guy from earlier tells
Don Krieg how we mistreated him,
everyone here would be like ants
crushed under a parade
of stampeding elephants.
Is that so...?
Then you're saying
I should've served him?
How would
the paying customers feel?
It would ruin the reputation
of the famous fighting cooks
of the Sea Restaurant Baratie!
You do know how many pirates
we've chased off, right?
If you're so scared, then quit!
What'd you say?!
Okay, sure, but all the waiters
quit because of your filthy mouth!
Patty!
It's your fault that we're overworked!
Ha! Those wimps were
a waste of space from the start!
Go for it!
Carne, take him out!
Clobber him, Patty!
Hey, you idiots!
Get back to work!
Yes, Owner!
So long, then...
By the way, I'm still gonna
go to the Grand Line.
Sure. Do what you like.
We're strangers.
Your life is none of my business.
Just thought I'd warn you.
Oh, and Sanji-san...
Thank you so much!
I owe you my life.
That meal was incredibly delicious.
Could I come back for more?
Any time!
Hey, Cabin Boy!
Boss Man!
There you are!
Go, Gin.
Ahh, sorry.
You're gonna get in trouble
for giving me a free meal, aren't you?
Well...
No proof; no trouble.
Don't get caught next time, Gin!
Sanji! Cabin Boy!
Get back to work already!
Hey, table three is ready!
Monkey D. Luffy
Bonded Cabin Boy
Sea Restaurant
Monkey D. Luffy
Bonded Cabin Boy
Sea Restaurant
I'm Luffy!
I'm your cabin boy for now.
Nice to meetcha!
On Hiatus From Piracy
Where's table six's dessert?
Hey, who took that order?!
Wasn't it you?!
I'm too busy right now!
Get your head on straight!
Wanna say that again to my fists?!
On Hiatus From Piracy
If you've got nothing to do,
go wash dishes, Cabin Boy!
Where's Sanji?
Flirting in the dining room.
Again?!
I'm annoyed enough as it is
just having him as the sous-chef.
Deal with it.
He's been here the longest.
Why does he stay? He doesn't get along with the owner at all.
He wants to be head chef someday.
You'd have to be blind to miss it.
Huh?
Hm?
Hey, Cabin Boy!
How many dishes
have you broken so far?!
Oh, sorry. I forgot to count.
That's not what I meant!
Apologize for breaking them!
Forget about washing dishes.
Clean over there!
Okay, you can count on me!
Don't pick at the plates!
That's an entrée!
Oh, don't worry about it!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Just get out of the kitchen!
Go and take orders, okay?
Go ask what customers want to eat!
You can do that much, right?!
Yep.
Chores are hard.
Koby musta been miserable.
Hey, Cabin Boy!
Ugh! You guys...
I heard you have to work
here for a year.
Can we change the ship's flag?
W-W-Why are you guys...
eating yummy food without me?!
How could you?!
There's no reason
we shouldn't be, right guys?
Take this!
For real...
Well, the food here is good.
I feel bad for you, so...
have a drink!
I can't believe you did that!
So gross! So gross!
My sides hurt from laughing!
They're a noisy bunch.
Could they be...
his crewmates?
Hm?
Pour it yourself.
Oh, dear ocean!
I am grateful for this day!
What?!
Oh, love, I can't bear this hardship.
Go ahead and laugh at me.
I would readily be a lowly pirate
—or perhaps even a devil—
to be by your side!
What a tragedy! The obstacles
between us are too great!
I'm that obstacle, right, Sanji?
The old fart...!
This is a good opportunity.
Go be a pirate with them.
I don't need you here anymore!
I see...
That cook saved your life,
and you made it back here.
Is that what you're saying, Gin?
Y-Yes... B-But...
I didn't know our flagship
was in such bad shape.
Don Krieg!
What?
I'll take you there,
to the Sea Restaurant Baratie.
Hey, you old fart.
I'm the sous-chef here.
What do you mean
you don't need me?!
You always cause problems with the customers.
You flare your nostrils
the second you see a lady.
Factor in your lousy cooking,
and you're just dead weight
to this restaurant.
That's why I don't need you.
W-Why you...
Besides, you're not exactly friends
with the other cooks.
So go be a pirate or whatever
and just leave this restaurant already!
What the hell...?
You're just gonna keep running your mouth, huh, you old fart?
The rest I could overlook,
but I won't let you insult my cooking!
I'll stay here and cook
no matter what you say!
I won't hear another word about it!
How dare you lay your hands
on the owner of this restaurant...
You pea-brain!
Damn you...
Quit screwing around...
No matter how hard
you try to kick me out,
I'll continue to work here as a cook...
until you die!
I won't die!
I'll live another hundred years.
The old fart just
has to have the last word...
Okay, you have permission
to be a pirate now!
No way!
Anyway...
Sorry about that.
By way of apology, accept this
fruit macédoine, my princess.
Wow, thank you!
You're so kind.
– The least I could do...
– We don't get an apology?!
I'm gonna sue for discrimination,
mister lover cook!
I'm serving you tea, aren't I?
Thank me for that, long nose.
Huh? You wanna fight?
I won't go easy on you.
Get him, Zoro!
Get him yourself.
Stop! Please don't
fight over me.
Yes, I'll stop.
Who said it was over you?!
By the way, you know...
Yes?
The food you have here is delicious...
but it's a bit on the expensive side...
Oh, of course your meal is gratis.
Thank you!
The rest of you have to pay.
Wha...?!
You're too predictable.
What are you sitting around for?!
Bring hand towels to the customers.
Yes, sir.
Two Days Later
Hey, what's the matter?
Hourglasses flanking the skull...
...to intimidate all opposition.
That flag!
That flag is definitely his!
The East Blue's most powerful man,
Don Krieg!
Why...?! Why are the
Krieg Pirates here?!
You see, Patty?!
They actually came!
You're gonna get rid of them, right?!
I-It can't be!
The head of a 5,000-pirate armada
is here?!
Why would he come to avenge
just one of his men?!
It's no mistake! He's really here!
Hey, this is bad!
Can't we leave yet?!
What a huge galleon!
That ship's humongous!
Maybe Gin came back to say thanks.
I doubt that...
But this is strange...
Huh?
– H-Hey...
– W-What the...?
Their ship sure is a mess...
It doesn't look like
damage from cannon fire.
But at the same time,
it doesn't look man-made.
Did they sail through a waterspout?
Here he comes...
Don Krieg
Pirate Commodore
S-Sorry... Can I have some
food and water?
We have money... tons of money...
W-What's that?!
He's set aside pride and might.
Is he really that Don Krieg,
commodore of a grand pirate fleet?
So he's hungry...
C-Captain!
Don Krieg!
P-Please! Help our captain!
He really is starving!
It's been days since his last meal,
so he'll die if he doesn't eat soon!
What a sight to behold:
the dreaded Don Krieg
in such a sorry state!
I've got money this time.
We're customers!
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, alert the Navy right away.
What?
He's on death's door!
This opportunity won't come again!
Don't feed him anything!
Just grab him!
He's right! Who knows what he'll do
once he recuperates!
He's a villain.
He deserves to starve
because of everything he's done!
No doubt he'll attack this restaurant
once he's back on his feet.
Don't even give him a cup of water.
I won't harm anyone.
Once I've eaten,
I promise I'll leave quietly.
So please... help... me...
Don Krieg, please stop!
Please stop begging!
It's beneath you!
Please don't do something so disgraceful!
I promise... Please...
I'll take leftovers or anything...
Anything...
Don...
Tch! Playing the sympathy card, huh?
Hey, move it, Patty.
Ah?!
S... Sanji-san!
Here, Gin. He can eat this.
Sanji-san...
Thank you!
Hey, Sanji!
Take that food away from him!
Don't you know who he is?!
He's the most powerful man
in the East Blue,
Foul Play Krieg!
He earned that name in prison
after he pretended to be a marine
and commandeered a Navy ship
by killing its senior officer.
That's how he got started as a pirate.
He would often raise the
Navy flag when entering harbors
to attack towns and passenger ships.
He also attacked enemy vessels
under a white flag.
He'll do anything to win.
That's how he got to where he is now!
What? That's playing dirty.
His physical strength is nothing to scoff at either.
Leave once he's eaten?
There's no way he'd do that!
Letting such a wicked fiend die
would make the world a better place!
What?!
Sa... Sanji!
This... This isn't what we
agreed on, Don Krieg!
You swore you wouldn't
hurt anybody here!
And that man...
That man saved our lives...
Yeah, that was delicious.
I feel alive again.
H-Hey... W-Wha...?
What the hell
is going on in there?
Let's go check it out.
What?! A-Are you serious?!
Oh? Are you scared?
Wha– Don't be silly!
Hmph!
This is strange...
That ship looks empty...
This is a good restaurant.
I'll be taking this ship.
So... that's what you want...
Ow, ow, ow...
My ship's a wreck,
so I need a new one.
You'll do as I say,
and then you'll leave.
W-What?!
Don Krieg,
this isn't what you promised.
I have 100 of my men
back on that ship.
They're starving and severely injured.
First, prepare 100 rations
of food and water.
Some have already starved to death.
W-Water...
There's no time to waste!
You want us to help pirates
that are gonna attack this ship?!
We refuse!
Refuse? Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not placing an order.
I'm giving you an order.
No matter who you are... don't you dare defy me!
– Sanji-san...
– Hm?
Sanji-san, I'm sorry...
I didn't mean for this to happen...
You bastard!
You got us into this mess!
Hey Sanji! Where're you going?!
To the kitchen.
I have to prepare 100 more meals.
– Sanji-san!
– Sanji?!
– What?!
Right. That's how it should be.
Are you working for Krieg, Sanji?!
We can't let you into the kitchen!
We're fed up
with your crazy behavior!
Go ahead...
If you want to stop me, go ahead!
I know...
I know he's irredeemable, the worst kind of villain.
But that doesn't matter to me.
Not one bit!
What happens after we feed them...
I don't care about that.
I'm a cook. No more. No less.
If someone's hungry, I'll feed them.
That's all there is to it.
Isn't that a cook's job?
Patty!
Hey, someone keep him restrained!
Sanji, you sometimes feed customers
I kick out the back door, right?
I dunno who's right on that,
but this time, you're wrong.
I won't let you keep doing
what you want.
I'll protect this restaurant.
Luckily, we've only got
one man to beat.
What could even Don Krieg
do against us?
We deal with pirates
here every day.
We know how to serve
every type of customer!
That's...
Are you full now, Krieg-san?
After the main course, how about...
a dessert of hot lead?!
Tainted Meatball!
Don!
I think I broke the door.
The owner's gonna yell at me again.
Well, you did it
to protect the restaurant.
It's a small price to pay.
Any idea what to do about those
still aboard Krieg's ship?
Lemme think...
Maybe we'll spread butter
on the ship and stir-fry it.
It'll taste good, right?
You pathetic cook!
How dare you serve me a nasty dessert?!
This restaurant is the worst!
You're annoying me, dammit!
From all over his body...
Bullets...
Don't defy me!
I'm the mightiest of them all!
Arms of steel
more powerful than flesh...
A carapace of
the strongest wootz steel...
And diamond fists
to destroy anything!
I have an array of weapons
hidden all over my body!
I command 50 ships
and 5,000 pirates!
I've never lost a battle!
I am the man fit to be called "Don"!
Out of my way, kid!
When I tell you to prepare food,
you shut up and do it!
No one defies me!
There's food for a hundred in here.
Take it to your ship right away.
– Owner Zeff!
What gives, Boss Man?
That's dangerous!
Z... Zeff?