Video Editing
Sewil
Timing
Bastia
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin
Gaijin
Yibis
Translation
DemonRin
Gaijin
Yibis
Opening Raw
Gavynnnnn
Whitebeard's era is over.
The Grand Line, Near the Sabaody Archipelago
Burning ambition spurs pirates
the world over into action.
On the other hand, Trafalgar Law is...
What? We're still not going?
Let's just go to the New World already!
I told you, we're waiting for the right time.
Trafalgar Law
Don't rush things.
The great treasure, One Piece, isn't going anywhere.
But you know, Blackbeard and his group
are causing a stir in the New World!
Rumor has it that they've
already crushed one pirate crew!
All these rookies with bounties over 100 million
are streaming into the New World!
If we keep hanging back here,
we're gonna fall behind, Captain!
Just let those guys continue
to take each other out.
I won't participate in pointless fights.
Quit whining and just follow my orders.
When the time is right,
we'll rise to the top.
Captain!
We'll follow you anywhere!
Aye aye, Captain!
A Winter Island, the New World
Kaido, one of the Four Emperors,
highly favors this island base.
I've been entrusted with guarding it.
And? What do you want me to do?
X Drake
I'm not telling you to do anything.
It's just a warning.
You're better off not angering Kaido, rookie.
In other words, if I take your head,
then Kaido will come for mine?
Indeed. If you understand,
then quit stalling and just–
That simplifies the matter!
An ancient zoan type, huh?
Now, that's rare!
Scratch!
A Spring Island, the New World
Scratchmen Apoo
How are there still so many?!
We really stepped in it.
Ouch.
Don't worry, guys!
We've got Captain Apoo on our side!
Listen up, men!
Aye!
Let's beat it!
What?!
Facing a herd of these wild boards
is a dance-off we definitely won't win!
Captain! We're headed straight for a cliff!
It's our best bet for escape!
We're done for!
Don't give up!
But... the ocean's right beneath the cliff!
Who cares?! Jump!
– Whaaat?!
What the...?!
Captain! I don't know if you noticed,
but we're running on air!
Looks like the boars are running on air too!
I can see that!
What the hell is with this island?!
It's so hot...
San Juan Wolf
My legs are totally exhausted...
There's no strength in my body either...
Ouch. A fish just bit me.
Quit fussing, Wolf.
On a certain Burning Island in the New World
Because of you, our raft almost broke.
That's why we're in this situation.
Trying to sail the seas of the New World
on that raft was an absurd idea anyway.
I should've stolen
Marshall D. Teach
a ship from Marineford when I had the chance!
We had grown attached to that raft, though.
Jesus Burgess
I'm saying that you are too careless!
Shiryu
In everything you do.
Put me in command!
Avalo Pizarro
I'll take over as captain for you, Teach.
Lafitte
Got a death wish?
We're the Blackbeard Pirates.
Heaven already knows the fate of all.
Doc Q
Vasco Shot
We're pretty low on booze.
Can't we go to an island with a town?
Catarina Devon
I agree.
But forget the ship; I need some nicer clothes.
I'm so sick of this prison outfit.
I'll go take a look.
Van Ogre
They're taking too long.
No argument here.
But these guys sure look to be going numb.
Ain't that right,
Jewelry Bonney?
Jewelry Bonney
Captain Bonney...
I'm impressed that a young lady like yourself
managed to get a bounty of over 100 million!
The New World is best left to the strong.
You did well making it
this far from the South Blue,
but this is the last stop on your voyage.
I don't need a weakling like you on my crew.
However, if you become my woman,
I'll gladly take you along.
Come see the waters ahead.
Screw you, you bearded pig!
Seems you've been rejected.
Forget it! You're one crude bitch!
A woman should be classy, after all!
I've already got all the ruffians
I need on my crew!
Yeah, you tell her!
We'll stick to the plan where
we hand you off to the Navy
in exchange for a proper warship!
Captain.
Huh?
I can see the Navy.
They've got the warship
they promised us, right?!
There's indeed a ship,
but I doubt it's intended for us.
Huh? How can you tell?
Akainu is on board.
Damn! This just got too rich for me!
Let's get the hell outta here!
A complete failure!
Where's Blackbeard?
He's gone!
When I heard you'd fled from the government,
my blood ran cold.
But it's all over now.
You! You won't get away with this!
The Holy Land Mary Geoise
He vanished?!
Yup, that's the honest truth.
Whose idea was this? Sengoku?!
No, much higher than that.
And I mean this in the literal sense.
He really just up and vanished!
It surprised me. I had no idea that the
Shadow-Shadow Fruit could do that.
This is no laughing matter!
It's fine. He was on the verge of death.
There's nothing he can do now.
Unless he somehow turned himself
into a zombie, you know?
Wouldn't that just take the cake?!
You're too nonchalant
about this whole affair!
That's quite some nerve you've got.
When, exactly, did you become my boss?!
You may hold a fair amount of sway
with the government, but I'm a pirate.
So I don't care!
The moment I lose interest in our little deal,
I'll just drop out of the Seven Warlords!
You'd best remember that.
Torino Kingdom, the South Blue
M-Mister Tanuki!
We tell you come back anytime,
but this too soon, right?
No, you've got the wrong man!
I may look like him, but I'm
actually his friend, Chopper Mask!
You trying too hard, Mister Tanuki.
You use disguise to hide being
embarrassed when come back so soon?
That's not it at all! I'm–
Mister Tanuki okay?
All being very mean.
In situation like this,
must play along.
Fine, you win!
Your kindness got to me!
Oh, Mister Tanuki!
That tickles, you jerk!
Truth be told, something came up.
Mind if I stay a bit longer?
No worry! You very welcome here.
I've never seen the many types
of plants that grow on that tree.
Please let me research them!
In that case, we have perfect place.
Also, I need to become
stronger and more capable.
No time to waste.
Oh, Mister Tanuki?
Back already?
This great!
Everyone, I'll be staying on this island
for a while, so let's get along!
Right, this is place.
What is this?
This be...
village library.
Use for research.
Look at all the books!
There're so many,
all the way from front to back!
Incredible!
They're all books about the plants I want
to research and the medicines I want to make!
There's no end to them!
On island, many plants make strong medicine.
Our technology make medicine, but birds
always keep ingredients away from people.
Was big problem for all.
I misjudged these islanders
due to their appearance,
but now that I think about it,
their weapons are really advanced.
They all resembled primitive savages,
but the science here is something incredible!
There's so much to learn here!
Mister Tanuki!
Maybe think you say all in head,
but every word Mister Tanuki say out loud.
And very rude too!
This country... I wonder how much
I can do while I'm here!
It's a yeti!
Shoot it dead!
Don't let it get away!
Take it down!
Pirates are incredible!
There are countless people like that out at sea!
Chopper, go out to sea some day.
If you do, you'll realize
just how small your own problems are.
Compared to the rest of the world,
your home island is this small!
Really?
No, it's smaller! Like this! It's true!
I can't join a human crew!
I'm a monster!
I could never fit in as a crewmate.
So...
So I've just come to...
to tell you how grateful I am.
Thank you... for inviting me.
I'm staying here, but...
if you ever feel like it,
please come vis–
Shut up!
Let's goooooo!
Ever since Luffy brought me out to sea,
it's been a struggle just to keep up.
How can I contribute more, Luffy?
I never want to experience
anything like that again.
But...
back then...
Luffy... was probably
in more pain than any of us!
Because you made me one of your crewmates,
I've been just fine,
not caring what others thought about me.
If it means I can be of any help to you...
then I'll even become a real monster!
Chopper!
Luffy!
I...
will definitely...
become stronger!
Kamabakka Kingdom on the Grand Line.
Tell me, vhaat vass that article?
I read you loud and clear...
Vhyy did you calm down after that?
I received a message from Luffy
that only his crewmates would understand.
Just from that article.
But you don't believe I'm his crewmate, so I'm
not telling you what I saw, ya big dummy!
You are so annoyingk!
Hey, who made this food?
Oh? You seem to have a
discerningk palate there.
Not just the taste. It's as if...
my body is getting rejuvenated.
Indeed. Thiss is aggression cuisine!
Many chefs on thiss island
can cook like thiss!
Yes!
Behold! The candies of thiss island have
beautiful yet strongk body types!
Kind hearts, too.
My candies developed thiss vayy
by eatingk aggression cuisine!
Your diet decides your condition,
your physique,
your personality!
Of course, you are vhaat you eat!
If 100% of the voorld population
drank milk every day,
vouldn't you know it,
but crime vould disappear!
Huh?
You see...
no aggression, no progression!
Using food to build one's physique...
I've never thought of it that way before.
So, every day, my cooking
could help them develop?
And then...
I could make Nami-san and
Robin-chan become even sexier?!
Vhaat do I do viith you?!
What will I do?!
I'm all fired up!
Please teach me aggression cuisine!
The answer is no!
Ow!
These 99 vital recipes have been passed
down through the Kamabakka Kingdom
as part of Newkama Kenpo's secret arts:
bride training!
It vill be a cold day in hell...
before I let a total stranger
like you learn them!
That is, unless you open
your heart to your femininity!
Study Newkama kenpo!
Not happening!
I was not born to merely befriend the ladies.
I was born...
to give them my manly love!
Vhaat a compellingk and movingk speech!
Vhyy not give you a chance?
A chance?
There are 99 grandmasters of
Newkama kenpo residingk on thiss island.
Each one of them vill possess a recipe.
If you are indeed a pirate,
then steal every one of those recipes!
However! It vill be hell for you
as every Newkama attempts to put
thiss Ssveets dress on you!
I vaant to see if you maintain
your manly composure!
Sanji-kyun!
We won't let you rest!
The Sweets dress.
I will make you remember
the joy of wearing a skirt!
Sanji!
Being girly's great!
You...
versuss the Newkama kenpo grandmasters!
Come out on top,
and I vill even loan you a ship!
Vhaatever you vaant is yours!
Now, decide!
Hey you, cook!
Join my crew!
Huh?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
Should I consider your silence
as resigningk yourself to your fate?
Because if you lose–
Once I've won...
Once I've beaten all of you...
it'll show how much stronger
I am compared to now.
Even if you pierce his body with hundreds of weapons,
nobody stands a chance
against a spear of blind determination.
Hey, Luffy.
Don't... Don't you lose.
I'm hoping to head out someday...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now!
It's not time yet.
Hey, do you know about the All Blue?
Nope!
What, you don't know?
It's a miraculous sea!
We've both got stupid dreams.
In order to reach my own goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah, I might as well tag along
on your journey to become the pirate king.
I'll be your ship's cook.
Luffy, the next time we meet,
I will...
support you as the greatest cook in the world,
so that you may become the pirate king.
I will...
live through...
this hell.
I accept...
your challenge!
How nice.
Let us not hold back, dearies!
Let's go!
I will definitely...
succeed!
This is Weatheria, a small sky island.
The research she stole...
...the weather ball...
...and Doctor Haredas!
We won't forgive you just because
you returned everything!
I'm sorry. I truly regret my actions.
You think we'll trust you now?!
Let's take all that she has
and kick her out of here!
Please don't!
Well then, to prove my remorse,
I will throw myself into the sea.
Huh?!
I hope you can forgive me in my next life!
What?!
Farewell!
We made her cry!
We were too harsh!
You're too young to just
up and throw away your life!
Goodbye...
We're sorry!
That's great. I forgive you.
Well, I'll be staying here awhile
to study up on your weather science.
Oh, my name is Nami.
But you can call me Nami-san.
Also, I'll need a house of my own.
Privacy is important, you know.
I require a soft, fluffy bed,
a bubble bath, and a walk-in closet.
I'm counting on you, sky geezers.
So, let's do our best!
Doctor Haredas, say something!
Good grief.
Weatheria drifts around the world
wherever the wind may take it.
We sometimes visit the surface
to gather goods and information,
and then we continue on our way.
Information?
Well, records mostly.
Records regarding the Grand Line's
unbelievable weather phenomena,
many of which are still–
What's this?!
Uh, are you listening to me?
You gotta be kidding me?
Raining lightning?!
Indeed. It literally rains lightning.
The falling lightning resembles a downpour.
It happens on an island in the New World.
If you plan to cross that sea,
remember that it defies
common sense like no sea before it.
Please... teach me, Haredas-san.
The New World's weather...
Teach me all about it!
You seem desperate.
Well, of course I am!
The lives of my crew are at stake!
I'm their navigator!
Out at sea, I have the
biggest responsibility of all!
It's my job to take the captain
wherever it is he wishes to go!
Luffy says he's gonna be the pirate king,
so I have to be a navigator
worthy of that cause!
Your captain is a lucky man
to have a crew that's so devoted to him.
I don't have a choice.
You don't?
That's right. I mean, he talks a big game,
but he's utterly clueless about the ocean.
He also has a real knack for finding trouble.
If I left him alone...
Luffy,
help me!
Of course I will!
He'd get himself killed without me.
He's just... a reckless idiot!
He sounds like one troublesome captain!
That's why I'm gonna help him.
This time, I will!
Hey, tell me about the weather balls.
Don't ask so casually!
This is Weatheria's greatest invention, after all!
In the wrong hands, they could
throw the entire world into disarray!
What's their potential in combat?
Hey now, don't just go saying such things!
Stop grinning!
Nami!
You're one of us!
The Kingdom of Tehna Gehna
Kenzan Island, the Grand Line
This is the Kingdom of Tehna Gehna
on Kenzan Island in the Grand Line.
Come on in and have a look!
This creature has the
appearance of a real skeleton!
What's more, his arms only have a single joint!
Is there a more extraordinary
creature anywhere?!
Hey! Don't pull a fast one, you con artists!
What? Does he not fascinate you?
That thing hasn't moved since we got here!
It's just a big doll, isn't it?!
Luffy-san has made his decision.
And so, I should make one too.
Hey, skeleton!
Don't jerk us around!
I cannot just sit here!
Oh, so you understand?
That's right, move!
This is a show, after all!
Is there any way I can help?
Just moving around would be plenty helpful!
Get up and do something!
What's going on here?!
You were not the least bit
scared when you saw me,
and what's more,
you invited me to join your crew.
Anyway... Hey, you!
Join my crew!
Yes. That sounds lovely.
– What?!
Fifty long years.
Could you imagine my joy, especially
after drifting on that dark sea for so long?
A certain man stole my shadow.
What're you talking about?!
If you need your shadow,
I'll get it back for you!
Do you realize how brilliantly
you were shining to me?
Fifty years of hoping for a miracle,
and that moment fulfilled my wish.
Give me back my money!
Yeah!
Damn! I thought he'd be our
meal ticket, but it looks hopeless.
If he won't comply, we'll just have to–
What the...?!
Forty degrees!
– What?!
Ah! That's difficult!
He's really talking and moving!
How creepy!
What in the world is it?!
If I try going below 45 degrees,
I end up slipping.
However, once I can master this...
I may be of more use to Luffy-san.
Or perhaps I should find another way.
He's got a guitar!
What's he about to do?
What are you planning now?!
Don't start any third-rate performance!
This is just a freak show!
"Freak show" works for me!
Call it whatever you wish.
"Loneliness" no longer exists in my vocabulary!
Ladies and gentlemen!
I'm sure you're all bored just staring at me.
What's with this rhythm?
It's making my heart dance!
Please listen to my new single,
"Bone to Be Wild"!
This is the underside
of the East Blue's colossal bridge.
A Colossal Bridge, the East Blue
Why the sudden change of heart?
But you're coming with us to Baltigo?
If so, we are extremely grateful.
Dragon-san has always wanted to meet you.
If I had known you were such charitable
people, I would have come much sooner.
W-We're sorry! We hadn't heard
about your team-up with Crocodile.
I'm joking.
Just a bit of fun, but I apologize.
I'm glad things turned out the way they did.
Set sail! Set sail for Baltigo!
Seventy-nine million belly?
An eight-year-old with a bounty that high?!
Apparently, she's a survivor of Ohara,
one of the devils plotting to destroy the world.
From Ohara?!
And I'm fuzzy on the details, but she
supposedly sunk six naval warships as well.
That explains the insane bounty!
She is a devil child
and can't be allowed to live!
Alright! Just wait right there!
Why are you trying to save me?!
When did I ever ask you to do this?!
I just... want to die!
No way...!
Are you all insane?!
With the entire world as your enemy,
you're all as good as dead!
Bring it on, then!
Robin-san, please come inside.
It's cold out here.
I'll be just fine.
I'm a pirate. You are revolutionaries.
I don't fully trust you yet.
I won't enter a cabin
where there's no escape route.
But that's...!
We have no intention of harming you!
Just let me stay. Back when I was
on my own, this was how I lived.
My apologies! Very well.
Hey! Go get lots of warm blankets!
Bring out a meal and a warm drink too!
B-But we set that all up inside...
Hop to it!
A wind screen and sofa too!
Right!
Luffy.
If I go to your father and let the
world's tides carry me where they will,
I wonder if I can become a little stronger?
Wanting to become stronger
for the sake of someone else.
I'd never considered it before.
We now return to Mech Island
on the Grand Line.
Futureland, Baldimore.
We've investigated the destruction
of Doctor Vegapunk's laboratory...
but we still haven't found the culprit.
Hey! Hurry up!
It wouldn't be an exaggeration to call
this the greatest loss of the century.
Do you know anything about it?
I heard that an intruder
resembling a gorilla entered the lab.
This is a real head-scratcher.
It's impossible to reach this island
without an icebreaker ship.
But nobody has seen any such ship.
They say that the intruder was
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hat Pirates,
but he was spotted less than a
month ago on Sabaody Archipelago.
We have no idea what route or means
he used to get to Baldimore.
Captain Gorilla!
The Snow Mountain search party is ready!
Very well. I shall go as well!
Wh-What is this?!
The explosion exposed a hidden entrance.
I can hardly believe it. We had no idea...
that there was a second laboratory in here.
This seems to be where he created
all those cyborg animal guards.
Hey, don't break anything!
You're one to talk, old guy!
The blown-up lab had some radical inventions
that would have changed how people live,
but I was more interested
in the weaponry I found here.
This is amazing!
It's everything from warships
to human genetics!
What's going on inside this guy's head?
Okay, I've decided!
I'm gonna live here!
– Wha...?! Live here?!
– Yeah!
I'll come down the mountain
sometimes for more cola,
so don't forget to keep
your house stocked, you hear?!
Don't sweat it. As long as you don't
rat me out, I'll keep to myself here.
I won't cause any trouble.
Quit screamin'! It's just my face!
– Don't look at us!
– Your face is too scary!
How's this?
It's the tiger skin rug.
Much better.
Frah... Frah... Frah-nky!
I'm freezing. Especially my legs.
Why won't you put on pants?
...would you please sail
on the ship that I've built?
Luffy... you helped me achieve my dream.
Franky!
Thanks for the ship!
It really is the best!
We'll take good care of it!
If you want your bikini back,
you'll just have to join our crew!
You took me along for the ride
in this wild, wide world.
Passing through sea after sea,
overcoming countless battles and troubles.
And once we've sailed to the end of the sea,
then we can truly say
she was the ship of dreams.
Hey, Luffy.
The Sunny still hasn't shown her full potential!
And the captain to make the
Sunny my dream ship?
That's you.
I'll learn the technologies necessary to get
the better of tough adventures to come...
tougher than any so far.
So, Luffy...
Hey. The tiger's on fire.
What's that?!
A monster?! Be careful!
So, Luffy... let's overcome the
rough waves of the New World together!
This incident in the Grand Line
is forever referred to as:
"The Legend of the Burning Spirit Beast of Baldimore."
Meanwhile, on the Bowin Archipelago
on the Grand Line.
Bowin Islands
The Grand Line
What is it now-un, Usopp-un?
Gotta burn this fat!
Gotta get in shape!
Oh! That's a great idea-un!
Gotta get stronger!
Good! You can't get
off the island otherwise-un!
And then... I'll get even stronger!
Yes! That sounds good too-un!
And then I'll get much, much stronger!
Th-That much-un?
Much, much, much, much, much stronger!
You're incredibly motivated-un!
To get you up and
working out so vigorously-un...
What exactly was written in that paper-un?
I... received a message from our captain.
A message?
What're you talking about?
Get on board already.
You're one of us now, aren't you?
Luffy!
U-Usopp?
Y-You...
were here too?
Defeat him! We're all
going back together, Luffy!
Of course we will!
I...
I imagined Luffy would become the pirate king
on his own, all while I stood by and watched.
We've finally made it this far!
When we've crossed the other half
of the world and see this wall again...
When that happens,
I'll be the pirate king!
But I was wrong.
He has lots of enemies
he can't possibly defeat.
Even Luffy can lose!
He's pushing himself too hard!
He's crying out in agony!
That's why...
he needs to depend on my strength!
Heracles-un!
I want to become stronger!
Much, much, much stronger!
Please... Master Heracles-un...
Huh? Master-un?
I've... been curious
about those weapons of yours.
Your strength and skills are what allow you
to survive on this island. Teach me your ways!
Strength-un?
I'm a strong master-un?
Yeah! My master is amazingly strong!
And,
my name is...
Heracles-un!
That's such a cool name!
R-Right! Take a seat, Usopp-un.
Yes, Master!
Listen up, Usopp, my student-un!
The local flora includes a
certain plant called pop green.
They can sprout anywhere in an instant
and have quite the mean streak!
Behold! Their seeds-un.
Pop green?
Indeed-un!
Each possesses a unique utility-un.
Indeed-un.
Just hang on, Luffy!
Run, Usopp-un!
This forest will make you stronger-un!
To help you become king of the pirates,
I'm gonna become the real Sogeking!
Now to Kuraigana Island on the Grand Line,
in the ruins of the Muggy Kingdom.
Muggy Kingdom Ruins
Kuraigana Island, Grand Line
I'm begging you!
Teach me the way of your sword!
I've misjudged you, Roronoa.
You would beg your enemy to instruct you?
How shameless!
Begone. I have no business
with a wretch like you.
It would seem...
I overestimated you.
What are you playing at?
Such actions are unbecoming.
I want to become stronger!
Powerless against baboons
and incapable of setting sail,
you returned here, tail between your legs;
I have nothing to teach a man such as you.
I defeated the baboons.
Did he now?
Now, I just need to take your head!
But I'm not so stupid to think
I can beat you right now.
Inconceivable.
If I am as yet your foe,
why prostrate yourself
before me and demand tutelage?
For what purpose?!
To surpass you!
You would have me temper the very sword
whose blade would claim my head?
You are indeed strange.
Foolhardy, to be sure.
And still, you remain shameless.
It would seem... your ambition
exceeds even your pride.
Hey, ghost girl. Tend to his wounds.
Hey! Don't tell me what to do!
Training commences upon your recovery.
Damn it! Everyone keeps
ordering me around!
Come on, get back to your room!
He is clumsy and foolish.
When a man of his caliber sets aside his pride,
it is always for the sake of another.
"3D" with an X over it, and "2Y"?
You're right!
It's tattooed onto Straw Hat's right arm!
We made a promise to meet
at a certain place in three days.
So much for that plan.
So "3D" stands for "three days"?
But the "3D" is crossed out,
and the "2Y" means...
Two years.
Two years?!
We won't be meeting up in three days,
but in two years.
Everything else was just a fake-out
to hide his true intentions.
This message was meant only for us.
Luffy has made his decision.
As we are, we'd be rushing headlong
into disaster in the New World.
We'll stay put, grow stronger...
and then we'll set sail once more!
In two years at the Sabaody Archipelago!
A Few Days Earlier
In the Calm Belt
Here he comes.
Jinbe! Thanks for everything!
I'm the one who ought to be thanking you!
You listened to my plea and
helped me escape from Impel Down,
and though I am shamed, I go on living.
I cannot thank you enough.
I thought I told you to stop that.
If not for you, I probably wouldn't
have gotten to Navy Headquarters.
Raise your head.
I suppose so.
And I might have the chance
to help you again someday.
With that said, let us meet again
in two years, at Fishman Island!
I look forward to the day when you
arrive together with your crew!
Sure!
Take care!
Luscaina, a Deserted Island
Northwest of the Isle of Women, Calm Belt
This island will do the trick.
Known as the Island of 48 Seasons:
its climate ruthlessly shifts once per week.
Luffy.
I will bring you food from the
Isle of Women each and every day!
What?! Seriously, Hancock?
Then bring more of that special dish,
the gorgon whatchamacallits.
They're so good!
O-Of course!
Snake Princess!
Whatever your heart desires most,
I will bring it to you!
Also... that's officially the 10th time
you have used my name.
Th-Then... are we engaged?
Nyo you are nyot!
And why do you keep moving backward?!
Hancock, we can't have you
pampering him like that.
While Luffy-kun is training, all your women
will have to remain off the island.
What gives you the right
to decide such things, Rayleigh?!
Your answer will determine
whether you turn to stone!
He can find all the food he needs
in the mountains, forests, rivers, or ocean!
Please release his nyose, Snake Princess!
If he can't handle basic survival skills,
he'll never make it as a pirate!
This is all to help Luffy-kun!
Did you say... this will help Luffy?
I did.
If it is to help Luffy...
then I shall endure it!
But Rayleigh, this island
is extremely dangerous.
If anything happens to him–
If nothing happens to him,
it wouldn't be training.
Send prayers if you're worried.
All right. Now we are the only
two humans on this island.
Behold this vast wilderness.
There was once a great civilization here, but
humans eventually lost the battle for survival.
It's a harsh environment
where only the strong can thrive.
I smell adventure!
The island is crawling with beasts.
There's no counting them all.
In your current state,
I sense about 500 that you can't beat.
You'll need to become stronger
to even sleep at night.
How can you tell what's here
or how many there are?
It's not just me.
You, too, will learn to use this power.
The power known as haki!
Hey, look out!
Something's coming, Rayleigh!
Gramps! Behind you! Behind you!
Listen well, Luffy-kun. Haki is a power
that lies dormant in people the world over.
An elephant?!
It's five times as big as a normal one!
That elephant is so cool!
Presence. Fighting spirit. Control.
People use it in much the
same way as their normal senses.
However, most humans don't
even realize they have this power,
or they spend their entire lives
trying in vain to develop it.
To never doubt: that is the power.
L-Look out!
Gear Second!
Jet Pistol!
Dammit, is this even an elephant?
He's not just strong but fast too!
Watch closely.
Most haki manifests within two categories.
Look out!
Relax.
The elephant will swing its trunk
at me from the right.
The power to sense your opponent's presence:
this is observation haki.
Amazing.
Hone this ability to discern the
location and number of foes unseen.
You can also predict the
movements of your enemies.
A kick with your left foot.
Mantra.
On the sky island of Skypiea,
they call this power "mantra."
That was close!
Next up: armament haki.
Imagine that using it is like
wearing invisible armor.
Gramps!
I... I know that one!
Ashigara Dokkoi!
Of course, the stronger your armor,
the more powerful your attacks.
Hey, ow! I'm made of rubber,
but that flick really hurt!
This is the most useful part of this power.
When battling devil fruit users, armament haki
is the most effective way to oppose them.
Otherwise, you must find a weakness
in their individual powers.
Even the practically invincible logia types,
who boast freely flowing bodies,
are vulnerable when struck by it.
Gramps, was this how you could hit Kizaru?
So, if I used this, even I could fight
Navy guys like Smokey or Aokiji?
People can also imbue
their weapons with this power.
You saw the Kuja Tribe's archery?
Yeah...
Then they weren't just steel arrows.
Observation and armament:
these are the two types of haki.
However,
a select few people in the world
can utilize another kind of haki.
Pay attention.
This power controls your opponent:
conqueror's haki.
Those who have made a name
for themselves in this world,
possess this power hidden within them.
However,
one can only learn to control it;
conqueror's haki cannot be
acquired through training.
It is the very spirit of the user.
It strengthens with individual growth.
That's what you used
back at the auction house!
I'm sure you've experienced it already.
Your potential as a conqueror
is already awakening.
But you should refrain from casually
using it until you have a handle on it.
There's a potential for affecting
innocent bystanders around you.
What is it?
Amazing!
The pirate king's crew can beat giant monsters
like these without even touching them?
Did your respect for me grow?
Yeah!
But I've seen this haki stuff lots before.
Shanks... Grandpa...
Enel and Aisa...
and then there's Hancock
and the Kuja warriors.
I'm sure you have. However,
learning to use haki is not so simple a task.
Right.
Usually, the amount of time
we have wouldn't be enough,
but you have a lot of potential.
Over the next two years,
I intend to try to teach you the basics of
observation, armament, and conqueror's haki.
You see, most people tend to specialize
in just one type over the others,
due to their skills or weaknesses.
They gravitate toward the one
they're best at and hone nothing else.
If you become skilled in all three,
you'll achieve so much more.
Sure, I got it.
Well then,
I won't go easy on you, Luffy.
Of course! I wouldn't expect you to!
Ah, hold on.
Gramps said this was the one safe spot, right?
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy
is taking a short break.
Oh, right.
This too.
Guys...
Luffy!
Hey, hurry!
Let's get started!
Got it!
I'm in your hands, Gramps!
That won't do.
Say, "Please teach me, Rayleigh-san"!
No, "Teacher"!
Or, "Master"?
Please teach me, Rayleigh!
Well, it doesn't matter.
Zoro, Usopp, Sanji, Nami,
Chopper, Robin, Franky, Brook...
and... Ace and Sabo!
To ensure I keep my promise,
I'm gonna get stronger!