Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
Galaxy 9000
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Bell-mère
All right. Let's hear this
reason or whatever, then.
– I'll pass.
– H-Hey!
I don't care about her past.
Where are you going, Luffy?
For a walk.
A-A walk?! You're not
gonna listen to this?!
No. I'll pass.
Who's he?
Don't mind him.
That's just how he is.
We'll hear you out.
Though I don't think it's
gonna change anything.
Yeah! I'll listen, too!
I wanna know what's
happening on this island!
Me, too! I want to know
everything about Nami!
And now he's sleeping.
Don't go to sleep right after you say that!
I see. This is why Nami
had such a hard time.
I fell asleep?
Huh? Nojiko?
Where could she have gone?
Just a little longer, Bell-mère.
Just a little longer, and everything
will return to normal!
Cocoyashi Village,
the tangerine orchard,
and even my dream!
It took eight years.
All done.
All done!
Damn it, Nami! Not again!
Let go!
Oh? Did it again, Nacchan?
I'm not a cat!
You just never learn!
You idiot!
How many times do I have to
tell you stealing is wrong?!
It's not my fault we're poor!
You meanie!
Bell-mère!
Bell-mère! Your no-good
cat's been at it again!
Bell-mère
Nami's and Nojiko's
Foster Mother
Bell-mère
Nami's and Nojiko's
Foster Mother
Whadya want? You're so annoying!
Oh! Welcome home, Nami!
I'm back!
Look! This is the umpteenth time!
She's infamous throughout the village now!
So?
Surely even you've
shoplifted before, Gen?
You're why she acts this way!
I'm just kidding!
All right. You paid for her, right?
B-Bell-mère...
Thanks so much.
I don't have money right now.
I'll pay you later...
with my body.
Th-That's not wh-what I meant!
Look at you blush!
Oh? And why are you laughing?
Try that again, and you'll
get 100 spankings!
I'm sorry!
But I really wanted this book!
If you wanted it,
why didn't you just tell me?
Because you wouldn't
buy it for me anyway.
Of course I would!
We do have some
money stashed away.
But the villagers said the weather's
been so good lately,
any old field will grow tons of tangerines.
We can't get a good price for ours,
and they won't sell anyway.
They can mind their own business!
You're so dumb, Nami!
I would've stolen it way better!
I said no stealing!
I was just joking!
That hurts!
But you know,
there's one thing for sure!
The maps you draw are
really amazing, Nami!
First you learned how to draw
sea charts, and now land maps!
This is a map of this island, isn't it?!
No one would ever think
such a little kid drew this!
I've been studying navigation, too!
Even navigation?!
That's Nami's dream, right!
Yeah!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to sail all the world's seas!
And then I'm gonna make
a world map of everything I see!
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your goal, then?
Yeah!
A world map, huh?
Nami! Someday, you will make
your dream come true!
I just know it!
Hey, Bell-mère.
You haven't been eating lately.
I've been eating tangerines,
though. I'm on a diet!
I don't need any food, either.
Since when are you
watching your figure?
Kids need to eat right!
You keep lying!
You don't have any food because
we don't have any money!
For real?!
You're suffering so that we can–
Diet!
You shouldn't underestimate
the rejuvenating power of tangerines!
They're the reason I still have such
glowing skin at the age of 30!
But your hands are yellow.
Just shut up and eat!
Here you are, Nami! All done!
It's Bell-mère's own
haute couture brand!
Another hand-me-down
from Nojiko?
Don't worry about it!
It looks great on you, Nami!
This lion used to be a sunflower!
That's just how it is!
You're two years younger
than me, you know!
Age has nothing to do with it!
I want new clothes, too!
Mine are old clothes, too, you know!
You get my stuff 'cause
you're my baby sister!
But I'm not your real sister!
We're not related by blood!
Nami!
Bell-mère!
So what if you're not
related by blood?!
Never say anything
stupid like that again!
Wh-Whatever...
You're not our real mother, either!
You'd be better off without us,
wouldn't you?!
That way, you could eat,
buy all the clothes you want,
and be free!
I wish...
I wish someone richer
had adopted me instead!
I-Is that so?
Fine, then! Do whatever you want!
If you hate this house that much,
then go live somewhere else!
Stop it, you two!
I will leave!
Nami!
Bell-mère,
the three of us are a family!
I'm sure Nami feels the same way!
She didn't mean what she said!
You're very responsible, Nojiko.
That was real immature of me.
Could you go bring Nami back for me?
I'll have an amazing dinner
ready before you get back!
Okay!
Okay, ma'am! How about this much?
What? Can't you do better than that?
Right over here!
Come see our low prices!
You can't beat my fruit when it comes to freshness!
So, coming here from the outskirts
of the village is "running away"?
That sure is nice and convenient!
Here. Drink up before it gets cold!
Bell-mère would be
happier if we were gone.
Why do you think that?
Having two children
costs lots of money,
and everyone in the village
hates her because of me.
You're old enough to consider
others now, huh?
Don't worry.
She was such a brat when she was your age, too.
Bell-mère was?!
Even now, she's still quite
a brat in the villagers' eyes!
Everyone in the village was stunned when that brat suddenly said
she was going to be a marine.
A marine?!
Bell-mère was a marine?!
Yeah.
"Pirates have to pay for
slaughtering innocent people!"
With those words,
she left the village.
She says she felt her time
to die had finally come.
Oh, well.
Is that your baby sister?
No. I don't know who she is.
You're still so innocent.
That was you, Nami.
When she saw you, Bell-mère
mustered up the will to live again.
It is a boat! I knew it!
On a stormy night like tonight?!
Who the hell could it be?!
Doctor! Call the doctor!
Bell-mère? Is that you, Bell-mère?!
– Bell-mère!
– What in the world happened?!
– These children! Whose...?!
– Doctor! They have terrible fevers!
They've been completely
worn out by the storm!
What?!
All right! But we need to tend to
those terrible wounds of yours, too!
Just hurry!
Please! Don't let them die!
Save them!
I beg of you!
What'd you just say, you troublemaker?!
I'm going to be their mother.
That's what I said.
You can't!
Don't do it! A punk like you
can't possibly raise children!
T-Take my advice! Give them
to a government institution!
I've already made up my mind!
I'm an adult now, too.
I was even in the Navy.
I think I'm a little more
upstanding now.
I'm going to be responsible for taking care of these kids.
I'm going to raise them
to be wonderful people
who won't succumb to
the world around them!
I'm going to live with these girls.
Nami and Nojiko saved my life.
You girls have a bond that goes
far deeper than a real family's.
Nami! I thought you'd be here!
N-Nojiko!
Bell-mère is waiting for us!
She's making a yummy dinner!
Okay!
I bet it's your favorite!
Omelets with tangerine sauce!
Yes!
Pirates, everyone!
Pirates are coming!
Pirates! Everyone hide!
– It's the Arlong Pirates!
– Arlong?!
That can't be!
What are fishmen from
the Grand Line doing here?!
Was the rumor about a split
in the Fishman Pirates true?
Nami! Nojiko!
Gen!
It's dangerous here!
Go hide in the woods!
Huh? But...
Go! Now!
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
you pathetic humans!
As of this moment, this village–
no, this island is now
under my control!
Listen up!
On this memorable day,
you will all buy your lives from me!
100,000 belly per adult.
50,000 belly per kid.
Those who can't pay... will die!
What do we do, Nojiko?
We can't pay that much!
But they might not spot our house!
You can't see it from the village!
How much did we get, brother?
Just over 25 million, I'd say.
Excellent!
Sounds like we'll have to pay 100,000 belly per person
every month for the rest of our lives!
100,000?! We can't
make a living that way!
Endure it for now!
We should just be glad no one
in the village has died.
All right! Time to go, brothers!
Arlong! There's smoke coming
from outside the village!
Okay!
All right, let's see!
That's too good!
Nothing's quite like Bell-mère's
special tangerine sauce!
Nami and Nojiko are gonna
leap out of their seats!
The smoke is coming from a house!
Oh? We almost missed it.
Damn!
Bell-mère!
Let's go! Let's collect our money!
Whoa, this is bad! The pirates...
...are headed to Bell-mère's house!
Hey! Nojiko and Nami are gone!
What?!
Ten more minutes for the duck in
the oven. And the stew is boiling.
This'll be a big blow
to our family budget.
But I guess I'll splurge, anyway!
Bell-mère's gonna...
Bell-mère's gonna be killed!
We can't just abandon Bell-mère!
Damn! Why did this have to happen?!
Don't jump the gun, Bell-mère!
Delicious! Nothing's quite like
my special tangerine sauce!
Ten more minutes for
the duck in the oven.
Got the side of vegetables,
and the stew is boiling.
Now just some fried rice omelets,
and everything's ready!
This'll be a big blow
to our family budget.
Oh, are they back?
It's open! Come on in!
Pardon me.
You've got bad luck. I'm a former marine.
What brings Grand Line pirates all
the way out to Cocoyashi Village?
What's so funny?!
Weak! You're weak! So weak!
Your inferior species is so powerless!
Let's escape with her
out the back door!
But the pirates might already be there!
We'll be fine!
Hold it!
– Doctor!
– You mustn't return home!
Wha...?!
Move! We have to save Bell-mère!
Nojiko! Nami!
Listen closely, you two!
This isn't the time to–
Actually, this is the perfect time...
I must tell you
a somewhat cruel story!
Doctor?
Bell-mère!
I can't do anything!
These guys are real monsters!
I'm gonna be killed!
Nojiko! Nami!
Bell-mère!
Don't waste your life for some
pathetic sense of justice!
Some battles aren't worth fighting!
Some issues can be solved with money!
Gen...
That's right, marine girl.
100,000 per adult. 50,000 per kid.
If you can pay for your whole family,
I'll let you live.
You should be thankful I'm telling you.
My whole family?
That's 200,000 in total.
How much do you have, all together?
Including what I've squirreled away...
a little over 100,000.
Hey! There's a meal for
three people in here!
Oh? A family of three, huh?
I almost forgot!
She invited me and my friend
to dinner tonight!
Come, Bell-mère.
Hurry and pay your amount.
Our delicious food's going to get cold!
Gen...
I hear you have 100,000.
Thank goodness you have enough!
Now everyone in the village is spared!
It's true.
The village register has no record
of her getting married or giving birth.
She's single.
Do you understand?!
There's no proof that you two
and Bell-mère are family!
Leave this island before
they take notice of you!
Escape across the sea!
There's no other way for
all three of you to survive!
I feel it's reckless to send you two
out to sea at such a young age!
There's a chance something
bad could happen!
But at least you'll have–
No.
I don't want to!
I... want to live in this village.
Is it because we're poor...
that I can't be Bell-mère's
daughter anymore?!
Why? Why?!
Thank goodness.
Now they won't kill anyone.
All right, we'll leave the village!
Nojiko!
Let's go! Because that means
Bell-mère gets to live!
Hold it.
Who said I paid for myself?
That 100,000 is for my two daughters.
I don't have enough for myself!
Bell-mère! What are you–
I'm sorry, Gen.
I just can't say
I don't have a family...
even... if it costs me my life.
How could she!
Yeah, maybe we're not
related by blood,
but we're a family.
I want to be their parent,
even if it's only in name.
They're... my kids.
Bell-mère!
Wait, you two!
I wish someone richer had
adopted me instead!
It was just a lie! I was lying!
Bell-mère!
I wanted... to buy you lots
more books and clothes.
I'm sorry!
I was never able to be
more of a mother to you!
That's not true!
We don't need anything!
Just don't die!
Stay with us forever!
I want you to see
the world map I draw!
Yeah... your map...
Make your dream... come true!
Live!
Bell-mère!
These're your girls, I take it?
Yeah, that's right!
Promise me you won't
lay a hand on them!
Of course! As long as
you die like a good girl!
Help us!
Now they're thirsty for blood.
Don't kill 'em. Just handle
'em as you see fit.
Perfect timing for our first
example to the others!
Now you die because of your worthless love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!