Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Funimation
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality-checking
alasta
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Sewil
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Subtitling
Sewil
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Big Sis!
Big Sis! What happened?!
Who is that? A man?!
What is a man doing in this land?!
What in the world happened?!
Oh I uhh...
He saw my back.
Then he'll have to die.
Huh?! H-How come?! I only saw her back!
I dunno why, but I could swear I've seen it somewhere before...
We would rather die than let anyone see what you saw on my back!
That thing? How come?
Who are you? How come?
Take everything you saw to the grave!
Love-Love Beam!
Huh? Slow-Slow?!
A Slow-Slow Beam?!
Oh no!
I'm turning slower! Slow...er...
Love-Love Beam!
Why won't he petrify?!
Does he not feel any excitement
from seeing me in the bath?!
That's not possible, Big Sis!
The beauty of your naked body would
charm anyone of any age or gender!
His fear of death must be
overpowering his wicked thoughts!
He's a pathetic yet lucky man!
I dunno what's going on
but I'm getting outta here!
I just wanna talk to someone important!
He jumped out from this height!
He won't get away!
Pistol Kiss!
Huh?! They don't bounce off!
They're not metal bullets?!
That man is an intruder!
Seize him, Kuja Pirates!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
A man?! What's a man doing here?!
Let's just catch him for now!
The Arena
Damn! Come off, you stupid things!
What are these iron rope-like snakes?!
We were too slow.
Let's just hope they don't
ask how he arrived here...
He's going to be killed, isn't he?
What's with this place?
There really isn't even one guy here.
Snake Princess!
Marigold-sama!
Sandersonia-sama!
Let me ask you this, man.
How and why did you come to this island?!
Seriously, I don't know either!
I suddenly went flying through the sky and before I realized it I was here!
Liar. You can't fool me with that ridiculous story.
You must be after something.
Well, you could give me a ship!
I'd appreciate getting a lift most of all,
but anyway there's a place
I need to leave for right away!
If you're the most important person here, then please! I want to set sail!
What nonsense is this?!
He must be plotting something!
You can't fool us!
I can keep fighting again and again!
How dare he speak so rudely and
tastelessly to the Snake Princess?!
He's appalling!
Don't think you can leave this place alive.
Your death is inescapable!
Please wait Snake Princess!
I-I don't think he's the
kind of person who can lie!
Marguerite!
Snake Princess.
E-Everything this man says is sincere.
He hardly seems like the type
to bring harm to our land!
Oh! You!
Yeah! Tell her for me!
A defense warrior?
My name is Marguerite!
The punishment of the crime of intruding into this kingdom,
which is forbidden to men, is death.
Why are you defending him?
I feel I owe him.
The person who let him into this country...
...was I!
Marguerite! Why?!
Snake Princess! W-We can explain!
Yes!
We found him in the forest
covered in mushrooms!
We thought he was from the village
and carried him here!
Sweet Pea! Aphelandra!
We're also responsible for
the crime of bringing him here!
That's right!
Stop you two!
I'm the one who suggested
bringing him to the village!
Does she know what this means?
Marguerite is way too honest!
Oh you guys!
You guys tried to kill me
but you're actually nice after all!
Only I'm guilty of letting
him into the country!
Marguerite!
It's all right.
Look up, honest Marguerite.
Love-Love Beam!
What the...?!
They did something stupid.
Hey, what happened to you?!
What happened?!
They turned into stone! Why?!
Hey, what did you do to them!?
They saved my life!
Yes, they have been punished for helping you.
Because of me!?
Wait! Turn them back to normal!
Bring Bacura to the arena!
Bacura!?
It's all over for that man now!
I told you to turn them back!
This place is the kingdom of the warriors, Amazon Lily,
where if you are powerful, you are beautiful.
You should die fighting.
We are gonna watch it.
That black panther's name is Bacura.
It is a carnivorous animal that was used as an executioner
by the empress of this kingdom for many generations.
After the execution, not even a single bone will remain.
What's gonna happen to these people?! Are they gonna turn back to normal?!
What a disrespectful way of speaking to the Snake Princess!
Go finish him, Bacura!
Bacura!
He's strong!
Bacura was defeated by a single hit?!
He didn't use Haki!
Then that was just brute strength?!
You guys are screwed up.
That woman...
Even after your comrades have been turned to stone by that woman,
why are you still laughing childishly?!
The savage is shouting at us!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
We feel sorry for those three, but what Snake Princess did wasn't wrong!
They're the ones to blame!
They broke the rules of our land!
Whatever I do...
...I will be forgiven.
If you ask why...
Indeed...
It's because I'm beautiful!
Snake Princess!
You think so, too, right?
You're pissin' me off.
Sister, get a hold of yourself!
This is just ridiculous!
There can't possibly exist a man that can't be captured by my charm!
I can't bear that man's existence!
How dare you say that to the Snake Princess?!
Hurry and execute him!
Execution!
Execution! Execution!
Go! Marigold! Sandersonia!
Take that man's head!
Yes! Leave it to us Big Sis!
These guys use devil-fruit powers, too?
Execution!
The younger sisters'
Snake Pit Dance is about to start!
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's
"Salamander" with my own eyes!
Youngest Sister Marigold Snake-Snake
Fruit Model King Cobra
And Sandersonia-sama's
"Eight-Headed Serpent"!
Middle Sister Sandersonia
Snake-Snake Fruit Model Anaconda
How magnificent she looks!
This is proof that they defeated
the monster, Gorgon, and took its powers!
Even after they were cursed, the sisters are still beautiful!
Cursed?
What are they talking about?
No matter how you look at it, you just ate a Devil Fruit!
Execution! Execution!
Execution!...
Perhaps I should swallow him whole...
Or squeeze him to death...
Don't tell me he's scared stiff!
Just stand there and die!
There!
They don't have any cracks, right?
You three wait here.
Sorry about this. Because of me you guys turned into stone.
If Chopper was here, I'd ask him to check on you right away.
It's just like when Robin and I were turned into ice by Aokiji.
You guys might be able to turn back to normal.
Shouldn't you be more concerned about your own safety instead of theirs?
Shut up! I can do whatever I want!
That man...
Is he trying to save Marguerite and the others?
That can't be!
He's already been sentenced to death!
Well then...
Anyway, I just gotta beat you guys up, right?
No way!
What did that boy just say?
He thinks he can beat the sisters up?
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
Men really are hilarious!
I can do that, right? Beat you up, I mean.
Yeah, sure you can.
If you haven't given up on your life yet, let me tell you something.
I wouldn't fall into the pit between
the seats and the ring if I were you!
I don't mind if it happens, but if you fall, you will be stabbed by the spikes below.
Then, let's start.
Kill him, Sandersonia, Marigold!
For the crime of intruding on this island of women!
For the sin of insulting me,
show him the art of the punishment!
I've been waiting for this!
Take that, and that, and that!
He's not bad at this huh?
Get him Marigold-sama!
What the...?!
Poison?! That was close!
It's a deadly poison! Too bad for you!
Rubber...
Stamp!
It bounced off!
That hurts!
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
See! He really is all bark and no bite!
But it's true that men stretch! Interesting!
Huh?! Am I not rubber anymore?!
No that's not it!
Then why do impact blows hurt?!
That's unfair.
Don't hog all the fun yourself, Mari.
I want to have some fun with him too!
Why does that hurt?! I'm made of rubber!
The guy with the battle-axe was like that, too...
Does that mean it's not a Devil Fruit power?
I take it you have powers too.
Damn!
But I take it you can't use Haki?
Most outsiders can't.
That's why you're weak.
A kick with the left foot.
Over here!
She predicted my move!
Snake Slam!
Yes!
That one didn't hurt.
Same as usual.
Rubber...
Gatling!
Snake Dance!
What amazing moves!
With Sonia-sama's Haki
there's no attack she can't dodge!
You're very straightforward.
I can read you like a book.
What's going on?!
She's guessing my every move!
Focusing entirely on offense
is nice and all but...
Snake Stick!
Ouch!
Don't forget that there are two of us!
He's falling into the pit!
That was close!
The Snake Princess put
her hair behind her ear!
Her loveliness knows no bounds!
This man is the very definition
of "nothing but talk."
I can't help but laugh.
Shut up you dumbass!
Oh my!
He spoke abusively to
the Snake Princess again!
Unforgivable! Hurry and kill him!
Sonia! Mari!
End that man's life at once!
To ensure there are no further outbursts...
from his filthy mouth!
It looks like playtime is over now.
Let's give the criminal despair and death!
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
What if she breaks?!
She saved my life you know!
We are going to break her.
You said she saved your life.
Then that's all the more reason to.
I feel bad for her, but this is your punishment.
Don't be stupid!
This duel is between me and you!
Damn! Let go!
You're the only one who
thinks this is a duel.
This is a public execution!
Just sit there and watch!
The emotional trauma you gave our
sister goes much further than this!
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
She's strong noble and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Hey! Stop it!
She looked up to you guys you know!
Everyone in this land does.
So I think this is what she would want!
The hell it is!
What are you stupid?!
Oh my. What crude language.
Here goes!
Three...
Hey! Stop!
Two...
It's no use.
One...
Marguerite!
I told you to stop, dammit!!
The warriors are fainting!
There's no way...
What a relief!
She isn't hurt anywhere!
Oh I guess you guys are sensible after all!
Just now... that was the Conqueror's Haki!
This can't be real!
Only one in a million people is capable of using the Haki of the chosen ones.
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
This boy has the qualities of a king,
capable of standing above all others!
He has the Conqueror's Haki just like me?
How can this be?!
Is he no mere boy after all?!
Just who is that guy?!
What's everyone blabbing about?
What's the big deal?
He doesn't realize he used Haki?!
I guess he hasn't figured
out how to control it.
Alright!
You showed me you're strong!
Now let's get on with the duel.