Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Halee
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing
Sewil
Raw provider
GS-Raws
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Kyros is fighting the mysterious gladiator, Ricky, who appeared out of nowhere!
Kyros wins!
After nine years, he has finally won three thousand consecutive fights! He is undefeated!
Kyros, the living legend, is the very definition of the word "invincible"!
Why did you fight without telling me...
King Riku?
I wanted to teach you a lesson. I was quite strong, wasn't I?
That said, you held back knowing it was me.
You're a failure as a beast.
Isn't this enough?
You've kept your own life locked away in this cage for nine years.
Dressrosa in Turmoil
Come out. There's a job I want to entrust to you.
Kyros, rather than regretting your past, you can move on and protect lives.
Isn't that a better way of life?
Yes!
Kyros, we're counting on you!
One year later
Kyros, thank you for all you do!
Dressrosa's Riku Royal Army Captain
Kyros (25 years old)
Kyros-sama!
You're quite popular, huh, Kyros-sama?
But you're still a murderer.
I can't fathom why my father would let you into the palace!
P-Princess!
Sister, don't bring up his old scars!
And then he makes you the captain of the army, with the job of upholding the law...
He must be crazy!
Sister...
You may have the rest of the country fooled, but not me!
Crown Princess of Dressrosa
Scarlett (Fifteen years old)
Someday, I'll expose you for what you really are!
Stay away from us! Do you understand?
But Sister, he's actually really...
Second in line (Younger sister)
Viola (Ten years old)
Hey, don't look!
His mind is obviously filthy!
But... I'm supposed to protect you...
No, thank you.
Scarlett-sama has been kidnapped!
It's pirates!
What happened to her escorts?
They've all been killed!
What?!
This is awful!
I-I'm so, so sorry!
I didn't mean to touch you!
Kyros! I was so scared!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
She's cooking?
What brought this about?
Oh, I couldn't...
What?! You resign as my daughters' bodyguard?
You couldn't be in love with Scarlett, could you?
What?!
N-No, of course not. Never!
Some of the citizens might give you their blessings, but this goes against the country's ethics.
That's just what the general masses are like.
Father! If I can't marry him, then...
I will die!
Scarlett-sama!
She died of a sudden illness. I'm sure she would have made a wonderful queen someday.
Scarlett.
Starting today, you are no longer a princess.
Society believes you are dead.
Yes.
I feel like I'm disrespecting all you've done for me, Your Majesty.
Indeed, this is unforgivable...
Or it would be, for anyone but you.
Kyros, this is completely unheard of.
Her name will be Rebecca.
Kyros, hold her.
She's your daughter.
I can't touch something so pure!
My hands are filthy! I don't want to corrupt her!
What a funny father you have, Rebecca.
Rebecca, you're like an angel.
I'll be with you. I'll always watch over you!
I'm your grandpa!
Grandpa!
Rebecca, how you've grown!
Father, will you take that mask off?
Kyros.
Gloves! I need my gloves!
You're such a cutie...
You're crying again.
The royal palace... it's burning.
What's happening to this country?
I'll go to the palace.
Scarlett, Rebecca, listen to me.
Father?
If the danger reaches here,
then wait for me at the red flower field.
I swear I'll come for you.
No!
What have you done to
this country and the king, pirate?!
The king burned the city. Didn't you see him?
His Majesty would never do such a thing!
Kyros!
Take this Sea Stone chain off me! I'm not a Devil Fruit user.
Kyros, your reputation precedes you.
Join me.
The king will be replaced, and the old royal family will be destroyed.
My men should already be going after your wife and daughter, who carry the blood of the king.
Watch closely.
Dressrosa's time under the Riku family is over.
He cut off his own leg?!
Kyros!
A toy?
That toy just ran off with the king -dasuyan!
I've been turned into a toy!
What's going on? Am I dreaming?
King Riku! It's me, Kyros!
I'm sorry. I've never heard that name before.
I'll forever be in your debt, strange, little toy.
Run, Scarlett, Rebecca!
Wait for me at the promised place!
Nobody knows my name.
I must get to the red flower field.
Scarlett and Rebecca are waiting for me!
Scarlett?
Scarlett!
Somebody's been shot!
The Riku Royal Army again?!
Why? Why didn't you wait for me?!
Of course.
I must have disappeared from your mind too.
Both our promise...
and our time together...
Scarlett!
Scarlett, hang in there!
Scarlett! Scarlett!
I don't know who you are...
but my daughter is waiting for me,
and she's famished...
Please...
It's me! It's Kyros!
Scarlett...
Scarlett!
How can this be our parting?
This is hell! It's too cruel!
With these tin arms,
I can't even feel your fading warmth!
Scarlett!
Soldier-san.
Soldier-san!
Oh, Viola-sama.
Are you alright?
We're in trouble. I can see our enemies coming at us from the first floor.
Unacceptable! So it was just someone impersonating the young master?
Straw Hat and the others must be on the second floor or higher!
Violet's blood was on the wall!
This is bad.
If we're about to be cornered into a fight,
maybe it'd be better for me to launch a sneak attack on Doflamingo right now.
Usoland and the others may not make it in time.
You're all pirates, huh.
I noticed it about Fraland and Usoland after a while.
You got a problem with that?
I used to be an outlaw myself.
As long as we share a common goal, I'll happily fight alongside you.
Corrida Colosseum
The ceiling in the Colosseum's basement is cracking!
Even before the finals,
hundreds of monsters were fighting here.
This day has taken its toll on the building.
Burgess's attacks are the final straw!
The entire place could collapse!
Surging Elbow!
That bastard!
Don't fire at us!
Good.
I'll tell you as many times as I have to, Rebecca.
It was I who shot and killed your mother, Scarlett.
Hey! My barrier can't block verbal attacks!
Soldier-san, I can't...
Mother, I'm hungry.
I'll go get us something to eat.
Okay.
I'm so frustrated, I can't even move!
Toys' House
Cyborg Franky has been brought down!
U... Usopp... you can do it.
Hurry and create some panic!
Usoland! Usoland!
The Underground Trade Port
There's an intense battle going on at the Commanders' Tower.
Hang in there, Usopp from the Straw Hat Pirates!
I've never even seen you, but hang in there, Usopp!
If you win, I'll be indebted to you forever!
Hang in there!
I don't want to be a toy for the rest of my life!
If you can turn me back, I won't hunt Straw Hat any more!
I'd gladly become your underling or anything!
Hang in there!
I'll give you as much money as you like! Just help me!
Trebol, hurry and get Sugar to the palace.
It's fine, Doffy. Nothing is gonna happen.
The enemy isn't even conscious anymore.
Usoland!
You can have this poisoned grape back.
The tatababasco...
That was our only hope!
You eat it...
and die.
Sugar! What are you doing?!
Get a grip!
S-Sugar...
fainted!
Su-
Sugar fainted!
I'm back to normal!
The toys are...
It keeps getting bigger!
I'm back!
Sugar!
Hey! Hey!
This is terrible!
What's that commotion about?
What?
What is going on here?
What?!
It turned into a weird old man!
What's happening to me?!
I'm back to normal!
Wait!
S-Sugar is... Doffy, I'm so sorry!
Quiet down, Trebol!
What about Sugar?
S-She's...
been knocked...
unconscious!
Hey...
Are you kidding me?!
All the workers we've gathered over the past ten years...
are reverting to humans!
The Hobby Hobby curse is being lifted!
I remember!
What on earth is going on here?!
Um, I mean...
What could be happening?! The toys...
The toys are turning into humans!
Some of them aren't even human!
Don't tell me Sugar has been...
Our ten years of work...
Sugar has been defeated by somebody -in!
That little brat is pathetic.
But...
I hope she's not hurt.
So hard-boiled!
Royal palace, please respond!
Everyone's calling in with emergencies!
Urgent report from the southern district, Sebio!
The toys assigned to work at the port have turned into pirates!
This is the eastern district, Carta!
The toys have become former Dressrosa soldiers!
Government workers!
Marines!
Officials from foreign countries!
Giant beasts!
Reporting from the Primula District!
They're real!
Hang in there, Usopp!
Usoland!
Thanks to you, we were able to become human again.
We did it...
Operation SOP is a success!
Everyone's so happy to be human again.
What's wrong, Onepoco?
Mommy, Onepoco's acting strange.
Onepoco!
One... poco?
No, you're...
I'm back!
Dear!
Papa! You're not Onepoco!
That's right, I'm your papa!
Papa!
How could we have forgotten you all this time?
It was a curse. I was afraid I'd spend my whole life as a toy!
Daddy, lift me up!
Up you go!
Damn, he's hiding again!
Where'd you go, stone man?!
Everyone!
Um...
I'm... alive...
The hero lives!
Usopp!
Usoland, we can't thank you enough!
It all... went just as planned.
So cool!
Now... my crew will handle the rest.
The battle... has only just begun.
Alright!
Take down Doflamingo!
Doflamingo tricked us all!
What are they talking about? He's a great king.
You don't know what he's really like.
He's the devil himself!
Kill Doflamingo!
Come out, Doflamingo!
We'll teach him how much we've suffered these ten years!
What's going on here, Issho-san?
Seems the tide has turned.
This country was covered by a much deeper darkness than I thought.
Bring down Doflamingo!
Who's that?!
Kyros!
I'd forgotten all about him.
What are you talking about?
Huh? Where's the tin soldier?
That's him.
Huh? But that's a human!
All the toys used to be human. They'd been erased from our memories!
Now that Sugar has been defeated, our memories have returned!
He is the former captain of the Riku Royal Army...
Kyros!
The mightiest warrior in the history of the Colosseum!
Isn't he the guy on that statue?
Yes, that's him. And he's also...
Rebecca's father!
Huh? But she said she'd never met him!
All these years while he'd been forgotten,
he had no way of telling her who he really was!
He's been watching over his beloved daughter for a decade!
He's stayed by her side every single day as a toy soldier!
Who are you?!
It's you!
Kyros?!
Yes!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting for ten years!
I'm here to save you!
I've come to restore the true Dressrosa!
Ten years.
We've had to endure your rule for ten years!
Doflamingo-sama!
Young master!
Damn you!
Mingo died!
But I wanted to send him flying...
I see them!
Over there! Damn you!
We've been spotted.
Fire!
Let's save Traf!
Corrida Colosseum
What's a gorilla doing in the spectators' seats?!
Run!
This is a disaster.
Trebol, you were supposed to keep an eye on Sugar!
You fool.
Hey, you done crying yet?
I ain't your babysitter.
You don't understand...
I...
I have a father!
That seems to have been this country's secret, Rebecca.
Everything has a core.
As long as you dig enough.
Now you're spouting confusing nonsense too, grand senpai?
The same goes for this arena.
It has a core.
How about we put an end to this match?
Dragon Claw Technique...
Dragon's Breath!
Amazing! Lucy's attack is unbelievably powerful!
The arena is sinking!
The arena exploded!
I'm losing my footing!
What have you done?!
Something came up. I'm going to win now.
Oh.
I heard a really loud noise from up there.
Hack?
Did he do something crazy again?!
He's on his way to the underground now.