Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
Then hurry and get ready!
Let's go outside!  Right now!
What?  R-R-Right now?
B-But I...
Well... I'm not...
You're not what?
This is all so sudden, so...
I'm not... well...
sure what I should do yet.
Please give me some time.
It's just a walk, what's the big deal?
Really!  Make it quick, then!
I really don't like you.
Okay, okay!
I'll wait, so hurry and make up your mind!
The Shirahoshi Kidnapping Incident and The Curse of the Mato Mato!
What have you guys done?!
Really,
you went way too far!
Indeed!  Apologize for your actions!
You were the ones who started this fight!  We're all in this together, you idiots!
We just wanted to threaten them and run away!
And I just wanted to go sightseeing and shopping.
Well, it's in the past now, so what can we do?
Don't complain!
"What can we do"?!  You think that's good enough?!
Just dropping by Fishman Island and then casually occupying Ryuuguu Palace...
How ruthless can you get?!
Ow...
So should we just have let them arrest us?!
I keep telling you, we should have just threatened them and fled!
First off, we don't know how we could escape.  Second, Luffy's not here!
Yeah, that's right, Luffy's gone!
Where did he go?
Where indeed?
We're really in a hurry here.
So don't be mean, and just tell us.
Yeah, we need to find Luffy!
Where is the treasure chamber?
Cut it out!
What?  Why?
Why are you acting all innocent?!  Consider our situation!
Now, everyone!
In this difficult time, let's sing a song and be happy!
Come on!
It'll work out somehow, it'll work out somehow.
And even if it doesn't, we'll die someday anyway!
Yeah!
You shut up too, Soul King!
Neptune-sama, are you alright?!
I can't believe that the champion of the sea, King Neptune, would end up like this.
My bad hip acted up
all of a sudden, so I couldn't fight.
I-I've really gotten old.
Quite a blunder -jamon!
Sorry!
We should have moved quickly and burst their bubble,
turning it into an underwater fight,
but they managed to get rid of all the water instead!
What are we to do?
Listen up, you scum!
Once the three brothers of the Neptune Army, Prince Fukaboshi, Prince Ryuuboshi,
and Prince Manboshi get back here,
you're going to regret this!
In any case, we can't stay on Fishman Island any longer.
Where is the Sunny?
We need to gather everyone up and set sail.
But the Sunny's coating was torn off
as we entered the island.
The Log Pose has been acting strange too.
Ever since we came here,
it hasn't shown any sign of stabilizing.
You're hopeless.  You can't navigate
the New World with such a simple Pose.
You ignorant pirates.
Huh?  This won't work?
What do you mean?
I'll tell you if you untie me.
Ding-dong.
That must be Prince Fukaboshi!
Akkamanbo!  Yay!  Yay!
Hmm?  How peculiar.
What could the guards be doing?
Click.
Hello, who is this?
Hey!  Why are you answering?!
Prince Fukaboshi!
Help us!
Be quiet, you two!
Prince Ryuuboshi!
Prince Manboshi!
Oh my!  Brother, something
must have happened -la-ti-do!
I think so too!  Are Father and Shirahoshi alright?!
It's me, Fukaboshi.  What is going on in there?
Lower the connecting channel right now, and let us in.
And what will happen if we do that?
No can do!
H-Hey!  What are you saying?!
Explain the situation to them!
That's right!  In that case, tie me and Caimie up too!
We don't want to be seen as your partners in crime!
Zoro-chin, you're scaring me!
Help us!  Prince Fukaboshi!
Are you, by any chance, one of Straw Hat's companions?
Fukaboshi!  He's the swordsman with the three swords from the Straw Hat Crew...
Pirate Hunter Zori!
It's Zoro!
Father?!
You've even got Father there?!
You hear that?  We've got plenty of hostages, including Neptune!
If you want them to live,
then start making preparations for us to set sail!
What we'll need is our ship, the Sunny, re-coated.
We don't know where it is, so you guys find it.
Also, the rest of our crew.
One gloomy woman.  One robot.
One raccoon dog, and one pervy water imp.
Oh, Zoro!  One billion beli, too.
Cut it out, damn it!
A pervy water imp!  How fitting!
That fits him perfectly!
This is no time to be laughing!
Pervy water imp!
Come on!  At least make a jab at the "gloomy woman" comment too!
I understand your conditions.
I will make arrangements for you and your crew
to leave this kingdom safely.
However, you must return all of the hostages unharmed!
Sure.
Brother!
We have no other choice.
The connecting channel is the only way
into Ryuuguu Palace.
Everywhere else, it's protected by a thick bubble layer
that we can't break through.
May I say one more thing, Zoro-kun?
I'd rather not tell you in this situation,
but I cannot dishonor my debt to Jinbe.
What is it?
From the former Warlord, Sea Knight Jinbe, to Straw Hat Luffy.
He wanted me to tell you this once you reached the island.
I have two messages to pass on.
Jinbe, huh?
Jinbe?!
Boss Jinbe.
Oh yeah, he did say that he was friends with Jinbe.
Ah, the man who was in the newspaper together with Luffy-san?
Despite being a pirate, he's an amazing man who everyone on the island trusts.
Luffy isn't here right now, but I'll pass the message on to him.
Say it.
"Don't fight Hody."
The second one is...
"I will be waiting for you in the Sea Forest."
That is all.
Click.
The Sea Forest... Hody...
Hey, did you hear?!
They really did it!
Apparently the Straw Hat Pirates have occupied Ryuuguu Palace!
What?!
What's their objective?!
No way!  And they seemed like such nice people.
How could they?
I just can't believe it!
Can't believe it!
No, I can totally believe it!
You can't believe it, can you?
So what if I can't believe it?
Kidnapping the girls from the bay,
and considering the future that was predicted...
It has to be them!
Things are progressing in that direction!
They've finally shown their true colors!
Apparently two of Straw Hat's companions are in the back room of the Mermaid Café.
The guards just went to capture them.
What is this creature?!
He transformed?!
Sanji is still recovering!  Don't touch him!
What do you mean "come to Ryuuguu Palace"?!  You're just planning to arrest us, aren't you?!
Hey... you guys...
Sanji!  You mustn't move around yet!
Hey!  Are you done thinking yet?
Let's go outside!
I'm so sorry.
I really... can't.
Why not?!  You said there were places you wanted to go, right?
But if I do something so selfish,
I'll be causing trouble for everyone in the castle.
If I'd been locked up in here for ten years,
I'd have gone crazy.
This is to thank you for the food.
I'll be there with you, so where do you want to go?
Uh... Well...
To the Sea Forest!
No, but...
that's just a dream.
I couldn't possibly do something
as selfish as breaking out of here.
Why are you starting to cry just from saying where you want to go?!
I-I'm sorry.
I had to gather up so much courage just to say it.
Please don't be mad at me!
You're scary, Luffy-sama!
You're such a pain!
What?!  What was that loud noise?!
Is he throwing something at us again?
What a rude guy.
What's that?
W-What is that sound -jamon?
Could it be Decken's doing?!
It's coming from Koukaku Tower -jamon!
S-S-Shirahoshi is in danger!
A-Are the guards with her?!
No, they're all tied up here!
How can this be?!
Hey, pirates!
Go and ensure the princess's safety in place of the guards!
Huh?  What're you talking about?
But Neptune-sama!
That means letting them know about the princess!
What choice do we have?!
Koukaku Tower is on the northeast side of the palace!
All of you, go there right now!
Why do we have to take orders from our hostage?
Silence!  Shirahoshi is my only daughter!
For that reason, she's constantly being targeted!
If anything happens to my daughter, I will drive you into the bottom of the deep sea!
So basically, she is the Mermaid Princess?  Am I right?
If so, I shall go to her as soon as I can!
And then!
I wonder if she will show me her panties?
Hey, wait, Brook!
Oh, what are we to do?!
He dashed off with indecent motives!
Now the princess is in danger
for an entirely different reason!
Wait, skeleton!
You can keep me tied up, but please take me with you!
Koukaku Tower is under my jurisdiction.
If anything happens to the princess,
I will never be at peace.  Even in death!
You...
You must...
really love her, right?
Don't be absurd!
How shameless!
No!
Sanji-san, I will be going there first if you don't mind!
I've always wanted to go to the Sea Forest.
All this time, throughout these past ten years.
But... everyone warns me that
it's too dangerous to leave the tower.
So I'm scared of going outside.
Luffy-sama, will you really take me there?
Sure.
Will you really protect me?
Leave it to me!  It'll be fine!
Hey!  If you're gonna cry, then I won't take you anywhere!
Besides, to be honest, it's more like you'll be taking me there.
I can't swim, after all.
I-I'm so sorry.  I'm just too happy.
You really are a crybaby, huh?
And a weakling.
But if we go outside, you'll stand out so much that you'll get spotted right away.
Right... I'm so sorry.
So I have an idea to deal with that!
Mermaid Princess!  Are you alright?
Hey, skeleton!  Look at the side of the tower!
Huh?
That's insane!  Those aren't the usual knives or axes that come flying!
That sound was human pirates crashing into the tower!
How bizarre!
That Vander Decken is insane!
What?!  V-Vander Decken?!
This isn't good!  They're getting up!
This means... Enemy soldiers have invaded the impenetrable Ryuuguu Palace!
This is a sneak attack!  The king is in danger!
The princess is in danger!
The sounds of the attacks have stopped, right?
Let's go, weakling!
Y-Yes!
I'm counting on you, Megalo!
Go, shark!
Megalo!
Luffy-san!
To the Sea Forest!
W-W-Wait!  Luffy-san?!
Hey!  Wait, Megalo!
Where are you going?!
Father, brothers, and everyone in the castle...
Please forgive me!
I'm going out without permission!
I'll be back in time for dinner!
Let's go for a walk!
What are you doing, Megalo?!
You left the door to Koukaku Tower wide open.
What if something happens to the princess?!
Pirate!  Hurry and see to the princess's safety!
You're working my bones too hard.
She's gone!  Princess Shirahoshi is gone!
What?!  The Mermaid Princess is not here?!
This is awful!  A national crisis!
When did this happen?  Who could have done this?!
She's been kidnapped!
Kidnapped?!
Princess!
Oh, princess.
She's been kidnapped, has she-
Hey!  What are you doing?!
The channel that connects
Ryuuguu Palace and Fishman Island...
Where is the switch to open it?!
What?  Switch?
Either way, we must hurry back to Neptune-sama, Skeleton!
We need to report this to him immediately!
We've got no choice.
Following their orders is our only chance of survival.
Tell us already!
Who are "they"?
If you don't, they'll kill us!
Kill you?!
What are you talking about?!
Listen up, pirates working for Hody Jones!
You're in luck!
You get to be a part of this historic event!
Vander Decken...
Isn't he the captain of the Flying Dutchman?
The captain of the cursed ghost ship?
Don't worry, I'm just his descendant.
I'm not a ghost.
But I, too, have been cursed.
I'm a fishman, yet I can't swim.
Let me show you the power of the devil
that I gained with the Mato Mato curse!
Alright, you'll do.  Human, come forth.
Hody!
Are you really going to do this?!
Stop this madness!
It's him!  Hachi-san!
It's Hachi-san!
It's Hacchan-san!
Hachi-san.
The Energy Steroid is just a drug that destroys your body!
Why are fishmen trying to destroy Fishman Island?!
Don't underestimate
the champion of the sea, Neptune!
Hachi-san, give it a rest.
I have no interest in your opinion.
I can hardly believe that
you were once a member of the crew I looked up to.
You've become weak.
Your time has passed.
I need Fishman Island if I want to teach
the humans a lesson, and Neptune is in my way.
You guys were the ones who taught us
that we are the superior species.
But Arlong-san lost!
Decken!  Hyouzou!  Why are you siding with him?!
You refused Arlong-san's invitation back then,
so why are you helping these young fools now?!
Helping?  I'm just working here because he pays me.
Arlong didn't want to part with his cash
so he couldn't employ me.
Too bad Arlong could only obtain a swordsman of your caliber.
So you're Hachi from Arlong's crew, huh?
Now that sure takes me back!
Your captain once tried to recruit me as his underling.
But I couldn't agree to that.
I could never let someone boss me around.
Hody here understands that.
Arlong-san's ambition and his
ability to act on it were admirable.
However, he was all brawn and no brains.
Even if we wanted to, we were too young to become pirates while you were out raising a ruckus at sea.
And now everyone who grew up in those days
has assembled here.
So our resolve is strong, and we've learned from our predecessors' mistakes.
I am the man who will carry on Arlong's will.
And you, a former member of the crew I admired, are saying that you have a problem with my plan?
That's really discouraging, Hachi-san!
And while we're on the subject, Straw Hat Luffy is here.  The very man who shattered your ambitions.
Don't you even care about that?!
He called me his friend,
even though I used to be a member of Arlong's crew!
The three of you are my friends!
I owe Straw Hat Luffy my life!
I would go to meet him right now...
but while Arlong's will lives on,
I couldn't possibly face him!
Humans are your friends?!  You piece of trash!
I'm utterly disappointed in you!
I'm locked on to you, Hachi.
Have you forgotten how pirates do things?
If you have a problem with someone,
you'll have to resolve it with violence...
I presume!
Where'd he throw it?
When I touched you just now, you became my target.
Whatever I throw and wherever I throw it...
it will change its course like a hunting bird,
and head straight for its target: You!
It looked like he threw that knife in some random direction, and...
It hit the octopus fishman!
The Mato Mato curse...
Of course, there are several ways to stop it.
Why don't we give it a try?
Stop!  Don't throw all those arrows.
I've heard rumors about your ability.
Hey, Hody, he'll kill me at this rate!
Please, stop Decken!
Didn't he just tell you, Hachi-san?
Vander Decken is not my underling.
We're two pirates who have made an alliance on equal terms.
Besides, you're just a nuisance.
You damn coward!
Damn it!
Here we go!
Good!  Run away, run away!
But wherever you go...
Wherever you go...
Wherever you go... they'll chase you down!
If only I could make it outside.
Alright, now I can escape!
Those arrows won't be able to follow me in the water.
Damn!  So it doesn't matter
if they're in the water or not?!
Stay away!
The number of targets I can keep in my memory is the same as my number of hands.
Two of them.
My right hand, that I haven't washed for ten years,
stores the memory of when I touched
the princess of Ryuuguu Palace.  Shirahoshi herself!
You get it?!  All the love and weapons I throw...
will pursue my target even into the depths of Hell!
That is my power!
Amazing!
So that's how you've been able to keep up
your insidious stalker crush...
without being seen or caught by the Neptune Army!
Indeed!
What a cunning man!
Cunning!  Cunning!
Now then, human pirates.
You understand Decken's ability now, right?
So now it's time to begin phase one of our plan.
They say it's impossible to
break into Ryuuguu Palace...
but one man has been able to
throw things in there for the last ten years.
Namely, Vander Decken.
In other words, this plan consist of you being the objects thrown by Decken...
and flying straight toward the Mermaid Princess in Ryuuguu Palace.
Though, you'll actually crash into the tower's hard walls.
Then, once you're inside Ryuuguu Palace, you'll open the gates from the inside,
and let us in.  That is your mission.
No way!  If you do that...
We'll crash into the walls and die!
Indeed you will.
Which is why we're using the lives of you worthless humans!
Down here, you're worth less than slaves!
Those who survive the crash will carry out the mission!
If it goes well, I will set you free.
If you refuse the mission, then...
I will throw you outside the bubble right now,
you inferior species!
N-No way!  If you do that, we'll drown!
In that case, you just have to take your chances on the method that leaves some slight chance of survival!
Go!
Today,
is the beginning of a new chapter in history for us fishmen!
It starts when we conquer the Ryuuguu Kingdom!
Yeah!
I'm coming now, Shirahoshi!
And now we return to the present.
Wait!
I will not wait!
Hurry, skeleton!  To the king!
Wait!  We have to open the way...
Or Hody will kill us!
Hey, Sanji!
He ended up...
beating up all the soldiers.
We hadn't done anything wrong!
Well, they wanted to put me in handcuffs!
Look!  Everyone is looking at us so coldly!
Their eyes are like the fish of the deep sea!
Oh, quit whining.  It's too late now.
You should have thought about that
before beating them up!
You took out half of them too!  With your Kung Fu!
You were pretty strong.
E-Even if you say that, I'm not happy at all, you jerk!
The voice of a lady!
Someone covered in blood has washed ashore!
Aren't you from the Fishman District?!
What happened?!
Someone, get a doctor!
I'm a doctor!
Hachi?!
What happened to you?!
Hey, Hachi, it's us!
How did you get all those injuries?!
What happened?!
It's you guys.
I'm glad I found you.  Is Straw Hat here?
He's not.  Wait, I'll help you.
Gather your crew.  Hurry!
You're better off...
not getting involved in this island's affairs any more.
Leave Fishman Island.
The New Fishman Pirates are going to
attack this island!
Ryuuguu Kingdom will be destroyed!
Neptune-sama!
She's been kidnapped!
The princess was carried off by someone or another!
Also, a group of pirates came raining down by the tower.
Anyway, we are under attack!  Under attack!
Kidnapped?!  Who could have taken Shirahoshi?!
An enemy attack, now?
What are we going to do?
Why now?!
We're already attacking the palace ourselves!
W-What should we do?!
On second thought, don't answer that!
We'll cut them down.
I said don't answer!
If we're going to survive...
We have to open the gate to the palace!
H-Here they come!
Aren't you gonna come out of the shark now?
N-No, I'd rather stay inside.
How does it feel,
being outside for the first time in ten years?
My heart won't stop racing.
I have done something really awful.
Just going outside isn't bad!
You're so weird.
Is this...
what they call an "adventure"?
Yeah.
If you're this excited, then it's an adventure alright!
You said something about the Sea Forest, right?
What is that?  Is it a fun place?
A grave...
There's a grave there that I haven't visited once since it was built.
Not once in all these ten years.
It's the one place I've wanted to go to the most!
Has it really been ten years...
since the assassination that took place in broad daylight, throwing Fishman Island into chaos?
How time flies.
The princes have grown into fine warriors...
and Princess Shirahoshi is still inside that tower.
But nobody has forgotten about your ideals,
Queen Otohime.
The New Fishman Pirates arrive at the Ryuuguu Palace.
While there, Zoro comes into conflict with Hody.
Meanwhile, Luffy and Shirahoshi encounter Vander Decken on their way to the Sea Forest.
Next Time on One Pace:
The Beginning of the Vengeful Plan!
Zoro vs. Hody!