Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
Soundtracking
Halee
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Quality Control
JT-421
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
JT-421
Pepperjack
TheFVGuy
His final words lured all sorts
of adventurers to the sea.
Timing
PhosCity
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
My treasure?
It's yours, if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Translation
Crunchyroll
DemonRin
Everything is right where I left it!
Special Thanks
One Pace Team's
Best Canadian
CyberLariat
One Pace Team's
Best Canadian
CyberLariat
Now pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
The Dawn of an Adventure
Hey, Luffy!
What are you trying to do?!
Monkey D. Luffy
Village Boy
I'm serious, and I'm pissed off!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Get on with it already...
whatever it is you’re up to!
Ouch!
You idiot!
What'd you do that for?!
Guys! A toast!
To Luffy's guts and to another
successful voyage!
Ah, it didn't hurt one bit!
Liar. You can’t pull
dumb stunts like that.
I'm not lying!
I'm not scared of getting hurt!
So, take me on your next voyage!
I wanna be a pirate too!
Like you'd ever make it as a pirate!
It's a fatal flaw for a pirate to be an anchor!
"Red-Haired" Shanks
Pirate Captain
I'll be just fine
if I don't fall overboard!
And besides, I'm a good fighter!
I've been training,
so my punches are like pistols!
Pistols? Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
Luffy!
What's eating you?
Loosen up and have some fun!
Yeah! Being a pirate is about having fun!
The sea is boundless!
There are tons of islands to explore!
It's all about freedom!
Guys, stop filling his head with nonsense.
But it's all true! Right?!
C'mon, Boss, why not take him
on just one voyage?
I'd second that.
Sure, but one of you stays behind.
Good chat, kid! Let's drink!
Weren't you on my side?!
Really, you're just too young, kid.
Maybe in 10 years, I'll give you a chance.
Shanks, you big jerk!
I'm not a little kid!
Hey, now. Simmer down
and have some juice.
Oh! Thanks!
– See?! You are just a kid!
– No fair, Shanks!
I'm so sick of this!
Luffy, try to understand
where the boss is coming from.
The first mate!
The reality is,
he's the head of a pirate crew.
He knows better than anybody
how tough and dangerous pirating can be.
You get it?
He's not trying to break your spirit.
No, I don't get it!
Shanks just likes making fun of me!
Anchor!
See?!
I see you're having fun as usual.
Yeah, I just love teasing this kid.
Luffy, would you like something to eat too?
Yeah! Put it on my treasure tab!
The treasure tab again?
That's fraud, you know?
No, it's not!
I'll pay her back once I
become a pirate and find some treasure!
I'm counting on it.
Shanks.
What's up?
How much longer
are you gonna dock at this village?
Let's see...
After a couple more voyages,
we'll leave this village for good
and head north.
A couple more voyages, huh?
So I gotta learn to swim
before you leave!
Sure thing. Knock yourself out.
Pardon us.
So, these are "pirates."
Looks like a sorry bunch to me.
We're mountain bandits.
But we ain't here to bust up the place.
We'd like some booze.
My apologies.
I just ran out of alcohol.
Then what are these
pirates drinking? Water?
I'm afraid I served
the last of it to them.
My apologies.
Looks like we drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this.
It hasn't been opened yet.
Hey, wise guy.
Just what do you take me for?
One bottle ain't even
enough for a nightcap!
The floor's all wet!
Take a look.
My head’s worth eight million belly.
I've killed 56 people,
all of ‘em comedians like you.
You'd better watch yourself.
But we're mountain folk and you're seafarers;
I doubt we'll see each other again.
Sorry about the mess, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
No! Leave that to me!
Seems you like to clean.
Maybe you'll find this more fulfilling.
Later, cowards!
Captain, are you all right?
Oh. No worries.
– Talk about lame, Boss!
– He got you good!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight back?!
You can't call yourself a pirate—or even a
man—if you laugh after something like that!
I get where you're coming from,
but he only got some booze on me.
There's no need to get bent out of shape.
Hey, wait, Luffy.
I've had it!
I don't wanna be a coward like you!
His arm stretched!
He didn't...!
What's going on?!
It's gone!
What?!
The Gum-Gum Fruit
we stole from our enemy!
Luffy! Please tell me...
you didn't eat a fruit like this.
I-I did... It tasted pretty bad.
That was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
It's a rare treasure of the sea
known as a devil fruit!
You gain a rubber body after eating it,
but you lose the ability the swim for life!
What?! No way!
You dumbass!
Gimme a fish, old fish shop guy!
Hey, Luffy!
I heard they sailed off without you again!
I don't mind!
Becoming a rubber man is way cooler
than going on some dumb voyage.
It's been a while since the captain
and his crew set out to sea.
I bet you miss them.
No way!
They're still not off the hook!
I can't believe I thought Shanks and
his crew were awesome pirates.
Really? I think it's
much cooler to shrug it off
and laugh after someone
humiliates you like that.
Makino, you just don't get it.
There are times when a man's gotta fight.
Maybe I don't get it.
Make way!
Those damn pirates ain't here today, huh?
We were in the area,
so we decided to drop by.
Don't just stand there!
Booze! Now!
Mayor, we have a problem!
What's wrong, Makino?
Luffy's in trouble with the mountain bandits!
Let go! Dammit!
Weird body ya got here...
Apologize already!
– What kind of creature is he?
– You bastard!
Dammit! You're gonna pay!
He might fetch a good price.
How stubborn.
Brat!
Did I say something to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Get your foot off of me!
Let the boy go!
I beg you!
I have no intention of fighting you,
but I'm willing to pay.
Spare the boy's life!
Leave it to a senior citizen
to know the ways of the world.
But no.
It's too late for that now.
After all, he pissed me off.
No...
I've had it up to here
with this rubber runt!
You're the bad guys here,
you mountain apes!
Forget selling him.
Let's just kill him!
– Luffy!
– Please! Let him go!
No one came to greet us at the port.
So, this is why.
They're the mountain bandits from before.
Captain!
Luffy, I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols.
Shut up!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
You'd best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and we'll
blow your head off, coward.
He said no closer!
Don't make me pull the trigger!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
you've put your life on the line.
The hell're you talkin' about?
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
N-Now you've done it!
These bastards fight dirty!
"Dirty"?
Cut the crap.
Think you're dealing with saints or something?
You're staring down a crew of pirates!
Shut up! This is none of your
damn business anyway!
Listen, bandits.
It doesn't matter if I'm doused
with alcohol or covered in food,
most of the time I'll just laugh it off.
But know this!
Hurt a friend of mine for any reason,
and you'll answer to me.
Shanks.
Answer to you, huh?!
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this.
Shouldn't be a problem.
Come on! Bring it!
That burns!
Don't get cocky, bandit.
You'll need a whole battleship
if you wanna challenge us.
So strong!
Unbelievable.
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
You're a wanted man, though.
A smokescreen!
– Come with me, brat!
– Let me go! Let me go!
Luffy!
Crap! I let my guard down! Luffy's gone!
What do we do, guys?!
Quit freakin' the hell out, Boss!
It won't take us long to find them!
I can't believe this guy...
I made a clean getaway!
I got no use for you anymore!
You bastard!
Later!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum,
but I couldn't even hit them once!
Dammit! Dammit!
You see the looks
on those pirates' faces?!
Pirates ain't nothin' but cowards.
Cut that out!
Quit making fun of Shanks and his crew!
Calm down, Luffy!
Stop making fun of Shanks and his crew!
Stupid kid.
W-What the hell?!
Help...!
It's gonna eat me!
Help!
Shanks...
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino-san told me everything.
You stood up for us.
C'mon, don't cry!
You're a man, right?
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm.
It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're not hurt.
Luffy finally understood the reason
Shanks never took him on a voyage:
the sea was harsh, and he was powerless.
But more importantly,
he discovered Shanks' greatness.
He aspired to become a man like him one day.
Shanks, you're not coming back?
Nah. We were able to stay awhile,
but it's time to part ways.
Right. I'm not gonna
ask you to take me this time.
I've decided to become a pirate on my own!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'd never make it as a pirate!
I will!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
and we'll find the world's greatest treasure,
then I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Oh? You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Come bring it back to me someday,
once you've become a great pirate!
He's got quite a future.
Yeah, he's so much
like the kid I used to be.
Set sail!
The boy's adventure would begin
10 years later from this very port.
10 Years Later
Well, Mayor, he's finally off.
He's disgracing our village
by becoming a pirate!
What a nice day to set sail!
What the...?
If it isn't our local sea monster.
You don't know who you're messing with.
Here's a technique 10 years in the making!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
We'
A
re go
re go
That'll teach ya, damn fish!
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
Alright! Let's go!
are
on
the
cruise!
I'm gonna be...
We
are!
king of the pirates!
We
are!