Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
Editing
Galaxy9000
Sewil
Timing
Graphics
Datenshi
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
QC
Feeso
Galaxy9000
Mr. Luffy
Sewil
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
The Town of Celebration
All right! Done!
This is the man that fell
from the sky, Mr. Snow Barrel!
That's such a crude snowman...
What?!
Look at my soulful artwork, the Snow Queen!
Whoa! That's incredible!
Okay then! Snow Barrel Punch!
What the hell are you doing?!
Ahh! Mr. Snow Barrel!
How dare you...!
How come they're so energetic
when it's this cold?
Damn you! Damn you!
Nami-san! How much snow shoveling
of love would you like me to do?!
Please continue until
it stops snowing, Sanji-kun!
Yaay! Nami-san!
Hey, you. Doesn't this ship have a heater?
I'm cold.
Shut up! You guys aren't guests!
Go help shovel snow or something!
Lightning?!
What on earth is going on
with the weather around here?!
It was sunny up until recently.
The next moment, it started snowing,
and now lightning...
The seasons, as well as the weather,
go around randomly.
It's just like what Crocus-san said.
It seems that you guys are
clueless about the Grand Line.
You haven't been steering for a
while now. Is that really okay?
I just checked the direction.
Ahhhh!
Wh... What?
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Nami-san?!
Ahhh... No way!
Turn the ship around 180 degrees! Hurry!
180 degrees?! Why're we going back?!
Did you forget something?
The ship has turned around and
is going in the opposite direction!
When I looked away from the
log pose for a second...!
The waves were calm earlier...
Are you really a navigator?
In this sea, you can't trust the winds,
sky, waves, clouds... anything...
The only thing that doesn't change is
the direction that the log pose points.
Do you understand that?
Stop bossing me around in those
cozy blankets and go help already!
Brace the yard!
Receive the wind from the starboard!
Turn the ship 180 degrees to the left!
--Usopp! Take care of the lateen sail!
--Got it!
--Sanji-kun! Take the helm!
--Leave it to me, Nami-san!
You guys! I'm counting on you!
She's such a slave driver.
Hey, wait! The wind has changed.
No way!
It's the first spring gale!
Why?!
Don't just sleep there while
the snow accumulates on you!
Hey! I saw a dolphin jump
over there! Let's go there.
You keep quiet!
The waves are getting high!
I see an iceberg in the
10 o'clock direction!
Nami-san! It's getting foggy!
What the hell's with this sea?!
W-W... we're gonna crash!!
Hey! Water's leaking at
the bottom of the ship!
We have to patch it right away!
Got it!
The clouds are moving fast!
Unfurl the sails!
That wind is too strong!
If we take it directly, we'll overturn!
Everyone! Eat this!
Let's gather our strength!
You're eating too much!
Oh crap! The sail is gonna be torn!
Forget about things up here.
Go fix the bottom of the ship!
There's another part of the
bottom of the ship damaged!
Dammit!
Ahhh, that felt good.
Hey, no matter how nice the weather is,
you guys shouldn't be so lazy.
We'd better be on the right track.
You...
Hm?
Why're you guys on this ship?
You're slow!
We're heading to their town right now.
It's called Whiskey Peak.
You mean we're taking them back?
We don't owe them anything.
Right, we don't.
Well, not like it matters to me...
Yeah, your faces say that
you're thinking bad thoughts.
What were your names again?
I-I'm Mr. 9.
I'm Miss Wednesday.
Right... Something has been bothering
me ever since I first heard your names...
I feel like I've heard them
somewhere before, or maybe not...
Well, either way...
How dare you sleep
comfortably all this time...
You kept sleeping no matter how
many times we tried to wake you up...
What?!
Don't let your guard down, everyone!
We don't know what else might happen.
I was finally able to realize
the danger of this sea just now.
I was able to understand the
reason why it's called the Grand Line.
There's no doubt about it since
my navigation skills don't work at all.
How blunt... Are we gonna be okay?
We'll be fine! Things will
still work out for sure.
In fact...
Look! Our first journey is over.
It's an island!
So this is Whiskey Peak...
But it's really a funny looking island.
Those cacti are huge!
Hm?
Well then, we'll be leaving now.
Thanks for taking us home, honeys.
If we're linked by fate, we'll meet again!
Bye bye, baby!
Huh?
They're gone...
Who on earth were they?
Who cares! We're landing!
There's a river at the front.
Looks like we can go inland by ship.
I-isn't it possible that there're
monsters or things like that?
It's definitely possible.
This is the Grand Line.
If we come across monsters,
we can just leave the island.
Hold on a sec.
Don't forget that we have to stay on this island for a certain period of time.
Why?
Unless we store the magnetism
of this island in the log pose,
we can't go to the next island.
Since each island requires a different
amount of time to store the log,
some islands require only several
hours while others require days.
T-Then even if this is a monster island that we want to escape from right away,
it's possible that we have to stay
here for days until the log is stored?
That's right.
Well, we can think about that
when it happens. Let's go already!
Luffy's right. Let's go.
It's not worth thinking about it.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect Nami-san.
H-hey, wait. Listen, everyone.
My chronic illness is suddenly...
My "do not go to the island" disease is...
Then we're going in.
Listen. Make sure you're
prepared to run as well as fight.
No...
Ah, well... like I said,
my chronic illness is...
Well, I guess you're not listening...
I wonder what'll appear...
Hey, it's a pirate ship.
Pirates are here!
Huh? Something's moving.
Humans? Humans are there!
Welcome to the Grand Line!
Welcome to our town!
To the welcoming town, Whiskey Peak!
F... Far from monsters,
we're being welcomed!
What's going on?
Pirates! Welcome to our town!
Hurray for the heroes on the sea!
Whoa! There're lots of cute girls!
Ahh! Look this way! They're handsome!
Maybe pirates are people's heroes after all.
Heeeey!
Welco...
Ma-ma-ma...
Welcome.
Whiskey Peak Mayor
Igarappoi
My name is Igarappoi.
I'm the mayor of Whiskey Peak.
Okay. I'm Luffy. Nice to meet you.
Pops, you went overboard on curling your hair.
Whiskey Peak is a town that thrives
on making liquor and music.
Hospitality is the pride of our town.
As for our proud liquor,
it's as bountiful as the seawater.
Would you allow us to throw a party for you so that we may hear your tales of...
Ma-ma-ma...
...your tales of adventure?
We'll be glad to!
All right!
Three idiots...
Say, by the way,
how long will it take for the log
of this island to be stored?
Log? Forget such boring stuff.
Please just rest after such a long journey.
Now, everyone! Prepare for the party!
Sing to entertain the adventurers!
Party time!!
Then I said with utter coolness,
"Sea Kings, don't you touch my friends."
--Wow...
--Captain Usopp!
--You're so amazing!
Well, regarding the Calm Belt,
even I trembled a bit, though.
A tremble of excitement, that is.
--Whoa!
--Amazing!
Cheers to Usopp-san!
Whoa! Amazing!
He finished his 10th cup!
This is it. I can't drink any more.
This girl's downing her 12th cup!
Take that!
More food!
Whoa! The captain finished
a meal for 20 people!
The cook is down!
Please, I can't go on...
Whoa! This young man is trying to
hit on 20 girls at the same time!
What's with this gang?!
It's really a fu...
Ma-ma-ma...
a fun night!
I'm glad that you all
seem to be having fun.
Yes, indeed, I'm very glad...
For that reason, we failed our
mission of securing food... however,
we'd like to report that we succeeded in
leading the gang to Cactus Island. Baby.
All right! If we submit this, we somehow
should be able to clear our names.
Right. I'll drop it in the
Unluckies Box immediately.
They'll deliver it for us...
...to the boss...
This is it. I quit. I'm gonna sleep.
Whoa! The young man is finally
down after his 13th cup.
What?! You're hopeless, Zoro!
There're only two left.
They're at the 15th cup.
She's competing against the sister.
You should quit soon, too,
for your own sake.
Don't be silly! I definitely won't
quit until I get the prize money.
Ahhh! Thanks for the food.
I can't eat any more.
Three cooks are also down!
Glad you enjoyed it.
I can't drink any more.
I won!!
Ahh, what fun!
She's finally down.
What a nice town...
This is a paradise.
So they wore themselves out
partying and fell asleep...
Sweet dreams...
...adventurers...
Again tonight the
Cactus Rocks look beautiful,
dancing under the moonlight.
You're such a poet, Mr. 8.
Oh, it's you guys...
What happened to them?
They've fallen...
Igarappoi,
a.k.a. Mr. 8
...to hell.
Geez... Since they were so stubborn,
I added a little alcohol in their drinks.
Otherwise they might still be up
and having a good time.
But was it really necessary
to put on an elaborate act...
...for just five weak looking brats?
The Sister
a.k.a. Miss Monday
We should've beat them at the harbor.
This town is already short of food.
Also we didn't have our hopes up
for the whale meat anyway.
You didn't have to say it like that!
We did try our best!
Calm down. Look at this.
I've checked them out beforehand.
Th-thirty million Belly?!
Them?!
It's foolish to judge a pirate's ability
based on their looks, Miss Mon...
Ma-ma-ma...
Miss Monday.
S-sorry.
But we've already settled.
Looks like we can send
a good report to the boss.
Confiscate all the money and other
valuables on the ship immediately.
If we kill them, the bounty drops by 30%.
The Government wants
to hold public executions.
Hey... Sorry, but...
do you mind letting them sleep?
They're all exhausted from
the journey this afternoon.
Mr. 8! Miss Monday!
The guy with the bellyband escaped
from the room when we weren't looking!
He's over there.
You bastard...! I thought
you were completely asleep!
Swordsmen never make the mistake of
letting their guard down that much.
So, let's see if I've got this right.
This is a nest of bounty hunters.
You dupe pirates who are in high spirits
after having just entered the Grand Line.
Looks like there're about
100 bounty hunters here.
I'll fight you all...
Baroque Works!
You bastard! How is it that
you know our company's name?!
Long ago, when I was in your line of work,
your organization tried to recruit me.
Naturally, I rejected it.
Employees don't know each other's
identity and are called by code names.
And of course, the boss' identity and his whereabouts is a mystery to everyone.
You're all a bunch of crooks who
loyally obey him - Baroque Works.
Humph...! Was it a secret?
This is surprising...
If you know our secrets,
then we have no other
choice but to kill you.
Another gravestone...
will be added to the Cactus Rocks...
Kill him!
H... He's gone!
Wh-where the heck did he disappear to?!
--Ahh!
--What?!
All right then.
Shall we?
How dare you mock us!
Fire!
Idiots! They shot each other!
H-he disappeared again!
Kill him already!
It's just a single swordsman!
Let me ask you a question.
Are you sure that you need
to add only one gravestone?
There he is!
I-idiots! Don't!
Are you gonna shoot me, too?!
Stop! Igarappa!
Where did that man disappear to?
Phew.
So that's a shotgun?
That thing sure is dangerous.
It seems he's good enough
that even we must be cautious.
Does he seriously think that he
can fight all of us by himself?
It's hard to believe
that he challenged us
even after knowing
we're with Baroque Works.
The new recruits that I got in Loguetown,
Yubashiri and Kitetsu III...
This is a good chance to
try you guys out in earnest.
I'm going to go all out!
There you are!
Die!
Tsk! Dammit!
First, I'll try Yubashiri.
It's light! This is a good sword!
There he is! This way!
Hold it!
Looks like they found me!
He went up!
Welcome!
Whoa! That thing's dangerous!
This is it for you.
Miss Monday!
Ahh... That was an expensive drink.
What a waste!
What was that feeling in my hand just now?!
How sharp this Kitetsu III is!
A legendary sword cuts only
when its master wishes it,
but this one is a problem child.
Huh?
Lord have mercy!
Lord have mercy! Please save us!
Merciful Lord Blinding Powder!
You should use such a cheap trick
on someone with a pure heart.
I used the back of the blade, so forgive me.
He went further up!
Corner him!
There's nowhere to escape up there!
S-Stop it!
Help me! Help me!
The ladder's falling!
Ahh! He's jumping over here!
Shoot him!
Two Swords Style!
Hawk Wave!
Watch out. That place is unstable.
What?
That was close! It grazed me!
Don't try our patience.
There's no man who can best my strength.
Superhuman...
Brass Knuckles!
We've wast...
Ma-ma...
We've wasted time,
but we finally settled it. The End!
What?!
M... Miss Monday!
What's the matter, muscle woman?
Didn't you want to have
a contest of strength?
Well?!
Shall we continue, Baroque Works?
Fighting isn't a joke.
M-Miss Monday was overpowered...!
I-impossible! This can't be true...!
I-I got it! The Navy made a
mistake on that wanted poster.
I see. It makes sense if this guy has
a 30 million Belly bounty on his head.
He is the real captain.
Right. I thought it was strange
that such a namby-pamby guy
was worth 30 million Belly.
But, even so, how disgraceful...
If we lose against one pirate swordsman,
we'll be held responsible since
the boss put us in charge of this town.
It seems that it's finally our turn to fight.
You may know this,
but with members of Baroque Works,
the smaller his number, the higher
his level and destructive power are.
The three of us, Mr. 9,
Mr. 8 and Miss Wednesday
are agents with a single digit number,
which means we're powerful people and stronger than those you just beat.
Humph. Aren't titles useless
when it comes to fighting?
The stronger one wins. That's all.
Igarappa!
Let's go, Miss Wednesday!
Okay, Mr. 9!
Come, Karoo!
I didn't say "give me your hand"!
Come over here!
Now, show him your quick speed
that leaves leopards in the dust!
Who said "sit"?!
What the hell is that?
Can you afford to let your guard down?
Follow my acrobatics, if you can!!
Hot-blooded...
Bat of Guts!
These're metallic bats. Be careful
not to chip your blades on them.
What's the matter? Are you
so frightened you can't move?
What happened to your proud acrobatics?
If you wanna see it that bad,
watch carefully!
Ahh...
Don't they have anyone better?
Anyone better? That would be me!
Be prepared... Mr. Bushido!
Now, take in my allure
to your heart's content!
Charming Perfume Dance!
Good boy...
I'll finish you off with...
Peacock Slasher!
Go, Karoo!
You went too far!
Fighting these guys is
starting to get embarrassing...
He escaped below using that hole.
That's useless...
Get a good taste of how
frightening I really am!
That shotgun of his is a pain...
How should I close the distance?
Ka-boom!
How dare you beat me like that earlier!
You won't get away with it!
You fell on your own!
Home Run Sneaky Bat!
I tied up one of your arms!
It's an iron chain...
You caught him.
Mr. 8, do it now!
I won't let you escape!
That's right. Don't move.
If you make a stupid move,
I'll have to take your
precious friend's life as well.
Good job, Miss Wednesday.
You can't escape or attack now.
That idiot! At least wake up
when you're being held hostage!
Prepare to open fire!
Preparations completed!
What?!
Igarappappa!
Is he a toy?!
Luffy! Let me use your belly!
What?!
Okay! Done!