Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
Translation & initial syncing
Yibis Fansubs
Syncing
Galaxy 9000
Sync-checking
Sewil
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Feeso
Soundtracking
Halee
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
Video editing
Sewil
Raw provider
SOFCJ-Raws (Opening),
Crunchyroll
"They're Enemies" artist
folkrack.deviantart.com
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Die for Me!
The Dangerous Man Makes His Move!
General Left!
Are you alright, Buffalo?!
Who is that guy -dasuyan?!
Don't ask me!
Anyway, why did he shoot at us for no reason?
What is that thing?  A Pacifista?
That can't be it.
Caesar has no interest in human weapons.
Buffalo!
Dasuyaniiiiin!
Fine.  I don't know who you are...
but if you want a fight, I'll give you one!
General Okay!
I didn't even scratch the paint!?
Now, take this!
General...
Shield!
Way too late, and way too small!
General Shield...
Boomerang!
He threw the shield!
Is he really that desperate?!
It seems...
that you can't be handled with my little toys.
Very well.  You're an enemy if you
want to stop us from freeing Caesar.
Weapon Metamorphose...
Espada Girl!
Dasuyan!
Easy!
General Left!
The young master's orders
must be carried out immediately -dasuyan!
Missile Girl!
Here goes -dasuyan!
Counting on you!
Dasuyan...
Spinning Projectile Cannon!
We'll be taking Caesar!
What're you on about?  What about Caesar?
Where am I?
I can't move... Damn it, is this the end?
The heart of Smoker, Vice Admiral of Navy Unit G-5.
What a thoughtful present, Law.
Smoker!  If nothing else, I'll at least...
take you down with me!
Inside Laboratory 3 - Building R
Hey, what are you doing, Straw Hatter crew?!
Get on, all of you!
If we let Caesar escape, the entire plan will be ruined!
What're you talking about?
Some of my crew-members haven't arrived yet!
Corridor Between Building B and R
Hurry up, Chopper!  Brook!
Alright, Usopp!
We're the ones doing all the running, you know!
You have to outrun the gas!
Hurry!  Just 50 more meters!
Building R, 2nd Floor - The Secret Room
The gate's about to close!  You have to slip through!
This building is done for!
I can't stay here either!
The gate's closing!
Luffy!
There they are!
We made it!
Alright! Everyone's here!
Don't make us worry so much.
I'm so glad you made it in time.
Yeah, and it's all thanks to you, Usopp!
We're the ones who ran our asses off, you know!
Anyway, this place is gonna blow!  Everyone get on!
Hurry!
We're getting out of here, guys!
Yeah!
Whatever shall we do?!
What shall we do about Kin'emon-san?!
What?!  Kin'emon?!
What can we do, with him like that?
K-Kin'emon!
Joker...
Can you hear me?
This is...
Monet.
Monet, I'm glad you're alive.
Vergo was defeated.  As was Caesar.
But Baby 5 and Buffalo
should be able to recover Caesar.
This is all a mistake on my part.
I apologize for putting you in this position.
But I'd like to make the most of this situation.
I want you to kill all those youngsters now.
The Third Laboratory holds a weapon that's identical
to the one that destroyed the island four years ago.
If you just press the self destruct button...
then only one person will be left alive.
The only person who can survive the lethal gas...
will be Caesar.
The button is located at-
Say no more, Joker.
That was my plan all along.
I'm right in front of the self destruct button.
The explosion will even reach the tanker they're planning to escape with.
One of our ships will go to waste.  Is that alright?
Forgive me.
Please, take it all down with you, and die for me.
Understood...
young master...
Die, Smoker!
I'm sorry, partner.
I've known you longer than any of the others.
You've done well, until today.
Did you enjoy that? My Missile Girl's...
flaming passion.
Hey, Baby 5!
Why do you need this weapon when you're a weapon woman?
Thanks for picking it up for me, Buffalo.
That weapon is blessed.
Whoever owns this weapon will become happy.
And if you buy it, I'll be happy too.
I am...
needed!
No, you were being used!
Look out behind you -dasuyan!
I don't know who sent you, but...
I am the invincible Iron Pirate,
and I don't protect the peace of the seas!
Iron Pirate!
He's persistent!
Weapon Metamorphose!
Revolver Girl!
As if that'd work!
This is so fast!
Why is a dragon riding with us?
Fath-
What is with you?
Father!
The eel is attacking me!
Hey, Momo!
Farewell, young master.
You are the man...
who will become the Pirate King.
Are you okay?
Yes.
There must have been an explosion somewhere, right?
It was most likely Building D.
More specifically, it came from the SAD manufacturing room that I was in.
Monet?
What's wrong, Monet?
Hey, Law.
My heart was supposed to be in Caesar's hands.
Why did you have it?
He'd gotten the wrong idea, that's all.
I want your heart!
And this seals our deal.
After that, I took your heart, when you came to the laboratory.
The heart of Smoker.  Vice Admiral of Navy Unit G-5.
What a thoughtful present, Law.
I just kindly returned the heart of his attendant Monet to him.
Answer me.
As they all say, when you do something good,
something good will happen to you.
This is not good!
The place is starting to collapse even faster!
Watch out!
The corridor is collapsing!
This tunnel is built in a mountainside.
If it collapses, we'll be buried alive.
Why are you talking about it so calmly!
This is bad!
The rubble's blocking the path!
Where are the brakes?
Awesome!  We're safe now!
I sure wouldn't want him as an enemy!
Even though he is our enemy.
There should be gas surrounding the exit as well.
Can anyone here control the wind?
As if you'd find someone with that special ability so easily!
I can control it.
You can!?
I can see the exit!
Alright, just a bit further.
Let's go!
Young master!
The young master isn't here.
He's probably in his room on the 4th floor.
No, he wasn't in there.
And the window was open.
Oh. Is that so?
Then I have no idea.
He left without taking any
subordinates with him again.
A-An iron security guard is in our way!
The Sea
So, the island and everyone on it haven't disappeared?
Make sure you kill him.
I'm on my way!
Punk Hazard Shoreline
What is that iron soldier?
None of our attacks do any damage.
It's because you tried to steal my cola.
Cola?
What's he talking about?
Bring it on, Hurricane-man and Weapon-girl!
He's wasting our time!
Let's go, Baby 5.
No one has ever been able to block this attack.
No matter what you try, it's super useless!
We're gonna bore a hole in that body of yours!
This weapon that spins around is...
Huh?
Sickle Girl!
Okay, I'll give you credit for that one.
It's impressive that you have the force to pierce through my General Body!
But you're basically like a mantis trying to fight a warship.
Even though it's wasted on you guys,
I'll show you the ultimate secret weapon
of the pirate ship that will one day control these seas.
The land-based, mobile version of the Gaon Cannon!
Its name is...
General Cannon!
What is this -dasuyan!?
Why is this guy stopping us from getting Caesar back?!
Isn't that Caesar lying down there?
What's he doing here?
I don't know who you're working for,
but we can't afford to lose!
Hey hey, now this is a surprise.
These guys aren't your average pirates.
Don't lump us in with that garbage!
In the name of Joker...
we'll be taking Caesar, by any means necessary.
Now I see!  So your goal...
is Caesar, huh?!
We're almost at the exit!
Keep on blowing that wind, Nami!
The outside is flooded with poison gas too!
We made it out!
You guys finally made it.
I was tired of waiting.
Look at that!
It's Shogun!
Super!
It's a robot!
How amazingly cool!
Buffalo?  And you're Baby 5!
Law?!
Are you really going against Joker?
You traitor!
Joker was saving the Seat of Hearts for you!
Who're they?
Are they your friends?
No.
They're enemies!
The entire Straw Hat Crew and the Navy's G-5 unit!
We can't defeat them all.
What is going on, Baby 5?
In any case, we need to take Caesar to the young master.
They just took Caesar and ran away.
Alright, leave it to me!
Flying enemies are the sniper's job.
Those guys!
Hey, hey.
Usopp said to leave it to him.
Don't underestimate our sniper just because his nose is long.
Don't be an idiot.
If they somehow got away, the plan would...
You made an alliance with us, right?
Weren't you watching just now?
I wish you'd put a bit more faith in us.
What alliance?
All I've been doing is running.
I want to start attacking.
I'm not afraid of an enemy that's far away and has lost the will to fight.
Furthermore, if the enemy's injured and has their back turned, I can handle him!
Just hurry up and get it done.
Okay, I'm gonna give you some water.
Let's do this.
Grow Up!
Black Kabuto Chomping Grass!
Now, eat and store some ammo.
Be careful, Buffalo.
They're going to attack.
Watch my back, Baby 5.
I'm the one who can fly.
We'll definitely complete our mission.
Understood.
You need me, right?
I'll stop the attack, even if it costs me my life!
Go!
Weather Egg!
Something's flying at us!
Now hatch from your egg, lightning-chan!
Thunder clouds?
Buffalo, I've got a bad feeling about this!
I'm already flying at full speed!
You're not getting away.
It's weather science!
Thunder Breed...
No way!
Tempo!
Baby 5!
Dammit, she's unconscious.
Here's the finisher.
Come on, chomping grass.
Deadly...
Shooting Star Rush!
Hey, Buffalo!  Protect me!
I can't move!
O-Of course.  Who do you think I am?
I am part of the Donquixote Family!
I will fulfill my...
What a useless idiot.
Do you really think that'll work, you fool?
I'm made of gas!
I-I have to get to Dressrosa, even if it means going there alone!
It's futile.
The last bullet was...
What is this?
...a pair of Sea Stone handcuffs!
Yes!  I caught him!
Take that, Caesar!
You can leave any enemy who's facing away to-
We get it already.
Alright, we've carried out phase one of the plan.
How about it?
They're pretty good aren't they?
I think I overslept.
Now, which way to Punk Hazard?