It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Translation
FUNimation
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Soundtracking
Halee
Infoboxes/Title Card
BernieCrane
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Editing
Feeso
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Quality Checking
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
Timing
Datenshi
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
With great drive Straw Hat Luffy gets back on his feet yet again!
Even after countless knockdowns he just gets right back up!
Luffy...!
Just what are you?!
Luffy!
He's unsteady on his feet!
And he's out of breath!
This guy is incredible!
And yet...
He still stands tall with a glimmer in his eye!
All for his friends!
Yes! Now this is a Davy Back Fight!
I'm so teary-eyed I... I can't see straight!
Luffy!
Luffy!!
I'm moved to tears!
Afro dude!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!...
A Luffy chant comes up from the crowd!
Has there ever been any other foe who's given our boss so much trouble?!
What do you idiots think you're doing cheering the enemy on?!
Boss...!
Boss!
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
Just you watch. I'll end this now!
Slow Beam Sword!
You'll have to do better than that!
Damn! He hasn't got enough strength left to run?!
Okay! It's time to finish this!
Slow Beam!
Our boss makes the first move! He starts by slowing down a cannonball!
Foxy Fighter!
A Megaton Punch with the speed of a cannonball!
It'll knock you out for good!
There it is! Our boss's cannonball stunt flying!
He's going for the finishing blow aboard the Foxy Fighter!
Luffy! He used a beam on you just before the ball!
Dodge as soon as you can move!
Oh! I can move!
The beam wears off on Straw Hat just a moment sooner!
It's no use!
There's no escape!
Luffy! Look out!
Here's a present for you!
He got him! All of his attacks nail Straw Hat!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
What's with him?! He didn't have to go that far!
H-H-He's... He's back up!
How...?!
I... win.
What?! You're barely even able to stand upright!
But if that's how you want it I'll pound you until you stay down!
Megaton Nine-Tails...!
Rubber...
Rush!
Gatling!
Such intensity!
The combatants now exchange an even more ferocious flurry of punches!
Slaughter 'im Luffy!
Their barrages don't stop! They just keep going!
Luffy!
Slow Beam!
Oh...?!
What the...?
He stopped moving...
S-Straw Hat has been knocked down!
No! Strike that!
Straw Hat is the one who's moving!
Just what has transpired?!
Curse... you...
How?!
Boss?!
A mirror! A mirror fragment
has fallen from Straw Hat's hand!
It was stuck... in my afro...
It's from the mirror in your room!
You little...!
Rubber...
Flail!
Oh no...!
Eight seconds to go.
Huh?
Huh?!
Could this be what I think it is...?!
Seven.
What?
Six.
Boss!
Five!
What are you guys doing?! Start counting too! Four!
What?
Dunno! But it seems fun!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Hurray!
Boss!
Our boss is sent soaring!
And he lands...
...outside the battlefield!
The final combat round of the Davy Back Fight
has ended after a heated epic battle between the two captains!
Our boss's legendary record of 920 wins and 0 losses has been broken!
Unbelievably, victory goes...
I won't... let you have.. a single member of my crew... even if it costs me my life!
...to Straw Hat Luffy!
Our boss... lost...
Foxy Pirates versus...
Hey! Don't just sit there! The boss needs our help!
All right! I'll go!
...the Straw Hats!
I'm going! Move!
I'm going too!
This orthodox-rules three-coin game Davy Back Fight is now over!
Boss!
Geez could you have been any more reckless?!
Take this! And this!
Quit poking him so much! He's seriously hurt you jerk!
He had us worried the entire time...
Afro power my butt.
Afros really are powerful Nami-san!
Oh! He's conscious!
H-Huh?!
The game! How'd the game end?!
I thought I won... Was it just a dream?!
Don't worry. You won.
That's a relief...
I was never worried in the least!
Liar.
Now that I think about it, I've got no reason to be a pirate for any other ship.
Boss!
You shouldn't be moving yet!
Hey Straw Hat!
How dare you tarnish my legendary undefeated streak?!
Boss!
Put 'er there brother!
All right Boss!
Spiteful Shoulder Throw!
Boss!
Are you that stupid?
Have you forgotten the rules?
Choose your 500 people already!
Yes! The final exchange awaits!
Give us your pirate flag!
What?!
You can't be serious! You'd strip us of our pride just like that?!
I don't need your sail. You need it to go places after all.
Wow! He's so merciful!
But our symbol's on there!
How do you expect us to use the sail?!
We don't need your pity! Just take what's yours!
All right.
Since your mark is all we need I'll draw a new one over it for you.
That way you can keep your sail.
Straw Hat... You're such a...!
Sail: Fox
There!
This sucks...!
Wow they're really grateful!
No we ain't!
Hey! Straw Hat!
I'll get you for this!
Do they ever stop being comedians?
There there. I won't ride on stilts ever again.
We can follow the village together now however many years it takes.
You folks...!
I went and kicked their butts!
You're really hurt...
This is nothing new.
Thank you...
Ah so that's why you accepted their challenge.
Not like you wouldn't have otherwise though.
Man you're rude!
Wh-What is this?!
Yikes!
I'm the champion! Yo!
Not another weirdo...
Champion of what?!
I'm the world champion of hole-digging!
I'm challenging my own record as we speak!
What kind of challenge has you wrecking the old stilts guy's house?!
"Old stilts guy"...?
Can you manage while I'm gone?
Sure. But make sure you come back as a champion!
But of course I will!
I promise!
Could it be? Are you...?!
It's me!
Grandpa!
Littonto!
I missed you! I missed you so much!
You went and grew so much since I last saw you...!
I'm sorry for worrying you...
He's your grandson?
I missed my grandpa so much and that devotion led me to hole-digging!
And before I knew it becoming the greatest digger in the world had become my greatest goal in life...
Isn't this great, old guy?!
Yes. I don't know how to begin thanking you...
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
Thank you!
Take care on your way home!
You too! I pray for your safe journey!
All right, men!
Let's go find a shipwright!
Yeah!