Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
There's something flying over there.
It's so far off, I can't see it very well.
Luffy-sama?  What is it?
Mom, what's that?
Hey, look at that!
What is that?
Ryuuguu Palace!  Ryuuguu Palace!
Please respond!  Ryuuguu Palace!
This is the border police!
Hello?  Hello?!
How strange.
Why can't we get in touch with them?
Is the Snail Phone sick or something?
Why are so many of those guys coming to Fishman Island now?
Who knows?
I doubt those dangerous guys from the Fishman District just said "Let's go shopping together!" either.
The Beginning of the Vengeful Plan!
Zoro vs. Hody!
Listen up, men!
Today is the day.
This day will go down in history as the first day Fishman Island was united under one flag!
We'll never make progress as long as
fishmen and merfolk don't see eye to eye.
Humans, who can't even breathe underwater,
should be ruled by us...
like the inferior species they are!
Yeah!
Now is the time to correct the mistakes of history!
Today will be the anniversary of our engagement,
Shirahoshi!
There is no need to rush things!
The wedding can wait... until tomorrow.
The branch of the Sun Pirates that have been such a nuisance to us,
Jinbe's group, isn't here anymore -dosun!
Sea God Neptune, and the three brothers Fukaboshi, Ryuuboshi and Manboshi...
Muhi, if we can just take down those four, eliminating the Neptune Army will be no trouble at all -hi!
I'll tear them all apart!
Just give the word, and I'll cut 'em down.
Let us begin.
All of you, go and take control
of the locations you've been assigned to!
Today, the Ryuuguu Kingdom will fall,
and we will become
the rightful rulers of the ocean floor!
Yeah!
S-Send a report...
She... got... away.
I got some information after all.
There is a Poneglyph here.
This kingdom holds a vital clue
to the mystery of the void century!
Don't make it sound like I cut them down
just for the fun of it!
Well, you did seem to enjoy yourself during the fight.
You're like a natural born killer!
So if a bunch of pirates
came running at you with their swords raised...
you'd just offer them a cup of tea instead?!
That's right, we should have offered them
a cup of tea and sorted out our differences.
That would not have worked on these guys!
In any case, now that you've taken them all out,
we have no way to find out what they were after!
And why should I care?  That's your problem.
It feels like things are going from bad to worse.
Why is our crew filled with people like him?
Well, look at the captain...
Yeah.  There's no use thinking about it.
I wonder if Luffy-san met the Mermaid Princess?
I would like to meet her as well.
Don't say that, just free me from these chains!
Give Shirahoshi back -jamon!
Again, why would we kidnap
the Mermaid Princess in the first place?
The culprit is Straw Hat Luffy -jamon!  Shirahoshi!
However, while I certainly saw
Luffy-san and the shark come out of that room,
I saw no sign of anyone
resembling a Mermaid Princess.
But she would never leave the castle on her own -jamon!
Shirahoshi is as large as I am -jamon.
There is no way she could leave without being seen!
What?!  The Mermaid Princess is huge?!
Ah'm the princess -jamon!
That is absurd.
Oh, I know -jamon!  He must have stuffed
Shirahoshi inside Megalo's mouth and dragged her off!
Don't joke around in this dire situation, Your Majesty.
Even if he came up with that idea,
how could he convince her to do it?
Anyway, our captain would never kidnap anyone!
If you're gonna suspect someone, then pick someone else!
No, I cannot think of anyone else.
If you do not return Shirahoshi to me unharmed, I will not return your ship or crew to you either.
Keep that in mind -jamon!
No way!  Why would you go that far?!
I-I did it!
It looks like the human pirates have succeeded.
Sunny!  You're alright!
You really are a super miraculous ship!
This place is called the ship graveyard.
Shipwrecks are carried here by the ocean currents.
Isn't it ironic?
That a place like this would
receive the blessing of the Sunlight Tree Eve,
and the most beautiful corals would grow here,
attracting the fishes and whales.
It's amazing.
There are lots of whales here that are many times bigger than the Sunny!
Whales can tell where the most fertile seas are,
and they gather there.
What a wonderful sea!
I make a living by investigating this mysterious Sea Forest.
I can hardly believe that this is the deep sea.
The same can be said for Fishman Island too.
I'm impressed that you managed
to get wood from the Treasure Tree Adam.
This is a fine ship,
worthy of the materials it was made of!
Right?  The materials are the same
as the ones Tom-san used for the Pirate King's ship!
And the blueprints were my greatest masterpiece!
Leave the coating of the ship to me.
I'll handle it with a Don!
That's really helpful, uh... what's your name again?
I'm Den.
Den-san!
Still, you really don't look like him.
You're a merman, and not a blowfish either.
Since you're Tom-san's little brother,
I thought you'd look more like him.
That's a very human way of thinking.
After all, you surface-dwellers usually resemble the members of your family.
But that's not the case with fishmen.
The genes of Fishmen and Merfolk
carry the memories of their distant ancestors.
If an octopus mermaid gives birth to a shark merman,
that just means that someone
in the mermaid's ancestry was a shark merman.
Whatever kind of child one gives birth to,
nobody finds it strange here on Fishman Island.
Because of that,
we can't understand why you humans discriminate against each other based on appearances.
By the way, were there any robots among your ancestors?
I'm human!
Human?
Oh, so your ancestors were humanoid robots?
I'm just a normal human!
Well, it doesn't matter.
Yes it does!
Oh, right.
I read about you and Iceberg-kun in a letter.
Oh, so old Kokoro wrote you a letter?
So I'm aware of what happened.
My brother lived in his own way, with a Don, to the very end!
And you came here to tell me that in person.
He had a good apprentice.
You're making me blush.
Oh, so you are a robot after all!
Well, let's just say I'm a perversion of nature
and leave it at that.
Oh, and I noticed that someone's
been sitting over there for a while now.
Oh, that's Boss Jinbe.
Boss?
Apparently he's waiting for someone.
He's a wanted man,
so he can't enter the kingdom itself.
Intruders!
How did you make it all the way to here?!
I don't believe it!
We thought we'd have to fight our way in here,
but Neptune and all the soldiers are already tied up!
I never would have expected
a present like this to be waiting for us!
Quite the surprise.
That face!
What's he doing here?!
So you finally show yourself, despicable Vander Decken!
And that's...
Hody Jones from the Fishman District!
Why has he come back here?
Hody?  Wasn't he...
He used to be a rather proficient soldier in our army.
Is this some kind of trap?
It seems too good to be true!
We just keep getting more and more guests.
What a lively palace.
You must be in league with them, right?!
Huh?!
You invited them here, didn't you?!
Hey!  If you guys hadn't brought us,
we wouldn't even be here in the first place!
Who are those tough-looking guys?!
Hey!  At least give us back our weapons!
Please!  Let us fight!
Vander Decken!
Now that you are here, I have no doubts!
You are the culprit!  Give me back my daughter!
Give her back when I haven't even married her yet?
You're getting ahead of yourself, Father.
Do not call me Father!
Where did you take Shirahoshi?!  She had better be safe!
What's with the attitude?
You make it sound like the princess isn't here.
Don't play dumb with me!
Who else could be responsible for the princess suddenly disappearing from her room?!
My Shirahoshi has disappeared?!
She's mine!  She's my daughter -jamon!
Neptune-sama, don't get so worked up
over this guy's nonsense.
Calm down, Decken.
Look.  The humans you threw,
aiming for the Mermaid Princess, arrived here.
That means, at the very least, that Princess Shirahoshi was still here when you threw them.
Help.
Besides, whether or not what they're saying is true,
you have a way of finding out where she is.
Finding out... where she is?
Indeed!  Hody, you're pretty smart...
I presume!
Is he leaving?
What's he planning to do?
Now, coral!  Fly toward Shirahoshi!
It's not flying toward Koukaku Tower!
Whoever it is trying to stand in the way
of our ten years of love...
They must die!
And so, he let out a gigantic fart!
Luffy-sama, you mustn't use such vulgar words.
Really?
If anyone else is trying to take you as their own...
then I would sooner see you dead, soaked in your own blood!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken went after Shirahoshi!
Neptune-sama!
I'm begging you -jamon!
I'll give you whatever you want!
Just let me go after Decken!
I'll give you all of our treasure.
You can even take my soldiers' lives if you want!
Hey, Your Majesty!
He'll catch Shirahoshi!
My beloved Shirahoshi!
How pitiful, Neptune.
I never thought that my destined enemies,
the Straw Hat Pirates,
would assist us in overthrowing Ryuuguu Palace!
Destined enemies?
That's Arlong's mark!
Jinbe told me that there was
unrest in the Fishman District...
But I never would have guessed that you, a former member of the Neptune Army, would be behind it!
You should be ashamed, Hody!
Ashamed?
That would make sense, if  I'd ever taken
pride in being part of the Neptune Army.
But the only reason I worked for you as a soldier was to gain combat experience.  That's all.
You wretch!
It worked.  I've become strong.
What?!
It's not like you bothered to
watch over every part of Fishman Island.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've seen fishmen being oppressed by humans.
You guys make me want to puke!
No matter how many of you we take out,
you pathetic humans, who can't even
breathe underwater, just keep coming back at us!
I looked up to Arlong's ambition, to knock those humans off their pedestals and teach them a lesson!
We are the ones who will continue his plan...
The New Fishman Pirates!
Ever since Arlong went to East Blue
to conquer the world,
I've been training so that
I could become his right-hand man.
But it never happened,
due to a certain group of humans.
Are these fishmen trying to carry out Arlong's plan?!
What?!  Arlong?!
Just kidding.
In fact, I've never eaten any Arlong before.
That hurt!  Usopp-san, why did you kick me?
Enough talking.  Let's get down to business.
Get out of my way!
W-What?
Rough Shark
What insane power!  What is he doing?!
This is bad!  This is so very, very bad!
Nami-chin?
Caimie, I have a favor to ask.
That's his natural strength, right?
Yeah.  He hasn't taken any Energy Steroids yet.
He crushed the wall!
Damn it!  The palace will be flooded again!
This is terrible!  Especially for me!
We're going to drown!
Oh no, water drops!
Get back!  He's about to use it!
Shark Archery
The water drops turned into arrows!
You filth!  Attacking my men at random!
Cease this, you fool!
Your Majesty!  Don't!
Never -jamon!  You are my vassals -jamon!
Neptune-sama!
What a fool!  A king shielding his underlings?
You really aren't fit to be a king!
Your Majesty!
Damn you, Hody!
This is awful!  They can't even fight back!
This guy is on a totally different level from Arlong!
N-No!  Wait, Boss Hody!  Don't-
He used his companion as a shield!  He's the worst!
Hey, you guys.  Untie the soldiers.
Our negotiations with this country have broken down.
We promised to return all the hostages unharmed, but we couldn't keep that promise.
How dutiful.
Right, I got it.
Oh no, my foot!
My strength is fading!  Help me, Nami-san!
What?  Where is Nami-san?
Huh?  Nami?
Where'd they go?  Caimie isn't here either.
Jeez... First Luffy disappears, and now Nami?
But freeing these guys is more important right now.
Hang on for just a little longer, Brook!
This is such a strain on my bones.
Please, hurry and escape.
I leave the task of untying the rest to you.
I have no strength left.
Untie them!  Pick up your weapons!
Don't let them pull any stupid tricks!
Crush the Neptune Army and the Straw Hat Pirates!
A surface flower blossomed!
I've never seen that flower before!
Take this.
What's this smell?!
Fools.  How ridiculous.
I can't take it any more.
Zoro!  This place is about to be flooded!
Please, let those two escape from the castle!
What about you?
If he comes after you,
nobody will be able to get away!
Don't get in my way.  This country will be mine.
Hang in there!  You'll be alright!
You have to get off the island!
This isn't the time for you to worry about us!
Just focus on your own injuries right now.
Who are you guys?
Return the mermaids!
Damn humans, you only see us as mere objects!
Huh?  What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb, pirates!
Three young mermaids disappeared
from the southern coast not too long ago!
Where are the girls?!
I don't get it.
Why do you think we're the culprits?!
Granted...
I love mermaids so much
that I really want to kidnap a few...
but I would never actually do it!
See?!  He just said he wanted to kidnap them!
Why would you say that to them?!  Be quiet!
It must be the humans' doing!
Get out of here!
There's still some left in this!  Don't waste it!
Silence, human!
Huh?  Sanji, Chopper!
Hey, Sanji!  You've recovered from your nosebleed?
Luffy, is that you?
What's with the puffer fish?
A-Are they your friends, Luffy-sama?
They're my crewmates!
Those people are...
Look!  Their captain is here!
That damn Straw Hat!
He's the leader of the mermaid kidnappers!
I mustn't be seen!
Megalo, close your mouth a little more!
I'm going down there for a bit.
What?
He jumped down!
Hachi!  Is it really you?
Straw Hat.
What happened to you?!
Who did this to you?!
Well... He won't say.
You have to... leave the island.
He keeps insisting we do that.
But I thought Straw Hat
was holding Ryuuguu Palace under siege?
They're mermaid kidnappers!
He must have left his underlings at the castle,
and come to kidnap more!
His ultimate goal must be to kidnap Princess Shirahoshi!
That's ridiculous.  There's no way he could do that.
The princess is a giant Big Kiss Mermaid.
Not to mention, she's the
only daughter of Sea God Neptune.
Even if he wanted to kidnap her,
who would be crazy enough to try?
What's with that puffer fish?
No!
Whaaaaat?!
Huh?!
Princess Shirahoshi?!
Uh... Well... Um...
You found me!
She's huge!  By "Princess", do they mean...
The Mermaid Princess?!
Huh?  What is it?
Is there somebody behind me?
Don't do it, Sanji!
Whatever you do, don't turn around!
What are you talking about?
If you turn around, you'll die, Sanji!
Aw, man...
The Mermaid Princess has been kidnapped!
P-Princess Shirahoshi!
She... really has been... kidnapped!
Hey!  Wimp!
Why'd you get out of the shark?
I-I'm sorry!
Luffy-sama, please don't be so angry with me.
That bastard made the Princess cry!
He really is just pirate scum!
Our poor Princess Shirahoshi!
Princess?
Wait a second... Princess.
They can't mean...
Don't do it, Sanji!
You absolutely must not turn around!
Wait...
You mean to tell me
that if I turn around and look behind me...
then the Mermaid Princess will be there?
That's right!  She's here!
That's why you absolutely
must not turn around, Sanji!
You nearly died from seeing regular mermaids.
So if you see the Mermaid Princess...
you'll definitely lose
every last drop of blood in your body.
It'll be the end of the line for you!
The Mermaid Princess.
The most beautiful woman in the world.
It's said that even the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock fails to compare.
The woman who is held above all other Mermaids...
is behind me right now?
Just forget about her!
I'm begging you... Please don't look behind you!
Chopper.
Instead of continuing to live without ever
fulfilling the dream that's within my grasp...
I choose to fulfill that dream...
and die!
What?!  Isn't your dream supposed to be All Blue?!
Stop!
Sanji!
Huh?  T-T-This...
Even my dreams were wretched, when compared to this.
This paragon of elegance.  She truly is...
the embodiment of absolute beauty.
He turned to stone!
I thought he'd bleed to death from a nosebleed.
Petrification?  That's a new symptom.
Maybe it's a side effect
of the Okama blood transfusion?
How can I explain?  Luffy-sama was only...
Hey, are you okay?!
You gotta tell me, who the hell did this to you?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
We got 'em!
We got the Straw Hat Pirates!
We're fishermen!
We risk our lives every day, fighting the Sea Kings!
Pirates are like nothing!
Don't try and pick a fight
with the Fishman Island fishermen!
The fishermen nabbed 'em!
Good job!
You guys are fishermen?  We aren't fish, you know!
Hey!  I remember you now!
Long ago you were with Arlong, weren't you?  You're a traitor!
You'll be fine now, Princess!
We'll hand 'em over to the Ammo Knights, and then it'll be off with their heads!
But... that isn't exactly what happened...
You see, Luffy-sama was just...
Hey!  You guys!  Something's flying this way!
Over there!
What?!  Don't say such dumb things!
You can't fool us!
Over there!  Hey!
There really is something flying this way!
Huh?!
You don't mean...
Vander Decken!
I've found you, I presume!
Shirahoshi!
Vander Decken-sama.
After hiding for so long,
he's finally showed himself on the island!
Princess!  Please escape!  We'll hold him here!
Give me your answer, Shirahoshi!
If it's yes, then you don't have to die!
Shall we...
get married?!
You mean to tell me that the man who's been throwing weapons at the Princess for the past ten years...
was just stalking her with marriage proposals?!
There's a limit to how crazy you can be,
Vander Decken!
Because of you, the Princess has spent the last
ten years scared out of her mind, fearing for her life!
I can't believe that you'd...
Give me your answer!  Shirahoshi!
It'll be a yes, I presume!
Well, you see...
What's that?  Is it a yes?
You're just not my type.
Huh?
Huh?!  That's her reason?!
Why you...
You've been leading me on for ten years!  Who the hell are you planning to marry?!
If you aren't going to be mine,
then it hurts me just seeing you alive!
Die, Shirahoshi!
Please, Princess Shirahoshi, we beg you to escape!
Quickly!  Even if we have to sacrifice our lives...
Don't run away!  Stay there, Wimp!
What're you saying?!  As if she'd trust a pirate!
That's right, you're working with Decken, aren't you?
Do you think you can just order the Princess to die?
If you're too far from me,
I won't be able to protect you!
Y-Yes!  I'll stay right here!
Princess!
You really think you can
threaten the Princess like that?!
You pirate scum!
Sorry guys, this is nothing personal, but...
you're in the way!
Luffy!
He can do that even when he's tied up?!
This is between me and my beloved Shirahoshi.  Why must you get in the way?
You must be the one who took her...
So you're the one?!
The one who threw all that stuff at Wimp!
I'll take both of your lives then!
I'll put the two of you together and cut you into four!
Just try it!
L-Let me go!
He... took out Vander Decken?!
He's still moving.  Now's our chance to capture him!
Shark!  Wake up!
Sanji!
Are you okay?
He turned into stone a little while ago, but it looks like
he's in a state of bliss now.  He's conscious.
I see.  Got it!
Mermaid Princess.
Is this heaven?  Is it paradise?
My dream's been realized.  I can die a happy man.
But wasn't your dream supposed to be All Blue?
Hurry up, Wimp!
O-O-Okay!
B-B-But... if it wouldn't trouble you too much,
could you perhaps not raise your voice so much?
It's making me really anxious.
I don't know why, but it seems like
we're no longer welcome on this island.
We should get out of here soon.
Thanks, Wimp!
We're outta here!
O-Okay!
Princess!  Why did you undo the rope?
That pirate scum... he's threatening her again!
I'm terribly sorry, everyone.
But I'll be back in time for dinner!
Huh?!
Shark forward!
Get out of the way, trash!
I ain't lettin' you get away that easily!
Wadatsumi!
I've seen him before.
He's the Umibouzu that attacked the Sunny!  He's one of Decken's underlings!
It's the Great Monk!
Wadatsumi!
Knock them out of the sky!
You got it!
My tooth!  My front tooth!  It broke!
Owie!  Owie!
That oversized brat!
Alright!
We're off, Wimp!
To the Sea Forest!
Okay!
Boss Hody!  Two females, a pirate and a mermaid,
have escaped from Ryuuguu Palace!
Let them go.
Nami-chin, is this really okay?
Leaving Zoro-chin and the others like that...
It's not like you could carry everyone.
Well, that's true, but...
Don't worry about it!
Worrying won't do any good!
I know that everyone's strong, but...
You see, Hody's not just strong.
His ideas are dangerous too, or so Hacchin says.
You know, in the past two years,
we've all gotten way stronger than we were before.
But more importantly,
what kind of person is the former Shichibukai Jinbe?
Huh?
Well, Boss Jinbe... He's a pirate, but,
he's so popular that he used to come and go
from Ryuuguu Palace as he pleased.
Yeah.  But he was in
the same crew as Arlong, wasn't he?
Hody said that he's going to
pick up where Arlong left off.
Jinbe left a message for Luffy: "Don't fight Hody."
I think I understand what he meant.
Huh?  You don't think that
he just meant that it would be dangerous?
I just hope Zoro and the others don't anger Hody so much that we get dragged even further into this mess.
At any rate, I wanna see Jinbe.
He said "I will be waiting for you in the Sea Forest."
This incident is going to have
a profound impact on the kingdom.
There's even a chance that there will be riots so huge that they shake the kingdom to its core.
I think he knew all of this.
Boss Jinbe knew that?
Caimie.
Take me to the Sea Forest!
Okay!
All men, listen up!
Yes sir!  We shall immediately remove
Hody and his crew from the premises.
That's no good -jamon!
Huh?!
I cannot fight properly.
As it stands now, you would all just die in vain.
You shall surrender the palace to them at once.
We will join up with Fukaboshi,
and then come up with a plan to recapture the palace.
Surrender the palace?!
Are you serious, Neptune-sama?
That Zoro... What do you think you can do
against a Fishman in the water?!
Usopp-san, my power's fading.
It feels like I'm gonna drown and die at any moment.
You're already dead.
Indeed.
Zoro!
The Ryuuguu palace falls into Hody's hands.
Meanwhile, Jinbe tells everyone about him and Arlong,
while parts of Fishman Island fall into chaos.
Next time on One Pace:
At the Sea Forest!
Arlong and Hody