Once there was a man who obtained everything,
the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
We turn the clock back,
to before the Noah began its descent.
Now ah'm mad!
Watch dis!
Threat: Mega Monk
He was already ridiculously huge!
Was there a point to that?
How's dat?  Surprised?
Ah'm a tiger blowfish fishman!
Ya scared?
Not really.  Why are you talking so fast?
'Cause if ah don' speak fast, da air'll get out!
The Kraken's way bigger.
What?!  Den how's dis?!
Blowfish!
Watch where your going!
We're gonna be crushed!
Help!
Wait, Wadatsumi-san!  Please stop!
You're crushing your allies!
You're still not as big as the Kraken.
What?!  Den dis'll do it!
Give us a break!
Your Majesty!
Are you alright?!
Please forgive us!
We weren't able to protect you, Your Highness!
What kind of vassals are we?
Never mind that.  More importantly, did you see the Noah?
Yes.
To think that it would move...
Damn that Decken.
If the Noah collides with the Princess or the island...
it will all be over -jamon!
When we learned what was going on,
we wanted to order the citizens to evacuate...
but all of the island's transmission stations
seem to be occupied by the New Fishman Pirates!
We're also trying to contact
the Border Police outside of the island, but...
Hurry and prepare to fire the bubble!
Quickly!
Why won't they answer?
Anyway, we must get His Majesty to safety!
No.
I will wait for the Princes.
What's going on here?!
Explain what's happening!
Why are there so many pirates?!
Well...
The Straw Hat Pirates...
Jinbe...
Where's the Princess?!
Hody... Decken...
There's no way...
Alright, I understand now.
I understand the situation now!
All troops, head into the plaza!
Support Jinbe and the Straw Hat Pirates!
Aye!
Since they've engaged the strongest enemies,
that leaves the rest of the troops for us!
To think that the crew we tried to imprison for
a crime they didn't commit is protecting our country.
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
The least we can do is show them respect
by supporting them!
Aye!
It's the Neptune Army.
They're no match for us.
Take them down!
It's time to show them our strength!
Go, slaves!
Now, this way!
Whoa, there!
A useless one!  Just drag him.
Pathetic trash.
How terrible.
Nico Robin.
Can you free the human slaves?
Are you sure?
They may blame Fishman Island for this.
If pirates hold a grudge and attack us,
I'll simply take them out.
But right now...
they aren't even being treated like people.
Hody's men are acting just like the Celestial Dragons.
I can't bear to watch it.
Alright, leave it to me.
Thank you.
My chains... came off!
Hey, what's going on?!
Who did that?!  Who removed the slaves' chains?!
What are you doing, slaves?!
Our chains...
Was that you?
Why did you save us?
I can't refuse a request from a handsome man.
If you want to thank someone, thank Boss Jinbe.
Jinbe?
Damn you... You shouldn't have done that!
Gotcha!
How'd you get onto my back?!
W-What's this?!
It'll be over soon.  Quiet now.
Let me go!  Who are you?!
Why are there two of you?!
Hammond-san!
Damn that woman!
We owe ya one, Miss!
How dare you guys do this to us?!
We're not gonna lose to you freaks!
The human slaves...
have started revolting!
This is the Border Police.  Is this the Minister of the Left?
Please pass this on to the entire kingdom!
The giant ship, Noah, has stopped moving upward,
and has started falling back onto Fishman Island!
What?!
The Noah's falling again.
Where are you now?!
In the Air Tank control tower!
Perfect!  Then you can
tell the entire country about this crisis!
None of the transmission stations in the country
are usable right now.
From where you are, you should be able to reach every state operated Snail Phone in the country!
Hurry!
Yes, Sir!
This is a transmission from the Air Tank above Fishman Island to everyone in the Kingdom!
Issuing emergency evacuation orders!
The giant ship, Noah, is falling toward the island again!
Evacuate the island immediately!
The bubble's gonna break!
The island will be crushed!
Leave it!  Don't worry about your possessions!
B-But!
Get into the ocean!  Everybody hurry!
No way!  It's coming back?!
Is Luffy okay up there?!
What happened to Princess Shirahoshi?!
Decken again?!  That insane pirate!
Let's run away too!  It's too dangerous here!
We'll take care of Hody and his men.
Those of you still watching,
get out of here and leave the island!
No!
What are you saying?!  It's particularly important that women and children get away!
Now, go!
The Straw Hat Pirates, a bunch of human outlaws,
are fighting to protect this island!
We can't just run away right before their eyes!
That's right!  We're the ones who asked them for help!
I can't do anything to help,
but I want to share their fate!
Me too!
And me, Right Minister!
Silence!
Listen, this is your duty!
Go!  You must pass on my words
to everyone else watching the battle!
Understood?!
Everyone here has to make up their own mind.
If you still want to stay, then suit yourselves!
Come at me, criminals!
Straw Hat Luffy-san.
This is the Air Tank.
I'm the one you met earlier.
Straw Hat?  What's with this broadcast?
We've been briefed on this terrible situation.
Our sensors have detected the falling Noah.
Luffy-sama, whatever shall you do about the Noah?
What are they doing?  Their transmission is being broadcast all over the country!
Shirahoshi... Straw Hat...
I wish we could do more,
but all we can do is entrust everything to you.
Don't tell me how hard it is!
Just hurry up and give the air to me!
That's Luffy's voice!  I'm so relieved!
What's up with this conversation?
I just heard the Princess's voice too!
Straw Hat... isn't he that notorious criminal?
The human?
Luffy-san, we leave Fishman Island to you!
Why is the Border Police relying on a human pirate?
Does he have some sort of plan?
A human's gonna stop the Noah?
Hey, Straw Hat.
Can you hear me?
Prince Fukaboshi...
Hody Jones...
I understand him now.
Bro-hoshi!  What do you mean, you understand him?!
Hody is...
a monster bred by his environment!
The New Fishman Pirates are nothing but monsters born of pure malice!
Their ancestors' hatred has been passed on
to them in the shadows of Fishman Island.
They fear that it might be forgotten.
They fear the day that
their grudge toward the humans fades away.
They live desperately...
and wish that humans will be evil,
just so their crusade will be justified!
These bloodthirsty monsters...
don't even want peace for Fishman Island!
What could have possibly happened to make you do this?
Answer me, Hody!
Just what did the humans do to you?!
Nothing.
What?  Nothing?!
We must bestow judgment upon the humans.
We were chosen by the heavens...
and given the power to do so!
I see...
That explains it.
Their grudge...
has no personal experience or will behind it!
There's no substance to it.
They are a completely empty enemy!
Their grudge...
has no personal experience or will behind it!
There's no substance to it.
They are a completely empty enemy!
Empty?  What's Prince Fukaboshi trying to say?
Hey, you guys!
Don't just stand there!  Get off the island!
I can already see the Noah above the island!
Hurry, Weak-hoshi!
Hody-sama has become even more terrifying.
The creatures known as humans are inferior to us.
Don't forget that, Hody.
They are... vile beings.
It's hopeless!  We're done for!
Now that the Age of Pirates has begun...
our brethren are dying every day!
The humans are kidnapping young mermaids and selling them to the Human Shop!
The only thing left for us is death!  Fishman Island is done for!
Damn those humans!
Amazing!
This is incredible!  It's the birth of a hero!
Praise the hero who blew up the Human Shop
at the cost of his own life!
Serves you right, humans!
This is great!
Yeah.
Heroes are so cool -hi!
Dosun!
Arlong-san sunk another human pirate ship!
This is a holy war!
Since ancient days, that trash called humanity...
has been jealous of fishmen, who were chosen by the heavens and granted superior power.
They fear us!
And...
they've responded by persecuting us!
The humans infest this world like maggots...
and they used their only strength, the fact that they outnumber us,
to drive fishmankind to the bottom of the sea!
Listen up, everyone!
Curse the humans!
This human named Rayleigh,
who I've known since childhood...
He's a different kind of human.
He doesn't seem scared at all when he looks at me!
Nyuu- Hody?
I don't like your stories, Hachi-san.
You make me want to vomit!
The humans fear us!
Carry on our ancestors' grudge!
You got that, Hody?
Never forget, Hody!
They are vile.  They are an inferior race!
Curse the humans!
Curse them!  Curse them!  Curse them!
This is terrible!
Tiger-san, the hero who freed the slaves...
was killed by the humans!
What?!
This means that Tiger wasn't the chosen hero either.
Who are you?  Please, leave us alone!
We heard that you donated blood to a human.
So what?!
A human was about to die right in front of-
Daddy!
The Royal Family's insanity
has infected the entire country!
They want to forgive the humans!
Unbelievable!
Did you hear?
Jinbe-san joined the Seven Warlords of the Sea -hi!
The Arlong Pirates are the only ones maintaining the dignity of our race.
Otohime-sama's been shot!
See?!  This is what humans are!
Her Majesty was so generous toward the humans,
yet they showed her no mercy!
If the Royal Family won't take revenge and uphold their pride,
then we can't trust this country at all!
We don't need a weak country like that!
The one responsible for the shameless campaign was punished by the heavens!
It's only natural that villains
who want to forgive the humans end up dead -dosun!
The time for our revenge has come.
The heavens have finally chosen us,
and given us power!
Is this...
Those legendary goods -hi?!
I can't believe you got them -dosun!
Can you mass produce them, Zeo?
I'll give it a try.
The citizens of the Fishman District are fed up
with this country and will eventually band together.
This is a holy war.  Start preparing!
Prepare to kill the humans for as long as we live!
We were chosen...
to carry out the justice known as vengeance!
The day of judgment is coming.
Humans, you despicable inferior species.
We've chosen to give our lives
so that we may have our retribution!
We were too late!
I don't know when it happened, but those in
the Fishman District who didn't share our view...
have become an incarnation of fishmankind's negative emotions!
As the outlaws gathered in the ocean's depths...
we just pretended that we didn't notice...
their distorted malice.
Hey, where are you going?!
Please let me go!  The Noah-
Don't be absurd!
We kept collecting signatures in Mother's place,
and only paid attention to the common citizenry.
That way, we thought we were making progress!
I know it must be difficult for you,
but your anger and hatred toward the humans...
Do not pass it on to the children!
We were too late!
They are the people that Mother feared the most!
Honorable brother.
We should have begun our fight...
in the outer reaches of our kingdom!
In the outer reaches, we should have fought...
against our species's loathing of the human race!
Mother...
Mother was killed by Fishman Island's malice!
She may have been aware of that fact.
Whoever the culprit is...
please don't be angry for me.
Don't lose yourself in anger and hatred because of me.
And yet, the voice of malice spoke
from somewhere in my heart, and I listened...
and resented the humans who killed Mother!
Prince.
The grudges of the dead must stay with the dead.
This malice is an illusion that
only the living create and nurture!
I couldn't fully abandon my grudge against
the humans, so I overlooked what was happening...
and allowed the malice
in the Fishman District to grow...
into a power so great that we couldn't stop it
when we did notice it!
At this rate, Fishman Island...
will destroy itself
because of a grudge against humankind!
Careful now.
This bubble can't protect the island, it has to envelope the ship!
We must hit the Noah!  If it misses, it'll be useless!
Straw Hat, I beg of you!
We don't need our past!
Please, give us a new beginning!
Please, destroy the ghosts from our past that keep this island away from the sun!
Alright... Now!
Go!
With your own hands, give Fishman Island...
a new beginning!
Enough of your nonsense, Fukaboshi!
Fishmankind's grudge will never fade!
Bro-hoshi.
If I get my way, you won't have to worry.
H-Hey... Aren't they the ones
fighting Hody's crew in Gyoncord Plaza?
Yeah, apparently it's the Straw Hat Pirates.
Boss Jinbe's with them too!
Huh?!
That's Luffy-chan's voice!
It's true!
Alright!  It's inside the air bubble!
We made the decision with Jinbe when we entered the plaza.
We won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!
You can leave it all to us, Bro-hoshi!
We're friends, ain't we?
How could we have doubted humans like these?
Hey, what's wrong?!  Don't stop!
We've got to get out of here!  Come on!
I'm... staying on the island.
What?!
Me too!
And me!
I won't run either!
Neither will I!
Luffy-sama, there's air on the Noah!
Great!
You can't escape from me!
Hody-sama is...
Weak-hoshi!
Stay close to me.
I won't let him hurt you!
A-Alright!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama!
Take this!
Ikaros's Fluttering!
Fluttering?!
That's not fluttering at all!
That's just spluttering!
Geso!
Ink?
Too bad for you -hi!
That was my Ink Clone!
Don't underestimate us command-
I'm gonna turn into grilled squid!
Alright!  It's General Franky's new finishing move!
He launched a fireball from his stomach!
It was you?!
Looking away?!  How disgraceful -gyaban!
You blocked my hammer with your bare hands?!
Ow... Maybe this wasn't the best transformation to fight a hammer.
Hey, Chopper!
Your human form has gotten pretty monstrous.
I'm alright.  I wanted to become human because I wanted friends.
Now I want to become a monster to help Luffy!
Is that so?
I wanna slice up those who laugh!
Show me why you're considered
the strongest swordsman on Fishman Island!
Right now, you can't even kill my boredom.
Straw Hat!
This is the end for you!
Weren't you listening?
I won't let anyone harm Fishman Island!