Video Editing
Gigglebot
Timing
Galaxy 9000
PhosCity
Quality Control
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
DolphinWeabu
danpmss
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Honoka
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
danpmss
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Sea Charts and Fishmen
Is this a treasure map?
It seems to be pointing
to Cocoyashi Village.
– Treasure in Cocoyashi Village?!
– Really?!
That's my personal map!
It's none of your damn business!
Hold it. What's with
the sudden evil eye?
What's this?!
What in the world happened here?!
It's the work of Pirate Hunter
Roronoa Zoro!
Never mind that.
Where were you, Hachi?!
This wouldn't have happened,
had you been here!
Of course it wouldn't have!
Had I only been here!
This is unforgivable!
So, you don't know where
Zoro disappeared to?
Well, all I saw was one slightly
suspicious swordsman,
whom I'd never met before.
It was him?!
You did see him, you idiot!
So, where did Zoro go?!
He wanted to see Arlong, so I took
him to Cocoyashi Village just now!
That means there's no reason
to rush out and find him.
He's looking for me, too.
He said he was a guest
of yours, you see.
And I didn't think you'd be
back so soon, Arlong.
Zoro, huh?!
Then, I just need to buy
myself a little more time.
Why are you getting in the way?!
Everything's so close to working out!
I'm so close!
D-Damn you! You looking to fight?!
You're getting in the way!
This is your fault!
This is what you get
for messing with Arlong!
Nami! You really disappoint me!
Even after you stole
our ship and ran off,
Luffy didn't suspect you one bit!
Even now, he completely trusts you!
How can you be so indifferent
about tricking someone like that?!
Money's the only thing I trust.
Those who get fooled deserve it!
Say what?!
It was all supposed to go
without a hitch.
You guys could ruin everything I've
worked for over the past eight years.
So the least I can do is to put
you down with my own hand!
You're acting more like a
pirate than before you left!
Put me down?
You, off me?!
Don't make me laugh!
You'd be wise not to mock me.
Oh crap.
If I stay here, I'm dead for sure!
Lethal...
Smoke Star!
The bastard used a smoke bomb!
Surround him! Don't let him escape!
Now's my chance!
I thought you'd do
something like this.
Nami!
D-Don't under...
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
N-Nami, how could you?
Die like a good little boy.
Way to get revenge!
Now that's why you're an officer
of the Arlong Pirates!
B-Big Sis Nami
k-killed Big Bro Usopp!
That's what you wanted, right?
To die at sea?
Nami. I'm sorry for doubting you.
You're one of us.
One of you?
I work for myself!
There's only one reason
why I joined this crew!
To buy Cocoyashi Village!
Keep your part of the bargain!
I'll have the 100 million belly soon!
But of course.
I'd rather gut myself and die
than break a promise
founded on money.
That's the kind of man I am.
Glad to hear it, Arlong.
You know the deal.
She's one creepy woman.
She's really coming into her own!
A witch! She's actually a witch!
There it is! Arlong Park!
Hey! Don't collapse on me now, cow!
Yeah, Big Bro Sanji's kicks
must've really taken their toll!
Hey! Not that way!
To the left! That building!
It's almost like we're flying!
Not "like"!
We are flying, dumbass!
W-We're falling!
We landed!
Yo! Zoro!
We made it! We made it!
Wh-What the hell...
are you guys doing?!
What do you mean?
We're here to get Nami.
Oh yeah. Where are
Usopp and Johnny?
Usopp!
Th-That's right!
There's no time to be
loafing around here!
What's wrong?!
That bastard's been caught by Arlong!
We gotta hurry before he's killed!
You're too late!
What?!
Big Bro Usopp is dead!
He was killed!
By Big Sis Nami!
– Hurry! Hurry!
– What's the big deal?!
It's the Navy! The Navy's here!
Some survivors from Gosa managed
to contact the government!
The Navy's come here to pick us up!
See!
We're saved!
We can finally escape this island!
So that's the infamous Arlong Park?
Pirates settling down so brazenly
is surely a sign of the end times.
Listen up, men!
Our mission today is to liberate
the survivors of Gosa,
the town destroyed
by the Arlong Pirates!
But I am left to wonder...
Would our brand of justice allow
us to overlook the castle...
of this unchecked pirate?!
It would not!
Our unit is to annihilate
Arlong and his men!
Prepare for battle at once!
Yes, sir!
Navy Branch 77?
Yes. That's what it said.
A newcomer.
Someone go and negotiate
with the one in charge.
If two million isn't enough to keep
them from trying anything funny,
get rid of 'em!
It's a surprise attack!
Arlong! Look out!
H-He pulverized that cannonball!
His bite is terrifying!
Arlong. The negotiations?
Canceled.
– All right! Let's go!
– Time to fight!
It'll be a Navy bloodbath!
Not so fast, guys.
We don't need to waste so much
effort just to take out the trash.
Officer Chew
(Kisser Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
Officer Chew
(Kisser Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
Officer Kuroobi
(Ray Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
Officer Kuroobi
(Ray Fishman)
Arlong Pirates
We'll go!
These humans are damn fools to pick
a fight with us in these waters.
Three of our officers'll
make for an epic fight!
That ship won't last
even three minutes!
That's odd.
Commodore! The cannonball
appears to have been a dud!
Fire another! We must demonstrate
our intent to fight!
We're dealing with fishmen!
Don't let your guard down, men!
Yes, sir!
He's been hit!
It's one of Arlong's men!
Get him! Commence attack!
Stop! Remain calm!
You're one of Arlong's men, yes?
I am Commodore Pudding Pudding
of Navy Branch 77.
We are a somewhat
well-known elite naval unit!
If you do not wish for death,
I suggest you dutifully surrender–
Commodore!
– How dare you!
– Kill him!
Wh-What caused that impact?!
Don't tell me there's
fishmen under the ship?!
I'm sorry to bother you like this,
but we just took the liberty
of removing your ship's rudder.
Wh-What?!
Commodore!
Are you all right?!
Don't worry.
I didn't hit any vital organs.
This is just hypothetical, Commodore,
but if one were to move a massive
rock directly into a strong current,
what do you suppose would
happen to the ocean?
What?!
M-Moving rocks underwater?!
That can't be possible!
All right! Right around there, Hachi!
Okay!
C-Commodore!
A giant whirlpool has
suddenly appeared ahead!
The rudder's not working!
What?!
I told you. We removed the rudder.
This rudderless ship is now headed...
into the depths of the sea.
This can't be happening...
That's the reality.
There's no way we can escape
from Arlong's control.
Thanks for that.
It was nothing.
We know everything
about these waters,
from the winds to the depths.
It was a cinch.
With our top-notch skills, no one
in these seas can challenge us!
And let's not forget
Nami's sea charts.
I moved the rock after checking that!
It even tells the flow of
the currents and everything!
Those are some damn
good charts, all right!
If we have Nami draw up charts
of all the world's oceans,
we'll be the eternal
kings of the sea!
Nami's definitely vital in the creation
of the Arlong Empire!
It's a real shame!
A shame?
He promised to let Nami
and Cocoyashi Village go,
once she saves up 100 million belly.
For real, Arlong?!
You're really going to let Nami go?!
For reals, for reals?!
That's a big waste!
I have no choice.
That's what we agreed
to eight years ago.
When it comes to money, I'd rather
die than go back on my promises.
Try saying that again!
I'll kick your ass!
Stop, Luffy. This has nothing
to do with Johnny.
If you don't wanna
believe me, then don't!
But I saw it with my own two eyes!
She killed Big Bro Usopp–
Quit spouting nonsense!
Nami would never kill Usopp!
We're friends!
B-But, I...
Who're friends, Luffy?
Nami!
Why are you here?
What're you talking about?
You're one of us!
We came to get you!
You're a big problem.
Nami?
One of you?
Don't make me laugh!
You're just a pathetic band
that looks out for one another.
Damn you! You killed him!
I saw it with my own eyes!
How dare... How dare
you kill Big Bro Usopp!
So what? Why not take your
revenge and kill me, then?
What?!
I'll tell you this much.
Right now, Arlong wants to kill
Roronoa Zoro and his men.
Zoro just had to go and
do something stupid.
No matter how monstrously
powerful you are,
you're no match for real monsters.
If you hang around here,
you will wind up getting killed.
Not that it matters to me, though.
She's enchanting even
when she's standoffish!
Hi, Nami! It's me!
Do you remember me?!
Let's set sail together!
Shut up, you!
You're just complicating things!
Say what?!
Love is always a hurricane!
Hey! Listen when people are talking!
Where's Usopp?
On the ocean floor.
Damn it! Cut the crap!
A swordsman would even
strike a lady, Roronoa Zoro?
What?! You don't even know
what's going on here! Back off!
I guess I'd be irritated too,
coming right off a humiliating defeat.
Huh?!
Hey, watch that mouth of yours!
Mind your damn business, asshole!
Bros! This is no time for
you two to be going at it!
That's right!
If you're going to fight,
could you do it off the island?!
Don't butt any more into
our affairs, outsiders!
You still don't get it, do you?
The one and only reason I got
close to you was for the money!
Now that you're flat broke,
I'm not interested whatsoever!
You can have your ship back,
so go find another navigator
and go to the Grand Line!
Go look for your
One Piece or whatever!
Just get the hell out of here!
You're an eyesore!
Goodbye.
Nami.
Big Bro Luffy?!
I'm going to sleep.
Sleep?!
At a time like this?!
And right in the middle of the road?!
I don't plan on leaving,
and I'm not interested in
what's happening here.
And I'm a little sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Huh?!
B-Big Bro.
Fine...
Fine, whatever!
Go ahead and die!
Na– Uh...
Hey, Big Bro Zoro!
What the heck are you thinking?!
Arlong is out to kill us!
So why aren't we running away?!
Now that we know what
Nami's really like,
there should be no reason
at all to stay on this island!
A reason for staying on this island?
There is one.
He's staying here.
Don't tell us you're still gonna try
to get her back too, Big Bro Zoro?!
I have nothing to do with it.
He decides who we have
as our navigator.
Big Bro.
A-All right! Understood!
It was a short reunion,
but our role as guides ends here!
I agree! I'm not trying
to get myself killed!
Yeah. Take care.
Well, until we meet again!
Be well, you guys!
You, too!
Back there...
It's for my business!
This was my only choice!
Back there,
Nami stabbed her own hand to
make it look like she stuck me!
If Nami hadn't done that for me,
Arlong would've killed me for sure!
What should I do?!
Manly Usopp can't just turn
tail after being saved!
For now, I gotta hurry and find Zoro!
Is that... Zoro?!
It is! Yes!
Nami didn't kill him.
Is that what you're tryin' to say?
Am I wrong?
I wonder.
I told her that she's a lightweight who
couldn't ever walk out on anyone.
She might've done it
out of frustration.
Whad'ya mean, "a lightweight"?!
What's so lightweight
about Nami's chest?!
Is that all you can think–
He's alive!
No, I think he's dead now.
You really know how to trash a place.
What's wrong, Nami?
Nothing. I'm just
here to rest a little.
Breaking glass and furniture
just to rest is a bit much.
You have that treasure map open
even though nothing's wrong?
We agreed you could tell me
anything, remember?
Something just made
me mad, that's all!
It was them, huh? Who are they?
You met them?!
Yeah. Captain...
something-or-other.
He kinda seemed like a liar, though.
Now I see.
Yeah, that'd hit you hard.
I'm surprised that someone
really showed up for her.
Friends, huh?
The most painful word for her.
Usopp!
Did Nami do this to you?!
Sorry. Me and this guy did that.
You did it!
L-Luffy! You're here?!
Yeah. We just got here.
Oh, I'm here, too!
Good to see you!
Someday I'm gonna kill you!
Oh! You're in pretty
good shape, after all!
Shut up!
Speaking of which,
we heard Nami killed you.
Huh?!
That damn Johnny! I knew it!
He was full of crap!
No. In a way, it wasn't a lie.
It's actually the opposite!
Nami saved my life!
It looks to me like there's a reason
she's in a fishman crew!
Obviously.
So, what do we do?
Do we storm Arlong Park?
H-Hold on! We gotta find out what
the story with Nami is first!
It's no use, either way.
No matter what you guys do,
Arlong's rule won't come to an end.
Nojiko!
Who's she?
Nami's big sister.
N-Nami's older sister?!
No wonder she's so beautiful!
What do you mean it's no use?
Please, don't get any more
involved with this village.
Leave Nami alone.
I'll explain the circumstances.
Circumstances?
You mean why she
joined Arlong's group?
Yes. You'll feel like leaving
the island once you hear it.
There's a Navy ship at the shore?!
It's a ship from the 16th Branch!
Maybe Headquarters is taking action,
after what happened
to the 77th Branch!
I am Captain Nezumi
of Navy Branch 16.
Bring me Genzo, the representative
of Cocoyashi Village!
I'm Genzo, Captain.
You, huh?
Lead me to the house
of the girl named Nami.
Nami? But what in the world for?
You simply need to lead the way.