Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Translation
Yibis
Soundtracking
Halee
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
Editing
Feeso
Infoboxes
BernieCrane
Formatting
Sewil
Datenshi
Edit-checking
Galaxy 9000
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
I'd heard some rumors that you were on this island...
I Couldn't Save Them!!!
So, that was true?
Seeing how you helped out these brats,
that must mean you're still a pirate, at your age...
Rayleigh-san?
If you people would withdraw my bounty...
I'd be able to retire in peace, too.
The pirates' sins won't disappear, right?
Especially not those of the Roger Pirates.
But if we were to try and catch you,
it would require a bit more dedication than we have right now.
What a relief, Zoro! This old man really is amazing!
The body I could not pierce no matter how many times I stabbed him...
He just stopped him! How?!
You can't let them leave, can you, Kizaru-kun?
Give me a break, here!
If we can't catch these kids...
Then we at Navy HQ wouldn't be able to face the Celestial Dragons in Mariejoa.
Would you please get out of my way?
Usopp! Brook!
Take Zoro and run!
Right!
Let's go, Brook!
Everyone, only think of how to escape!
Right now...
We can't...
Beat these guys!
Oh, great. That's really annoying.
Franky!
I'm gonna use all my cola energy...
This'll be my last attack!
Coup de Vent!
That damned idiot must have felt that!
Run!
Pops, thank you!
No problem! I'll pray for your safety!
Mirror of Yata
It's bright!
Light! He's doing something!
I won't let you pass!
It's been a long time since I used my sword.
Sword of the Gathering Clouds of Heaven
I'm in trouble here...
I was expecting things to be easy when I came to this island...
Worries are also a part of life, Kizaru-kun.
The light ahead of us disappeared.
Seems like the old man saved us again.
T-T-That was scary!
Seems like he's the real Dark King.
This is the first time I've seen anyone stop the old guy.
But we're just one step away from catching Roronoa with his bounty of over 100 million...
PX-1! Roronoa is half-dead!
Go take him out!
He's...
Franky!
Take care of Nami-san! Please go on without me!
Be careful! We'll be alright!
Sanji-kun?!
He's going after Usopp and the others!
Put me down...
I'll let you escape...
Don't be ridiculous! You're even more useless than I am right now!
We're running together!
That's what Luffy wanted us to do!
Could it be...?!
He's here!
Usopp-san!
Usopp-san, go on ahead!
Stop it, Brook!
You know how strong he is, don't you?!
Hurry!
All for one, one for all!
There are times when a man has no choice but to act!
A bone-crushing defeat...
Brook!
Don't come here!
Stop right there, you damn bastard!
Sanji!
My leg...!
Run, Sanji!
He's aiming for you!
Idiot! Hurry up and go!
As you can see, my subordinates are more than strong enough.
Zoro, I'm sorry! I dropped you!
Are you alright?
They're in trouble over there!
I won't even need my broadaxe, will I?
I thought I told you, you don't have time to worry about your friends!
Leg Locked, Heave-Ho!
Luffy!
How can that guy's attacks hurt a rubber man like Luffy?!
Damn!
Chopper! Don't stop!
Sanji!
Damn it! They'll all be killed!
Don't do it, Chopper!
Stop it, you people!
Rumble
Chopper!
That's the thing from back then!
What's this?
I had heard of this...
That's an interesting power, but...
It seems like you've lost your common sense, huh?
Luffy, watch out!
That Chopper... He did that again?!
I don't know why, but he seems to be distracted by him...
Now's our chance!
Sanji, Brook! Get up!
Let's hurry up and get away from here while we have the chance!
He's gonna fire another beam!
Hey, hurry and wake up, Brook!
Sanji!
Wait, PX-1.
Another one showed up!
What's going on?!
No way!
How many of these guys are there, anyway?!
This guy...
...He's the real one!
So, you survived, Roronoa?
Thanks to your mercy...
H... Hey, Zoro...
This is no time to be talking...
Hurry!
If you were to go on a vacation, where would you like to go?
Hey, Zoro!
If you don't hurry up and run...
Huh?
Z-Zoro...
Damn you!
What did you do to Zoro?!
He was...
He was just...
...Right here!
Zoro...?
Z-Zoro?
Zoro?
Zoro!
Zoro!!!
Stop it, Chopper!
Don't be reckless!
Zoro... Where did you go?!
He doesn't have any self-control...
Regardless, that Kuma boy...
What is that bastard doing here?
Bartholomew Kuma...
This is why you can't trust pirates!
They're surrounded over there, too?
Zoro just vanished!
Does this mean that the real one showed up at last?
There's no mistake...
I've seen that ability before...
Back at Thriller Bark, he used that...
...To get rid of a girl...
...Tnd she never came back!
This is really bad!
Hey! What'd he do to Zoro?!
Where'd he disappear off to?!
I have no obligation to answer.
I'm the most tight-lipped man in the world.
I don't know if it's true or not, but they say that
anyone who gets blasted off by his pads
is sent flying through the sky for three days and nights...
Nobody except the person who was sent flying knows where to, though...
But it definitely won't be on this island...
Or anywhere else where you might meet them anytime soon.
They might end up on the edge of some distant sea.
What?!
Say something, you damned freak!
Where'd you send Zoro?!
So, he finally showed up...
The real Warlord...
There are three of them who look the same...
What's going on?!
Th... The real Warlord...
Don't come any closer!
Damn it... Stop!
I've got 8000 subordinates, you know!
Hey! Can't you hear me?! Don't come any closer!
Look out, Usopp! Behind you!
Behi-?!
Stay out of this.
He even got rid of his own comrade?!
Even PX-1?!
What're you doing with your allies, Kuma boy?!
Run, the three of you!!
Luffy!
Just run away, everyone!
We'll think things over once we're safe!
Go!!!
Hey, let's go!
But... Zoro...
Like he said, we'll think about that later!
Let's go!
Let's go! The beam only grazed me!
I'll lend you my shoulder, quick!
Be careful, you two!
Brook!
Brook!!
I shall protect you!
Even if it costs me my life!!
...Though I am already d-
Brook!!!
Damn it... What am I doing?!
Two of my comrades just vanished before my eyes!
Damn it!
Get going, Usopp!
Don't be ridiculous! We're leaving together, Sanji!
Why, you...!
Stop it, Sanji!
Damn pad-bastard!!
Sanji!
Stay away!
Gunpowder Star!
Damn!
Usopp!
Run!
Run!!
Usopp!
Sanji?
Damn it to hell!
Stop it, Sanji!
Even Sanji...
What's going on...?
What are we gonna do?
No way...
Everyone's...
The situation over there seems pretty hopeless...
I'd like to help them out, but I'm getting too old...
You're holding off a navy admiral on your own,
and you're still trying to do more?
You're making me look bad here, so just cut it out already!
You are the "Dark King", Rayleigh, are you not?
Huh?
Kuma?
Luffy?
You really expect me to believe what you just said?
Decide that for yourself.
I am already endangering my own position.
Just what're you planning to do, Kuma?
As long as it doesn't directly affect the World Government...
We have no obligation to get along with the navy.
I will not answer that question.
You bastard!
Gear Second!
Get out of our way!
Strong Right!
What?!
Wait!
You can't, Luffy!
Rubber
Jet Pistol!
No!!!
Luffy! Help!
Nami!!!
Luffy!
Chopper...
Chopper!!!
Stop it...
Please, stop it!!!
Luffy!
Robin!!!
Luffy!!
I couldn't even...
...Save a single one of my friends!
So, you're gonna send him off and be done with it?
I hope you have a good explanation for this.
This is a huge problem, you know?
We will never...
...Meet again.
Farewell.
Grand Line...
Sabaody Archipelago...
Grove 12...
On this day...
...The pirate crew, led by captain Monkey D. Luffy...
...The Straw Hat Pirates...
...Were completely and utterly defeated.