Editing
Feeso
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
Timing
Lance
attained everything
this world has to offer.
Quality Assurance
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
Soundtracking
Halee
My treasure? If you want it,
you can have it!
Graphics
Datenshi
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
jyuu
shin
ba
n
nan
te
jyuu
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
What was that?!
What did he do?!
For Whom the Bell Tolls
It looked like his arm stretched!
Get real!
He sent Captain Kuro flying!
I leave the rest to you!
I'm gonna get me some treasure!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
You guys!
Stay away!
Say your prayers, butt-ler!
It's punishment time!
Lousy pirate!
Disrupting this village's peace!
S-Stop!
Darn you!
Take this!
You brats! What are you doing?!
What're those runts doing?!
Stop that, you guys... Stop!
Alright! We'll let you
off with just that!
Now Captain Kuro is really mad!
Captain!
I knew it!
You were fighting, Captain!
Why didn't you tell us?!
That's unbare!
No! You mean "unfair!"
Who cares about that!
You guys just gotta
get out of here! Run!
No!
We're gonna fight, too!
The Usopp Pirates will
be shamed if we run!
You idiots! Get out of here, now!
Captain!
That hurt a bit...
That's quite a strange
technique you have there...
I take it you...
...have Devil Fruit powers?!
Yep! I ate the Rubber-Rubber Fruit!
I'm a rubber person!
What?! A Devil Fruit?!
He's dangerous!
They really do exist?!
I thought he seemed strange!
I see. A rubber person. So I didn't
hallucinate his arm-stretching...
Jango!
Yeah?
I'll handle the boy.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
As we planned, have her write a will...
... then kill her!
And those three little ants...
They're an eyesore!
I'm on it.
Stop.
I can't let you pass.
Butchie!
Cat...
...Astrophe!
Not again!
He's on a completely
different level than before!
Crap!
Dammit...
I'm out of strength...
Dammit... Dammit! Dammit...
D-Damn...
Usopp Pirates!
Y-Yes, sir?!
Listen to me!
We're not going to run!
Not after they did this to you!
We're going to avenge you!
Protect Kaya!
Listen closely!
I'm giving...
I'm giving you the most
important task there is now!
Take Kaya and get away from here!
Don't tell me you can't!
That was the reason we
formed our pirate group:
to become men who protect
what's important to us!
Usopp-san...
That's... a direct order...
Yes, Captain!
Hurry, Kaya-san!
This way! This way!
He sure knows how to talk big.
He basically just told 'em to run away...
The woods are like our backyard!
O-Okay...
Jango!
I wound up gawking!
The fools!
They can't possibly escape me-
Howdya like that?!
Damn you!
Go after them, you fool!
Y-Yeah, okay!
How pointless.
I know very well just
how weak Kaya is...
She'll never escape Jango.
If you want to help her,
go right ahead.
If you can get past this
hill alive, that is.
Butchie!
You already lost to me once!
I told you not to get in my way!
Move!
Is that hypnotist still behind us?!
Nope, I don't see him!
Let's lose him for good!
Like he can really catch
us inside this forest!
Don't worry, Kaya-san!
We will keep you safe!
Yeah! In the name
of the Usopp Pirates!
Thank you...
Not there...
Where are you, you runts?!
Don't think you can escape me!
I can shave this whole
forest bald, if you'd like!
Whoa! He seems really mad!
He's not just a hypnotist?!
Where did you run off to?
This way!
W-What's that sound?!
Who knows?
Jango is probably tearing the place up.
Why not go and see for yourself?
Though it may already be too late...
Damn you...
Don't you even have a shred of pity?!
You lived with her for 3 years!
No.
I already told you, Kaya is nothing
more than a pawn in my plan.
Once she's dead, then I'll
express some gratitude.
Damn you...
What a helplessly evil guy!
I don't plan to help him, though!
Usopp!
Go to them!
We'll take over here!
Leave it to us!
Oh? You can still move?
How impressive.
Shut up...
I refuse to let you...
... have your way!
You went and betrayed the villagers'
and Kaya's feelings...
I refuse to let you have
your way anymore!
Usopp!
D-Dammit...
I... can't... move...
You really are a riot!
Just stay on the ground there.
Though, even if you did
catch up with Jango,
you'd be no match for him anyway.
This way is probably safest for you!
Even if I am no match...
Even if I am no match for him...
I will protect them!
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates...
... and a brave warrior of the sea!
I won't let you lay
a finger on the village!
What's with him?
He's yellin' somethin'!
Check it out, he's cryin'!
What's so funny?!
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
Nope! Hurry!
Th-Thanks...
I'd actually be much faster by myself,
but they're inside some woods.
I'm gonna need your directions
to catch up to him.
Hold it, you two.
Who gave you permission to pass this hill?
I did!
Go! Zoro! Usopp!
And another!
Rubber-Rubber Spear!
Darn! He disappeared again!
Oh, well! They're past
the hill, at least!
Before fighting, I have
one thing to ask you.
Why is an outsider like you butting
into this village's business?!
Because there's a man in this
village I don't wanna let die!
How simple.
Are you okay with that being why you die?!
Yep! I'm not gonna die, though!
I'll make sure you do!
Rubber-Rubber...
Whip!
... and Pistol!
You're making me yawn!
Why, you...!
Hey! East! East! I said east!
Like I know where that is!
Tell me left or right!
Then turn right!
That's the opposite way!
Where did you run off to?
Kaya-san!
I'm sorry... You run on ahead...
What are you saying?!
Our mission is to protect you!
Oh no! She's got a really bad fever!
Eh?! Hang in there, Kaya-san!
A doctor! Get a doctor!
You idiot! This is no time for that!
Someone's trying to kill her!
But it's dangerous for
her to run any more!
But...
Where are you, you runts?!
I won't let Kaya-san die!
Alright then!
Prepare yourselves, Usopp Pirates!
Alright!
Let's fight him!
No!
You're still just children!
You mustn't die for my sake!
We're not gonna die.
We're gonna fight to live!
Damn...
He cut my mouth...
That straw hat guy's
insanely strong, and yet...
Th-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
Get 'im!
Hurray for Captain Kuro!
Captain Kuro!
You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
Don't call me by that name!
Do you still not get it?!
This plan is so I can be completely
rid of the name "Captain Kuro!"
I'm tired...
Devising plans everyday for you men
who only care about mayhem...
Being relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters...
I was absolutely sick of it all!
The navy, huh...
Kuro of a Hundred Plans
(3 Years Ago)
This is the third time this week...
It can't be helped.
We're doing stuff that makes people chase us.
Plus you've made quite
a name for yourself...
Yes... That name is what
draws them to us.
That's why I'm giving
up being Captain Kuro.
That's pretty funny.
But it's no use.
I think the navy'll keep
following you until you're dead.
I am going to die.
It would seem that piracy
just isn't for me...
B-But you're this ship's captain!
You can be captain!
I'm sick of this tumultuous lifestyle.
I'm... going to kill
myself for all to see!
Captain Kuro!
Captain!
How many vessels?
J-Just one!
What should we do, Captain?!
Should we blast 'em back?!
Lower a small boat.
Huh?!
A boat!
Vice-Captain Jango!
Captain Kuro just-
Yeah, I know.
"You know?!"
It's way too reckless for him
to go there by himself!
Don't tell me he's
turning himself in?!
H-huh?!
The cannon fire stopped...
Dock with their ship.
B-But...
Just do as I say, damn it!
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey, get ready to fight!
I see... So that's why...
Th-The marines...
They've been wiped out!
Now, then...
Let's begin the plan...
Hey, now. Pull yourself together.
I was kind enough to leave
you alive, you know...
Sh-Shut up...
I-I'm not gonna beg for my life...
F-Finish me off, damn you...
That's a good look.
If you can howl that much with
a shattered jaw, then that's perfect!
I'm giving you, a nameless,
low-ranking soldier, a treat.
Accept it gratefully...
...The head of Kuro,
Man of a Thousand Plans!
Your name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was your doing.
One, two, Jango!
My name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was my doing.
And you're the man who
caught Captain Kuro.
Return to base and execute this man.
One, two, Jango!
I'm the man who caught Captain Kuro!
You're doing it again, Vice-Captain!
Perfect...
With that fake gone, Captain Kuro
will disappear from the world.
And when my plan today succeeds,
my goal will be fully achieved...
Money and peace of mind will be mine.
Do you understand, boy?
I cannot allow this plan
of three years to fail!
My plan will not be disrupted!
Seems you can do more than just stretch!
That's right! I've toughened
myself up, to be a pirate!
You're "tired?!"
You're not fit to be a pirate if having
a name on the seas scares you!
My ambition is much greater than yours!
Th-That guy...
He broke Captain Kuro's "Cat Claw"!
That leaves only five more
of those weird swords!
It's okay! He can still fight plenty!
Yeah! He still has the other claw!
Scratch him up and
kill 'im, Captain Kuro!
Hey! That name is taboo now!
I think his name in this
village is Klaha...something
Kla-san, then!
Kla-san! Get 'im!
Be quiet...
All of you!
Huh?!
We got him! Now!
Take this! Pepper Attack!
Push...
Hyaaah!
Oww! Oww! Oww!
End of the line, hypnotist!
Don't get cocky!
Darn it! We failed!
You made a mockery of me.
But I am a pirate...
Onion!
You pretend pirates have
interfered a bit too much...
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
I'll start by executing these three.
You can reflect on your foolishness
to meddle in a real pirate fight
in the next life.
There you are.
No!
Run, Kaya-san!
Hey!
Yeah! That's them!
They're the other way?!
I'll come exterminate
every one of you later...
Jango too, of course!
W-Why us?!
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
It's still not too late for us
to attack the village, right?!
And if Captain Jango gets her to write
her will, the plan should work!
You need not worry about this plan;
your corpses will be enough for me
to place the blame on you...
I never intended to let you leave
this village from the start...
I can't have people who know
I exist stay alive...
You can't be serious!
Then you planned to kill
us from the very start?!
That's right...
Since three years ago, when I was
still known as Captain Kuro...
It was all...
All part of my plan!
Man, you guys are dumb.
You're such an uncool pirate group!
"Uncool?"
Pirate groups are nothing more than
a collection of social outcasts!
Without plans, what can
they possibly do?!
Every last one should just
shut up and follow my plans!
Crew members are loyal
pawns of the captain!
Whether my men live or die is all
up to my orders as their leader!
No matter how powerful the obstacle,
they simply need to stand up
to it and die for my plan...
This is how pirates are!
Don't you talk down
to me, traveler boy!
No matter how many hundreds or thousands
of men follow you as their captain...
... you'll never be better than Usopp!
What?!
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid
pretending to be a pirate captain?
That's right!
You're hilarious!
Don't get cocky just because
you snapped one of my claws!
How exactly is he better than me?!
Let's hear it!
Character.
What?!
You don't know what a true pirate is!
H-He...
He kept up with the Pussy
Foot Maneuver's speed!
How insulting...
If you want to know about real
pirates that much, then I'll show you
that terror...
The terror of a pirate who's been
face to face with death many times!
Hey! That stance! Is he-
He's gonna use that technique?!
But he's only fighting one guy!
But that's definitely it!
He's planning to use
the Out of the Back Attack!
Isn't it bad for us to be here?!
He'll get us, too!
He plans to kill us, too!
He even said so earlier!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Anything but that technique!
We'll do anything you want!
Please, Captain Kuro!
What's the big deal?
He's only wobbling back and forth...
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
Out of the Back Attack!
What a small haul...
I thought they'd have a little
more treasure than that...
Let's see, is the fight over by now?
Huh? Everyone's stopped...
... Is it over?
Th-There it is!
Why over there?!
Not again!
Now it's the wall!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
It's no use! He attacks at random
using his Pussy Foot Maneuver!
Because of his speed, not even
he knows what he's cutting!
So many crewmembers have
fallen victim to-
Hey!
W-What's happening?!
People are suddenly being cut!
Show yourself, butler...
Who do you take your friends for?!
Luffy...
Found you!
Bastard!
You should've let yourself
be cut like a good boy!
Look!
Thanks to you, my adorable men
are left alive and in agony.
It would've been better for them
to die in that attack!
Now what?
You look like you
have something to say...
Yeah...
I will never be...
...a man like you.
Not "will."
Someone like you can't be like me!
Especially since you're
going to die here,
while you writhe in agony as
I hack you up like raw fish...
Please stop this!
Leave them alone!
I'll write my will!
N-No!
You'll be killed if you
write it, Kaya-san!
Fool.
Don't try to make
a deal with me.
Captain Kuro told me
to get rid of everyone.
You can't be serious!
If you don't do as I say,
then you won't get to kill me!
I won't write my will, either!
H-Hold on!
Don't act hasty!
I absolutely must get you
to write that will!
K-Kaya-san!
Alright! I'll let the brats go!
Though they're really
in no condition to run...
Don't forget to sign your name!
I know...
"I leave my entire fortune
to Klahadore, my butler..."
Excellent!
This is your will, all right!
That saved me the trouble
of hypnotizing you!
You promise not to kill them, right?
Don't worry.
I may not look like it, but I'm
known for being an honest man.
Kaya-san!
There they are!
There they are! There they are! Stop!
I've been cut there, you know!
Over there!
Alright, I'll be back!
Hey!
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
He followed me here?!
Looks like I better finish this quickly!
Everything so far has been playtime.
You get the special treatment.
I'm going to let you taste plenty
of fear, then slowly cook you!
Out of the Back Attack!
Just try your foot technique now!
Damn you! Get away from me!
Now your plan of three years
is a complete failure!
What?!
He caught Captain Kuro!
Hey, if he wins, that means
we won't get killed, right?!
Now you die!
Oh, no, you don't!
You damn kids!
Looks like you're one step
too late, Belly band!
I wouldn't say so!
Yes! That branch was in the way!
What?!
Usopp-san...
Captain!
Eat this, hypnotist!
Get 'im, Rubber Guy!
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
Get away!
You guys have no right to cheer me on!
Let go!
Rubber-Rubber...
Special Attack: Exploding Star!
My plan will not be disrupted!
Bell!