Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
KaitouYahiko
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
TheFVGuy
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Town of Beginnings and Endings
You raised your price again?!
Aren't you charging a bit too much?
Raise it again and I'll stop buying it!
What's the big deal?
It's just a paper or two.
It's a big deal when you're
buying it every day!
You know you don't need to save up now
that Arlong's gone from your village, right?
You can stop obsessing
over money, too.
Show's what you know!
Now that everything's over,
I can save up for myself!
I don't wanna be some poor
pirate who can't even dress up!
Hey, easy there!
I'm trying to make my
special Tabasco Star!
An eyeful of this
will make any bad guy–
C'mon! Just one!
Water! Water! Water!
No!
This is Nami's tangerine orchard!
I won't let anyone lay a finger on it!
Nami! Nothing will get past
my loving protection!
Yeah. Thanks, Sanji.
She's got him wrapped
around her finger...
C'mon! Just one tangerine!
Cheapskate Sanji.
I said no!
Oh, well! I'm pretty happy anyway!
The world's always so chaotic.
Another coup in Villa...
A flyer?
Marine HQ
Operated by the
World Government
So, at the very least, they've become
too much for our branches to handle?
Correct.
Even before he had a crew,
he took down a Marine branch
captain—Axe-Hand Morgan—
and he's shown no signs
of slowing since.
Buggy the Clown: 15 million.
Pirate Fleet Commodore Don Krieg: 17 million.
Fishman Pirate,
Saw-Tooth Arlong: 20 million.
Commander Brannew
Marine Headquarters
The average bounty in
the East Blue is 3 million belly,
but these major pirates—each worth
more than 10 million—were taken down!
It's globally unprecedented for
a bounty to start at thirty million belly,
but it's not so excessive
an amount, either.
Seeds of villainy
must be nipped in the bud,
before they have a chance
to blossom out of control.
Absolutely.
We're wanted criminals now!
It says I'm worth 30 million belly!
Look! I'm gonna be seen around
the world! Girls might fall for me!
What?! They included
Long Nose but left me out?!
Where are you?!
I don't see you at all!
Right there!
It's just the back of your head.
It's nothing to brag about.
Don't be so glum!
If you turn enough heads, you'll get
one even without being a captain.
Seriously?!
Well, just keep trying!
Let's hurry and get to
the Grand Line, you guys!
Yet again, you guys are
missing how serious this is!
All of our lives are in danger now!
This is no time to be taking it easy
and relaxing in the East Blue...
Thirty million belly...
Marine HQ is sure to act
on a number that high...
and we'll be swarmed with
strong bounty hunters.
They'll be a bigger challenge
than anyone we've faced!
Miss!
Miss Kaya!
What's wrong, Merry?!
Have a look at this!
Usopp!
That's definitely Usopp
facing the other way!
Now that you mention it, you're right...
Finally!
Luffy! You've taken the first step
toward your dream!
I'm Luffy. The man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
See ya!
But the next time we meet,
we may be enemies!
We're finally approaching
the Grand Line.
There's a famous settlement
on this island... Loguetown.
Loguetown?
It's known as the Town of
Beginnings and Endings.
Its reputation precedes itself.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
was born and executed in that town.
The town where the King
of the Pirates died...
Wanna go?
Yeah! I have to see it!
The man who got the One Piece—
everything the world has to offer—
was born and then died there!
Anyone who wants to flee
should do so now!
This bastion of peace will not
tolerate any weakness
during this age of piracy!
The weak and the feeble are not
to blame! They will have justice!
If evil persists upon the seas,
then we Marines must drive it
away with the utmost of force!
In the name of absolute justice!
"Justice"
– Yes, sir!
Wow! What a huge town!
The place used to be full of pirates
on their way to the Grand Line.
So it has everything you could need!
Alright! Our next adventure
is going to be a big one,
so I'll need get us some equipment.
Looks like I can get some
good ingredients here.
Good women, too!
There's something I wanna buy, too.
Oh? How are you gonna do that?
You're flat broke, as I recall!
Alright! I'm gonna check
out the execution platform!
– Huh?
I'm gonna see where
the King of the Pirates was executed!
Hey, wait! We haven't decided
where we're meeting up yet!
Man, that guy...
The King of the Pirates was
born here and died here!
He might have walked
down this very street!
Yahoo!
Damn, these are expensive!
Too expensive!
Lend you money?
No problem!
But after interest, you'll owe me
300 percent of what I lend you!
I can't afford to borrow
any more from her...
but I can't enter the Grand Line
with just one sword...
What do I do?
"Monster"?! Now, that's just rude!
Huh?
Shut it!
Our boss is behind
bars because of him!
Then learn from his mistake.
That's rich!
We ain't happy with things as they are!
We're gonna let him see
your corpse when we drag it to him!
Very well. I will fight you.
Will you now, girlie?!
Don't make us laugh!
What can a girl possibly do?!
Die!
Yeah!
She did it!
You're one tough lady!
You're amazing!
I can't tell if she's strong or weak!
Glasses... Glasses... Glasses...
Where are my glasses...?
My glasses...
Hey. You looking for these?
S-Sorry for the trouble!
Thank you!
How's this?
Oh! You look wonderful, miss!
It's so elegant, miss!
And this?
Elemental, miss!
This one?
Electrical!
This?
Elegy!
Will you be purchasing all of these?
Nah, I don't want 'em.
I want something a bit more rugged.
Come again!
Oh! A top-quality aperitif!
Oh! Two Poinderine
champagne-like beauties!
The whole town is brimming with
the finest ingredients around!
Damn, I can't decide
what to go for first!
I just found the main dish!
"Love-Love Pirates"
Awesome! What is this place?!
Everything here is a collector's dream!
Welcome!
Everything here once belonged to pirates
who returned alive from the Grand Line!
These goods are especially valuable.
Then all these items were used
during adventures in the Grand Line?!
That's absolutely correct!
We only do business with
warriors of the sea here,
so it'll be my personal pleasure to
serve a gentleman such as yourself!
What do you say? This was
the favorite gun of the Gold Roger!
What?! The Gold Roger?!
Yes!
How about it, sir?
Sh-Show me more!
Thanks! Come again!
Where are we going exactly?!
You broke my glasses.
I told you. I'll pay
you back... somehow.
You don't look like
you have any money!
Something about you just seems off!
T-True, I don't have any money, but...
Those wrinkles between your eyes!
You look like you
haven't eaten for days!
Is your mother sick?!
Did your wife run out on you, leaving
you to raise five kids on your own?!
L-Listen, you!
I don't need the details!
Just come with me!
Th-The Marines?
Here.
If you work for the Marines, you'll
never need to worry about money!
Screw that! Why should
I work for the Marines?!
You're just going to take off?!
I'm trying to do you a favor here!
Look, you...!
Sergeant Major! It's time for training!
Bye! Please work hard, okay?
Sergeant Major?!
Damn it! I'm getting nowhere like this!
Looks like three-mop style is best!
Let me try again!
You! What are you doing here?!
I knew it! You're Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Why the hell are you
in here cleaning?!
Intel says you've joined
Monkey D. Luffy's crew!
You're under arrest!
Well... now what?
What happened here?!
It seems someone attacked them!
There's no trace of the assailant!
"For your glasses."
Man, that freaked me out...
Dammit! She looks
way too much like Kuina!
Not to mention
she's a swordsman, too...
The world sure is a big place,
but I doubt I'll ever see her again.
I'd like some swords.
Ah, yes! Welcome!
Browse to your heart's content!
Ipponmatsu
Weapons Merchant
Our shop's been in business
for 200 years now!
I have 100,000 belly.
Sell me two swords.
What...? Two swords
for 100,000 belly?
Damn, he's a bum.
Fifty grand a sword will only
buy you some dull blades.
I'll make do with whatever.
I just can't afford anything else.
You'll make do with whatever?
Hmph! What an amateur!
That sword on his waist!
Could it be...?!
O-Oh, h-h-hold on. L-L-Lemme
see that sword of y-y-yours!
What's got you all agitated?!
J-Just let me see it!
Weirdo.
I-It's the real thing!
C-Calm down! This is your chance!
An absolute amateur just waltzed
right in here with a named blade!
You need to play it cool!
Wow, this is a nice sword
you've got here!
What do you say? I can take it off
your hands for 200,000 belly.
That'll net you a total
of 300,000 belly!
You'll be able to buy three
decent blades at 100,000 apiece.
Huh?! What're you talking about?!
Oh, alright! I-I'll make it
250,000... No! 300,000!
Then, 500,000...?
Look. Raise the price all
you want, this sword isn't–
Alright, then! I'll buy it
from you for 650,000 belly!
I get it! You're a pro!
How does 800,000 belly sound?!
Hello!
Did you finish polishing my Shigure?
Thank goodness! You're all right!
Someone went on a rampage
at the Marine outpost earlier.
You went missing, so I was worried!
How dense can she be?
Thank goodness! What a relief...
But the fact that you're
here, safe and sound...
means you must have scoffed
at my kind offer and ran off!
Here, take your money back.
I can't accept money
from someone that cold.
Besides, I already bought
some new glasses!
Don't tell me this sword
is the Wado Ichimonji!
It has to be the Wado Ichimonji!
Wado...?
Don't say it! Don't say it!
A beautiful straight temper line!
I believe it's one of the
twenty-one great grade swords!
See! Look at this! It's worth
no less than 10 million belly!
But how did you come
across a named blade?
Dammit! You just had to go
and run your mouth!
I'll sue for obstruction of business!
O-Obstruction of business?
I'm sorry! Did I say something wrong?
You're here for Shigure, right?!
I'm done polishing it!
Take it and get the hell out!
Why did you run straight into those?!
I-I'm sorry.
That klutz saved you!
Really though, a named blade
is wasted on a guy who
wields it without knowing its value.
All the swords in that barrel
are 50,000 belly apiece!
Just pick whatever two you want!
What's he so mad about?
You must really like swords
to want to carry three of them!
It reminds me of that
one bounty hunter!
A bounty hunter?
He's very well-known.
His name is Roronoa.
I hear that name a lot.
Yes, he's known all
throughout the East Blue...
but he's a demon!
Using swords to hunt
bounties is unforgivable!
Why has evil grown strong in this era?
All the famous sword masters
are pirates or bounty hunters...
And they possess the majority
of the world's named blades.
It's a real shame...
Well, everyone has their own
set of circumstances, right?
Every profession has to
keep up with the times somehow...
In any case, with my Shigure,
I'm going to hone my swordsmanship
and someday I'll retrieve all the named
blades from the criminals of the world!
The twelve supreme grade swords,
the twenty-one great grade swords,
and the fifty fine grade swords...
I'll risk my life for them!
You gonna take this sword, too?
The Wado Ichimonji, was it?
That is... It's not that I want
the named blades for myself.
I'm just saying I don't want
criminals to wield them!
This sword...
That sword! I think it's...
I thought so! Kitetsu III!
It's the Kitetsu III!
Its predecessor, the Kitetsu II,
is a great grade sword,
and the Kitetsu I before that is
listed as a supreme grade sword!
Mister! Is this sword
really only 50,000 belly?!
Y-Yeah...
Incredible! The grade of this
sword is very respectable!
That one! You have to buy that one!
It normally goes for one million belly!
It's an absolute no-brainer!
N-No! I can't sell it!
Well, sure! Selling this for 50,000
belly would be extremely odd!
No, that's not it...!
A cursed sword, huh?
You knew?!
No. I can just tell.
From their first incarnation,
every Kitetsu has been outstanding,
but each of them carries a curse!
Many famous master swordsmen
have met tragic deaths after
taking up Kitetsu swords.
Nowadays, you won't find a single
person willing to use a Kitetsu
because they'll take you from this world
even if you use one unknowingly!
I just wanna get rid of the thing,
but I'm afraid it'll curse me...
I-I'm sorry! I had no idea it was
such a terrifying sword!
I should've minded my own business!
I like it! I'll take it!
A-Are you a moron?! I can't sell it!
If you die because of it,
then it'd be like I killed you myself!
You're the moron! Just get the sale!
Honey!
Then let's do this.
My luck, or this thing's curse?
We'll find out which is stronger.
You can't...!
Stop! It's sharp enough
to take your arm off!
I'll take it.
Hey. Could you pick
another one for me?
S-Sure...
H-Hold it!
With a black lacquered sheath...
and its blade's uneven
temper pattern...
The fine grade sword Yubashiri!
My shop may not be much,
but this is the finest sword I own!
I can't afford it. I already
told you, I got no money.
Forget the money. And I don't
need any for the Kitetsu, either.
I'm sorry for trying
to cheat you earlier.
I've not seen the eyes of
a good swordsman in ages.
They say the sword
chooses the owner.
I'll be praying for your good fortune!
I definitely feel more
at ease with three swords.
Oh, what's this?
Hard to believe a miser like you
gave away the family treasure.
Can't a man entrust
another with his dream?
And I dream of you
taking out the trash!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
It scared me so much
that I still can't stand up...
What's that?
Lemme see.
Hawk Eye! What're you doing here?!
Calm down. I have
no qualms with you.
Where is your boss?
Camping out on an island like this...
What a carefree man.
B-B-Boss!
I-I-It's Hawk Eye!
Hey there, Hawk Eye.
This is unexpected...
I'm not feeling my best right now...
Have you come looking to fight?
I have no intention of
settling our grievances...
now that you're missing your left arm.
I encountered an interesting pirate...
and was suddenly reminded
of a story you used to tell.
A story about an interesting boy
from a certain small village...
You don't mean...!
So you've made it, Luffy!
Captain "Red-Haired" Shanks
Red Hair Pirates
In that case, Hawk Eye...
I can't just let you leave now.
That so, Hawk Eye?!
Okay! Drink up! Drink up!
Today's a celebration!
Did you not have a hangover?
Don't sweat it! It's a celebratory drink!
C'mon, now! C'mon, now!
Just gulp it straight down!
You ain't half bad!
Let's drink! Let's drink!
Yeah!
But, wait! Boss!
You said you felt sick 'cause
you drank too much before!
You dolt! How could I not drink
on a joyous day like today!
The sun's still up.
Don't sweat it!
Let's throw a party!
Hey! Luffy's a wanted man now!
Good for him!
Y'know, this village might just
produce a great pirate!
That'd be great!
Quiet, you knuckleheads!
Mr. Mayor!
What's so good about a criminal
coming from our village?!
A toast!
Honestly! Every last one of them...!
Come on, Mayor!
Luffy looks so happy here!
A pirate's a pirate!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Sure, but it's his dream.
Does that worry you?
His dream... or fate?