Ah! That was fun!
An elephant bluefin tuna, huh?
Ahhh! I can't wait to cook it!
Hm?
What's the matter, Nami?
The air has changed...
Air?
It's gonna rain.
Huh? When the
weather is this nice?
There's no doubt.
Hey, someone's
on the execution platform!
Who the heck is that?
That old man said that the pirate king died here 22 years ago.
He showed up?!
Yes! We were watching
the square like you told us,
and the guy from the wanted
poster just showed up...
Okay.
Let's go flashily.
So he just walked right up to it...
Just wait, you brat.
Wow! So this is what the pirate king saw.
Please wait...
Captain Smoker!
Come along, Tashigi.
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
KaitouYahiko
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
The Legend Has Begun
Hey, you over there!
Come down right away!
Why?!
That's a special execution platform owned by the World Government!
Come down right now!
Hmph! Now's not
the time for small fries.
Hm?
I've been looking for you, Luffy.
Long time no see...
Don't tell me you've forgotten my face.
How pretty!
She's stunning!
She is a woman of unrivaled beauty!
Her skin looks so smooth.
I don't know anyone like you.
Who are you?
I'll never forget you because you're the first man who hit me.
What? I hit you?
When your passionate
fist struck me...
Oh, it felt indescribable!
Hey... who's the most
beautiful in the East Blue?
That'd be you!
That's right. It's me.
There's no man in this world
that doesn't bow before my beauty.
And I like strong men.
I'll make you mine, Luffy.
Shut up! No way!
Who the heck are you?
You still haven't figured it out?
This is the police!
Come quietly, lady!
You're under arrest for
battery against the police captain!
And you over there! Get off the
execution platform already!
Oh? Who'd you say you'd arrest?
Captain, this is a problem! She's beautiful!
So what?! Should we arrest her?!
But she's so dazzling!
Surprise!
A terrorist bombing!
It's heading straight for her!
Wh-What the...
The fountain slipped!
What just happened?!
That was dangerous, you know.
Flashily sorry. But your smooth skin
is unharmed, of course.
So no harm done...
fairest Alvida.
Huh? Alvida?
I don't see Alvida.
I'm Alvida! You blockhead!
Really? You don't
look like her at all...
I changed a bit after eating a devil fruit.
The name of the fruit is...
the Smooth-Smooth Fruit!
No attack can hurt my skin
because it slides off it.
Unfortunately, my beauty
couldn't be improved that much.
The only big change was that I indeed lost my freckles.
N-No, that's not really what I meant.
After becoming a new person,
I joined forces with him since he also wanted to find you.
Now, the main star can make his flashy entrance!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Since the day you sent me flying,
I've been obsessed with getting revenge on you.
That determination fueled me until I finally found my crew.
It was indeed a great adventure.
I was missing parts of my body.
It was a tale full of both laughter and tears.
I call it
"Little Buggy's Great Adventure."
You see, Buggy was...
Wait, why am I telling you this, you bastard?!
What? Wait, what was your name again?
Boggy? No, Boogie?
It wasn't Behie...
Oh yeah! Buffoon!
Buffoon?! Stop messing around!
You're as irritating as ever, you moron!
Th-That's Buggy the Clown!
They're p-pirates!
It's the Buggy Pirates!
You people stay where you are!
I'm going to show you how scary I can be.
Oh, that's right! It's Buggy!
You just remembered it?!
Wh-What's going on?
Long time no see, rubber man.
How's Roronoa Zoro doing?
Okay, Cabaji. Good job.
I ask that my hundreds of billions
of followers
around the world watch closely!
We're about to host a super flashy public execution!
Monkey D. Luffy! You can't move even an inch now.
You should feel honored, Straw Hat!
You get to die in the same place as the king of the pirates.
The atmospheric pressure
is dropping like crazy.
I've never seen such
a sudden change before.
Now that you mention it,
I can feel the wind...
A storm is gonna hit this island!
A-A storm?
We'd better hurry back to
the ship or we'll be in trouble.
Will it be a big one?
Hey...!
Hm?
Zoro!
Have you seen him?
You mean Luffy?
Pirates're here!
Run!
It's Buggy the Clown!
What?!
Buggy the Clown!
What? Then...
Y-Yes!
Straw Hat Luffy, Buggy the Clown and Iron Club Alvida are all present.
The square has been taken over by notorious East Blue pirates!
Right under my nose...
What arrogant scum.
What should we do,
Captain Smoker?
Deploy Unit #1 to the port.
Unit #2 is to secretly surround
the square from the side streets.
And have the rest stand by within
shooting range of the square.
That's all.
Yes sir!
Give this order to Unit #1.
Yes sir?
"Destroy any pirate ships
as soon as you see them.
Not a single pirate is to leave this island."
An execution!
An execution is starting!
Buggy the Clown will
be executing Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy's gonna be executed?!
That idiot!
Let's go!
Take care of this!
S-S-S-Sanji!
Treat it like a lady! Got it?!
Oops!
We have to hurry, too!
Hey! Hey, Nami!
Where're we going?!
The harbor, of course!
H-Harbor? Oh yeah, of course!
Captain Smoker!
Please take a look.
Things are getting weird.
Hm?
Wha...! Th-That kid...
What's he doing?
Monkey D. Luffy. This can't be!
It looks like he's about to be killed!
Captain, are we
swooping in right away?
Idiot. Don't be hasty.
A pirate is about
to kill another pirate.
They're saving us the trouble.
Listen! Once that
Straw Hat's head rolls,
apprehend Buggy,
Alvida and the rest!
Don't give them time to think!
The pirate Monkey D. Luffy is going to die...
for the crime of pissing me off with his arrogance!
Let's do it with a bang!
This is my first
time seeing an execution.
We're executing you.
What?! Stop joking!
You stop joking!
Take this board off! You bastard!
Sure, we'll get on that!
The public execution will now begin!
Take it off! You liar!
You stupid head!
Ahhh! Stop it!
I don't wanna die!
I just saw a big cumulus cloud in the east.
A storm is definitely coming.
It's gonna be unimaginably big...
If Buggy, Luffy and the others go
crazy, the marines will take action.
We're done for if the ship is washed
out to sea when we have to escape.
I see. That really is a big deal!
The marines may have
already made their move.
The Going Merry is in danger!
Th-The Going Merry
will end up in Navy hands?
C-Come on, Nami! Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Hurry to the harbor!
Riding around on the Richie bike!
Who's that man?
Who? Who? Who's that man?!
Me!
So this is the rubber guy's ship...
It's bigger than the last ship.
Captain Buggy is about to begin the execution.
However...! Even if there is no chance for the rubber guy to escape,
it's better to be safe and burn their ship.
I'm so sorry... I won't do it again.
Please forgive me.
Like hell I will, you idiot!
Hmph! This is what happens
when someone goes against us.
I guess this is it for
the man I had my eye on...
You have a big audience;
do you wanna say something before you die?
No? Well, that's okay.
It wouldn't matter anyway since you're about to die.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Wha...
D-Did he just say "king of the pirates?!"
In this town, of all places...
That's crazy...
Well then, I guess this is it, you rubber twerp.
Stop...
the execution!
Zoro! Sanji!
It's Pirate Hunter Z-Zoro!
Zoro?!
So you're here, Zoro?!
But you're too late!
We'll bring down...
that platform!
Roronoa Zoro...
Guys... get them!
Leave it to us!
Big Sis Alvida!
Out of our way!
Not even Zoro can stop me now!
This is the end of your captain!
Damn bastard!
If I could just cut down the platform...
Listen.
The moment Monkey D. Luffy's
head rolls, we're to attack all at once.
All units. Prepare for battle.
Yes sir!
Zoro! Sanji!
Usopp! Nami!
Hurry up!
This is heavy!
Sorry. I'm... dead.
Idiot...
Don't say something so stupid!
He smiled!
I'm still alive.
Neat.
H-Hey,
reckon that was an act of god?
Phew, lucky me.
I was worried for a moment.
Stop talking nonsense.
Let's focus on getting out of here!
It's just one thing after another.
Now! Corner the pirates!
Yeah!
Here they come!
Amazing! Amazing!
It's suddenly gotten crazy!
Amazing! Ahh! Amazing!
Hey, Luffy!
Ahhh... Z-Zoro!
This is no time to be watching!
We need to get out of here!
We'd better hurry back to the ship or
we'll never be able to leave the island.
We won't be able to enter the Grand Line!
What?! That's no good!
The Straw Hats are running!
Catch them!
Go after them!
Why did he smile?
Did he know he'd be saved?
No. In that moment, he genuinely
thought his life was over.
He accepted death and smiled like he was ready.
Captain, we have to apprehend the pirates.
Hey... have you seen a pirate who
smiled on the execution platform?
N-Never! Even if
they're acting tough,
at the moment of death,
they all turn pale and die in despair.
Straw Hat smiled...
The pirate king smiled 22 years ago in this town...
on that execution platform.
Captain...
Where did Straw Hat go?
He ran towards the sea, sir.
What's Unit #1 doing? They should've
destroyed their ship by now.
Well... They had to return for
refitting because they couldn't...
use gunpowder due to the sudden rain.
What?!
A reserve unit is currently
moving to attack the ship instead.
Captain Smoker! If we let them set sail now, they'll enter the Grand Line!
The wind is blowing towards the west.
It's a tailwind for their ship.
Are these all coincidences?
It's as if the heavens have plans for that young man.
We'd better hurry
We're gonna make it to
or we'll be in trouble!
the Grand Line like this!
I'm White Hound Smoker.
On my honor as a
Navy Headquarters captain,
I won't let that
man leave this island!
What's with this storm?!
If we don't leave soon,
we'll be stuck here.
Nami was right when she said
we should hurry back to the ship!
Attacking me is a waste of time.
There isn't a man alive
who can touch my smooth skin.
For a second there,
I saw a field filled with flowers.
Captain Buggy, you're alive!
No way I'd die!
Buggy, this isn't good!
They're marines from headquarters.
There'll be no end to them!
I couldn't care less if the marines
want to stick their nose into...
Whose nose did you say is sticking out?!
I didn't say anything like that!
What're we going to do?
The rubber runt! Go after the rubber runt!
Mohji and Richie should have
burned down his ship by now.
He can't get off of this island.
We'll kick his ass as we
leave this island, guys!
Yeah!
Motor!
Yes, Captain!
Part-Part Buggy!
Here we go!
Igniting the bomb engine!
Set the slope!
Yes, Big Sis Alvida!
Friction-less...
Smooth-Smooth Tracks!
Don't let the pirates get away!
Wh... What's this smoke?!
What the hell...?!
White Out!
Smoker!
I don't have time for you, small fries!
H-He's too strong!
So that's the power
of Smoke-Smoke Fruit.
He took down Buggy's
crew in a split second...
Fire!
Captain! He caught
us all in one fell swoop!
How dare you, Smoker!
What's with this annoying steel net?!
Firing a weird pistol like that...
It's a special cage shot
the Navy developed to deal with devil fruit powers.
Dammit!
Bring me the Billower Bike!
I'm going after Straw Hat!
Yes, sir!
Dammit! Why did it have to start pouring down...
when we have to burn this ship down?!
Dammit! This is bad, Richie!
We can't get a fire going like this!
One more time!
Be patient, Richie! I'll feed you later.
What're you doing?!
Mohji!
Oh, it's you, the female thief.
Go, Richie!
Lethal Fresh Egg Star!
You...
Damn! The rain made my hand slip!
Richie! You're such a...!
Now! Let's get on the ship!
Yeah!
Hold it! You have to get past me!
Mohji, the first mate of the Buggy Pirates!
I won't let you board this...
Prepare to fire!
Marines!
This is bad!
Aim!
Fire!
Contact the cannon unit!
We'll capture the pirate ship!
Yes, sir!
N-N-N-Nami!
Yeah!
Which direction is the sea?
I can't tell where we're going
because of all this rain!
There they are!
What persistent bastards!
Should we stop and fight?
We don't have time.
Oh?
Who's that lady?!
I didn't realize you were
Roronoa Zoro, and a pirate to boot.
You gonna take this katana, too?
You... You lied to me!
What?! What'd you do to her?!
You just didn't ask for my name.
It's not like I meant to deceive you.
A rogue like you can't be left to use a named blade!
I'm going to claim your sword,
the legendary Wado Ichimonji!
You jerk! How dare you attack a lady!
Go on ahead.
Let's go.
Hey, Zoro! If you hurt the
lady, I won't forgive you!
Chief Tashigi!
I can't let you have this
sword no matter what.
Chief Tashigi lost...
The Chief Petty Officer never loses...
Well, then... I'm in a hurry, so...
Why aren't you finishing me?!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
You're lucky you were born as a boy, Zoro.
Even if men are physically stronger,
it's insulting not to be taken seriously because I'm a woman!
I'm sure you don't understand that burden,
but I often wish I was born as a boy!
I don't carry a sword as an accessory!
I hate the fact that you even exist!
Listen! Your face looks just like my friend who died a long time ago!
And now you're starting to talk just like her!
Stop imitating her, you copycat!
What?! Grow up!
I am who I am! I don't care
what your friend was like,
I'm the one who's been wronged here!
Don't you think before you speak?
Wh-What'd you say?!
I see the exit! The harbor is right there!
Hey, who is it now?
You're finally here...
Straw Hat Luffy.
Some things cannot be stopped.
The tides of time,
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
A pirate, huh? Fine by me.
I'm Captain Smoker.
I run Loguetown for the Navy.
You're under arrest.
Huh? Arrest? Forget it!
I'm just about to head to the Grand Line to become king of the pirates!
King of the pirates?
I refuse to get
arrested in a place like this!
Then you'll have to beat me first.
Hey, Luffy...
Sanji, go on ahead. I'll be right there.
Fire!
Fire the cannons!
If we stay here any longer,
the Going Merry will be sunk!
A-Are you going to set sail?
Luffy and the others aren't here yet!
We don't have any other choice!
It's better than sinking here!
Right rudder full!
Then what're we going to do
about Luffy and the others?
We'll pick them up later.
Don't let them get away! Follow them!
Nami!
Sanji!
Nami, I'm back!
Where're Luffy and Zoro?
We'll have to pick up those damn morons later.
Sanji!
Behind you!
Dammit! This is endless!
I'll cover his back! Get closer!
We can't head back because of the strong current.
Ahhh, dammit!
Usopp!
Bastards!
Usopp! Sanji!
What?! What?! What's going on?!
I ate the Smoke-Smoke Fruit. So my
body can become smoke at will.
What's wrong? Finished already?
Gum-Gum Gatling!
What? Eww, that's gross!
White Blow!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Get it now?
You can't enter the Grand Line.
Didn't I just tell you that?
You're wanted for 30 million belly?
Looks like you've run out of your devil's luck.
Don't be so sure.
You're...
Wh-What's going on? Who's that?
The government is after your head.
The world is waiting for our answer.
Th-This is...
Wh-What just happened?
Luffy!
Nami!
We'd better hurry up or the
ship will drift away!
Alright!
Gum-Gum...
Wha?!
W-Wait!
I have a bad feeling...
Rocket!
Ahhh, I knew it!
Everyone...
Gee, that sudden gust was a lucky break for us.
We were able to escape because I kept calm.
Where're we going now?
Let's head straight to the Grand Line.
How nostalgic!
If that's your decision, then go!
Why? Why did you
help that man... Dragon?!
Why would I interfere with another man's voyage?
Set sail! We're going after Straw Hat!
What?
We're entering the Grand Line.
B-But, Captain!
This island is your post.
I don't know what
the higher-ups would say if...
Just tell them I don't care about their orders!
I'm coming with you!
Chief Tashigi!
I won't forgive Roronoa.
I'm definitely going to capture him!
It feels like the ship's gonna capsize!
See that light?
Is that a lighthouse?
The entrance to the Grand Line is just past that guiding light.
The Grand Line is beyond that light...
What do you wanna do?
D-Do we have to enter during a storm like this?
Okay, then!
Shall we hold a launching ceremony
to commemorate entering this great sea?
Hey!
Sure!
Let's do it!
To find the All Blue!
To be king of the pirates!
To be a master swordsman!
To draw a map of the world!
T-To be a brave warrior of the sea!
On to the Grand Line!
Yeah!