This weather's great!
If we hold course,
we should see the naval base soon!
You're pretty incredible, Koby!
We're really gonna get there?
Of course!
Sailors should at least
be able to navigate the seas!
This is no time
to be laughing, Luffy-san.
He's being held prisoner there.
The infamous Pirate Hunter...
Roronoa Zoro!
The man slashes up his marks
like a bloodthirsty beast.
People say he's a demon
in human form!
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
Soundtracking
Halee
obtained everything
the world had to offer.
Quality Control
Gaijin
JT-421
Pepperjack
Gaijin
JT-421
Pepperjack
His final words lured all sorts of adventurers to the sea.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
PhosCity
My treasure?
It's yours, if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Everything is right where I left it!
Translation
DemonRin
FUNimation
Raws
Df68
Now pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
あ
re go
ri
り
ing
tta
った
った
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
shin
針
しん
なん
じゅう
use
jyuu
滞
たい
shin
針
しん
なん
te
て
jyuu
渋
じゅう
tai
滞
たい
って
って
it's
でん
じゃ
tsu
な
ja
い!
でん
じゃ
na
な
i!
い!
th
en
it's
っか
っか
いい!
いい!
った
った
ット
イン
ット
イン
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
We made it! The naval town!
The Pirate King and
the Master Swordsman
H-Hey, Luffy-san!
You're not serious about him
joining your crew, are you?
I haven't decided yet,
but if he's a good guy, then–
He was caught because he's not a good guy!
Mmm! Yum!
Can you tell me if
Zoro's at that base?
I think the name "Zoro"
is taboo around here.
Let's see the base anyway.
You wanna become a marine, right?
Y-Yes... But I'm not really ready yet...
Rumor has it a guy named
Captain Morgan is at this base, and...
What a funny town!
No, it's weird.
Zoro's name I get, but why are they
afraid of a Navy captain's name?
I suddenly have a bad feeling
about this...
You sure they weren't
just really excited?
That clearly wasn't it!
All right! We're here!
I finally made it!
I guess this is
where we part ways, Luffy-san.
We didn't know each other long, but–
There we go!
Luffy-san!
What in the world are you doing?!
Now, where's this demon?!
He wouldn't be out in the open.
I'm sure he's in a cell or something.
Found him!
Perfect!
See! There he is!
I'm telling you!
He wouldn't be out–
A b-black bandanna
and a belly band...
That's R-Roronoa Zoro!
If we untie his ropes,
we'll easily get him outta here!
D-Don't be stupid!
If he got loose,
what do you think he'd do?!
I bet he'd try
to kill you, Luffy-san!
Don't worry! I'm tough!
Is this guy for real?!
Hey, you two.
You're annoying.
Beat it!
Luffy-san! You're a goner
if he joins your crew!
Oh, no! Luffy-san,
you have to stop her!
She'll be killed!
What?
You must be hungry!
I made you some onigiri.
You got a death wish, kiddo?
Go home!
Mister, you haven't eaten anything
this whole time.
Here!
It's my first time making them,
but I worked real hard!
I'm not hungry!
Now, stop bugging me and leave!
B-But...
I don't want 'em!
Don't make me kick you!
Picking on little girls?!
Helmeppo
Captain Morgan's Son
You seem surprisingly well, Roronoa Zoro.
What's with that
weird guy down there?
Thank goodness!
He must be with the Navy!
That girl will be in good hands!
Oh? Well aren't those some tasty-looking onigiri?
Don't...!
It's too sweet!
You made them all sugary!
Onigiri are best with salt! Salt!
But... I thought sweet
might taste better...
– Take this! And this!
– Stop it! Stop it!
H-How can he be so cruel?
I-I worked so hard
to m-make those...
Didn't you get the memo?
"Those caught aiding
criminals will be executed!
–Captain Morgan of the Navy"
So, even the brats here know how scary Daddy can be.
"Daddy"?
Then that's Captain Morgan's son!
You. Throw the kid over the wall.
Sir?!
I said, throw her over the wall!
Got a problem following orders?
Don't make me tell Daddy!
Y-Yes, sir... Right away!
No!
Th-Thanks...
Are you okay, Luffy-san?!
Are you all right?!
What a horrible guy...
Does anything hurt?
Damn you.
You sure are stubborn
about staying alive.
Yeah! I'm gonna
survive the whole month!
Well, good luck with that.
Only 10 more days!
Assuming you live that long!
What drives someone
to be so cruel, Luffy-san?!
He's gone?!
I hear you're a bad guy.
Are you still here?
Getting put out here
for all to see...
You're pretty strong, right?
What's it to you?!
If it were me, I'd probably starve
to death in three days!
Then you lack spirit.
I will live through this...
I swear it!
You're a pretty weird guy!
Wait!
Could you... get that for me?
You're gonna eat this?
It's more of a mud ball now.
Just shut up and give it here!
Told you so.
It was good.
Thanks for the food.
Really?!
Yeah! He ate every last bite!
I'm so glad!
But then, is Zoro really
as bad as they say?
He's not!
After all, he let himself
get crucified in my place...
Huh? What do you mean?
It's all that Helmeppo's fault.
He's Captain Morgan's son...
Outta the way!
Make way for my precious,
adorable little pooch!
Get in the way,
and you get executed!
No! Stop that!
Hey, you!
You got some kinda problem
with my adorable pooch?!
Rika! Stop that!
We'll get in trouble!
– Oh, crap!
– He's in trouble now!
Helmeppo punches and kicks him
while he's tied up!
I... I...
So that's what's happening.
I'm hungry!
Let's get a free meal!
Hey! Bring me a drink!
Oh, yes.
To alleviate my boredom,
I'll have Zoro executed tomorrow.
Save the date, everyone!
W-What the hell're you doing?!
Luffy-san! Please stop!
This guy's scum!
Y-You hit me!
I'm Captain Morgan's son, you know!
So what?!
When I tell Daddy,
he'll execute you!
Fight me yourself!
Luffy-san! Calm down!
Do you want the Navy
as your enemy?!
I've made up my mind, Koby!
I'm... gonna get Zoro
to join my crew!
I am...
great!
Yes! You're exactly right, Captain Morgan, sir!
Then why are the recent tributes
to me falling short?
W-Well, the citizens' wallets
do have their limits...
It's a matter of respect.
Wouldn't you agree?
Daddy!
I want you to kill someone for me!
You again?
You've got nothing but free time.
I'll untie you if you'll join my crew.
Say what?!
I'm looking for people
to join my pirate crew.
Forget it! I'm not desperate enough
to become an outlaw!
Screw that!
What's wrong with being a pirate?!
Pirates are despicable!
Who'd wanna be one?!
Oh, gimme a break!
You're already known
as an evil bounty hunter!
People can say whatever they want,
but I've never done anything I regret.
I will live through this...
and achieve my goal.
Oh? I see.
But I've decided
you're gonna join my crew!
Like it's up to you!
So you're a swordsman?
Yeah. But that idiot son
took my stuff...
I'll get your treasure back!
What?!
You'll get your sword
when you join my crew!
Don't screw with me!
He's... going in all by himself?!
All right! Keep it steady!
Stand it up in one shot!
Daddy! Won't you go
and avenge me?!
That guy hit me in the face!
Not even you've done that!
Do you know why
I've never hit you before? Do you?
S-Sure... Is it because I'm–
Yes. Because you're...
"Axe-Hand" Morgan
Navy Captain
my hopeless son who isn't even worth hitting!
Let's get one thing straight!
The only great one
around here is me! I'm great!
By the way, I heard a rat snuck
into the crucifixion grounds.
I-I-I mean, there was that one runt,
but I saw to her punishme–
You killed her, I hope?!
N-No! I mean,
she was just a little kid...
You, there!
Go to town and execute her!
Y-You can't mean that, sir!
She's just a little girl!
I can't in good conscience...
Anyone who disobeys my orders
is a traitor, even little brats.
B-But... I can't do it!
Lieutenant!
Y-You didn't have to go that far!
I ascended to the rank of captain
with nothing but my own strength.
Listen! In this world,
rank is everything!
Captain is the top rank
on this base,
which makes me superior to everyone here!
In other words,
everything I do is right!
Right, you maggots?!
Yes, sir!
You're absolutely right!
We can execute the brat later.
For now, observe!
It took years of construction,
but the symbol of my authority
is finally complete!
Now, stand it up!
Display my greatness
at the apex of this base!
That's weird. There's no one here...
If I find the idiot son,
he can lead me to Zoro's sword.
Pull! Pull!
You, there!
You bumped it, didn't you?!
I heard something up there...
I-I'm sorry, sir! I was careless!
I told you this statue embodies me!
The slightest scratch or speck of dirt
is the same as treason!
I'll check it out!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
Now you pay!
I jumped too far!
What is that?!
It flew up from below!
Got it!
Sorry...
Seize him! I'm going to kill him!
Right away, sir!
Daddy! That's him! He punched me!
Oh! It's you!
I've been looking for you!
Come with me!
I need you to return something!
Let me go!
Master Helmeppo!
After him! Don't let him escape!
Captain! Someone's
on the crucifixion grounds!
What?!
It's one traitor after another...
You need to escape, Zoro-san!
You'll be killed
for doing that, you know!
I can't stand by
and watch marines act like this!
I want to be an honorable marine!
Stop! I'm not running! In just 10 more days–
Your execution is tomorrow!
What?!
Helmeppo never intended
to honor your agreement!
So Luffy-san got angry and clocked him!
He did?
And now the Navy's
after Luffy-san.
I won't ask you to be a pirate,
but please, help Luffy-san!
He's the only one
who can save you.
And I think, right now, you're
the only one who can save him.
End of the line!
Where's Zoro's sword?!
I-I'll tell you! I'll tell you!
Just stop dragging me!
All right! Tell me!
In my room... We just passed it...
What? Why didn't you say so?!
Now we gotta go back.
Halt!
Release the young master!
No.
Shoot if you want!
No! Don't!
Move it!
For the crime of treason against me,
I sentence the two of you to death!
This the room?!
Bingo!
But there're three of 'em!
Hey! Which sword is Zoro's?
Oh, he passed out.
Koby!
Your actions here have
been interesting, to say the least.
You and that straw hat kid
are plotting a coup d'etat, correct?
I've always fought alone.
Unlike a certain bastard who hides
behind his terrified flunkies!
Roronoa Zoro...
Don't you dare underestimate me!
You may be strong,
but that's meaningless
before my authority!
Aim!
I...
can't afford to die here!
That's the match!
The winner is Kuina,
with 2,000 wins and 0 losses!
D-Damn it...
You're still weak, Zoro.
You're such a disappointment.
Especially for a boy.
Hey! Zoro isn't weak!
He's the strongest guy here!
He can even beat grown-ups!
But he's weaker than me.
Even with two swords,
a weakling's still a weakling.
You whine like puppies.
You losers should keep quiet.
Another defeat, Zoro.
Even after you've come so far.
Sensei!
Are you giving her secret training
'cause she's your daughter?!
Don't cheat!
No, no. Of course I'm not.
Zoro has indeed improved,
but Kuina has grown stronger as well.
Zoro?
I'm gonna wash my face.
Damn it!
Why can't I beat Kuina?!
Why?! Why?!
I'm gonna be the world's
greatest swordsman! So why?!
Zoro?!
What're you doing out here?
Right back at you! What are you
doing here at this hour?!
I'm here to challenge you
to our 2,001st duel!
I intend to make this our last fight!
I'm going to end this!
Fight me with a real sword!
You have one, right?!
Against me?
Sure.
My 2,001st win.
Damn it!
This sucks...
I'm the one
who should be crying.
Huh?
When girls grow up,
they're naturally weaker than boys.
It won't be long before
even you catch up to me.
You're always saying you'll become
the world's greatest swordsman.
But my father said that dream's
impossible for me because I'm a girl.
I understand...
I understand that's how it is!
But... But it's frustrating!
You're lucky, Zoro.
You were born a boy.
I want to be the world's
greatest swordsman too!
My breasts are
even starting to grow.
If only... If only
I had been born a man...
How can you cry like that
after you beat me?!
It's not fair!
You're my goal!
Zoro...
Boy this! Girl that!
Is that gonna be your excuse
when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
You're insulting all the hard training
I've been doing!
So enough of that crap!
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will be
the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete and see
who gets there!
You dummy. You're so weak...
– It's a promise!
Gotta get stronger!
Gotta hold more swords!
If two's not enough,
then I'll use three!
What do you guys want?
Kuina...
Kuina's dead...
Apparently, she slipped
and fell down the storehouse steps.
The storehouse?
She was looking for a whetstone
to sharpen her beloved sword.
What would she need that for?
I don't know...
She was just a child too.
Who knows why anyone does anything...
No one could predict
something like this.
People are...
such fragile things, Zoro.
Sensei...
Let me have... that sword.
Kuina's sword?
I'll get stronger
for the both of us now!
I'll get so strong
my name reaches the heavens!
I'm gonna be
the world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her...
I...
Yes. It's yours.
I leave Kuina's spirit and dreams...
with you.
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
Fire!
– What are you–
– Luffy-san!
Straw Hat?!
No way...
That won't work!
I told you I was tough!
Wh-Who the hell... are you?!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who's gonna be
king of the pirates!