Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Tsuki
Yibis (Opening)
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
Soundtracking
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
Video editing
Sewil
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Raw provider
Crunchyroll
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose! I'll find One Piece. I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
B Block on Fire!
Outlandish Competitors and King Punch!
Garp was a demon to us pirates back then.
It's been decades since then, but my wound still hasn't healed.
Hey, is that true?!
No, no, no... I just misheard him! I'm Lucy!
I will make you to pay for what your grandfather did to me.
Blame grandpa for that!
So you are Garp's grandson!
No, I'm not!
If you're the real Straw Hat Luffy,
I'm gonna cut you down here and now!
If I had found out about the existence of Garp's son Dragon sooner,
you would have never been born.
Hey, what happened?!
Don Chinjao is going crazy!
That's not good!
Hey, wait a minute, pops!
Take that beard off!
Stop! No!
You've got to be kidding! Is he gonna attack again?!
I don't know how much weaker he's become since then,
but his bounty was over 500 million in his prime!
Damn you, Don Chinjao! Don't get in my way!
He's my prey!
Cavendish drew his sword!
Is that it?!
One of the world famous swords, Durandal!
Here we go!
Military Head!
Beautiful Sword!
Blue Bird!
It's piercing his head!
No, it isn't!
They're going at it!
I can't stab him with Durandal!
A head that can't be stabbed by a sword, and the power to push back a giant!
These guys aren't human!
I can't take him down while holding back!
You bastard!
I told you to knock it off!
He knocked down Chinjao!
Who is that little bearded guy?!
Oh my...
Wow! It didn't phase him!
Could the legend be true?
They say he broke up the
Ice Continent with a head-butt!
The Ice Continent?!
It didn't work at all. I thought I used enough strength.
Oh my...
It seems like the two of you are quite strong!
But you still need more training!
It's true. That strength... There is no mistaking that you're Straw Hat.
What do you want from me? Leave me alone!
Stealing others' popularity,
and being born as the grandson of a demon,
you really incur everybody's hatred.
Neither of those things are my fault!
I'm Lucy, by the way.
If you keep interfering, I'm gonna kill you too, young knight!
Wait, old man! That's enough!
If you cause trouble here, they'll disqualify you!
It's Sai and Boo from the Flower Country.
Let go of me, my dear grandsons!
No! I don't know what's going on, but you have to stop!
I finally found it! A way to settle the duel with Garp!
If we get disqualified here,
we can't achieve what we came here for, Grandpa!
Hey, you guys! What's going on over there?!
We'll have to ask you to leave if you're fighting outside of the ring!
Guards, huh?
I don't care if I get disqualified here or not!
I'm going to...
Where did he go?!
Old man, if it's about the guy with the fake beard,
he's in C Block with us!
If you wanna kill him, do it in the ring!
You're not getting away, Straw Hat!
I'll take your life before the match starts!
What a mess. What was that all about?
I heard the word "Straw Hat".
If you heard "Straw Hat" they were probably talking about the pirate, Straw Hat Luffy.
Do you think he entered this competition?
No way!
Boy...
I promised Franky that I wouldn't let anybody know who I am!
I-I can't believe it! Tank was beaten!
The captain of Dressrosa's Self-Defense Army, Tank Lepanto was eliminated!
He fell prey to the evil duo, Abdullah and Jet!
They keep using dirty tricks!
Captain Tank!
Over 100 competitors have been eliminated,
and there are only 30 some men left in the ring!
It won't be much longer.
It doesn't matter how tough the remaining one will be as long as we have the King Punch...
Who's next?!
If you want to bleed, come out!
Tank Lepanto was taken out
by the evil combination of Abdullah and Jeet.
Bellamy!
"Atrocious"! "Evil"!
Those are the only words fitting to this man!
In the meantime, the Jiaokungdo martial artist, Blue Gilly
and the mysterious gladiator, Ricky
are fighting each other with all they have!
That Fish-Man is so strong!
He's been knocking out all of his opponents with a single blow!
That's so cool!
I'm so excited!
Stop him!
Unbelievable!
How much more does Bartolomeo want to offend these people?!
Why is nobody kicking his ass?!
In front of this huge audience,
he pulled it out and started peeing!
No one has ever done such a thing in this Colosseum!
It feels so good!
Somebody, stop him!
Here comes that somebody!
Some of us are taking this thing seriously, brat!
What?
You'll have to excuse me for attacking you from behind!
Hey, wait! I'm defenseless!
The hero who came in to punish him is the Fish-Man warrior, Hack!
Four Thousand Tile...
Do it! Kick his ass, Hack!
Punch!
Psyche!
What did he do?! Hack is the one on the ground?
What's going on?!
What was that?
W-Who the hell are you?!
Bartolomeo!
Hack was defeated!
He was beaten without even landing a punch!
What did Bartolomeo do to him?!
Damn! I was rooting for Hack! That bird brain!
Gatz-san, you're supposed to be unbiased!
There is still no clear winner!
24 competitors remain in B Block.
It's winding down, huh?
Such cheek...
Almost everybody has wounds of some kind!
It's about time!
Powerful competitors are getting eliminated too, one after another!
Following Hack, the unknown gladiator, Ricky, has also got taken down!
Blue Gilly is strong!
Blue Gilly-sama!
What do you think you're going to cut with that sword, old man?
I guess you can't fight against age.
I can't stand all this cheering.
I can't stand you, Doflamingo!
There aren't that many men left thanks to Dagama's tactics!
When Dagama gives us the cue, we'll disband.
Then we'll fight amongst ourselves until one of us wins.
Men! Take care of Blue Gilly while we're fighting together!
Okay!
Dagama?!
You did a fine job, you stupid dogs!
Why?
Hey, you haven't given us the cue!
Don't tell me... Dagama!
You two!
Sorry! I've been told to hunt you dogs!
Were you plotting together...
To get rid of us from the beginning?
I will pay you later! Your job is done now!
Dagama!
Warriors who can't use their brains just end up as pawns on a battlefield!
I'll be counting on you, Longleg man!
Now that you turned your back to me, you're dead too.
Blue Gilly.
What?!
You betrayed me, Blue Gilly!
Dagama the tactician was eliminated!
Way to go, Longleg guy!
Blue Gilly-sama!
I can't believe people would trust a
dubious guy like him in the first place.
What's this? Meanwhile, on the other side...
Bellamy went in for the attack but ended up on the ground!
What did Bartolomeo do?!
I-I can't believe it!
Our Bellamy is barely breathing!
What devil fruit did he eat?!
Bellamy...
It's just like with Hack! Bellamy took damage from his own attack!
What did he do to him?
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
Now what are you gonna do, Elizabello?
Nothing is more helpless than a king without his court.
Everyone's dying to take your head.
Dagama did a great job.
The time has come.
All that is left is to throw it!
You guys are the ones who were protected while we were in that battle formation.
Because nothing is more dangerous than an exposed blade.
Isn't that right, punk?
Hey, I just thought of something.
What?
There was a report about the king of Prodence.
They said he destroyed an enemy country's fort with a single punch.
No way! He must've used some kind of weapon.
No, they say it could even take out one of the Four Emperors.
What?
If that's true, everything in front of him,
including these seats will get destroyed!
What?!
No way! That can't be true!
I've heard those reports too!
No! He wouldn't throw such a dangerous thing at a place like this!
There is a restlessness in the air!
The king who kept quiet in the battle formation is now on the move!
We of the Prodence Kingdom will be taking the Flame Fruit!
I've got a terrible feeling about this!
You've got to be kidding!
Whoa-whoa, this is bad!
Run!
Maybe he really did destroy the fort!
You're so persistent! What are you doing?! Get off me!
No way! Don't underestimate the power of my spring!
King...
I'm gonna kill Elizabello!
Outta my way!
Shooting...
Punch!
How...
How powerful was that?!
I don't think anyone in the ring could have survived!
That was a hell of a punch!
I've never seen anything like that before!
Bellamy! Blue Gilly!
And all other potential winners have been eliminated!
The winner of the B Block battle royale, against 138 contestants,
came from the Prodence Kingdom...
Hey, look! Somebody's there!
You see? Right over there!
The audience in that direction didn't get blown away
because he defended it!
Barrier!
People can create barriers by crossing their fingers.
Even kids know that!
I ate the Barrier Fruit and became a barrier man.
Barrier Crash!
"The Fighting King", Elizabello II has been knocked out!
The winner of B Block is...
Dammit!
...Bartolomeo!
Every one of you can go to hell!
Go away!
Screw you!
What? That strange guy won.
I will take the Flame Fruit to that person for sure!
Inside the Colosseum
Passages to the Audience Seating
Then, you, too?!
Shh! Shh!
Not so loud!
You're plotting to destroy the factory too?!
Indeed! My friends and I have been carrying out preparations for it!
Tell me where it is! I'll destroy it right away!
You can't do that!
Because we want to save the workers in the factory!
Our plan is a big project that could lead to the fall of this country!
If you have the nerve and are determined to go against Doflamingo,
I'm going to tell you everything about this tragic kingdom of Dressrosa!