Hey.
Who are you going to push into the sea?
Seems you don't know your opponents.
Don't hold back! Throw them overboard!
What's that?
It's Jinbei!
Fishman Karate!
Spear Wave!
Hey!
Oh, how careless of me.
That's the ship we're gonna use, isn't it?
Gomu Gomu no...
Oh no! Oh no! Run away, Straw Hat!
Champion Stamp!
It's no good! My wax won't work against him now!
Doru Doru Cancellation!
That was close!
Venom Demon!
Let's get out of here!
Hurry!
Hell's Judgement!
Damn it all!
Hey... Help me!
Take me with you!
You idiot! Don't touch me!
The poison is... spreading!
Doesn't matter if it's wax or stone...
The poison keeps spreading like an infection!
Damn it! Now the Doru Doru armor is completely useless!
Impel Down Main Entrance
What happened to Straw-chan and the others?
How's it going with the warships?
I can hear gunfire, but I can't really tell what's happening in that mist!
I'm sure they'll be able to steal one of the warships, but...
In any case, they're pretty far away.
It's going to take a while for them to steal one and then bring it back.
Doesn't that mean that Magellan might get here first?
Straw Hat Luffy is strong and all but...
I doubt he'll be able to hold Magellan back very long...
Straw-chan...
Damn it! Please hurry, Jinbei!
Force them into the sea! Don't let them take the ship!
What's with this guy's body?!
His whole body is made of blades!
It's the Supa Supa Fruit.
Supa Supa: Sound of slicing
I just remembered who this guy is!
He's the West Blue assassin, Daz!
Sables!
It's only a matter of time before they take the ship!
That would be a huge disgrace for the Navy!
Sink it, immediately!
Yes, Sir!
Prepare to attack!
It's that thing from before!
Damn it, our gunpowder's all wet!
Jinbei, huh?!
Load another battery, and shoot him!
Hurry! Hurry! He's right behind us!
Hey! Guys, are you there?!
That's Straw-chan's voice!
We've gotta run!
There's some monstrous thing chasing after them!
It's Magellan! There's nowhere to run!
We got a warship yet?!
Straw-chan! We're still waiting for a ship to get on!
What?!
Hell Wink!
Iva-chan?!
What a surprise!
It... It seems Vi made it in time...
He hit the back of his head so hard he passed out!
Iva-san! And Inazuma, too! You're alive!
Thank goodness!
Iva-sama!
Those two!
Straw Hat! It's from Jinbei!
A Baby Snail Phone!
Well done, you two!
Why did you even come along?
Luffy-kun, so you made it?
I'm here! He's still chasing us, though!
We're gonna hit a dead end at the exit!
Forgive me. We've stolen a ship, but we're too far away from you!
But don't stop moving!
Jump straight into the sea!
Get everyone to throw themselves into the ocean!
What are you saying, Jinbei?!
We're in the Calm Belt, you know!
You can leave the rest to me!
Do what he says!
Wha-?!
Three! Come help me one more time!
Are you insane?! If we leap into the ocean, we'll die for sure!
He works for the Government! He's not worthy of our trust!
That damn Fishman bastard!
He's Ace's friend!
I trust him!
To the sea? If you think you can, then just try and get away!
The moment you touch the water, you'll be in the Sea Kings' nest!
Be careful! Don't let even a drop of his poison touch you!
That's impossible!
It's over!
Hell's Judgement!
Gear Third!
This is a special service!
Candle Wall!
It's pointless!
Gomu Gomu no...
Gigant Stamp!
He pushed him back!
The poison's still coming toward us!
Jumping into the sea is our only hope?!
Here it comes!
Iva-chan! Iva-chan, wake up!
We're in trouble!
Iva-chan! Wake up!
Hey! Hurry and wake up!
Hmm? What?
We gotta hurry!
Who are vyou? Straw Hat Boy's son?
Use that move of yours!
The Wink!
Okay then.
Hey, you can't be serious! If we do that...
Here Vi go!
Hey, wait a second, Iva-sama!
Your plan is pointless!
If you enter the sea without a ship, there's no hope for you!
Everyone, grab on to his face!
His face?!
I will not let you escape!
Hell...
Wink!
You won't get away!
We're falling!
There's something under the ships!
What is that?!
What?
W-We landed on something!
Hey! Look at this!
What is this?!
So you made it in time...
I'm sorry for calling you out to such a dangerous sea!
It's a school of whale-sharks!
Jinbei called them here!
Awesome!
He's amazing!
We did it! We've finally reached the warship!
We managed to escape!
It's like I'm dreaming! I never thought I'd make it out of Impel Down!
We don't have time to celebrate yet!
We've got to hurry and get out of here!
We did it!
Thanks, whale-sharks!
You saved us!
Be careful on your way back!
Vwe have to cure Inazuma's poisoning.
Bring all the medicine vyou can find in the medical office!
Yes!
I'm never going back to that Hell!
Me neither! I'm turning over a new leaf! I'm gonna go home and be with my family!
We are free!
And who do you have to thank for that?
Go on, say it!
Captain Buggy!
I never thought they'd make it that far...
Marines, send one of your ships back here.
I'll come with you, and take them down myself.
Understood.
It looks like they haven't noticed that they're trapped yet.
Rear Admiral! We have repaired the cannons that Jinbei disabled.
Very well.
All ships, open fire!
They've started shooting!
This is really bad!
How many ships are there, anyway?!
The entire fleet is chasing us!
We're hit!
Everyone ranked Vice Admiral or above has already been called to Marineford...
but a warship is a warship. They're still tough, no matter who's onboard!
Don't you realize that it's useless?!
The Gates of Justice won't open...
to pirate scum like you!
That's right! I forgot about this!
This is bad! These gates will never open for us!
Oh no! We've made it this far, and now we've hit a dead end!
Don't imitate me!
What're we gonna do, you damn shark?!
We'll break through!
That's just impossible!
This is the worst possible situation!
How can you be so calm?!
First of all, we've gotta protect the ship! Don't let them sink it!
Are you just gonna sit back and take their attacks?
This is a warship too, remember?
Aren't you gonna shoot back, you worthless fools?!
That was gonna be my suggestion!
Let's shoot back at them, men!
Understood, Captain Buggy!
Sables!
Gomu Gomu no Balloon!
How's that?!
Damn these prisoners...
They must have realized that they're trapped, so why are they still heading towards the Gates of Justice?
The Gates can only be opened by operators inside Impel Down.
There's no other way to open them!
Fire! Send them to the bottom of the sea!
The Gates of Justice are opening!
How can this be?! What's going on?!
Why are the Gates opening?!
It's open!
H-How can this be?
Is it a trap?!
Alright! I don't know why, but the Gates are opening!
What?!
Warden Magellan! Hurry aboard!
No, wait!
Impossible! Why are the Gates opening?!
Are you sure opening the Gates was a good idea...
Warden Magellan?
Yes, this will do. Have my orders ever been wrong?
No, it's not that I doubt you...
As soon as their ship has passed through, you are to close the Gate immediately.
Do you understand?
Very well, Sir.
Don't let them escape!
Letting them get away is unforgivable! Fire!
Are these Magellan's orders? What is he thinking?!
I don't understand what he intends to achieve by doing this.
What is Warden Magellan thinking?!
Uh, well, I don't think this was done by the Warden.
He was just standing on the bridge by the main entrance.
Why-? What is happening?!
Control Room! What are you doing?!
Who told you to open the Gates of Justice?!
W-Warden?!
Oh, my.
Is that really true?
Bon-chan...?
You!
That's right!
It's me!
I tricked you again!
It was a fake?!
Look! The Gates are closing!
They're closing!
If we can get through, the Navy will be trapped on the other side!
He was just with us at the exit!
The only reason we managed to meet Iva-chan and the others,
and escape from there, was because Bon-chan was with us!
And you're telling me we should just go on without him?!
There's no time to waste.
Are we just gonna abandon him?!
We've already abandoned countless allies who fell along the way!
Do you intend to return there and fight Magellan again?!
Then there will be even more sacrifices!
We'd waste even more time, too!
If someone hadn't stayed behind, the Gates would never have opened for us!
I'm the one who can pull it off best.
I'll open the Gates of Justice!
And what do you intend to do afterwards?
If I told you that, it wouldn't be as cool, would it?
Don't tell Straw-chan anything before we part ways!
Words are not needed for an Okama's parting.
It's still connected.
The Baby Snail Phone has a very short range.
As soon as the Gates close, we'll lose contact with him.
How dare you transform into the Warden?!
Good thing I memorized your face back then!
Open your eyes, Hannyabal!
What happened here?!
W-Warden! Let go of me!
Touch.
How dare you?!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan?!
Hey! Can you hear me? Bon-chan?!
Why are you doing this again...
just like you did last time?!
Jinbei! Didn't you promise not to tell him before we'd lost contact?!
Weren't we gonna escape together?!
You just keep saving me over and over again!
If you're there, then answer me, Bon-chan!
Is that how it is...?
That Okama-guy...
he stayed behind alone for our sake...?
Bon-chan!
Answer us, Brother Bon!
Why won't you answer?!
Bon-chan!
Mister Two!
Mister Two, you're...
I'm so sorry for everything!
Bon-boy!
Fire!
Don't let them get away!
Blow them to pieces!
Bon-chan!
Bon-chan... The Gates are closing.
We're... going.
Thank you!
Brother Bon! Thank you!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Straw-chan...
You have to save your brother, no matter what!
I'm sure... you can...
save your brother!
Bon-chan!
The Gates are closing!
Sink them!
Long time no see!
I'm perfectly okay!
Quit joking around!
Straw-chan! I've come to save you!
In the name of our friendship!
Hang in there, Straw-chan!
Hang in there!
Words are not needed for an Okama's parting.
Bon-chan!
How can this be?
They got away!
If he hadn't been here, we'd be at the bottom of the ocean by now!
Even in Hell, there is a single blooming flower of friendship.
It rocks back and forth over the waves,
leaving one single petal behind as a memento.
Someday, it will certainly bloom.
Okama Way!
Bon-chan!
Brother Bon!
Bon-boy!
Mister Two!
Do you have any last words?!
Satisfaction!
Let us meet again on the field of Okama.
On this day, the number of prisoners who escaped from the world's most feared prison, Impel Down...
was a total of 241.
It was the greatest disgrace Impel Down had suffered in its entire history...
but this incident is still not over.
Time remaining until
Portgas D. Ace's scheduled execution...
4 hours.