Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it
becomes King of the Pirates!
Isn't that exciting?!
Cool new adventures
are waiting out there!
BON
VOY
AGE!
AGE
Hi
!
to
Light
cour
grow
BON
VOY
AGE!
AGE
Hi
!
Light
Hi
to
Light
cour
no
yu
cour
grow
Mi
I
rai
caught
he
a
no
glimpse
SHI
at
te
grow
PPO
what's
cho
be
tto
yond
caught
he
a
no
glimpse
SHI
at
PPO
what's
cho
be
tto
yond
Back
yo
zon
i
when
sho
we
wa
first
min
star
Back
Video Editing
Feeso
Sa
i
Back
when
i
sho
when
we
sho
wa
we
first
wa
min
first
star
min
na
star
ted
we
had
se
parate
i
na
ted
deas
a
bout
where
we
would
soon
parate
ni
i
e
deas
gai
a
te
bout
i
ta
where
chi
we
Graphics
Datenshi
chi
he
we
would
he
i
would
soon
i
sen
soon
go
sen
I
Things
ma
have
na
changed
Things
kyou
Things
have
ru
ma
na
have
changed
na
ra
changed
now
when
we
look
towards
our
ra
now
,
dreams
we
all
share
one
te
le
scope
hi
when
to
we
tsu
look
no
towards
bo
our
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
PhosCity
Scolines
Zenef
bo
u
our
dreams
u
en
dreams
we
en
kyou
we
all
kyou
de
all
share
de
no
share
scope
ru
Ki
When
mi
you
no
find
KO
that
your
RO
heart's
ma
been
stray
u
Ki
When
n
mei
no
sho
ppai
KON
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
PA
SU
Ki
mi
When
you
mi
no
you
find
no
KO
that
your
KO
RO
your
heart's
RO
ma
heart's
been
ma
do
been
stray
time
to
ca
li
brate
su
stray
your
com
pas
ses
u
time
brate
Soundtracking
Halee
sho
ppai
brate
your
ppai
KON
your
course
turn
bles
course
ka
,
turn
ka
ji
turn
bles
ru
yo
bles
now
BON
VOY
AGE!
Shed
RA
your
gage
past
BON
VOY
AGE!
AGE
SHI
!
Shed
SHI
GA
Shed
your
GA
RA
your
gage
ko
mo
gage
past
Bo
Smiles
ku
can
ra
weath
past
so
storm
know
wa
that
ra
be
e
tter
te
than
ru
a
Bo
Smiles
Smiles
can
ku
ra
can
weath
ra
na
weath
storm
so
re
storm
know
de
mo
know
that
mo
wa
that
be
Timing/Typesetting
Gab
wa
ra
be
tter
ra
e
te
tter
than
te
ru
than
Don't
me
you
wo
fret
Don't
ra
ba
Subtitle Editing
Camotoy
Gordingus
Lorphex
Pollychan
Yu
me
Don't
you
me
wo
you
fret
tears
shed
a
long
the
wo
fret
,
way
to
your
dreams
are
not
in
vain
ka
tears
na
shed
e
a
ru
long
your
mi
dreams
vain
Translation
Funimation
PamkinPinguin
O
You
shi
know
ku
that
wa
you're
nai
all
ba
vain
PRE
CIOUS
IN
MY
LIFE
O
You
shi
know
ku
that
wa
you're
nai
all
PRE
CIOUS
IN
MY
LIFE
Mi
I
rai
caught
he
a
no
glimpse
SHI
at
PPO
what's
cho
be
tto
yond
caught
he
a
no
glimpse
SHI
at
PPO
what's
cho
be
tto
yond
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Concerto
Just a little more...
Everyone will be so impressed
if I find the gold first!
Ruins up here, too...
Ow!
What's with this place?!
The ground is slanted...
I'll go around that way.
Gold! Gold!
Stay.
Stay, Holy.
Holy, stay.
I got too cocky!
I should've just gone back!
I'm gonna die...!
You're the third one
to make it here today...
Huh?
Who are you?!
That spider-head is so careless!
You must've beaten Gedatsu.
He must mean that guy from earlier!
Oh, don't worry.
The world is a better place
without an imbecile like him.
Wouldn't you agree?
Huh? I tripped over–
Don't be scared.
That's my pet dog Holy.
He won't bite.
B-But...! This guy is just
lying here, torn to shreds!
Holy is well trained,
so he won't bite anyone on a whim.
I'm the one who cut him up.
That's even scarier! Who are you?!
Who are you?
My name is Ohm.
You're scary!
Just be silent!
He's too scary!
I am lamenting the frailty of man.
I don't like him!
Huh?
Why do humans fight and die in vain,
despite knowing
the transience of life?!
What the...?
From the day they are born,
they spend their lives
pursuing happiness...
only to die fighting!
It would have been better if
they never did anything at all...
Such is the fate of humanity...
Truly a tragedy...
However, there is
one path to salvation!
Everyone must die!
Why's he saying such scary stuff?!
This is crazy...!
What have you come here for?
Oh, I'm just looking for gol–
Greed begets strife.
Huh?
Allow me to save you.
You're going to save... me?
Your earthly desires shall
vanish upon your death.
He doesn't plan to save me at all!
Kamakiri...!
Kamakiri!
Go...
Go, Raki...
But, Kamakiri...!
Wyper... is headed...
for God's Shrine...
But Enel... isn't there!
You can still stop him...
Stop Wyper...
All right! I got it, so save your breath!
No one... can beat him...!
I am lightning.
He's... invincible...
He is pure lightning... a divine force
that has been feared for millennia...
I'll stop Wyper!
Wait here.
I'm going to leave Aisa's bag with you!
No one... can beat him...!
He's... invincible...
Kamakiri is so strong...
yet his will has been broken!
The Thunder-Thunder Fruit...
To think that Enel ate a logia devil fruit,
the most powerful kind of all...!
I have to stop Wyper quickly!
I think I recognize
this place... Or not...
No, I do...
Or not...
No, I do.
Does it just look similar?
Did you just laugh at me?!
What? You're the one who
tagged along just to get food.
That's what you get for
sticking around. Get lost!
Hey, dumbass!
Whoa, whoa!
Wait! There's no more food in there!
Let go! Hey!
Where are you flying off to?!
This is a crazy place I wound up in!
A dead end?!
You can't be serious...
I walked all this way!
Wait...
Could it be a trick door?
I got it!
I bet I can get through if I
just punch it hard enough!
Gum-Gum Bazooka!
Huh?
It didn't even budge...
What's going on?!
He's not following me... Phew...
Is he a priest too?
There are lots of places to hide here.
I just need to escape and meet up
with Luffy and the others!
He seemed like a swordsman,
so if I stay hidden and keep
my distance, I can escape!
He's run quite a long way.
How foolish, running from salvation.
That in itself is an attachment to life, an earthly desire.
However...!
There are no means to survive
on the sad path to attaining peace...
This is the Ordeal of Iron,
with a survival rate of 0%!
Aisa?
I can't just sit here!
I'm going to find Raki!
Hold it!
Stop! Don't!
What a pain...!
I said stop!
What's your problem?!
Let go! Let go of me! Let go!
This has nothing to do with you!
Maybe not, but I can't just
let a kid run off and die!
I'm a warrior!
Yeah, yeah, alright. Little warrior.
Your glares don't scare me.
Um, are you all right?
Just fine!
Come on, quit struggling! Let's go!
No! Let go! I'm gonna
save everyone! Let go!
Knock it off or I'll slug you!
And no crying!
Even two people from
our crew were beaten!
I can't just let you go alone!
Now, hurry and get on.
No way!
Whoa, that scared me!
What's with this cave?!
First there's an earthquake,
then a flood of sea clouds...
I almost drowned there!
Stupid thing!
Open up!
Why is it so huge?!
Damn you!
Where's the exit?!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Nami!
That leads into the forest!
What do we do?
They went into the forest...
Damn it!
You're tough!
Whaat's that?!
Who is that?!
Wait... something's coming!
Shoo! Go that way!
It's the Maaster of the Sky!
Was that... Aisa?!
We're...
inside the forest...!
Hey! Put me down!
Are you listening to me?!
You stupid bird!
I oughta chop you up!
Huh?
Th-The giant snake!
Hey, fly higher!
We're gonna get eaten!
Hurry it up! Hey!
It's still coming after us!
That snake seems pissed!
Why, you...!
God's Shrine is at
the top of Giant Jack!
That's where I'll find Enel.
I'm gonna take him down and bring
an end to this 400-year struggle!
Here he comes.
Wyper... Climb that vine any farther
and you'll reach God's Shrine.
Who gave you permission to pass?
Ohm!
There is no longer any point
in heading for God's Shrine.
Gan Fall!
What are you doing here?!
Still attached to the position of god?!
No, but I've yet to finish
taking responsibility.
I've just come from
God's Shrine up above.
It was tragic. The shrine
was completely obliterated...
Naturally, Enel was
nowhere to be found.
Perhaps that means he
no longer has any use for it...
It seems their six years
of diligent service is nearing its end.
I thought it fitting to bid you farewell.
Just what is it
you people seek, Ohm?!
Did you say that Enel
isn't in God's Shrine?!
One of Straw Hat's comrades?
Ah, that hurt...!
That bird's gonna pay!
It's you!
Where am I?
Ruins, huh?
Looks like we got us
some feisty ones here...
Hey, hand over the gold!
Oh, my. How tragic.
No one can escape from
my Ordeal of Iron.
If you're going to get in my way,
I'll wipe you all out!
Tell me where Enel
and the Holy Host are!
What's going on with this cave?!
Well, I'm sure you gentlemen
have all sorts of things to say,
but if you wish to be heard,
you'll need to survive here first!
Let's go, Holy.
Go as wild as you want.
That man is our target, Pierre.
We have to stop Enel's priest first!
I can't believe that giant snake
made it all the way up here...
Dammit!
I can't break through. It just
keeps going topsy-turvy!
This cave is messed up!
You can all...
die together!
That's one pesky weapon...!
You Blue Sea people
don't know anything!
The sky has nothing
for outsiders like you!
I'm not about to waste my time
figuring out your problems.
This whole sky thing has
nothing to do with us anyway!
Thought so!
I was planning to take you out
anyway! Works for me!
Die!
This guy's tougher than I thought.
Die, already!
That's right...
It's got poisonous fangs!
This one's got fangs, too!
What's with this dog's moves?!
His name is Holy.
I'm warning you.
I'm a rancher in the sky.
In other words, a sky breeder!
My animals receive training
far beyond ordinary methods.
I trained him to walk on two legs
and even in hand-to-hand combat.
Savor his attacks!
Isn't that a little too far?
Gan Fall...
Even Shura managed to beat you.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
You probably can't even lift
that spear anymore, can you?
You old fool!
Even so, I cannot withdraw!
I still don't know what
you're planning to do!
Don't be conceited!
Even if you knew, someone
like you wouldn't be able...
to understand God's noble ideals!
Aafter them!
After the Shaandians!
What the heck? What was that?!
I heard a "maa"!
Goats?
They're warrior monks!
If we get caught, we'll be killed!
What do you mean "warrior monks"?!
They're Enel's goons!
Hurry up and get out of here!
H-Hold on just a minute!
Where exactly are we headed?!
That damn snake!
It keeps getting in my way!
Hey, Chopper...
Hey! What happened?!
I see...
He was part of the Blue Sea group.
Hey, watch your step over there.
What was that?!
Barbed wire?!
So that's the "ordeal"...
Chopper!
Hey, Chopper!
Say something!
Why did you come here
all by yourself?!
Hey!
Such a shame...
They're made of iron cloud.
Light as a cloud and as hard as iron...
They're blown into shape
by a milky dial.
Each one connects
to an area of the ground.
If you step on one, it'll discharge.
On this battlefield, it's impossible to
know when and where they'll strike.
My contribution to defeating
that animal was minimal...
since he fell victim to
the ordeal on his own.
I take it you'll be
seeking revenge now?
No.
Fighting for revenge
isn't really my style.
Oh?
Is that so?
But...
I could make an exception.
I'm sorry. Is this the
right place, Conis?
They were going to meet
at this seashore, right?
Yes, Father.
Nami told me so.
But what should we do?
I didn't think we'd be the ones
looking after the ship.
We must defend it at all
costs until they return!
Shall we sound the horns
to scare off the enemy?
Yes, Father!
It'll be reassuring!
This will do.
Would you stand watch
over there, Su?
Okay! I'll do my best
to take care of you!
Please hang on, both of you!
Please, everyone... be safe...
I'm sorry things are
like this on the sky island.
Head to God's Shrine!
Now is the time to take Enel's head!
Don't let them get to God's Shrine!
Climb up Giant Jack!
Wyper! Don't use reject anymore!
Warrior monks, retreat!
Stop the Shaandians!
Don't challenge Enel, Wyper!
We can't...
We can't defeat Enel! Ever!
That's right.
All of you, ascend to the Upper Ruins
and eliminate one another.
There will be five survivors.
God's prophecy is absolute.
Enough, Wyper!
I am–
You're what?!
You gonna say that
you're not my enemy?!
To us, you and Enel
are the same, Gan Fall!
So you refuse to listen, is that it?!
You son of a bitch!
My burn bazooka didn't work...
What's with those scales?!
I... I can't take this cave anymore!
What did you just...?
This is why Blue Sea
people get on my nerves.
This sword is also
made of iron cloud.
In other words...
iron cloud is added to the blade
by a dial built into the haft,
so it won't allow anyone to escape!
Were you able to understand that,
swordsman from the Blue Sea?
Yeah, it's like a whip.
I didn't know White-White Sea
warriors could be circus clowns too.
Holy...
Let's fight separately.
It seems the Upper Ruins
are getting a little crowded.
I didn't expect that even the Maaster of the Sky would be here...
We will assist you, Master Ohm!
You guys...!
Looks like...
Yeah, we're the only ones left.
We'll help you reach Enel, Wyper!
I got it! I'll just dig my way out!
That giant snake...
– ...is laughing!
Hold it!
Go away!
N-Nami?!
Aisa!
Young lady!
Kill them!
Aisa! What're you doing here?!
Nami! Why're you here?!
Zoro! Where is everyone?!
Wyper!
What are you Blue Sea
people plotting?!
Aisa! Get away from that woman!
That was close!
Demon! You're a demon, Wyper!
Why did you two come
to a place like this?!
Why?!
Because a huge...
snake...
That idiot...!
Aisa!
Wyper!
You fools can't even
protect yourselves.
Quit worrying about others!
In the end...
no one will survive!