Video Editing
Galaxy 9000
Wealth, fame, power...
Timing
iconsumekidneys
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Soundtracking
Halee
His final words lured all sorts
of adventurers to the sea.
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
My treasure?
It's yours... if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin
FUNimation
Everything is right where I left it!
Raws
df68
Now, pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
shin
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Townsfolks' Emergency Shelter
Something's the matter.
The mayor's not usually gone so long.
Something really is
happening in our town!
Also, there's been
more cannon fire than usual!
Alright! I'll go into town
and check it out!
You all stay here!
I'm coming too!
Fool! There are pirates in town!
Those wretched Buggy Pirates!
And that's precisely
why I'm coming too!
What kind of citizens are we
if we can't even
keep our mayor safe?!
It's no use trying to stop us!
This is all of our own accord!
Fine, whatever!
Let's go, everyone!
Pirate Buggy "the Clown"
Never in my life
has anyone made me angrier than he did!
That bastard Shanks stole
enormous riches from me!
I don't know how you two
are connected,
but I'll say whatever
I want about him!
– Get him! Get him! Fight!
– Don't neither of you lose!
The North Pole!
No, the South Pole!
You won't budge, huh?!
You got it! And I'll keep sayin' it 'cause I'm right!
Oh, you got guts! I'm gonna
settle this once and for all today!
Go ahead and try it!
Alright, you bastard!
I'm gonna bust you up flashily!
Counterattack!
Knock that off!
Who cares whether it's colder
at the South or North Pole?!
If you wanna know that badly,
go to both and find out!
Now cool it!
A ship!
Enemy ship to the north-northeast!
Alright, get ready! Time to fight!
Alright! I'm gonna plunder up a storm!
You look happy, Buggy!
Obviously! Enemy ships
are like treasure chests.
Pirates love to crack 'em open!
Am I wrong?!
Well, there is some truth to that.
You're too soft!
You and everyone else here never
talk seriously about treasure!
You don't know what it
means to be a pirate!
Wh-What's this?!
A-A-A treasure map!
I-I've never seen
one before! Awesome!
It's just sitting there
on the bottom of the ocean?
Yes! Now my life is flashily decided!
Today was another easy win!
Hey! Drink up!
Hey, Buggy!
You're not gonna party with us?
The loot today was really somethin'!
I-I ain't got nothin',
and I don't know nothin'!
What're you talking about?
Oh, uh...
You said you were gonna
leave this ship sometime.
Got any big plans?
I'm gonna have my own ship.
I'm gonna gather a reliable crew
and then see the world.
I'll do it at a nice, leisurely pace,
and as a pirate, of course.
You always spout that sentimental crap.
Say what?!
I can't deny you're good in a fight,
but were you a bit more ruthless,
I'd make you one of my henchmen.
Your henchman? Get real!
Huh?
Our outlooks are too different,
so we should just
go our separate ways.
Very pirate-y of us.
Who made you
the expert on pirates, huh?
And if we ever cross prows,
we'll also need to cross swords.
Yeah. That'd also be
very pirate-y of us.
You're pretty hard to make out.
Anyway, you said
something about loot...
Yeah, we found a devil fruit.
Devil fruit?
I heard they're
incarnations of sea devils.
They say if you eat one
you gain a devil's powers,
but the sea will hate you
and turn you into an anchor.
You'd have to be stupid
to eat something like that!
I'd never get that treasure
on the ocean floor if I couldn't swim!
Still, I bet it'd sell
for 100 million belly...
What?!
I, pirate apprentice Buggy,
will now eat this devil fruit!
Kids are a riot a minute,
never thinking of consequences.
He ate it!
Well, Buggy? Anything different
about your body?
No... Not really...
So, what? Was it fake?
Not surprising; I've only heard
about devil fruits from rumors.
Yes! That worked flashily well!
What I ate this afternoon
was a fake I made!
Can't believe everything
went so smoothly!
Now to jump ship
before they find out the truth!
The money from the devil fruit?
The map's treasure?
That much will get me
a pirate crew right away!
Hey, Buggy!
Whatcha grinnin' about?
O-Oh, it's you!
Don't scare me like that!
What kind of look is that?
If you steal too much from the kitchen,
the cook'll give you hell!
Whew, that was close...
Oh, that reminds me!
The captain just–
– What the...?!
– Shanks! Damn you!
My... My... I'm...
What's that scrap of paper?
Ahh! My map!
H-Hey, Buggy!
Wh-What gives? I can't move...
So then it's true that you
turn into an anchor?! Crap!
Hey! Buggy! What're you doing?
You're great at swimming!
Buggy!
H-Help me...
I'll save you, Buggy!
So Shanks saved you?
That's not what I'm trying to say!
Because of him, my plan in life
was suddenly delayed 10 years!
And then I had a revelation!
If underwater's no good,
I'll obtain all the treasure on land!
Using this Part-Part power.
That's why I won't let anyone
who touches my treasure live!
Let go...
of my treasure!
Crap! He spotted me!
Don't think you
can escape me, Nami!
I'm going to flashily
slice you to pieces!
M-My parts... my special parts!
You're still dealing with me!
Hey!
Leave that treasure
and get out of here!
He'll just keep coming.
No!
Leave the treasure and
get out of here?! Absolutely not!
Why should I
leave my treasure behind?!
Your treasure?!
Of course it is!
I'm a thief who only
steals from pirates,
and I just stole from a pirate!
Meaning, this treasure
now belongs to me!
Ah, I see!
My ass, it is! That's my treasure!
Do you think stealing
it makes it yours?!
Honestly! What kind of
upbringing did you have?!
A criminal, trying to lecture
another criminal? That's rich!
What?!
I haven't fallen so low that I need
to be lectured by pirates!
I hope you're ready to face
the consequences, Nami...
Part-Part...
Festival!
Just try and help your friend,
if you can, Gum-Gum!
Damn, he's split apart even more!
What's this?
Nami!
Give me my back my treasure!
You wish!
Coochie, coochie, coo!
Damn, you're stubborn!
Knock it off!
No, you knock it off!
Thanks for the treasure back!
Let go?! This is my treasure!
Let go! Let go! That's mine!
You let go!
Die!
I told you... you're dealing with me!
That last kick...
was for the old mayor guy!
Th-Thanks, I owe you one.
Yeah, no problem!
Oh yeah! The map!
My treasure–
This isn't over yet, Gum-Gum!
He's still alive!
Shut up!
How dare you flashily do this to me!
You'll pay for this!
Assemble! Part-Part Parts!
Huh?
Looking for these?!
My parts!
Way to go, thief!
D-D-Don't!
Go flying, Buggy!
Gum-Gum...
Bazooka!
I win!
Hey! Captain Buggy went flying off!
Wh-What do we do now?!
Act unconscious for now!
Good idea!
It's all torn up now...
Well, that's okay!
I can still put it on,
plus I sent Buggy flying,
so I'm satisfied.
It's all right. I'll fix it for you later.
Huh? What?
Nothing!
So anyway, I split it into two bags,
so carry half of it!
It's too heavy for me!
There sure is a lot!
If anything, Buggy does know
quality treasure when he sees it!
All this should go for no
less than 10 million belly!
Here you go.
Huh?
It's a map to the Grand Line.
You want it, right?
You're giving it up?!
You did save me.
Thanks, Nami!
I finally got a map to the Grand Line!
Hooray!
Oh! Does that mean
you'll join our crew now?!
I told you I'm never
going to join a pirate crew!
But okay! Staying with you
guys seems profitable enough.
But let me be clear:
We're just teaming up.
Don't forget that!
Yeah!
Hey! Zoro! Wake up! Zoro!
We're going!
Did we take care of everything?
Yeah! We also got the map
and a navigator!
No good... Out of blood...
I don't think I can walk...
Ya think?! If either of you could walk
after that, you wouldn't be human!
Wait, why me too?
You're the most suspicious of all!
Anyway, let's help the mayor...
Oh, yeah!
We gotta wake up
the old mayor guy now.
You, there!
Are you outsiders?!
Yeah... Who are you?
We're this town's citizens!
Did the pirates disband or something?
If you know anything, tell us!
Oh, it's just the citizens!
I was scared it was more pirates.
Oh, Mayor!
Oh, no! Say something!
Hey! Mayor!
– He's out cold!
– This had to be the pirates!
How horrible!
My bad.
I had to knock out the old man.
What?!
Hold on!
You don't need to tell them that!
You saw it.
Yeah, but you had an actual reason–
Why did you guys do this
to our mayor?!
Don't give us your excuses!
Who are you?!
Are you with those pirates?!
They're really bloodthirsty...
If we accidentally say
we're thieves or pirates–
We're pirates!
– Just as we thought!
You idiot!
It's the truth!
Pirates! How dare
you ravage our town?!
Kids or not, you're in for it!
What now?
Sounds like they won't hear us out.
Run!
There's no escape!
How dare you hurt
our beloved mayor?!
Ugh! Why did you
make things worse?!
This is a good town!
Wha...?!
Everyone got so upset
over the old mayor guy!
I'd bet giving excuses
would just make things worse!
We're turning here!
H-Hold on!
Give a girl some warning!
They ran into the alley!
Chouchou?!
That dog!
H-Hey! Move, Chouchou! Hey!
Those guys are bad pirates!
You're barking at the wrong people!
Why are you getting in the way?!
Chouchou! Let us through!
Chouchou!
Later, dog!
That was scary!
We managed to escape
thanks to Chouchou!
Why do we have to put up with this?!
Does it matter now?
We're done here anyway.
Maybe so, but...
Hey, is this your boat?!
It's great!
I don't think it's so great.
I stole it from some idiot pirates.
That's a big mouth ya got!
Been waitin' for ya, thief girl!
Never thought you'd run
into us here, didja?!
You know them?
Yeah... sort of!
Not sort of! We're bound by fate!
So you had friends, huh?
Guess we'll hafta punish you, too!
You'll discover the price you pay
for stealing other people's stuff!
Hey, you! Wouldja stop
freakin' ignoring me?!
Huh?!
Mayor! Are you conscious?!
Thank goodness! You're all right!
What on earth happened?!
What in the...?!
It was already like this
when we got here!
There were some pirates left,
but they all ran off!
Did you not see anything
that happened?!
Where are those youngsters?!
Huh?
"Those kids?"?
Do you mean those three kids?
So they're alive?!
Those fools! How dare they harm
a senior citizen like me!
We just finished driving
those idiots away!
But it's still not enough!
They almost seemed
to be mocking us!
They'd never understand how we felt
when they attacked our town!
Yeah! Yeah!
There's still time to go
after them and catch–
Enough of that!
I'm the only one who's
allowed to complain about them!
I won't let anyone else
talk badly about them!
Wh-What?! Why are you
protecting pirates?!
Damn them... So they plan
to just disappear?!
Where did they go?!
They, uh, ran toward the port.
Damn it!
Mayor! Mayor!
They think they can do
whatever they please in my town!
I have lots to say to you all!
Alright! Let's get going!
Isn't that Buggy's
mark on your sail there?
Well, this is his boat.
I'll get rid of it sometime!
Hey! Wait! Youngsters!
The old mayor guy!
I was ready to die!
I was ready to die filled with despair!
Thanks! We're in your debt!
Don't worry about it! Take it easy!
Dammit, kiddos. Dammit, kiddos!
Dammit, kiddos...
I have no words...
What?!
You left one of the treasure bags?!
Yeah.
I'll have you know just one
is worth five million belly!
But they need money
to fix their destroyed town, right?
That was my treasure!
Do you know how much
I suffered trying to steal it?!
Why did you do that?!
Stop! I can't swim!
That's the whole idea!
If you want it,
go back and get it then!
I can't do that! You go get it!
No! That's really dangerous!
I could die, you know!
Then at least die once!
Do that again and I really
will throw you into the ocean!
Well, for better or worse,
looks like a navigator's
joined our journey.