The clouds floating in the cobalt blue,
Translation
skywalker6705 @ Vegapunk Fansubs
got lost and will soak us all tomorrow.
It'll be fine if you just smile before the sunset.
Initial timing
Kuzan @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing
Galaxy 9000
If it's your wish, you can just
Quality checking
Sewil
say a spell in your chest.
Editing
Sewil
For your hopes...
Our quick premonition
Soundtracking
MaideV and Halee
is showing in the rainbow colored music notes.
Raw providing
SOFCJ-Raws
Won't you come with me?
We're fallen angels,
we'll fire arrows into your dreams.
What color shall we add
into the cobalt blue?
Destroy the sad reality that reflects in your eyes.
Let's raise our wings, full of warmth.
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts.
You're my grandson, so I'm not gonna capture you here.
As for the Marines, I'll give 'em some excuse so don't worry.
Instead of an excuse, let's just say they got away.
Anyway, I'm more of an escort than anything.
Take these two and have a good long chat.
I'm going back.
Okay, bye.
That was too quick!
Care more you fool!
I'm your Grandpa you haven't seen in a long time!
What do you mean?
The only thing you've done is hit me!
Even then, I still wanna be loved by my Grandson you idiot!
That selfishness is definitely a family trait.
The Extent of the Grand Line and
The 600,000,000 Crew!
But man, that's a pretty wild Grandpa he's got.
That part about Dragon really surprised me.
It seems there isn't a single average person in their family.
Where's Luffy?
He's out front talking with Coby.
You alright with that?
You're friends right?
It's nostalgic but...
The one who saved Coby was Luffy.
Nami is gone too, ever since she heard what the marines had to say...
Maybe she's being shy.
She went to the pool with Kokoro-san.
The pool?
The Galley-La Company's employee pool, out back.
Nami-san in a swimsuit?
I'll go take her something to drink!
So, you guys went over that mountain to enter the Grand Line too right?
Uh, no.
We didn't pass over Reverse Mountain.
At headquarters, they have ships that are able to move through the calm belt-
What!? That's unfair!
Of course, they aren't 100% perfect though.
But how!?
There are Sea Kings there that are bigger than battleships!
They really messed us up!
The truth is, the undersides of the ship are covered in a rock known as sea-stone.
So what about it?
So you see,
Sea-stone puts out the same kind of energy as the sea,
So to all the fish in the ocean the ship seems-
The sea's energy?
So that's it!
That way even if they move through the creatures' homes
The Sea Kings won't even notice the ship's presence!
That way even if they didn't take the entrance at Reverse Mountain,
They could still enter the Grand Line at will.
As expected of the Marine scientists.
I got some good information.
Big sis, big sis!
Aren't you gonna swim?
Hey!
Be quiet for a second Chimney!
This is a rare chance!
Pirate big sis's so selfish!
I'm spying right now!
Is that something you're supposed to yell?
The person responsible for this groundbreaking research is most certainly the marine's scientist...
Dr. Vegapunk.
He's amazing.
Indeed, he truly is amazing.
Straw Hat, that devil fruit you ate,
He's the one who identified the power it contained.
And he invented the new technology which allows objects to consume devil fruits.
And that's just in the last few years!
Dr. Vegapunk...
Hmm, he seems pretty amazing.
Indeed, this world is full of amazing people!
If I hadn't met Luffy-san back then, I wonder what a small world I would live in.
You made me aware of this sea.
That day, if you hadn't come bursting out from that barrel...
I would certainly still be stuck at work on Alvida's ship.
That's right!
You were on Alvida's ship weren't you?
Wasn't that hilarious?
The reason why you got on that ship in the first place!
What now?
I haven't heard this story.
We're truly grateful.
That's why we want to try and repay Vice-Admiral Garp by-
No way.
I wanna show him what it's like in our shoes.
Oh, that sounds good you evil-idiot!
What was that?!
What? Are you really going back already?
Eat with us! Eat!
We're really enemies...
We can't act friendly together.
Luffy-san!
Do you know what the second half of the Grand Line is known as?
Further beyond the Red Line, the sea becomes more vast.
That final sea, people call it by one more name...
The New World.
The sea where those who wish to usher in a new era gather!
The man who controlled that sea was...
The Pirate King!
Luffy-san!
We will certainly meet again there!
And next time I'll capture you!
I'll become even stronger!
One day, in the Navy, I'll...
I'll...
Become a Navy Admiral!
No...
S-Sorry.
Sorry, I just got carried away.
I'm embarrassed, just saying I want to become that.
I've just felt kind of inspired since we found you and-
Coby!
You're gonna fight me, right?
Then of course you'll become that strong!
What else?
B-But an admiral?
Next time we meet, we'll be even stronger.
Even more amazing!
Why?
It's just a wavering dream I blurted out but...
Why is he able to believe me wholeheartedly?
What's this?
Are you still a crybaby, Coby?
That I was able to meet you two again today...
I'm truly grateful!
It truly will be a challenge to go after these two!
We're going to keep becoming even stronger!
And in the New World we'll meet again!
Let's go!
Uh, hey!
You two better prepare yourselves!
We've got the guts to surpass you!
Hey, wait up!
Alright!
No one can stop us now!
What're you saying?
You've lost your mind!
Luffy, you've made yourself another unbelieveable opponent, haven't you?
Coby's a capable guy. I just knew that.
Nami-san!
The water-water meat is done!
Okay!
Grandma, you're amazing!
It sure smells good!
Doesn't it?
Now, say 'aaaah'.
Delicious!
Water-water meat barbeque!
Sogeking!
When did you-
Alright, eat as much as you like!
Why are you crying?
Shut up!
The smoke just got in my eyes is all.
How is it, Robin-chwan~?
Different from the stocked foods isn't it?
Yes, it's delicious.
Oh, it's them!
Straw Hat-san!
Have you finally woken up?
Oh, the Franky family!
Come and eat!
It's a barbeque!
My favorite!
Hey, there's a ton of us, we need to get more meat!
It's Sodom and Gomorrah!
I'm starving.
Me too.
The giants! Heey!
Straw Hat!
So you were awake?!
The Galley-La Company!
What are you doing at the pool...
Why you shameless girl!
This is a pool, you know.
Gaah, something smells good.
Iceburg-san!
I absolutely can't let you see this, this woman is some kind of pervert!
Hold on there!
We can't take a break when building a ship.
That's right! So we're gonna take that moment right now!
You're got room for me too right?
Right? Right?
We were waiting on you Brother!
Alright, let's begin!
The Number One: Sogeking!
I'll sing!
Alright! It's a party!
On the Island of Snipers,
I was born.
Listen from there, Nico Robin.
It can't be...
Aokiji?
Why didn't you escape like always?
You should have been able to escape from CP9 if you were alone.
That's because this time was different.
To just let them be killed,
I couldn't do that.
The giant that fought for Ohara
20 years ago, Jaguar D. Saul...
He was my close friend.
That day I respected his wishes, and spared your life.
Therefore I feel I have a responsibility to watch how your life turns out.
But after twenty years without a place of your own,
I felt it was to risky to let such a dangerous bomb continue to roam freely.
Truly, I felt that you finally had to die.
This time, I wanted to finally finish off with what had happened at Ohara.
Of course, there was no way I could have expected the CP9 to be defeated.
Have you finally found your place?
Yes.
What Saul told you, whether it was wrong or right...
From here on, will you show me that answer?
I intend to.
In that case, live strong.
Ohara is not yet forgotten.
Aokiji!
Hey, Robin!
Look over here!
Robin! Over here!
Robin!
How much meat can you eat?
That's the greatest Luffy!
Seriously, try and have some manners.
You were just stuffing yourself a second ago.
You wanna try?
As if!
Hey, Robin!
Hey, over here.
Maybe I should try too?
Yeah, do it Robin!
Please stop, Robin-chwan!
She hasn't done anything yet...
Five Elders!
Five Elders, something terrible has happened!
What is it?
At the New World, the fleet we sent a few days ago was defeated.
Emperor "Red Hair" Shanks and Emperor "Whitebeard" Edward Newgate,
Have finally made direct contact!
What?
Old man!
Red Hair wants to have a meeting with you.
Sure, show him in.
But the brat has better got some good booze with him.
Is it true the whole fleet was defeated?
Yeah, it is said.
Have Red Hair and Whitebeard come in contact?
Attention!
Listen up!
I don't know what will happen from here on.
Stay on strict guard and await orders!
Yessir!
Cease the course!
Rise the sails!
Captain!
We're receiving Red Hair.
Here he comes... Red Hair.
You weaklings better stay back.
You won't handle it.
What does that mean?
Nevermind that, just go inside.
What's wrong?
What's happening?
It's already too late.
Don't panic, they're just unconscious.
If you're half-prepared, you won't be able to hold your senses before that man.
As always...
What an insane Haki.
Haki: Ambition
Excuse me.
I had to be a little threat since it's an enemy ship.
Just seeing your face makes the wound given by that bastard ache again.
I've brought some healing water, I've got no intention to fight.
There's something I want to talk with you about.
And that comes from the one who just showed off their Haki?
You idiot.
Hey! Red Hair!
Bastard, look at what you did!
Oh! If it isn't the first division commander, Marco?
Won't you join my crew?
Shut up!
Old man, should we...?
Yeah, doesn't look like he wants a fight.
Leave us alone.
West Blue liquor, this won't do.
From all of the seas I've been in, there's no liquor that surpasses this water's skin healing properties.
It's liquor from my hometown.
Please, drink it.
Not bad...
Roger,
Garp,
Sengoku...
Only a few of those who knew the seas back then remain.
It's been 22 years, it's only natural.
You've also climbed the ladder...
You were just an apprentice on Gol D. Roger's ship.
You were pretty good on Roger's ship,
With that weird faced partner of yours.
Here we come, Whitebeard!
I hope you're prepared!
I'll rip off that beard of yours!
Who're you calling red nose?!
He was always with you.
Has that funny red nose died?
Buggy?
That takes me back...
The day of the captain's execution, we went our separate ways in Loguetown.
Come with me, Buggy!
Like I'm gonna be your subordinate, idiot!
I heard rumors that he's still a pirate.
It seems like it was just yesterday to me.
There are just a few of the ones who became legends.
The daily duels between you and Hawk-Eyes still sound new in my ears.
When a man like you return from East Blue with a lost arm, anyone would be surprised.
What kind of enemy did you give it to?
That left arm of yours.
This...
I wouldn't have taken you with me anyway.
As if you could ever become a pirate.
I will!
Someday I will find crewmates who will beat to this crew.
I'll find the greatest treasure in the world.
And I'll definitely become the Pirate King!
I made a bet...
...on the New Age.
Well, if it was worth it, then fine.
Whitebeard.
I've been through numerous battles, and received many wounds, but...
Right now, the one that aches...
...is this wound.
This one isn't one I got from an adventure, nor received from Hawk-Eyes.
The one who gave me this, was one of yours...
Blackbeard, Teach!
It's not like I was being careless.
Do you see what I'm trying to say?
Whitebeard.
He was quietly waiting for a chance.
He didn't take the title of commander to be renowned.
He wanted to conceal himself.
Up until now he remained hidden under the shadow of the name of Whitebeard.
And in order to gain power, he made his move.
In the end, he aims to get to the top,
With his own will.
He might even come to steal your title.
What do you want me to do?
That's the main question.
Please stop Ace!
Even though he's young, your 2nd division crew commander is a man of trust.
Ace is strong, I know that.
But, that fame and trust can twist things.
This isn't the time for those two to fight yet!
Leave your hands off Blackbeard Teach.
That's my only request.
The old man is laughing.
That's like the way of talking of that funny nose.
His crime is... something that should never be done on a pirate ship, murder of another crewmate!
He broke the iron rule.
Since the time he got on my ship, no matter how stupid he was, he became my son.
Where does the soul of a murdered son go to?
I have to show that man that you can't cross this world without morals!
It's my responsibility to show Teach of his foolishness!
Have you got it, moron?
You're a hundred years too soon to instruct me!
No one could have stopped this...
The rampaging point of this age!
Not enough to scare me!
I am Whitebeard!
That red haired bastard! What's he doing to the old man?!
Just take it easy.
He isn't the type of man that does stupid things.
But, it seems something went wrong in the conversation.
Take a look in the sky.
The clouds...
No, the sky has been split in two!
Brother, isn't that Iceburg?
Isn't it?
You're really going at it, Franky.
Hey, why did you come?
Gaah, what about it?
Can't I give you a hand?
Bastard, did you come to interfere with my plan?
You've been doing nothing but dismantling; aren't your skills dulled?
Show me your blueprints.
All of Tom's Workers are present...
Even if we have to build a ship in this empty place.
This is for the Straw Hats!
Should we give you a hand?!
Taking care of such a rushed job alone has gotta be rough.
Is it okay that you do it here instead of in town?
If we're building a replacement for that burnt ship,
All of the employees had to come and lend a hand, no matter what.
You guys!
Every single one of you...!
Such good guys they are.
They are.
You better not slack off!
Alright! Let's show them what the 1st Dock is capable of!
Hey!
Look!
It's today's newspaper!
It shows the events at Enies Lobby.
I-It finally came!
Hey! What's written about it?
It's an article that could decide our fates!
Well... that...
T-That...
About us...
There's nothing recorded.
R-Really?!
Not at all?
There's no mistake!
And we were preparing for a permanent fugitive life!
Thank God!
What an unexpected thing to do.
Hey, take a look!
It's an article about Straw Hat!
It seems he took down the judiciary island.
With this, his bounty will definitely rise!
Enies Lobby is famous for having the sea train running all the way from Water Seven.
It's not far from here.
We might get the chance to meet him again.
To be within our firing range...
How pitiful... an unlucky bunch they are...
Let's go, Captain!
Of course we're going!
Well then, prepare to leave!
Don't get delayed!
Hey!
Wait a minute, Teach.
I've been looking for you.
What does this mean?
After all the trouble the Franky Family caused.
Could it be that your grandpa didn't want to involve ordinary people and didn't report them?
No... such a thing...
I think not.
It is surely Aokiji's doing...
What an unpredictable man.
No matter what, I'm glad.
It's fine for us, but for them to become fugitives would be quite unfortunate.
And in their place, it says some awful things about what we did.
"Declaration of War on the World Government".
They even blame us for burning the island.
With this our bounties will rise.
W-Will I also get a bounty on my head?!
Well, that's very probable, but...
The most badass will be me.
"A Big Star Appears".
What're you getting excited for?!
Franky is building us a ship?!
Oh yeah, you were asleep, right?
Yay, this is great!
How about that? He's a good guy after all!
What kind of ship will it be? I'm looking forward to it!
He was a nice guy, a nice guy...
Then let's use the rest of the money to buy supplies.
Hey, do you think the ship will be huge?
Well since we got here I was wishing for more wide areas.
Where is the 100 million beli that was here?
Oh, that was spent during the party, buying meat and booze.
Spent...?
Our money?!
Wasn't it for our party?
Almost nothing remains!
Well, of course!
Almost everyone in town stayed at that party to the very end.
It sure was fun!
Well, since we'll get our ship, it doesn't matter anymore.
And I thought of getting some wonderful furniture for the ship...
Let's go to the canal to look for some.
Hey, Robin, since I'm out to play, can you lend me some money?
I can't take it anymore!
You're not getting anything!
Understood!
Usopp?
What's that?
Luffy, you want me to come back now?
Geez, it can't be helped.
If I'm not there, you can't do anything.
Alright, since you insist, I'll come back to the crew.
Maybe it's best if I say it this way.
This is the 23rd pattern...
Hey, Chopper, we're having nice weather today.
Let's go fishing!
Hey, Luffy, what about you?
This one is also good.
The "act as if nothing ever happened" strategy.
Or...
I've decided to go to Elbaf!
What? Please don't go!
I was kidding.
I can understand your feelings.
Will you be coming back, Usopp?!
Of course, idiot!
Geez, you guys sure love me!
What is he doing?
That idiot.
Iceburg, you seem tired, how about some sleep?
That would be you!
I'm beaten...
My body...is hot...
I'm still alive...
At this rate... I will die...
No one's here.
An abandoned scrapped ship.
Scrap...
Iron pieces...
A place which calms me down...
First, if I don't do something about this unmoving body...
The log is set.
The log pose is pointing to the next island.
Then, all that's left is to get on the ship.
It'll be fun!
That's right, since it's going to be a surprise, he told us not to go and see it.
You guys, if you follow that log, do you know where you will arrive?
No, where?
It seems to be pointing down a little.
That's right.
The next island is...
The bottom of the sea paradise,
Fish-man Island.
F-F-F-Fish-man Island?! At last?!
Eh?! What's wrong, Sanji?!
Fish-man Island?
How complicated...
Oh yeah, because of what happened in your village...
But, that fish-man was a pirate, right?
That's correct, you really did understand it, right, idiot?
Even though you're stupid.
Fish-man Island is a famous landmark on the Grand Line!
The world's most beautiful mermaids draw arcs in the sea.
A dream kingdom where you can coexist with the fishes.
Is that so?!
Amazing!
But, can't we dream?
That's what we pirates do!
There are young ones too!
However, getting to the paradise isn't that simple.
I'm worried about this "bottom of the sea" concept, though...
We'll know once we go there.
The problem isn't there.
Take a look at the most recent newspaper front page.
What's this...?
"Once again this month, 14 ships have disappeared."
What does this mean?
That triangular zone is...
The Florian Triangle.
It's an area you're forced to pass through to get to the paradise.
Every year over 100 ships disappear in that sea for unknown reasons...
Then, much later, the ships are found without any of the sailors.
There are eyewitness reports of a ghost ship carrying those deceased ones who sailed in that sea.
Ghosts appear?! That's scary!
Will we see living skeletons?!
What're you imagining?
No!
I definitely don't want to encounter or see them!
Such an awful ship!
What could happen in that sea?
Who knows...
Anything could happen there.
Those who enter that sea never come back, that's why I don't know...
It's a foggy, deep, dark sea...
Be careful...
Anyway, before entering that extremely disastrous, dangerous sea, you better be firmly prepared.
Ghost ships that are mere shadows of what were once merchant ships or pirate ships...
Are indispensable parts of the legends of treasure ships.
Let's search for the ghost ships!
Leave it to me!
Eh?! I don't want to!
I intend to stock up with lots of provisions in case we have an accident, so don't worry.
A treasure ship?
There might be swords as well.
Pirate bros!
Straw Hat!
You need something?
Brother Franky told us to come and call for everyone!
The dream ship is complete!
It looks great!
Is it complete already?!
That was fast!
The five top-notch shipwrights stayed up all night building it!
Building it!
Alright! Then let's go!
Yeah!
Straw Hat-san!
The Franky family!
What's wrong with you guys?
You're out of breath.
To be honest, we just heard about it!
Did you see the wanted posters?!
Wanted posters?
You have been given an incredible bounty, Straw Hat-san!
Also, everyone else has one as well!
Me too?!
Alright!
Instead of talking, see it for yourselves.
All seven of you now have bounties!
Straw Hat Luffy
Bounty 300,000,000 beli.
It went up!
Pirate Hunter Zoro
Bounty 120,000,000 beli.
Burglar Cat Nami
Bounty 16,000,000 beli.
No wa-
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper (Pet)
Bounty 50 beli.
Fifty...?
The Devil's Child Nico Robin
Bounty 80,000,000 beli.
Who's that...?
Black Leg Sanji (Attempt to take a photo failed)
Bounty 77,000,000 beli.
There's also one for Sogeking.
Y-You have my sympathies and I'm sure you have many things to say to each other but,
Please wait.
What we're requesting, is this.
Please look at this.
Franky!
Cyborg Franky
Bounty 44,000,000 beli.
This is terrible, Brother has a bounty on his head!
It's terrible!
That's right.
We somehow managed to avoid this, but Brother couldn't...
Brother's life will be in danger if he stays in Water Seven.
If he gets caught this time, we won't have the power to save him!
Surely, Brother must be worried about us and doesn't want to leave the island.
That's why we all came to talk with you...!
Straw Hat-san, I beg of you!
Even if it is against his own will, take Brother out to the sea!
That man was the child of a pirate to begin with!