Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
Lance
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Translation
Funimation
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Slope
Alright. They're going to attack
from this shore at daybreak.
But, the only route into
the village is this one slope.
Everything else is cliff,
making it tougher to come through.
In other words, if we can
defend this slope to the death,
the village won't get attacked!
Oh! That's easy!
Talking about it is, but the rest
depends on our strength!
What can you guys do?
Cut.
Stretch.
Steal.
I can hide.
– You're gonna fight!
I'm just kidding! Geez!
Oh, Klahadore! Welcome back!
How is she?
She's resting now.
She seemed quite exhausted...
But to think such a thing happened
while I was at the next town over...
That Usopp lad certainly
knows how to cause trouble.
Indeed...
And of all things,
he claimed you were a pirate...
It's not even a good lie!
Indeed.
What is this?
Oh, that is a present
from the lady to you.
She said it's your
third year at the mansion,
so it's a sort of commemoration.
Commemoration...
Your current glasses
seem to slip often,
so she custom-ordered those!
She's such a nice, thoughtful person!
A commemoration?
Indeed, tomorrow
is a day to commemorate.
What's that?
It's a crescent moon tonight.
Huh?
Nights like this make my heart race,
and my blood stir...
K-Klahadore!
Wh-Why did you break
the lady's gift she got for you?!
Oh, I'll be accepting
a present, all right.
But it won't be this.
It will be this entire mansion!
Wh-What are you saying?!
There's no need for me
to continue this charade.
An accident is going to occur
in a few hours, anyway...
It's truly been three long years!
Miss! Run away!
Captain Jango!
It's almost daybreak!
Please wake up, Captain Jango!
Good morning, Captain!
Good morning!
You idiots!
My policy is to say "good morning"
when the sun is up!
He seems to be in a bad mood.
– Our apologies, sir! We're sorry, sir!
Alright then, good morning.
Okay, men!
Set sail!
– Aye aye!
Alright! Perfect!
Now they won't be able
to climb up this slope...
thanks to all this oil
we've laid out here!
We'll let 'em slip and slide around,
then attack them while they flail about!
Oil, huh...
No matter what,
we will protect this slope!
Conversely, let's just hope that
none of us slips down there.
It'd be dumb to get
caught in our own trap.
You sure did come up
with a slick plan!
But of course!
When it comes to
daring ideas and my slingshot,
I'm utterly confident!
It's almost dawn.
They'll be coming.
We're here!
Alright, men! Go ashore!
Trash the village
and head for the mansion!
Captain! There are
two strange boats here!
What?!
Shall I check them out?
Leave 'em. I doubt
they would have treasure.
Don't screw up our schedule!
Understood!
Get going, you guys!
– Aye aye!
Where are they?
The sky's all bright now.
Where could they be?
Maybe they overslept or something'?
Say...
Maybe it's just my imagination,
but I hear, "Yaaar!"
coming from somewhere...
Yeah, I definitely hear it!
N-Now that you mention it...
Hey! What is it?!
There's a place just like this
to the north, too!
You don't suppose...
You mean this
is the wrong shore?!
This is where they had their
secret meeting, so I just assumed...
Hey! Let's hurry!
They're gonna get into the village!
Where is this place?!
If you run straight north from here,
you'll get there in three minutes!
It looks almost exactly like this place,
so we just need to
stop them at the slope!
Oh no!
The north shore is
where our boats are!
They're gonna take the treasure!
I'll be there in twenty seconds!
Dammit! My brilliant oil trap
was all for nothing!
My treasure...
Hey!
What're you doing? Let's go!
Y-Yeah! We have to hurry-
Help! I'm slipping!
Let go, you moron!
Sorry!
Huh?
Perfect!
Thanks, Zoro!
Sorry! The treasure's in danger!
Try to get back up somehow!
That girl's gonna pay!
I refuse to let them enter the village!
But Luffy sure runs fast!
I can't even see him anymore!
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
They're in big trouble
if they touch my treasure!
There's someone at the top of the hill!
You!
My name is Captain Usopp!
I've been waiting for you all this time!
W-We're fully prepared to fight you!
Turn back now, if you don't wanna die!
Wh-What the...?
I'm the first one here?!
But he was running way ahead of me!
Dammit!
What do I do?! I can't climb up!
I'm in the village now! That's weird!
He said north, so I ran
in the coldest direction!
You're that kid... who overheard our plans.
What do you think you're doing?
I-I'm warning you!
Turn back while you still can!
Or else my 100 million crewmen will
beat the crap out of you guys!
Hey now, no one's falling for that!
What?! A hundred million?!
W-Wow!
He's obviously lying, Captain!
He's so naive...
They saw through it?!
He seriously thought
he could fool us, too...
Why, you...! How dare you trick me!
Captain Jango! Shocking news!
Really?! Is it bad?!
No! It's not bad!
We found treasure
in those weird boats!
An incredible amount!
Maybe four, no, five million belly!
What?
F-Five million belly...?!
Why is there that much money
in those guys' boats?
That's my treasure!
I'll let you have it!
What?! You'll give us the treasure?!
That's right!
In exchange for that treasure,
I ask that you turn back now!
Wha...?! You think you can
buy us off with money?!
What a scummy guy!
You fool... We're pirates.
Of course we're going
to take this treasure!
But that doesn't mean
we have to turn back.
Y-You have a point...
Alright, then! On "one, two,
Jango," you'll let us by!
It's that weapon from before!
One! Two!
Jan–
Quit saying stupid crap!
Wh-Who's she?!
Captain! This is no time to hypnotize
yourself and let people by!
That boat's treasure is mine!
I won't let you have a single belly!
Hold on to it for me
because I'm coming for it!
That hurt!
Who said you could
give them my treasure?!
Well you could have just said so!
What're you talking about?!
I just saved you!
Huh?
I forgot to mention, but don't look
at his ring when he starts counting!
He's a hypnotist!
H-Hypnotist?!
So, where's Luffy?
He got here first, right?
Dunno! He either
chickened out or got lost!
He must be lost, then.
Geez! Just when we need him, too!
I'll take command here.
Go kick their butts! I'll cover you!
What?! Hold on, why me?!
There's no way I can take on
that huge army! I'm weak, you know!
Don't think I'm stronger
just 'cause I'm a guy!
I'm so scared my legs are
shaking like crazy! See?!
Big deal!
I'm so scared my eyes are tearing up!
Your eyes are bone dry!
If you're gonna lie, be more realistic!
I don't need you telling me that!
We don't have time
to bother with this...
Just charge over them
and head for the village, men!
H-Here they come!
Oh, yeah! I have caltrops!
Oh! You do have some good stuff!
Gimme, gimme!
Take this!
Caltrop Hell!
Damn that Nami!
She's gonna pay for this!
I made it!
W-Which way is the north shore?!
Straight north!
Straight north! Straight north!
Which way is north?!
Oww!
Yes! We got 'em!
Now, then...!
Lethal: Lead Star!
Bastard!
Way to go! Keep it up, now!
I'm gonna quit fighting for a bit.
You haven't even fought yet!
What is it?!
There are caltrops behind us too...
You moron! You dropped 'em there!
Outta the damn way!
Do you seriously think
you can stop us?
Let's go, guys!
Captain Kuro is waiting!
– Yeah!
Wh-What the...?!
Let go, you bastard! Let the hell go!
Damn you! Take this! Take this!
I... can't...
let you get past this slope.
Because I only lied like I always do...
the village is going to have
just another ordinary day.
So I absolutely will not let you pass!
Damn kid! Shut up!
Damn girl!
Oww!
Are you...?!
That's enough now!
Hey, you guys!
Quit bothering with them
and get going already!
Have you forgotten
this is Captain Kuro's plan?!
If anything happens
to throw his plan off,
he'll kill every one of us!
Do you understand that,
you dumbasses?!
H-Hey, now...
Yeah, hurry to the village!
S-Stop...
Dammit...
Stop!
Stop... Don't go to the village!
Shut up!
Stop! Please...!
Please don't kill everyone!
I love this village!
I want to protect it!
Wh-What is this, Captain Jango?!
Nobody mentioned guys
like this were in the village!
About time...
What's with the lack of
challenge from these guys?!
Don't ask me! I'm not satisfied either!
Nami! How dare you
kick me down there!
Usopp, you jerk!
You didn't say which way was north!
Who're they?
They're late...
They all know full well what happens
to those who upset my plans.
They think they can
take their sweet time...
If they've already forgotten that fact...
then I'll slaughter them all!
Y-You guys are that strong?!
What took you guys so long?!
You're the one who
got me stuck back there!
I couldn't help it, okay?!
Besides, It was better for one of
us to fall, rather than both of us...
Then you should've stayed!
Seriously! How am I to know which
way is north, and which isn't north?!
What?! You're the one who
ran off first, all full of confidence!
Well, I was just trying to help you.
Night is long gone now...
He, Captain Kuro,
has a short temper...
Hey, men! Don't tell me those
two brats did you all in?!
Listen! We don't have time
to be dilly-dallying here!
If our enemy is strong,
we just need to be stronger!
Now watch this ring closely!
On "one, two, Jango",
you guys will grow strong.
Your wounds will be
completely healed,
and you will grow
stronger and stronger!
What're they doing?
It's hypnosis!
He's trying to convince
them to be stronger!
How ridiculous!
One!
Two!
Jango!
No way!
H-He gouged out the cliff!
What power!
They really did get hypnotized!
With that many people that strong...
Go! Crush anyone
who gets in the way!
You guys get back!
We'll handle this!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy?!
You got hypnotized too?!
Wh-What a simple-minded person!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Damn you, Captain Kuro...
You were wrong to think
he'd have no effect!
These guys are no ordinary brats!
Where is he going?!
What's he planning to do?!
Go! Luffy!
He's gonna destroy the ship!
No, he's not!
He's gonna crush us with that!
Please do something, Captain!
On "one, two, Jango," you'll get sleepy!
One!
Two!
Jango!
Looks like they're
just about wiped out!
I guess so.
Hey! Never mind that,
Luffy's trapped under there!
He won't die.
Worry about your own
injuries or something.
Damn that brat!
Now the plan's really screwed up!
If Captain Kuro caught sight of this,
he'd slaughter all of us, too!
Hey, Buchi! Come look!
This is bad stuff!
What the hell?!
We still have a trump card!
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
It is Klahadore from the mansion!
Where is he going
this early in the morning...?!