Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Feeso
Timing
Lance
Typesetting
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Zenef
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Translation
Funimation
Raws
df68
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Silent Man
You! How dare you
make a fool of me...
insulting me for having
the blood of a pirate!
Stop, Usopp!
Klahadore...
Are you there, Klahadore?
M-Merry!
Merry!
What's wrong?! What happened?!
Open your eyes, Merry!
Please don't die!
M-Miss...
Thank goodness, you're all right...
Merry!
Merry? Wh-Who did this?!
Klahadore! He... attacked me!
He...
He was a pirate all along!
Wh-What are you talking about...?
He got close to you
so he could get your fortune...
Then... what Usopp
said yesterday was...
Yes. Now that I think about it,
he tried his hardest to help
us when he learned the truth!
Yet, not a single one of us
even tried to hear him out!
You gotta run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
But you gotta escape for now!
We protected a real villain
and drove off that brave lad...
who ran about with
desperate resolve...
all for the villagers' sake!
S-Someone help! Merry is...!
It's no use, Miss!
The staff has been
on leave since yesterday.
What?! Then I'll...
You mustn't get flustered!
The incident hasn't happened yet!
You must think calmly about
what you need to do now!
If Klahadore's goal is your
fortune and mansion,
then just let him have it all!
They're not worth
protecting with your life!
You're right.
Cruel as it may be,
you are the only one who
can stop Klahadore now.
Can you do it?
This isn't your responsibility, but...
Even I know this isn't
a situation I can run from...
I understand that fully!
I'll talk things over with Klahadore!
What?! That butler Klahadore
went to the shore?!
Yeah! And he had a scary
look on his face!
Hey! Quit sleeping!
But I should still be in bed...
This is no time to be sleeping!
We could be in trouble!
Huh?
I think pirates really
are going to attack us.
Our captain said he was lying,
but I think that was a lie!
I think so too!
Me too! Something just wasn't
right about our captain yesterday!
It's Miss Kaya!
She's alright!
It looks like something has her worried!
Miss Kaya, walking outside
all by herself...
Something's up!
Something's gotta be up!
You called, Captain Jango?
You called?
Sham...
Sham
Ship Guard
Buchi
...and Buchi!
Together, we are the Meowban Brothers!
Buchi! Sham!
We absolutely must get past this hill...
but an obstacle is in the way.
Get rid of it.
W-We can't possibly do that!
Right, Buchi?!
Yeah, he looks strong!
Huh?
And besides, we're just
supposed to guard the ship!
Yeah! This isn't really
our place to fight...
W-What? They're not
their trump card?!
Sham! Get going already!
What?! M-Me?!
Hurry!
O-Okay, okay! I'll go!
He's in tears! What's he trying to do?!
Why's he making him fight?
Hey, you! Get ready!
I'm gonna scratch you good
with these claws!
What am I supposed to do?!
Hey, you! Stop or I'll kill you!
If you can!
What?!
What the hell?!
You! You just underestimated
me, didn't you?!
I'm impressed you could block that
after my innocent cat act!
You seem to have a little skill,
but I wouldn't underestimate
Sham of the Meowban Brothers!
Missing something?
Don't look at me, though...
There it is...
"Cat Burglar"...
Give those swords back!
Give them back?
But you already have a sword.
These are just in the way.
Alright! Now I'm much lighter!
You're supposed to take good
care of other people's things!
Bastard!
What?!
What did you cut?!
I can bend like a cat!
You're up, Buchi! Get 'im!
Right, Sham!
Cat...
Astrophe!
Damn!
He got away!
Hey! Hold him down, Sham!
My bad!
The bastard's way
stronger than I thought!
What the hell?!
One hit from that would turn
every bone in my body to powder!
He's not getting away this time!
That's right!
I'm not that great at
the one-sword style, but...
Let's go, Buchi!
Okay! Let's do it, Sham!
– Pussy Willow March!
Oh no! They got Zoro
on the defensive!
What're you doing?!
He's not gonna get anywhere
just blocking those two guys' attacks!
I'm gonna help him out!
Take this!
Lead Star!
Gotcha!
Why're you attacking
a guy on our side?!
No, it's not like that!
It seemed like he let it
hit him on purpose...
Huh? On purpose?!
Usopp, you dumbass!
Do you want to die?!
You don't suppose...
we're the ones who just got saved?
Had you hit them with that slingshot...
those two probably would've
come after us instead!
He...
But this is no time for that!
Damn it! If I just had another sword!
I'm gonna get his swords!
If I give 'em back to Zoro,
he'll win for sure!
In that case, I'll do it!
Don't push yourself!
You can barely even stand!
Hey! Nami!
Nami!
What do you need swords for?
Uhh! I-I can explain!
Night is long gone now...
so it seemed odd that the plan
wasn't making any progress.
C-Captain Kuro!
W-We're dead!
This can't get any worse!
What the hell is all this?!
To think that these brats
have held you back...
How the Black Cat
Pirates have fallen...
Right...
Jango?!
B-B-But...
you said letting that kid go
wouldn't cause any problems!
Yes, I did say that.
But so what? We knew he was
going to try to stand up to us.
The only thing I didn't count on...
was your guys' feebleness!
Us, f-feeble?
Who're you calling feeble?!
Watch what you say, Captain Kuro!
Yeah, you were strong before!
But that was three years ago!
It's not like we partied while you
lived the easy life in this village!
That's right! We've attacked lots of
towns and sunk lots of pirates!
Your point being...
You've done nothing for three years!
There's no way you can beat
the Meowban Brothers of today!
S-Stop! Buchi! Sham!
You're not our captain anymore!
Sorry, but we're gonna kill ya!
Wh-When did he get behind them?!
And those weapons...
Who are you going to kill?!
He snuck...
...behind us!
Huh?! He's gone!
There it is!
The Pussy Foot Maneuver...
You're right.
I do feel a bit of sluggishness.
He's handling them like kids,
after they had the upper hand
against Zoro and his one sword!
That man's "Pussy Foot Maneuver"
is a silent movement technique.
Even a group of fifty assassins would
be killed before sensing him!
There's no way we
can escape his plan!
And I got chills after seeing that
habit of his again three years after!
His odd way of lifting his glasses
to avoid cutting his own face
with those cat claws...
clear proof that he hasn't
forgotten how to fight!
It seems I've grown
a bit good-natured myself...
during my last
three years on dry land...
I'll give you five minutes.
If you can't take care
of things here in five minutes...
then I'll kill every last one of you...
with my own two hands!
F-Five minutes...
Five minutes should be enough!
H-Him! If we just beat him,
we can get past this hill!
We had the upper hand
against him just now!
We'll cut him up in five minutes!
We're counting on you,
Meowban Brothers!
Zoro!
What?!
H-Hey! You're kicking
my swords now?!
Where's my "thanks"?
Yeah...
Thanks!
It's no use! Three swords
won't help you!
Your skill's still the same!
Tiger...
You don't get it, do you?
...Trap!
Four minutes.
Just having three swords is different...
from knowing the three-sword style!
He's strong...
One hit...
H-He beat the Meowban
Brothers in one hit!
Don't worry!
I'll crush every last one of you
before your five minutes are up!
Two minutes.
I-I'll... Slaughter him...
C-Captain...
H-Hypnotize me...
P-Please, Captain!
He's alive. You do sloppy work.
His tough fat saved him, huh...?
Get 'im, Buchi!
More hypnosis?!
This guy means trouble! He could
already crack the ground apart!
What happens when he's powered up?!
This is my chance!
I gotta wake him up while I still can!
What is that crafty girl...
up to now?
Everyone's seriously hurt,
and he's just sleeping!
Die!
Get up!
Nami! Look out!
Split in two!
Dodge it!
Wh-What the?!
A chakram! It wasn't
just a hypnosis tool?!
Nami! How dare you
stomp on my face!
H-He's alive?!
Can't tell if he has
good or bad timing...
L-Luffy...
Luffy!
Oww...
Oww!
H-He's alive again!
This is bad!
Five minutes is impossible now!
Nami! That hurts, you jerk!
That wasn't me!
It wasn't me...
N-Nami! Did you hurt your shoulder?
I-It's nothing. I'm fine...
I've done everything I can for now...
so I leave the rest to you...
We absolutely can't
afford to lose this fight...
Yeah!
Try hard! For my treasure!
Okay! That sounds like you, alright!
One minute.
You can't be serious!
Not even Captain Jango and Buchi...
...can finish them in one minute!
Buchi! There's no time to think!
Kill that bellyband bastard!
And I'll handle that weird kid...
I'll kill Straw Hat!
It's about time for
everyone to die now.
Huh? That bad butler is here too!
Don't approach me...
from behind!
Kaya!
Usopp! Are you okay?!
K-Kaya... What are you doing here?!
I'm so sorry, Usopp...
I know you may not accept my
apology, but I just couldn't believe it...
K-Klahadore, a pirate...
Never mind that!
Why are you here?!
I told you to run away!
Your life is in danger!
But you're fighting!
Even after I treated you so horribly
and you've been hurt so much...
you're still fighting for me! So I...
Miss Kaya...
Why are you here?
S-Stop this...
Stop this, Klahadore!
Merry told me everything.
Isn't that the girl from the mansion?
Meaning she's the plan's final target?!
Then there's no need to
go to the village now?
We just need to kill her, right?!
Klahadore, please! If you want
my fortune, you can have it all!
Just please leave
this village! Right now!
I will gladly accept it, but...
there's one other thing
I want, you see...
What I want...
is peace of mind.
Peace...?
Yes. I want simple peace.
I find the villagers' trust that I've
fostered these past three years
to be nice and comfortable now.
So I want to have that
peace of mind forever...
And I...
And I will have that peace!
And your fortune...
In short, pirates will
come to the village!
And...
you will leave your will and die!
These two things are absolute.
N-No...
Y-You're not...
Run!
Run away, Kaya! There's no use
talking to him! Run away!
Y-You're not Klahadore...
You're not Klahadore!
Kaya...
Leave this village! Leave this minute!
I see. You've certainly grown
a lot these past three years...
Miss Kaya.
Do you remember? So much
has happened in three years...
We spent so much time together...
even before your parents passed
away and you became bedridden...
So much time...
So many memories...
Together we suffered,
together we rejoiced...
K-Klahadore...
I would visit the city with you...
and whenever you had a fever,
I constantly looked after you...
You listened to my
stories so happily...
I devoted myself to you...
For so long...
Yes, for so long...
I endured it...
Yes, it was all so that
I could kill you today!
I, a man once known as Captain Kuro,
had to smile humbly
for some snot-nosed girl!
I went against my nature
and sucked up to you...!
Damn you...
Do you understand these daily insults?
Do you understand this man once
known as Captain Kuro?!
Kuro!
Come to think of it...
I still owe you for hitting me.
Usopp!
You hit me with all your
might, as I recall...
If you hate getting hit that much,
I got a hundred more punches for you!