It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Translation
FUNimation
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Soundtracking
Halee
Infoboxes/Title Card
BernieCrane
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Editing
Feeso
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Quality Checking
Alasta
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
Timing
Galaxy 9000
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Adventure on a Long Island
Emergency report! Emergency report!
Ship spotted at 12 o'clock!
Huh? Are they bad guys?!
This is the worst possible time!
Actually there's no flag or sails!
I don't know what kind of ship it is!
Seriously nothing at all?!
What are they on the sea for then?!
Heck if I know!
The crew seems unusually small too...
Plus...!
They're looking really timid!
Almost like they're lifeless!
Sea Monkeys! Run!
Again?!
They followed us?!
Crap! There's no wind!
Hurry! Furl the sails!
Row! Row!
What the...?! Is that ship gonna be all right?!
The wave's gonna swallow 'em!
Hey! You guys!
A giant wave and monkeys are coming! Turn!
Oh!
Whoa! A ship!
A pirate ship!
Men! Get up! An enemy ship!
Let's swipe their treasure!
Wait! A giant wave's coming!
We gotta escape first!
We can't let that ship get away!
Ready the cannons!
Who made you boss?! You do it!
Turn! Someone turn!
What an unorganized ship...
Forget 'em. They're not on our side.
They wanna steal our treasure.
Which way do we turn?!
How should I know?!
Someone give orders! Navigator!
Don't got one!
Captain!
Who just fired that?!
Grrr!
It's no use! It's gonna swallow us!
Damn! You're all incompetent!
You're one to talk!
We can't handle a single wave?!
It's finally calmed down.
Those waves were actually
the Sea Monkeys' doing.
The humidity and temperature
are pretty stable now
so we must already be in
the next island's climate zone!
Hey Robin. See anything?
An island's been visible for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
Listen! Whenever you see an island say this!
Go ahead!
Men! I see an island! Yahoo!
Now you say it!
The fog is rather thick.
Fog? We gotta be careful.
Chopper! Keep forward watch!
Right!
Hey! Do you know how much we've
been waiting to see an island?!
I'm sorry. I'll be more mindful.
Really? In that case okay.
Hey is anyone else curious
about that ship from earlier?
They said they had no captain or navigator
and they didn't even have flags
sails motivation or organization...
What kind of pirates
would go around like that?!
Probably got into a battle and lost.
And their captain died
and they got plundered...
No that can't be it!
I got a good look at their ship!
There weren't any signs of a battle at all!
Yet the ship was completely bare of
all the essentials that pirates need!
So they weren't pirates then.
Don't worry about it.
But they sure seemed like pirates to me...
I somehow get a bad feeling about this...
You always do.
Okay! I wonder if there's a town!
I hope they have a shipyard!
Luffy! Don't go jumping off right away!
I hope we'll get a good shipwright to join us!
We're near the shore! Get the anchor ready!
C'mon guys... Listen to me...
Chopper! Usopp's got the
"Can't Go On the Island" disease!
There's no cure for that.
All right! All right!
There's nothing at all!
What is this place?! So cool!
It's all grass as far as I can see!
Man what a dull place.
Do you suppose anyone lives here?
Yahoo!
Hey!
Me too!
Sheesh. They barge right into
uncharted territory like it's nothing...
With a view like this
it's clear there's no danger.
What is it Choppe-?
A human?
No human's this fluffy and shaggy!
It's a bear!
Whoa! So long! A long bear!
So high up!
Hey! This is an apple! It's so long!
Don't eat it!
Yum!
All the other trees are crazy tall too!
Hey look! Is that a house?!
Yeah it looks like it.
Let's check it out!
It's your relative!
That's a deer! I'm a reindeer!
Man talk about long...
Why is everything here so loong?
I feel like just looking at them's
gonna make me looong too...
Just what kind of island is this?
Hi! We're coming in!
Just like that?!
H-Hold on Luffy! I bet this is
where the boss of the island lives!
He's gonna be some horrifyingly long
snake-man monster! I just know it!
No one's here.
Hey! Luffy! Usopp! I found a giraffe!
What?!
That ain't a giraffe...
It's got a long neck
but it's a horse. A long-horse...
You're a horse?
What a pretty horse!
She's a girl! She says her name is Shelly!
This saddle must mean
someone's here after all...
What's up Luffy?
Usopp.
See those two bamboo trees?
Yeah.
Whoa! I can't see their tops! Talk about long!
Take a closer look...
Okay...
They're running away!
Wha...?! This must be another long animal!
The bamboo tree's attacking Luffy!
H-Hey! You all right?!
I can't let you beat me bamboo!
Careful Luffy!
Rubber Whip!
All right! You beat it!
Yeah! I cut it!
Where's your owner?
You don't know? That sounds lonely...
It could be bad guys! Stay there and hide!
What's going on?!
Actually...
...I cut a bamboo tree and a spirit appeared!
Our ship's... been blocked from leaving?
What are they planning?!
That's the ship I saw earlier...
Who are you guys?!
If it's a fight you want get down here!
We are the Foxy Pirates!
Don't be hasty! All we want... is a showdown!
A spirit?
Yeah. He appeared after I cut the bamboo tree.
Hey. Say something you.
Of course I remember you.
It's been a long time. How are you guys?
One of you knows him?
Nope.
Me neither...
Ah no wonder I didn't recognize you.
Whoa what a flake! Who are you old guy?!
Nomad
Tonjit
My name is Tonjit. You have my thanks.
I assume you're the ones
who knocked me off my stilts?
Stilts?
Oh! They are!
But they were so long
we couldn't see the top at all!
Indeed. I was at the very top!
Oh so you're not a spirit that came
out because I cut a bamboo tree
you're an old guy who fell
'cause his stilts broke?
Why were you on such long stilts anyway?
I've always been fond of stilts
so I tried to make the world's longest
stilts using this island's bamboo!
I managed to get on them but then
I was too scared to come back down!
You're crazy old guy!
I was up there... for ten years!
You're really crazy!
You were on stilts for ten whole years?!
That's right. The bamboo continued
to grow the entire time too...
Making it even harder
for me to come back down...
So scary...
That's your only comment after ten years?!
There are many trees on this island
just as tall as the stilts though.
I was able to survive on fruit I could find.
He talks about it so casually.
Especially after being up there for so long...
Speaking of long...
Why is everything on this
island so long old guy?
It might seem that way to an outsider
but there is a reason.
As you can see a giant
grassy plain covers this island.
In short everything here is long
due to a longing for excitement.
Whoa. He went and said it.
Over there for example...
..is a plaaatypus.
You just said it longer!
That's a Daaachshund.
Be careful. There are ferocious animals too.
See? That's a snow leooopard.
Don't let it bite you!
Leopard?!
Why is it only long sideways?!
Come to my house! I'm in your debt!
Let me offer you some hospitality!
All right! Food!
Yeah!
It's custom in this village to treat
visitors to milk from our farm animals.
Village? Where's the village?
And your farm animals...
The village is gone! And the farm animals!
Get real. Villages don't just
disappear in ten years you know.
Oh actually...
Well I can explain it later.
For now, let me treat you.
I believe I had some milk stored away...
Stored away? You realize you were
on those stilts for ten years right?
Hopefully this cheese is to your liking...
Don't look away! That's obviously
your ten-year-old milk!
I see. That's a shame.
Please make yourselves at home then.
Huh? This cheese is edible old guy?
Don't even try!
It's okay! It's only ten-year-old cheese!
Unlike you folks I live a
laid-back life on this island.
It's made my stomach different from yours.
Honestly now. Whippersnappers
these days are so frail...
Call... a doctor...
I told you so you idiot!
Doctor! Doctor!
Th-That's me!
It's food poisoning.
Obviously!
You're funny old guy!
You're nomads?
Yes. We're carefree nomads
that're always on the move.
So that's how your village
disappeared after only ten years...
This is the island of
Long Ring Long Land. Welcome.
It's technically a single ring-shaped island
but because of the sea it's usually
divided into ten separate islands.
But on one day a year
the tide gets especially low,
and for those few hours the island
regains its true singular form.
We use this fact to migrate from one
island to the next every three years.
So you got left behind
after the village moved?
I like you old guy! You're a big dummy!
If they stay on each island for three years,
then it'd take 'em thirty years
to come all the way back here.
Taking away the time you
were stuck on those stilts
you won't see them again
for about twenty more years...
Pretty much.
If I only I had a hooorse.
I could catch up to the others in five years...
By crossing to a new
island once every year...
"Hooorse"?
Yes. The most beautiful
animals on these islands.
They gallop through the
grassy plains so gracefully...
They're absolutely necessary
to migrate from island to island.
They're strong and can carry large loads.
I can't migrate on foot either.
The tide would come back in before
I even got across to the next island.
Can't you just take a ship?
We don't know how to sail.
Besides even if we charged a Log Pose here,
it wouldn't point to the
next island in the ring.
All ten islands are actually
one big island after all.
I'll just wait here for twenty years.
You sure? It'll be lonely...
Oh wait!
Is a "hooorse" a "horse"?
Oh right! A horse! We saw one!
Oh! Shelly! You waited for me?!
Oh Shelly! You're so adorable!
This sure brings back memories!
You've grown so long since I last saw you!
That's a good girl!
You must've been so lonely
all by yourself all those years!
Thank you! Thank you!
I'll never leave you again!
Ah so that horse was waiting
for him the entire time...
She's great!
She must really like him a lot!
Man that horse sure is
fast! I wanna ride too!
She really is graceful!
Shelly. Let's cross the sea
together on the next low tide day!
All those days with rain...
All those days with snow...
Thank you for waiting through it all!
Shelly... Do you really insist
on waiting for Tonjit-san?
We're going to take all
your friends with us...
Are you sure?
We won't be back here for 27 years,
and we have no idea where Tonjit-san even is.
You'll be all by yourself!
Take my advice and come with us!
Live well Shelly!
Whoa there Shelly!
You know I'm afraid of heights!
Horse!
Old guy!
Shelly!
You okay?!
We heard a gunshot!
What's this net?!
Old guy!
The horse is mine now!
Yeah! Yeah! That horse is our boss'!
Who are you guys?!
Who am I you ask?
They're so rude!
Don't pretend you don't know this face!
I don't know your face! I'm gonna beat it up!
Th-They don't know me...
Oh no! Boss! Don't get depressed!
He's lying! I bet he's just saying that!
He can't possibly know him.
Stop laughing Hamburg!
My name is Foxy! I take whatever I want!
Let this be a lesson you fools!
Why are you so worked up
about a single horse?!
Hunting is nothing more than entertainment!
Why you...!
Rubber...!
Stop Straw Hat Luffy!
How do you know my name?!
Of course we know who you are!
We've done our homework!
Monkey D. Luffy with a
100 million-Belly bounty.
Roronoa Zoro with a 60 million-Belly bounty.
A total bounty of 160 million
with only seven people...
That's really something.
We Foxy Pirates challenge you
Straw Hats to a Davy Back Fight!
Stop talking crazy! Just bring it on!
If you wanna fight let's fight!
Wait Luffy... A Davy Back fight is...
Ah! That explains the ship
we encountered near here!
Which way do we turn?!
How should I know?!
Someone give orders! Navigator!
Don't got one!
Captain!
Hold on Luffy! That game...!
Don't do it! We'll lose crew members!
What's the deal Usopp?!
I'm telling you don't agree to his game!
Fool! I heard you say it Straw Hat Luffy!
You clearly agreed to my challenge just now!
Foxy Pirate
Foxy The Silver Fox
Bounty: 24 Million Belly
Didn't he Porche-chan?!
Yes Boss! I heard him too!
Foxy Pirate
Fighter
Porche
Do you honestly think you can back out now?
Well you can't.
Foxy Pirate
Fighter
Hamburg
Or what? You're not man
enough to keep your word?
I am too!
Don't get talked into it!
But... the horse!
Shelly... Oww!
Don't push yourself! You hit your back hard!
You two! Step aside!
Old guy!
Shelly faithfully waited ten
years for me! How dare you!
Wait old guy! They're pirates!
A Davy Back Fight?
That's right! The fight begins the
moment two captains are in agreement!
"Unruly"
As we speak our captain
is challenging your captain
Monkey D. Luffy to battle!
Challenging? Why bother?
If you want a fight just start one!
Hey you've never heard of a Davy Back Fight?
It's not a fight. It's a pirate game.
Yes. A game that supposedly arose
long ago on Pirate Island.
Which is said to be a pirate
paradise somewhere in the sea.
In it pirates plunder each other
for top-notch crew members.
Pirates plunder each other?!
Yes.
I'm amazed you've survived this
long without even knowing that!
A Davy Back Fight is about
swiping crew members!
After each match the winner can take...
any crew member they want
from the opposing team!
Whoever's chosen must immediately
swear loyalty to their new captain!
In the name of Davy Jones,
the pirate of the deep!
So if you lose... you lose a crew member?!
That's right!
In addition... if the enemy ship
has no one of interest...
They can instead be stripped of their
Jolly Roger, the life of their ship!
So crewmates and pride are on the line.
Winning will make you stronger,
while losing will mean a serious loss.
What a vicious game.
Wait... does that mean
that ship we ran across earlier
without an organized crew
sails or even a captain was...?
Oh? Did you run into the
Fang-Frog Pirates' ship?!
They fell prey to our game earlier!
Say hello to our new crewmates!
Yeah! Long live the Foxy Pirates!
I was the former captain of that ship!
Former ship doctor!
Former navigator!
Former shipwright!
We tried five three-coin
games but lost 'em all!
Fourteen men and our flag
taken just like that!
With so many people jumping ship like this,
it was more like a merger than anything!
Yeah!
There's no talking reason with you!
But we'd never agree to such a
ridiculous game in a million years!
Fool! A regular crew member
can't make that decision!
This game only begins when
two captains reach an agreement!
Like it or not you're all in this game
if your captain nods his head!
They're right Nami-san.
This is an unwritten rule
in the pirate world.
Run and we'll be completely humiliated.
So what if we're humiliated?!
I'd rather die than live in shame.
What he said.
Are you two crazy?!
Forget about it. This is how men are.
Urgh! I gotta stop Luffy then!
Don't bother. It's no use.
The captains will signal
the start of the fight
by firing shots at the same time!
Just sit here and...!
Please no...!
He agreed to it...
Fine by me.
This should be interesting.
He's agreed to the game!
You idiot! You idiot! You idiot!
Why did you agree to it?!
You have no idea how horrific this game is!
Then we just won't lose!
Our challenge is now officially accepted!
Yeah! I'm gonna kick your butt!
That'll be the day!
I will too Split-Head!
Split-Head...?
Boss!
How dare you?! Our boss is a sensitive man!
He has a heart of glass.
Doesn't suit him though.
Hey! I told you not to laugh!
Look Luffy!
Thinking about the horse and the
old guy makes me mad too but...!
Use that anger to thrash 'em!
He got back up way too fast!
Leave it to me!
I'm going to teach you a thing or two!
Frankfurters! Get your frankfurters!
Rum and cheese! Crackers and salted meat!
I've got fried buckwheat noodles too!
It's time for the opening ceremony!
Please quiet down! Please quiet down!
Shut up! You be quiet!
C'mon! Let's hear the odds!
All participants get ready!
This is looking fun!
These are all Split-Head's crew members?
Wow! There's so many!
Hi. Five jumbo fried buckweats please.
Cotton Candy
Fried Buckwheat Noodles
Stop that old guy!
Okay men! Simmer down!
Porche-chan!
Sexy!
It's time for the pledge to follow
these three rules about losing!
First the only way to take back crewmates
Jolly Rogers or anything else
is through another Davy Back Fight!
Second anyone taken by the winner...
must swear loyalty to that
ship's captain immediately!
Third if your Jolly Roger is taken
you can't ever display it again!
Nami-san! I bought some cotton candy!
How can you guys be so calm about this?
Are you still moping about that?
Should you break these rules
you'll be considered dishonorable pirates
and sent to Davy Jones' Locker!
Do you swear to uphold them?
I swear!
I hereby announce this three-coin
orthodox-rules game...
...to Davy Jones!
Who's Davy Jones?
An old pirate cursed by the devil...
who's said to live in the depths
of the sea to this very day.
He lives at the bottom of the sea?!
That's what the legend says.
All the ships and treasures
that sink into the sea
are said to go to his ship's hull--
his "locker" in other words.
The bottom of the sea is scary...
Sweet!
Pirates call this a Davy Back
because you steal whatever
you want from the enemy
just as Davy takes everything
that comes sinking his way.
A captain, a swordsman,
a navigator, a sniper,
a cook, a doctor, and an archaeologist, huh?
Well then. Who shall I take first?
I guess it'd have to be that one!
Sheesh!
You've gotten us into a real mess Luffy!
All we gotta do is win!
Hey! You forgot somethin'!
Write down your rosters and
give them to our party organizer!
Once you've chosen
your roster it's set in stone!
Hey what if we lose?
I bet they'll want Captain Usopp...
No I bet it'll be me. Because I'm cute...
I'll now announce the rosters
submitted by both teams!
Actually my "Can't Be in a Race"
disease is kicking in...
Round 1:
Donut Race
Contestants:
Usopp, Nami,
Nico Robin
I don't wanna do it either
you know! Just accept it!
Don't go slowin' me down!
Round 2:
Groggy Ring
Contestants:
Zoro, Sanji, Chopper
That's my line!
I'm... gonna try my very... hardest!
Round 3:
Combat
Contestant:
Monkey D. Luffy
Let's do it!
I, Itomimizu, the Foxy
Pirates' party organizer
will be your commentator
for this competition!
First up is Round One; the Donut Race!
Boats for the Donut Race can only be made
from two oars and three empty barrels!
Use of any other materials
means instant disqualification!
This is a chance for
shipwrights to show their stuff!
Time is nearly up! Is everyone ready?
The Straw Hat team of Navigator Nami,
Sniper Usopp, and Archeologist Robin!
They'll be riding the Barrel Tiger!
That orange-haired chick is hot!
I want that dark-haired girl on our crew!
Don't need that other guy!
Yeah. Never mind him.
Oh! The final odds are in!
The top spot obviously goes to our idol,
the member of the powerful
Team Foxy: Porche-chan!
Ooh! Just leave it to me!
With her is the swordfish fishman
Capote and the star shark Monda!
They're riding in the Cutie Wagon!
This'll be a cinch! You can do it!
Hold on! You're using a fish!
There's no rule against fish you know!
I'll be providing commentary during the race
from atop Chirp-Chirp a rare
South Blue Super Sparrow!
Are you sure this won't sink?!
I already told you...
I'm not a shipwright!
Okay! On your marks!