Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Meggo
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Zenef
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Zenef
His final words lured all sorts
of adventurers to the sea.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
arch1t3cht
Gab
My treasure?
It's yours... if you can find it.
Subtitle Editing
Gab
Gordingus
JT-421
Ravenfire
Westfal
Gab
Gordingus
JT-421
Ravenfire
Westfal
Translation
arch1t3cht
Chloelyy
Gaijin
PamkinPinguin
arch1t3cht
Chloelyy
Gaijin
PamkinPinguin
Everything is right where I left it!
Raws
df68
Now, pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
shin
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Storm
What the...? What do you
think you're doing?!
If we revive the pirates on that ship,
they'll take over the entire restaurant!
That's only if they have
the will to fight.
Isn't that right,
you Grand Line washout?
N-No way.
Don Krieg failed on the Grand Line?
Even the conqueror of the East Blue...
couldn't make it with
a fleet of fifty pirate ships?!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Grand Line?
You... You're...
Red Leg Zeff.
You're alive.
No pirate could compare to you,
being both a cook and a captain...
I'm alive. So what?
It's none of your concern.
As you can see, I'm passing
my time as a cook now.
It sounds better
when you say it like that...
but you're not just
passing time as a cook.
it looks like you can only
pass your time as a cook.
Red Leg Zeff was a master of kicks
who never used his hands in battle.
His mighty legs were said to shatter
bedrock and even leave footprints on steel.
And "Red Leg" referred to your boots,
washed in the blood of those
you kicked into submission.
But you seem to have lost
one of your precious legs...
I guess the rumors were true.
A stroke of bad luck
doomed you to an accident at sea.
I suppose losing a leg would mean
you've lost the ability to fight.
I don't give a damn about fighting.
I may have lost a leg, but I can cook
so long as I have these two hands.
Whatever it is, get to
the damn point already!
Red Leg Zeff,
you once sailed the Grand Line
and returned unscathed.
You must have the logbook
from that year-long voyage.
Hand it over!
Wow, Boss Man!
You sailed the Grand Line, too?!
I did...
My logbook, huh?
Sure, I've got what you're looking for.
But there's no way in hell
I'm giving it to you.
That logbook is the pride
of all those who sailed with me.
The likes of you
couldn't even handle it.
Then I'll just have to take it!
I admit the Grand Line
got the better of me.
That being said, I'm still
the indomitable Don Krieg...
and I had the power necessary
to cross such a treacherous sea.
I had the men.
I had the ambition.
The only thing I lacked
was information.
I just didn't know what to expect.
I will have that logbook.
With it, I will reassemble
my pirate fleet, seize the One Piece,
and rise to the top
of this Great Pirate Era!
Wait just a minute.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Cabin Boy?!
Hey, back down, Cabin Boy!
You're no match for him!
I can't back down. Not about this.
Did you say something, kid?
We can pretend
I didn't hear you say that.
No need to pretend.
I'm only stating the facts.
This is no game, boy.
Of course not.
I will conquer the Grand Line.
It's no joke, you brat!
Putting aside what we didn't know,
our fleet of 5,000 sailors only lasted
seven days on that devilish sea!
A kid like you doesn't stand a chance!
S-Seven days?!
The Krieg Pirates only
lasted seven days?!
What the hell happened to them?!
I'm sorry, but I hate it
when people joke around like this.
If you persist, I'll just
crush you right here and now.
If you can.
Perfect.
As you wish, I'll be
sending you to the afterlife.
Gonna fight, Luffy? Need a hand?
A-And if you don't need help,
th-that's fine too...
Zoro! Usopp! I didn't see you there!
I'm fine. Just watch from there.
I-If you insist!
Are those your men?
Don't you think
your crew is a bit small?!
What're you talking about?!
We have two more!
Hey! You counted me, didn't you?!
I'll deal with you later.
I'm going to feed my men first.
Anyone who wants to live
should clear out before I get back.
I'm only after your
logbook and this ship.
If you still want
to throw your life away,
I'll spare some time
to bury you at sea!
Make your choice.
I'm so sorry, Sanji.
I had no idea he'd go this far.
You don't need to apologize, grunt.
Every cook here did
what they thought was right.
That's all there is to it.
Chef Zeff!
You're not seriously taking
Sanji's side in this, are you?
That's right!
It's his fault this happened!
He's trying to destroy
your precious restaurant!
Shut up, you damn eggplants!
Have you ever felt such hunger
you thought you'd die?!
Can you comprehend the terror of running
out of food and water on this vast ocean?!
Can you comprehend such suffering?!
Huh?
Ch-Chef Zeff, what do you mean?
What sets Sanji apart from the rest of you
is that he knows exactly what I mean.
Hmm? What's he talking about?
What does Sanji know?
If all you're going to do
is bitch and moan,
crawl out the back door and get lost!
I'll stay and fight.
I'm too pissed off to let
myself get whupped like that!
I'm staying too! This is
where I work after all!
We have nowhere else to go anyway!
What are you doing?!
You saw what the don is capable of!
Hey, Gin!
Let me tell you something.
My duty as a cook is to feed
those who are hungry.
That said...
when those looters
turn on me with full bellies...
I don't want to hear you complain
when I beat up your fellow pirates.
Just try to take this restaurant,
and I'll kill you without
a second thought.
Understood?
You'd kill him after saving his life?
You're hopeless, Sanji...
Shut up, you crappy cook!
See? He's pretty cool, huh?!
That's nice, but enough about him!
We have to get out of here!
Settle down!
He may be Krieg,
but he's in bad shape.
Gin, you said you don't know anything
about the Grand Line, didn't you?
But you've been there.
I still don't know a thing
about the Grand Line.
What we saw on our
seventh day on the Grand Line...
I don't know if it was a dream...
or reality...
I still can't wrap my head around it.
It was unbelievable!
How could a lone man...
destroy a fleet of fifty ships?!
– What?!
It happened out of nowhere.
Before we even realized he was there,
the ships began to sink,
one after another.
If we hadn't been lucky enough
to encounter that storm,
our flagship would have
met the same fate.
I don't know how many
of our ships survived.
It's just too horrible
to believe it was real.
I want to forget what happened!
I want to forget that man—
how he could seemingly kill
with just a glance—
with that hawk-like glare!
What?!
Huh?
Could it be...?!
There's no mistaking it.
That must be the man
known as Hawk Eye.
What?
Just telling us that his eyes were like
those of a hawk wouldn't be proof alone.
But knowing he was capable of something
so devastating is plenty convincing for me.
The hawk-eyed man!
Huh? Do you know him, Zoro?
Yeah...
It's who I've been looking for.
Is it possible he had some sort
of grudge against your crew?
I'd never seen him before!
Maybe you woke him
from a nap or something.
Don't be ridiculous!
Who the hell smashes
an entire fleet over that?!
Don't get so worked up.
It's just an example.
That is, it's an example of what
kind of place the Grand Line is.
What kind of place is that?!
A place where anything could happen.
Hey Luffy, we shouldn't
go somewhere like that!
Luffy!
Hey, Luffy?
Whoa, that's so freaking cool!
I knew it had to be crazy there!
At least acknowledge
how dangerous it is!
Well, that settles it. My only goal
at this point is the Grand Line.
What?!
I'll find him there...
I'll find that man on the Grand Line!
Are you nuts?
You're the type
to charge in and die first.
You're right, but saying I'm "nuts" is going too far.
I threw my life away when I decided
to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Only one person can call me nuts,
and that person is me!
Yeah, the same goes for me!
Yeah, me too, since I'm
a man of the sea and all!
In your case, that's a lie.
Ridiculous...
Hey, hey!
Do you numbskulls have any idea
what's going on here?!
Outside this restaurant is a massive galleon
from Pirate Commodore Don Krieg's fleet!
You can build your castles in the sky
when the battle is over!
– We're saved!
This is great! We're gonna live!
It's like I'm dreaming!
We're free from that nightmare!
We made it back alive
from the Pirate Graveyard!
That's right...
We can once again turn
our sights on the Grand Line.
Huh?
What's with those looks?
W-We're going back there?!
Any other objections?
First,
we'll abandon this irreparable wreck
and take over the restaurant.
Our enemy is a staff of punk cooks.
They've got nothing on us.
Attack!
They're coming!
I can hear them yelling!
Hold them off! This ship—
this restaurant is ours!
Make way, you scum!
What was that?!
What happened?!
Don Krieg!
Our flagship was...
sliced in half!
Sliced in half?! Did I hear that right?!
Our massive galleon?!
How could...
something so preposterous happen?!
Weigh anchor!
It'll bring the whole ship down!
Yes, sir!
Not good!
Nami, Yosaku, and Johnny
are on the ship out front!
Dammit! It's probably too late!
Big Bro!
Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you guys okay?
Where's the ship?! It's gone!
What happened to Nami?!
Well...
I'm sorry, Big Bro! She's already gone!
See ya! Tell Luffy and his crew...
Big Sis Nami...!
“See you again if our paths cross!"
She took all the treasure and ran off!
– Wha...?!
– What did you say?!
That man...
What'd you say?!
Nami ran off with the Going Merry?!
What the hell is she doing?!