Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Timing
Halee
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing
Sewil
Raw provider
GS-Raws
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Bird Cage
The arena has been completely destroyed!
And is it just me, or is the water level sinking?!
I can't guarantee that the Colosseum is safe any longer!
Everyone, please evacuate as fast as you can!
I give up, I give up!
Watch what you're holding on to, you're gonna choke me!
The water...
My strength's...
Stop!
We weren't going to actually give that prize to anyone!
They're all outside the arena! I win!
The one who gets the fruit wins, right?
The Mera Mera Fruit?!
I can eat it, right?
A winner! We have a winner!
This might not be the best time...
but the one who managed to take advantage of the chaos to claim the Mera Mera Fruit...
is this tournament's ultimate dark horse, Lucy!
He has won!
Yuck!
Ah... can't hold on... any more...
Grand master... Save me too...
You're a man, right? Save yourself!
I thought you'd say that.
Here comes another shot, so watch out!
What?!
Dammit, he ate the Mera Mera Fruit!
Isn't that the Revolutionary Army's...
Hot! The flames really did appear!
I've got his clothes!
No wait, it's just my imagination. It's not hot at all.
I've become fire!
Ace!
I'm using your technique!
Fire!
The Underground Trading Port
Curse you, Straw Hats and Tontattans!
I'm not letting you out of here!
Everyone, take care of Usopp.
Understood!
We're getting out of here!
Don't let them lay one finger on Usoland!
You're out to destroy the Smile factory.
Right, Nico Robin?
Beta Beta Chain!
Hold it!
A giant?!
Are you guys dwarves? I'll be taking your friend for a bit.
U-Usoland!
You fought for us, until you were half dead.
From what I hear, there are people here who were toys for a decade.
I can't even imagine your suffering.
Ow. Don't move me.
If it weren't for you, we would have remained toys forever.
We had been turned into slaves, and you saved our lives.
Have a good look, warriors!
This man...
is the hero who lifted the curse on us!
His name is...
Captain Usopp!
Thank you!
What's that?!
The ceiling is collapsing?!
A light from the heavens!
D-Don't tell me... this man...
is a servant of God?!
Are we... seeing...
a miracle?!
He's divine! Truly a god!
I ... just want to rest, you bastard!
Will ... you just stop?
You're so annoying!
See my face ...
b ... leed ... ing all over.
You ... piece of shit!
"I will lead you"?
"I will lead you"!
You... really are...
our savior, sent from Heaven!
God Usopp! God Usopp! God Usopp!
Please guide us, God Usopp!
What must we do?!
Alright...  Then destroy that factory behind me...
and rescue my tiny friends.
As you wish!
Yeah!
Usopp...
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Dammit!
That guy wasn't Straw Hat!
And he ate the Mera Mera Fruit that I wanted!
God dammit, now how am I supposed to explain all this to Doffy?
Who are those guys?
I'll make you pay for turning us into toys.
Let's take him out along with the factory!
Oh, they used to be toys working underground.
That scared me...
It just caught fire.
This is hard to control.
Um...
Wait up, leaving me behind like that was mean, grand master!
Sure, I am a man, and I can put up barriers...
He's...
Who are you?
Me?
My name is Sabo.
Revolutionary Army
Chief of Staff
Sabo
Revolutionary Army
Hack
We're warriors from the revolutionary army.
Then the first Lucy...
The first Lucy was the man who will one day become the Pirate King, with a bounty of 400 million,
Straw Hat Luffy.
A pirate?!
Yeah, he's my little brother.
Take care of him.
Luffy is a nice guy, isn't he?
He hasn't gotten any less reckless either.
He's exactly the same.
You're pretty reckless yourself, Sabo-kun.
Really?
Why is the revolutionary army in this country?
That's...
The weapons shipped from this port are prolonging wars all around the world.
We... came to stop it.
The revolutionary army has sent soldiers
to this country several times,
but since they were all turned into toys,
we could never unveil this black market.
Hey, that guy's dangerous.
Yeah, that's Sabo, isn't it?!
What's the revolutionary army's number two doing here?
We've gotta tell the young master.
But it looks like the weapons are being made somewhere else.
Where are these weapons being made?
If we could find out, it'd make a great gift to Dragon-san.
Royal Palace
Damn you, how dare you kill the young master?!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Buffalo!
Traf!
I came to save you!
Straw Hat?!
I'm glad you're alive!
You shouldn't have any business up here, Straw Hat!
What happened to the factory?
Did you destroy it?
This is the key to his handcuffs.
You've prepared for everything.
Wait right there, Straw Hat! Violet!
I won't let you lay a finger on the young ma-
Young master...
King Riku, sorry to have kept you waiting.
Just wait a sec, I'll get you out right away.
Sorry you've come all this way,
but our alliance is over.
Get out of here.
Well you're pretty selfish. I'm the one who decides those things, so shut up!
Who's the selfish one?!
Hurry up and unlock the cuffs.
Oh yeah.
Our alliance is over.
That means we're enemies again.
If you let me go, I'll kill you.
Don't move!
I can't touch Sea Stone,
so unlocking this is tricky.
Stay steady.
Are you guys even listening to me?!
It's the stone guy.
It's Pica!
You've screwed me over far beyond my imagination.
Mingo's alive!
Young master!
What kind of body does he have?!
Thanks to the release of the toys, the country is in a state of chaos.
And I don't know why, but the revolutionary army also seems to have invaded.
This is a bad situation.
I'll have to use the bird cage.
The bird cage?!
Right, Law?
Smile Factory
What are we gonna do?
The guys who were toys...
are attacking the factory!
Don't worry.
Nobody can get in here without the keys.
This factory is as important as life itself to the young master.
And it's made of Sea Stone. Even the ceiling caving in wouldn't damage it.
And last, but not least...
We've got two top commanders protecting us!
Nobody can defeat those two!
This factory's protection is impenetrable!
In the Trading Port
Koala!
Robin-san!
I knew it was you.
Are you doing well?
Yeah.
Sabo and Hack, you haven't changed.
Hey.
Did you meet up with Luffy?
Yeah.
It's that guy.
He's our crewmate, Usopp.
Just let him lie down.
Outside the Lift
It's Doflamingo!
Excuse me, let me through.
The King's Land
In front of the Rampart Tower
What's with the noise?
I guess something's going on down there.
Anyway, where the hell did that rock guy go?
The Royal Palace
I must deal with this right away.
You freak!
How can you still be alive, Doflamingo?!
Want me to teach you how to kill people?
Soldier!
Kyros!
This is how.
Straw Hat!
There are two of him?!
Forgive me, I let my guard down.
Gomu Gomu no...
Arming!
Jet Gatling!
Luffyland!
What is that clone?!
That hurt...
It looks like a marionette made of strings.
I've never seen him do that before!
King Riku.
Do you remember how you felt that night ten years ago?
The night you had to kill your beloved citizens and burn this peaceful city to the ground?
Please stop this!
It still keeps me up at night.
What of it?!
The tragedy that is coming will be infinitely worse.
You're not serious! What are you planning to do?!
That tragedy can never-
I'll let you go.
Pica.
Get these pests out of here.
Doflamingo...
please...
don't cause any more...
damage to this country!
Gomu Gomu no...
Balloon!
He threw us all the way out to the garden by the Rampart Tower.
As long as Pica is here, we can't get near Doflamingo.
It's started...
The bird cage!
Captain, what's that?!
How should I know?!
Anyway, we gotta get off the island!
There's no point trying to fight Doflamingo, he'll just kill us!
Captain, there's something in front of you!
Ow!
B-Blades?
Huh? What's with this fence?
Doflamingo doesn't want the truth about this island to get out.
So he's going to...
kill every single person on the island.
The fence has us completely surrounded.
Where is the exit?!
What's that?
Vice-admiral Bastille. We can't contact HQ.
Huh?!
Likewise! We're not getting through to our base!
We haven't reported in to them yet.
Hey! What are you doing to the people?!
I-It's not me! My body's moving on its own!
Hey, stop it!
W-Why did I...
No!
Stop! Get out of the way, everyone!
Parasite String.
Reporting in!
All across Dressrosa, people are indiscriminately attacking others!
Even some of the marines have started going mad!
If this goes on, countless civilians will die!
What now?!
T-The Royal Grounds are sinking!
H-Hey, the ground's lowering itself!
What's happening?!
It's Pica.
He can change the whole terrain, as long as it's made of stone!
The palace is going off somewhere!
Wait, palace!
The factory is rising!
What's going on here?!
Somebody...
Please, stop me!
Flower Hill...
is growing and swallowing the city!
The Royal Palace
Citizens of Dressrosa and visiting guests.
I could simply have ruled you with fear from the start.
Now that you know everything, I'm sure many of you want to kill me.
So I've prepared a little game.
A game to kill me.
I'm in the royal palace.
I won't run, nor will I hide.
If you can take my life, naturally the game will end.
But there is one other way to end it.
That is, if you take down every last one of the people I'm about to identify.
Furthermore, I will put a hefty bounty on each of their heads.
Kill, or be killed.
Everyone in this country will become hunters.
There is no way out, except for you to kill!