Hey...
Are you really planning to cross this lake, Luffy?!
The Burning Lands
-Luffy's Side-
Yup.
And just how are you planning to cross this lake?!
Parts of it are on fire.  Others are frozen!
Then the water temperature might be fine.
And I am quite sweaty...
Shall we swim across?
Don't be absurd!
Me and Robin can't swim, you know.
You want to ride us across, don't you?!
Well, whatever I think...
If we don't cross the lake,
we'll be taking a huge detour.
Guess there's no choice.  I'll handle it!
Alright, let's do this!
Fan Grass
What's this grass?
It's a boat!  That's amazing, Usopp!
And this fan grass will serve as oars!
You have all sorts of seeds, I see.
How wonderful.
The Boyn Islands were a treasure trove
of strange plants, after all!
Whenever I entered a dangerous area,
I managed to snag some convenient plants!
I survived on that island for two whole years,
so you could say that there's nothing I can't han-
Get aboard, Usopp!
You'll get left behind.
Hey!  I was the one who made that!
Alright!
Cast off!
To the land of shaved ice!
Row, damn you!
The wind is so strong!
And it's a headwind, at that!
Of course.
The extreme temperature difference
on the island causes the wind to blow.
The water's boiling out here.
If we'd tried to swim, it would've been a disaster.
We're not really making much progress.
You have to row, dammit!
You won't get away.
Wait, you bastards!
Look out!
It's the centaur from before!
Hey!  Did you decide to join my crew after all?
Did you just invite him again?!
Will you stop asking every freak we meet to join us?!
A horn?
Boss!
Boss?
That reminds me,
didn't the Snail Phone say...
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
The intruders are heading your way!  Please take care of them!
Something just appeared on the shore.
Is that his boss?
So the emergency transmission was from him?
In that case,
it would be silly for him to try to attack us!
One of them is carrying a sword.
Is that the...
samurai who cut down our comrades?
A volcanic eruption?!
Visiting this island...
makes me feel like Akainu and Aokiji are glaring at me!
Scary!
Let's just leave!
Fire, please.
A river!
Hey, that was amazing, Smokey!
Incredible!  How did you know
there was a river behind the ice, Smokey?!
You really are great, Smokey!
I didn't notice anything at all, Smokey!
It was obvious to anyone watching the water currents!
You lack basic observation.
Also, don't be so familiar!
But this creates a question.
It does.
The issue isn't that there's a river here...
We should be asking,
was the ice blocking this current natural...
or was it placed intentionally?
You mean...
someone might have hidden it on purpose?
You're saying that someone might live
on this island, in this gas cloud?!
No way!  They'd have to wear masks all the time!
The voice we heard in the transmission definitely said the name of this island.
We must have heard wrong, Tashigi-chan!
Even Snail Phones would die in a place like this!
You got that right!
If you've got time to laugh,
then you've got time to clear the next ice wall!
What the hell is that?!
A wall of ice!
If we crash into that, the entire ship will sink!
This is not good!
Smash it!
Fire!
The frozen lands - Inside the mysterious facility
-Nami's Group-
This way, children!
You better run if you wanna get out!
You sure are fired up, Chopper!
Of course I am!  Sanji gave me a mission...
to protect the children
and get them safely out of this building!
And I'm gonna do it!
I will complete my mission!
As the only man here, I must do my best!
But where should we go?
You should figure that out!
Sheesh!
Lady, are you alright?
Of course!
I can't even count the number of times I've been in situations crazier than this!
Just follow me and don't worry.
Sure!
Inside the mysterious facility - Biscuits Room
-Sanji's Group-
Super!
H-He's installed weapons all over his body!
It must be him!
The one who destroyed the door to the room!
You seem interested in my weapons.
Alright!  I'll show them to you as much as you want!
Load your guns with poison gas bullets!
There aren't any kids in the room anymore!
Don't hold back, riddle him with bullets!
In that case, let's remove your masks
so we can breathe the poison gas together!
Damn you!
Don't be so anxious.
He got our masks!
Our air tanks too!
Don't fire the gas bullets!
What are they?!
Sheep?!
What're you doing?
This is unlike any man I have faced before!
Who could it be?!
I cannot seem to take him down!
Seriously, what are you talking about?
I speak of my torso!
Huh?
Mysterious facility - Front Entrance
-Brook-
Whoa, hey wait!  What is this?!
W-W-Who are you, good sir?!
What happened to your head and legs?!
Scary!  Please say something!
Fire!  Fire!
We'll soon be finished travelling this river.
What lies ahead?
I have a hunch.
By any chance... might you be... a ghost?!
If that is the case, isn't this inappropriate?!
It's midday!
Haven't I always been good?
I just came ashore to make snowmen!
Ah, if you like, shall we make some together?
If we work together,
we might even be able to make a snow sculpt-
I was joking!
What is going on here?!
That man has no eyes,
so how is he able to attack so accurately?!
Though, come to think of it, I don't have eyes either!
Scary!  Strong!  Scary!
What has gotten into you?!
At least tell me why you're fighting me!
Nitouryuu?!
Two-Sword Style
Please, stop this!
Scary!  Scary!
Creepy!
Master.
Did you catch the escaped prisoners?
No, I came to report on the G-5 ship.
Oh, them?
The poison gas cloud didn't stop them...
and at the moment, the warship
is using its cannons to destroy the ice walls,
and they're slowly making their way inland.
Before long, they'll reach this laboratory!
Why? Why do they go to such lengths
to land on this island?
Did they get tipped off in some way?
Who is commanding the ship?
It's Vice-Admiral Smoker.
Smoker?!
Of all people... What a troublesome man!
Conceal the ships
that are docked at the main entrance!
Should we deal with them?
Nobody is allowed to be here...
so make sure they don't see you!
Then what about you, Master?
Don't be absurd!  There's no way I could go out there!
But that leaves us with no way of stopping them!
Want me to go?
There's no gas here.
It's true!  I can't believe it!
Then why was there all that gas before?
It must be the work
of someone who doesn't want us here.
Is there really someone here?
Doctor Vegapunk's research facility.
Or rather, it used to be.
It's supposed to be abandoned,
an empty building devoid of people or equipment.
Who's been living here?
Hey!  Come out!
What's wrong?!  Are you scared of us?!
There's no need to be polite and ring the doorbell!
We can open the door in no time
if we just blast it with the ship's cannons, Smokey...
Uh, Smoker-san.
Hey, answer!
Open the door!
You listenin'?!  This island is off-limits!
Whoever you are, you're under arrest, you moron!
It's opening!
You finally understand your situation?
We are the Navy!
What business do you have at my vacation home...
White Hunter?
This is impossible!
That man...
Used to be a rookie with a 440 million Beli bounty...
but now...
alongside Hawk-Eye Mihawk...
the Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock...
Donquixote Doflamingo and the rest...
he is one of the Government-authorized pirates... the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Trafalgar Law.
Let's get out of here, Smoker-san!
I don't want anything to do with that guy!
You know, right?
In order to become a Warlord...
he delivered the hearts
of one hundred pirates to Navy HQ!
He's completely deranged!
He gives me the creeps!
Why are you here?
This island is forbidden
to both pirates and the Government alike, Law!
I could ask you the same thing.
Inside Dr. Vegapunk's old laboratory
-Nami's Group-
Daddy!  Mommy!
Hey, you said you weren't sick anymore, right?
Yeah.
What disease did you have?
None of you show any symptoms.
I don't know.  They just said "You have a disease",
and "You'll be fine after a year".
A disease that passes after a year?
Yeah.
Mommy and Daddy asked some people to cure me
and then those people took me here.
So, your parents told you to come here?
No.
It was those people,
they told me all of this outside of my house...
and then I was taken here.
They said that I could've infected Mommy and Daddy.
I didn't even get to say goodbye.
Was it like that for the rest of you?
Yeah.
Me too.
Yeah, right!  This definitely sounds like kidnapping!
So you were brought here by strangers,
and didn't even talk to your parents first?
You know what this sounds like?
You were suffering from a really terrible illness!
Are you a complete moron?!
Is all this running too much for any of you?
I'll carry anyone who's worn out.
But you've already been here more than a year, right?
Chopper, have a look at them after this.
Then we'll know for sure.
Sure.  Will do.
Nami!
Out of the way!
One more time!
It's open.
You've gotten really powerful.
Amazing!
You're so cool, Raccoon Dog-chan!
Wait, I'm not a raccoon dog!
But you just acted like one.
You're right!
It's freezing!
Chopper, lend me your fur coat!
Alright...
Wait, I can't take it off!
What is this place?  Are we outside?
Or maybe a freezer?
It's so dark, I can't really tell...
This climate's perfect for me!
It's so dark, I can't...
Oh, now I see it!
There's a door at the other end!
You're right!
Let's keep going!  This isn't a dead end!
Alright!
Lady!  I don't wanna go in there!  It's scary!
What?!
What's wrong, everyone?
Hurry up!  They're still after us!
They took me through here
when I first came to this island!
Really?  Then it must lead to the exit!
It's pretty cold, but try to bear it everyone!
Hurry!
That's not the problem!
I mean...
around us...
Around us?
There's something...
inside the walls.
I'm scared of this place
because there are frozen people here!
Huh?!  What is all this?!
Frozen... corpses?!
They're above us too!
And under us!
Noooooo!
Ah!  Please, wait!  Don't leave us!
Well, that takes care of that.
Inside the laboratory ・ Biscuits Room
-Sanji's Group-
Hey!
You've blocked their way.  That's more than enough.
Let's keep moving!
I just felt a surge of emotion from Nami-san's heart!
She may have realized her feelings for me!
Still, what are these guys?!
They have sheep legs!
Isn't there some kind of mythical creature like that?
There's no point worrying about them now.
They'll have to wait
until we know what's going on here!
Wait!
Leave me!  I will remain here!
I saw no sign of my son
among the children you helped escape!
There must be other rooms!
I should remain and search-
And how are you planning to move around?!
Leaving you behind
would be the same as abandoning you to die!
It would leave me with a terrible aftertaste!
But I came here to save my son!
You're such an annoying bastard!
Just ask us!  Say "Please search for my body"!
Where is your body anyway?!
I refuse to be indebted to a pirate!
I would sooner die than ask for your help!
H-However...
if you were to search for my body...
I would not complain.
Damn this guy!
Why is a detached head
acting like he's better than me?!
You intend to use violence?!
I-I have no regrets!
I will not beg villains for my life!
Hey, give it a rest!
Would crushing a defenseless head really make you feel better?
The moment that you took him out of the cell,
you'd already lost, Sanji.
But...
This guy is really getting on my nerves!
I was a fool to admire his resolve,
even if it was just for a second!
I don't wanna help him any more!
Alas, I would be defenseless if you left me here,
but if you want to take me with you...
I would not complain.
Damn... I'm gonna get you for this once you get your body back!
You show no mercy, even to a detached head.
Yes.  I should be careful what I say.
I wonder if Nami and the others have found an exit?
Let's go after them!
Damn it, that itches!
Main entrance to the laboratory
Hello?  My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm the man who's gonna be the Pirate King!
You answered too soon, and you're saying too much!
Please, help me!
What's wrong?!
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
No, I'm not your boss.
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
Where are you?!
Somebody please save me, I don't care who.
I'm on...
Punk Hazard!
The name of the island,
plus the mention of the cold climate.
There's no doubt about it,
this call was sent from this island.
You know Straw Hat Luffy, don't you?
Gomu Gomu no...
Fuusen!
Repel!
Room...
Shambles!
He got me!
Two years ago, during the incident
with the Celestial Dragons from the Roswald House,
you, Kid, and Luffy worked together.
What's more, during the great war...
Bring Straw-Hatter over here!
I'm gonna take him away from this place!
Let me take care of him for now!
When Straw Hat was being pursued by Akainu...
you helped him escape.
What business do you have with me?
False distress calls is your specialty, isn't it?
Unfortunately,
this transmission wasn't one of our traps.
Quite a mystery.  But I don't know anything,
so this conversation is over.
Cut the crap.  Let us into the laboratory!
It's my vacation home now.  I refuse!
Is it so wrong for a pirate like me
to stay on an island that you've abandoned?
I'm the only one here.
If Straw Hat does show up, you can have his head.
If that's all you want, then you should leave!
Those frozen people were so scary!
I've had enough of this place!
Look!  There's a door!
We can get out of here!
Yay!
There's someone in there after all!
I'm out!
We're out!  It's freezing!
We're out of the building!  We can go home!
I can see Papa and Mama again!
It's so cold!
The Franky...
Tank is here!
Out of the way!  Out of the way!  Super-out of the way!
I will crush anyone who's in my way!
But I will avoid crushing flowers!
The just a little kindhearted, Franky Tank!
Super!
I can't tell what's the weirdest!
A giant raccoon dog, a winter bikini,
giant kids, a robot, or a detached head...
Am I dreaming?
I've seen you before!
Yeah!  It's the guy from Sabaody!
Were you the one who imprisoned these kids?!
You scum!  We're not giving them back to you!
And you!
Of all the atrocious fiends to run into... it's Smoker!
And with him is always a cutie-swaaan!
This isn't good!  We've run into the Navy!
We can't go this way!  We'll have to find another exit!
Hurry back inside!
Quickly kids!  Through to the other side!
There's gotta be a back door!
What's the Navy doing here?!
How should I know?!  Anyway, run!
Huh?  Isn't the Navy supposed to be good?
I suppose.  You can go to them!
No way!  They look like gangsters!
They're here, aren't they?!  Alone, my ass!
They were indeed here... to my surprise.
Soldiers!  We will capture the Straw Hats!
Right, let's go!  Follow the Captain-chan!
Wait!
Is everyone alright?!
They've made things much more complicated.
The warship is floating!
Even the river is floating with it!
What is going on?!
I can't let you leave this island anymore.
Sorry that I said there wasn't anyone here.
This guy's bad news!
Stand back.
You can't lay a finger on him... He'd just pull it off!
Get him!
Show him the power of G-5!