Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
Translation & initial syncing
Vegapunk Fansubs
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
Syncing
Galaxy 9000
Sync-checking
Sewil
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Quality checking
Sewil and Galaxy 9000
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Video editing
Sewil
Soundtracking
Halee
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Already Negative!
Usopp's Courageous Stand!
Moriah's Dance Hall
Perona's room
Within Thriller Bark: The Mast Mansion
Usopp and Sanji fell below...
Are we just gonna leave them?
Yeah!
They'll be fine.
Anyway, we gotta find Moriah before he moves.
As soon as we find that giant leek I'll beat the hell out of him!
Got it!
That's the fastest way to solve all this trouble.
That's the entrance to the Dance Hall, where Luffy's shadow was taken!
And we last saw Moriah in the freezer room which is beyond it.
Alright!
You!
Did you defeat Perona?!
Hogback!
What's with this reindeer?
Is that Dr. Hogback?
He's the guy who was with Moria.
Should I kick this guy's ass too?!
W-Wait a minute!
Wait, Luffy!
Why don't you leave this guy to me?
That's the doorway there, isn't it?
That's the freezer room.
Go ahead!
Alright! I got it!
Such a lack of manners, going to meet Moriah-sama without notice!
Cindry-chan! Get him!
Yes...
One!
Two!
What?! Plates?
Thr-
What's wrong, Cindry-chan?!
Go ahead, Luffy.
Thanks, Robin!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Hogback!
I'm disappointed in you!
I won't accept you as a doctor!
I couldn't recognize you, Dr. Chopper!
So you were a Zoan type user all along...
No wonder I thought you were a strange creature.
I have no idea how you avoided being carried through Perona's Garden, but...
You won't be escaping this time.
I'll take your shadow!
No...
Better yet...
How about I kill you here and turn you into a marionette?
They will do it.
This passage is incredibly long!
Alright! I'm out!
What's this place?
Found you!
Yo!
It's just you...
What's with this hugeness?!
Is this some sort of archdemon?!
I've never seen a giant like this!
Is this a zombie?
Is this...
Luffy?
No use!
It's all over!
It came to kill us!
What is he planning to do?!
This looks good.
Alright! Now I'm all set!
I'll definitely be the Pirate King!
I was kinda surprised when the building collapsed.
W-What?
He didn't even notice us?!
That thing's speech sure resembles Luffy's...
Luffy's power certainly is dangerous when embedded in a body like that.
Let's just...
Forget your shadows...
Of course not!
Even if we give up our shadows, we haven't saved Nami-san yet!
Pull it together!
In any case, getting past here is the problem...
It seems Usopp and I fell along with the stairs, but...
Even if we try to change our route...
This bridge has collapsed and we can no longer go to that mast-like mansion.
Jumping isn't an option either...
Our shortcut has turned into a detour infested with zombies...
Hang on thirty more seconds!
I'm not sure about this ornament.
He built a bridge!
All this rubble and wood is more than enough to build a bridge or two.
But despite this being an emergency, you gave it a lot of detail.
You expect me to make a shoddy job?!
No, this is just fine.
Anyway, you saved us. Let's go!
What's wrong with this room?
Quite the eye-catching type of room.
I planned on having the zombies on the stairs and bridge make you their prey.
I didn't think Oars would fall down.
What a nosy nuisance.
Those ghosts...!
Is she... the one controlling them?
Who the hell is she?!
By now, you must be aware of how terrible these ghosts are!
Thanks to the Hollow Fruit I'm a ghost woman, capable of creating ghosts at will!
These ghosts are branches of myself.
They empty people's hearts.
This is it for you all!
I can't believe those troublesome ghosts are being controlled by that cutie-chan!
No time for that!
If we get hit by those things, we'll be done for sure!
There's no choice but to run!
They're certainly dangerous!
Negative Hollow!
My existence is worth less than a maggot's...
You're right...
I wish I were born a stray dog...
I don't deserve to walk on the same ground as all of you...
It's all... over...
Seize them.
How simple.
Only the ones above remain.
Riot Shot: Salt Star!
Who is it?!
I won't let you...
Lay a hand on my crew!
Damn!
So he just pretended he was hit?
Negative Hollow!
What?!
My name is...
Captain Usopp.
Why?!
Why isn't it affecting you?!
The ghost hit you!
What kind of trick did you use?!
It is no trick...
I've always been...!
Negative!
He's immune to the ghost's negative power!
What an incredible man!
That's not possible...
There's no way a man immune to the negative hollow can exist!
People cling to life.
That fact alone allows them to keep moving forward, and yet...
And yet... this man...
Do your best!
Fight!!
Do your best!!
Live!!!
Don't cheer me now!
Do your best!
Come on, snap out of it already!
Let's hurry and go rescue Nami and Brook!
You can't...
You can't expect to beat her with your inferior abilities.
I'll take care of her!
What's this reliant sensation...?
He wasn't affected...?
Curse you!
But... take care of the zombies around her!
God knows I can't beat them! I'd certainly die-
We'll leave it all to you!
What? Ah!
No-!
That's not-!
Wait a-!
I didn't-! I was-!
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Groom Absalom...
Do you take Nami as your wife, in sickness and health, to love and to cherish until death do you part?
I do!
And, Bride Nami...
Do you vow to love Absalom for all eternity?
Yes! I sure do!
I really love Ab-sama!
You may kiss the bride now.
No matter how you look at it, it's still impossible!
With this simultaneous attack, you'll lose your will to live for good!
Fourfold Negative Attack...
Negative Hollows!
They got him!
The four of them completely passed through him!
Ever since the creation of Thriller Bark...
There hasn't been anyone immune to the ghosts' depressing pow-
The negative ghosts...!
Have gone negative!
Kumashi, sorry for everything...
Even Perona-sama was affected!
Is that guy a holy man?!
He's a holy man, isn't he?!
Listen well, all of you...
When it comes to thinking negative...
There's no one who can surpass me!
Such confidence in something so useless!
Who'd have thought Usopp's negativity would be useful in such a place.
Perona's Wonder Garden
If he hadn't been there, we'd be dead by now.
What a terrifying ability he has.
I'll leave you here and head to where Nami-san is.
Got it!
Give it all you got!
Of course!
I'm the will-o'-wisp of love!
Nami-swan!
You won't be someone else's bride!
He jumped...
Is he even aware of how high we are?
Well...
The more your tension rises, the less pain you feel.
Anyway, we're heading to the top floor of that mansion!
Alright!
The skeleton must be there!
Just like the phoenix...
Then again, more like a zombie.
You shouldn't be able to stand anymore.
It is time I stop your movements for good.
So you never show up again to reclaim your shadow.
Would you like me to finish you off with my special "Arrow Notch Slash"?
You know nothing.
Don't use that name!
The name of the quick slash technique...
from the Surprise Attack Squad of the kingdom I came from is...
Requiem: Type of song sung during funerals
Banderole: Horizontal fencing attack or banner
Requiem la Banderole.
And the alias my comrades gave to that sword technique, which they praised so much is...
Three-Pace Hum: Notch Slash!
Although you have my personality and skills, you've lost my memories and humanity.
So you have no right to use that name!
If you're the real one as you imply...
Then try to overcome my fake sword skills!
This is your last chance...
Three-Pace Hum...
Notch Slash!
Laboon!
More than anything, I'd like to apologize to you...
It has been fifty long years in this dark sea...
And yet...
There was no point in staying alive after all...
So lonely...
My life has been...
First...
Obviously, I'll get rid of that afro.
What?!
The mansion is shaking...!
Hey! What's with this shaking?!
Who knows...
Maybe an earthquake?
Is this the laboratory?!
Found him!
Hey! Skeleton!
You've been beaten up pretty badly.
Are you still in this world?!
Are you alive?!
Y-You...
Why are you here...?
Pathetic...
Pitying the loser after his defeat!
Hold on a second!
Are you...
The legendary samurai who is rumored to have sliced a dragon long ago?
I wanted to meet you.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Hey! Wait a minute!
What's this shaking?!
I can't kiss my bride!
Absalom-sama!
What?!
Did you find anything?!
This giant ship, Thriller Bark, is being sucked into a weird current!
The whole island is shaking!
How did this happen?!
It seems like... the Special Zombie is messing with the rudder.
What?!
It's moving! Moving!
General Zombies!
Set out immediately!
Stop Oars!
Roger!
Oars!
That's as far as you go, Special Zombie Oars.
Start cutting at his legs!
Where's Oars?
He's gone.
Being so huge...
How can he move so swiftly?
Found him!
Above!
Rubber...
(Even though I'm not rubber...)
Gatling!
Don't interfere with my adventure!
Annihilated?!
The ones who came from here?!
Y-Yes...
Everyone was crushed...
They're the ultimate Zombie Army of this island!
They're the General Zombies!
Yes, in a blink of an eye...
Impossible...
Isn't Oars supposed to be our ally?
Why is he rampaging mindlessly?
Zombies are supposed to do nothing but obey.
If we rely on such a guy,
There's no telling what'll happen to Thriller Bark!
Nami-swan!
I'm here to rescue you!
There she is!
One of the Straw Hats...?!
Amazing...
He pushed Ryuma away...
Who is he...?
Just a wild pirate swordsman who uses the Three Swords Style.
He's fairly strong.
If your pride allows it, he can take back your shadow for you...
What do you say?
My shadow...?!
Really...?!
I beg of you... please... recover my shad-
Shut up! Just be quiet!
Hey, skeleton!
You...
That's one fine blade you got there...
Good eye...
This certainly is one of the 21 Large Sharp Blades...
A black sword with a riot edge...
Shusui: Autumn Water
The Wicked Clove... The famous sword, Shusui.
An item recognizable anywhere.
An Large Sharp Blade, huh?
A splendid thing to come across.
I expect no less from someone calling himself a Samurai.
Alright then.
I think I can use that sword.
You're way too cool!