Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Meggo
Wealth, fame, power...
Graphics
Datenshi
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
obtained everything the world has to offer.
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
What he said in his final moments
drove people to the seas.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Gab
Typesetting
PhosCity
My treasure? If you want it,
you can have it.
Subtitle Editing
AphantasticRabbit
EvoWarrior5
Silence
Zenef
AphantasticRabbit
EvoWarrior5
Silence
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin
Funimation
rangicus
DemonRin
Funimation
rangicus
Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
Raws
df68
People set their sights on the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams.
The world has truly entered
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
shin
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Gin!
No matter how incredible he was
in the past, he's now just a cook.
Blowing his brains out would be easy.
Sanji, do you want to save this man?
Then please... leave this ship
without a fight.
I'd like to keep from killing you.
Leave this ship?
Piss off!
You look ridiculous, you old fart.
You can't set a good example
for the fighting cooks like that.
I don't need a lecture
from a little eggplant.
Who are you calling
"little eggplant," old fart?!
Quit treating me like a kid already!
Sanji, you son of a...
He's not turning his back
on the head chef, is he?
Gin!
Point that gun at me instead.
Are you stupid?! You'll die!
I might.
Sanji, why...?
If you're that desperate to die,
I will give you a gentleman's death.
But you'll need to hold still, or else
we'll blow the proprietor's head off.
Pristine Pearl...
Present!
Sanji!
Why didn't you dodge that?!
If I did, that damn underling
would pull the trigger.
Why?
If you leave this restaurant,
then everyone lives!
It's a no-brainer!
This restaurant is his treasure!
It's my fault the old fart
lost everything...
His power...
His dream...
So I've decided...
I won't stand for the old fart
to lose anything else!
Sanji! Watch out!
Pearl...
Close!
Sanji!
The All Blue?
Yeah!
It's a legendary sea.
It's definitely out there somewhere!
Because of a Dream
Don't be silly!
The Orbit
A Passenger Ship
I mean, there is a legend like that...
We're seafaring cooks, after all,
so we've all dreamed
of that sea at one point.
Right?
Sanji (9 Years Ago)
Cook's Apprentice
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
You say you'll find it, but...
For starters, do you even know
what kind of place the All Blue is?
Of course I do! I'm not an idiot!
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
A sea where fish
from all four seas live...
That's the All Blue.
To seafaring cooks,
it's an irresistible paradise!
That's my dream!
That's the place!
The seafood in those waters
is from all over the world.
Any cook would be itching
to show their skills there!
Yeah.
It's worth risking your life
to look for that sea.
That is, if such a sea exists...
What?
There's no way a miracle sea
like the All Blue could exist.
It's obvious when you think about it.
Some daydreaming cook
must have told it as a tall tale.
Now, enough with the silly stories.
Go collect the plates, Sanji.
What a waste
to leave so much food...
They barely touched this one.
I was sure they'd like it.
Customers these days
sure are pampered.
You guys, stop eating
the customers' leftovers.
Some of the food
I threw out earlier looked rotten.
Saying things like that shows you're
still just halfway to being a cook.
Don't forget we're seafaring cooks.
The sea is an unpredictable place,
so it's best not to waste food.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
I don't want it!
Everyone, calm down!
Please calm down!
Pirates!
Pirates?!
That ship belongs to...
the Cook Pirates!
It's Red Leg Zeff!
So they came back
from the Grand Line!
"Red Leg" Zeff
Captain of the Cook Pirates
I take it you're the pirate
captain Red Leg Zeff.
How can I help you?
Plunder!
Steal all their valuables!
Dammit! I can't get killed here...
not by scumbags like them!
Whoa!
Are you serious, kiddo?
Hey, punk. It's dangerous
to swing something like that around.
Look. Blood. I'm so injured.
Shut up! I'm not gonna be
killed by bastards like you!
Sanji!
Stop it! Don't fight back!
If he's got a death wish,
then just kill the brat and move on!
I don't want to die!
If I'm dead anyway, I'd like to take
a few of you bastards out first!
Sanji!
Man, you did it, Captain.
Always so merciless.
I'm not gonna die...!
I...
Someday... I will find the All Blue!
He said "All Blue"!
That's one hell of a goal!
Captain, tell him how we
couldn't even find it in the Grand Line.
That idiot! He's still spouting
that nonsense...
I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna be killed by some
damn pirates in a place like this!
Captain! Let's withdraw!
This storm is bigger than we expected!
That decides it, men!
Hurry and load
the treasure onto our ship!
We're withdrawing!
Sanji!
Captain!
That damn brat!
Why'd he do that just for a little brat?!
So you've come to, little eggplant?
You're very lucky.
Pirat–
Figures you can't move.
You think you can just
shrug off a kick from me?
So the ships...?
Who knows? The sea was very rough.
It's likely they were
completely destroyed.
We're the only ones
who washed up here, after all.
This rocky skerry has
neither fruits nor animals.
Sure, there are fish in the sea below,
but the waves have
curved the rock inwards,
which sadly means going down
is a one-way trip.
We're in this mess because of you!
I'll kill you!
Complain all you want.
We have no choice
but to wait for help anyway.
But if no one comes, we'll just
dry up and become skeletons.
I'll become...
a skeleton?
That bag over there is your share.
What?
It's food that luckily washed up here.
If you eat it normally,
it will last you only five days.
Use your head and ration your food.
It's a good thing we're both cooks.
Wait a second!
Is that your share?!
It's at least three times
bigger than mine!
Of course it is.
I'm an adult.
My stomach is larger than yours.
Be grateful I'm even
sharing the food with you.
Don't expect any pity from me.
You old fart!
You watch the other side of the sea.
As soon as you see
a ship, let me know.
Until then, we'll stay out of contact
with each other to conserve energy.
Good luck.
That old fart!
I won't talk to him even if I see a ship.
It'll be fine.
I have five days worth of food.
That's definitely enough time
for a ship or two to pass by.
But just in case...
I'll make it last twenty days.
That has to be enough time
to see a passing ship.
It'll be all right. I'll definitely survive.
It's easy!
No ship passed by today.
No problem. I'll just be
patient for a few more days.
I don't wanna die...
My last loaf of bread.
It's kind of moldy...
What a waste
to leave so much food...
You guys, stop eating
the customers' leftovers.
Some of the food
I threw out earlier looked rotten.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
I don't want it!
My last loaf of bread...!
I wonder if that old fart...
kicked the bucket yet...
He's still alive...?
And look at all his food!
He still has so much!
There's that much food!
I'll take it no matter what.
It was all his fault to begin with!
I want to live!
What are you doing
over here, little eggplant?
Did you see a ship or something?
I came to steal your food.
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
I'll die of starvation anyway.
All this food to yourself...!
Weren't we going to stay out of contact
with each other until we saw a ship?
Why?
This is all treasure...
Isn't it odd that we can't eat
despite having so much money?
Hey...
This bag is filled with treasure...
What the hell?!
What's going on here?!
Where's your food?
You haven't eaten this whole time?!
Hey! Say something!
What happened to your leg?
And what about the food?
Did you give it all to me?!
That's right.
Without that leg, you won't be able
to be a pirate anymore!
That goes without saying.
Why, though?!
I never asked for your help!
I can't think of any reason
for you to be kind to me!
So why...?
Why'd you do it?!
Because you...
Because you have
the same dream as me.
The All Blue...
But...
even your men said it doesn't exist.
But it does!
When the time comes,
head to the Grand Line.
You'll surely find the All Blue there.
As you pointed out,
my pirating days are over,
so that's why it'll be you
who goes and finds it.
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
Don't you be selfish and die on me!
I-I wonder...
I wonder how many people
died cursing the sea...
as grand as it is.
I've experienced crises like this
where I was starving.
And each time, I wished...
that there was a restaurant
in the middle of the sea.
A restaurant?
Yeah. I was thinking that
if I could leave this place alive,
I'd build a restaurant
and dedicate the rest of my life to it.
Great! I'll help you do just that!
So don't die!
A little eggplant like you
couldn't possibly help!
I'll become strong too!
So... don't die!
Hey!
Help!
You gotta help him!
Please help the old fart!
Hey!
The old fart...
gave up his leg so that I could live.
– What?!
I can't...
I can't repay the old fart
for his kindness
unless I risk my life for him, too!
Why are you getting up... Sanji?!
I'm getting up to keep this place
a restaurant for as long as possible.
Is that asshole trying
to get himself killed?!
Damn brat...!
You put it so elegantly for us.
But this restaurant is closing shop,
and it will henceforth be a pirate ship!
Stop it, you idiot!
Keep your hands off of them!
What's he about to do?
Gum-Gum...
Battle Axe!