Wealth, fame, power...
Editing
Feeso
Gold Roger,
the king of the pirates,
Timing
KaitouYahiko
obtained everything the world had to offer.
Quality Control
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Sewil
His final words lured all sorts of adventurers to the sea.
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
My treasure?
It's yours, if you can find it.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Everything is right where I left it!
Translation
Gaijin
FUNimation
Now pirates head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has entered...
the Great Pirate Era!
We'
A
re go
re go
PIECE
nd
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ra
mp
shin
jyuu
shin
ba
n
nan
te
jyuu
it's
it's
Friend?
Friend?
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are,
are
on
the
cruise!
We
are!
Parallels
Captain Smoker! Terrible news!
We received a message from headquarters!
Monkey D. Luffy and his crew are headed here, to Loguetown!
He just earned a 30-million-belly bounty in the East Blue!
30 million...
That's almost admirable.
He's an incredibly wicked rogue;
he defeated Don Krieg
and the fishman Arlong!
Quiet!
Damn your shouting.
You made it fall apart.
I'm sorry, sir!
It's a mistake to be so flustered.
I think it's best to do things at your own pace.
Don't you agree?
Y-Yes, sir!
Then why so tense?
Right!
It's just been a while since such a formidable pirate group showed up!
You shouldn't worry.
Has a single pirate been able to escape this town...
since I took command?
N-No, sir...
Then calm the hell down.
You're gonna screw up my pace.
Captain "White Hound" Smoker
Navy Headquarters
Yes, sir.
Reporting in, sir! We have word that
pirates have appeared at the port!
Please head there immediately!
It must be Luffy's group!
They've already arrived!
30 million, huh...
I hope he at least puts up a fight.
Sir?
Just talking to myself. Forget it.
Don't you wanna look at this?!
"Justice"
Captain! Please give
each unit their orders!
No need.
But you need to
consider how powerful he is!
Never mind that. Where's Tashigi?
Y-Yes. She mentioned she'd be busy this morning,
but that she'd attend the training drills.
That clumsy girl.
Where'd she run off to?
Yay! Three scoops!
Slow it down!
You'll drop them if you run!
C-Captain Smoker!
M-My ice cream.
I-I'm very sorry about my daughter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry 'bout that.
My pants ate your ice cream.
Here, buy yourself five scoops.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
T-Thank you!
Thanks!
Loot everything!
Don't leave a single potato behind!
I, Gally the Crescent-sama,
will need these food supplies...
to become king of the pirates!
Hand it all over!
Hey.
Who's in charge here?
What do you want?!
You're Monkey D. Luffy?
Let's see if you have what it takes to survive in my town.
Cut the crap!
Get 'im!
Captain Smoker?
Yeah. He was one of the
toughest guys from Navy HQ.
This town used to be a haven
for pirates headed to the Grand Line.
But ever since he took command,
every pirate who's come to town...
has wound up behind bars.
His strength is extraordinary.
He's a monster.
They even say he has
devil fruit powers.
Devil fruit powers?!
Incredible, Captain! You captured
Luffy's crew in no time flat!
Are your eyes just for decoration?
This guy obviously isn't Luffy.
Eh?
The world would end before this guy is worth 30 million.
T-Then, where is Luffy?
He'll show up soon enough.
The fun's just getting started.
Huh?
How did I wind up at the harbor? Seriously?
Hey!
Is he one of these guys?
I don't think so...
Perfect timing! Do you know how
to get to the execution platform?
The execution platform?
I'm looking for it.
I've never seen you around here before.
Yeah! I just arrived on this island!
This town sure is huge! It's way
different from Foosha Village!
Why're you looking
for the execution platform?
I wanna see the place where
the pirate king died!
So you don't know where? Well...
Wait. Follow the smoke.
Oh! That way?! Thanks!
This sucks.
I keep trying to get
to the execution platform,
but I keep getting lost.
Oh, well. I'll get
there sooner or later.
Is it this way?
Let's see...
Gold... Roger?
Do you work here, old guy?
It said "Gold Roger"
on the sign outside.
Is that this place's name?
Scram.
This ain't a place
for a runt like you.
Besides, we're closing for good today.
You're going under?
We're not going under!
I'm shutting it down myself!
Now get lost!
I was just curious about the name.
I'm trying to get to the execution platform but I keep getting lost.
Can you tell me how to get there?
What's that on the table?
A skull?! It's huge!
This is what's left of Killer Giant.
A fiend who sent hundreds
of pirates to the afterlife.
Until Gold Roger finished him with just one blow.
Gold Roger did?!
With lightning-like speed!
This is the wound he received!
He was a terrible man anyway,
but with his dying breath, he conceded,
"Roger... I take my hat off to you;
you will always be honored among pirates."
So awesome! That's cool!
When I heard he had conquered
the Grand Line a little later,
I wasn't surprised, just happy and excited he was the one to do it.
22 years ago today, Roger died
on that execution platform.
And ever since that day,
every cocky upstart...
has tossed their
hat into the pirate ring.
It was the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era!
But look what's happened!
This town's full of nothing but cowards and scum now!
Men crazy enough to challenge that
evil sea are all but gone now!
That's why this bar is closing for good today.
Well, I'm going to the Grand Line!
Huh?!
Gold Roger's so cool...
He's how a pirate should be!
That's why I set out to sea.
I'm gonna go to the Grand Line,
find the One Piece,
and become king of the pirates!
Those're some mighty big words!
And in this bar, of all places!
I only said what I meant.
Kiddo! If there're still patrons like you out there,
should I hold off
on closing this place?!
How should I know if there are?!
You're right!
There's no way of knowin'!
I haven't been in this good a mood for ages!
I'll treat you to a drink!
I don't drink alcohol.
Alright! Then how about this?
Let's have a toast!
To the eternal king of the pirates!
Here's to the king of the pirates!
Amazing!
That's an elephant bluefin tuna!
That's right! It probably got
mixed in from the southern waters.
I caught it with a pole and line!
A pole and line?!
An elephant bluefin tuna...
Okay, then, haul it away.
Okay!
H-Hold on a second!
Hm?
How much is it?! Let me buy it!
I got a lotta good stuff!
Now my preparations to be a brave
warrior of the sea are complete!
All I've got left is...
Oh, yeah! I forgot
the most important thing!
Goggles!
A first-class sniper needs
to have first-class goggles!
That's a necessity!
I gotta spare no expense on these goggles...
if I'm gonna be a first-class sniper!
Goggles! Goggles!
This is it! These goggles are perfect!
It's gotta be these!
Lady!
You got a good eye! Them's the
latest model from the North Blue!
I got 'em from a naval import ship
that only visits once a year!
What's wrong? You got no money?
I don't do business with
people who don't got cash!
What's it gonna be?!
N-No, it's...
Oh! Right! My backpack...
I'll take these goggles, please!
My! What a cute little girl!
Yes, yes! You're in luck!
This is the only pair in town!
Hold it right there!
I was here first!
Butt out, old man!
O...
Old man?
Stop! Stop right there, you!
Listen! First things first!
There's no way I'm an old man!
I'm more like a big brother. Got it?
Huh?! What're you talking about, old man?!
Dammit, you said it again!
Just gimme those goggles already!
Huh?!
You got a problem?! Huh?!
Keep up yer damn complainin'
and I'll call the marines!
M-Marines?
Yep! The town's naval captain is like a family friend.
The old smoky man!
W-Who is this girl?
Don't you know who I am?!
I'm the great Captain Usopp!
I destroyed Arlong's Fishman Pirates!
It was truly a battle to the death!
There I was, surrounded by 200, no, 300 fishmen!
I beat them all mercilessly single-handed!
Thanks to that, I now have a
30-million-belly bounty on my head!
Really? 30 million...
Yep! That's right!
Papa!
Papa?! I'm not your papa!
Here's a present for you, Papa!
Happy birthday!
Oh, Carol...
What a considerate little angel you
are! I love you, Carol-chan!
Papa! I love you, Papa!
W-What's with this family?
But this old man was being mean and trying to swipe your present!
Now, now! You mustn't say "swipe"!
Remember your manners, okay?
Are you the gentleman who's
picking on my precious Carol?
P-Picking on?
That's not all!
Huh?
You have a bounty of
30 million belly, I hear?
Let's see here...
Are those the new wanted posters?
Yeah, I just picked 'em up from the naval outpost...
600,000... 1,300,000... 700,000...
30 million... Straw Hat Luffy?
For a starting bounty to be this high...
Hold it, boy.
Y-Y-Yes?!
No, you see, sir!
I'm obviously not the person
on that poster! I was just lying!
It was just a silly little prank! Well, bye!
That's you.
T-T-That's right!
It sure is! That's me, all right!
But I have to warn you!
If you lay a hand on me,
my captain Luffy won't stand for it!
He's an awful,
cold-blooded, devilish man!
No one's ever crossed him
and lived to tell the story!
You got a kid, right?
You shouldn't be risking your life...
I see. It doesn't sound worth it.
It's clear that this Luffy fellow is no ordinary man,
since he has a bounty of 30 million.
Papa! You're obviously
way stronger!
You're the strongest in the whole wide world!
Carol. It's all right.
I have nothing to prove and your safety is far more important to me.
As long as I earn enough to provide for us, I'm happy.
Papa...
The guy's backing off 'cause of what I said!
Well, in that case...
So you realize how terrifying I am?!
Take my advice! Just hand the
goggles over and move on!
Huh?!
Don't worry! I'll pay for 'em!
So just give 'em here!
He was just about to let you go, you-!
Papa?
Then let's resolve this.
I assume you have no problem
with us settling this like gentlemen?
Gentlemen?
Here!
Y-You're not talking about a duel, are you?
If you win, the goggles are yours.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6... 30 pistols?!
D-Don't tell me you're...
Daddy the Father?!
A duel!
There's gonna be a duel!
Daddy the Father's
gonna face somebody!
Did he say Daddy the Father?
Daddy the Father is like the greatest gun-slinging bounty hunter out there!
Everyone in the East Blue knows that!
So what kind of idiot would challenge him to a duel?!
Oh. that kind.
Good luck, long nose!
Don't worry if he beats ya!
We already got a place dug for ya!
H-How did things turn out
like this? What's wrong with me?!
The rules are simple. We both walk
ten paces and then turn and shoot.
Y-Yeah...
What are you doing?!
Nami!
Facing Daddy the Father
in a duel... Are you suicidal?!
S-Shut up! It just happened!
You get one shot. Are you ready?
Yeah.
Yeah...
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
This is bad... Really bad...
There's no way I can
possibly beat Daddy the Father.
Six!
Am I going to die here?!
This can't be happening!
Seven!
I just started on my journey!
I haven't even had the chance
to build up any courage or manliness yet!
Eight!
Later!
Papa! You're amazing, Papa!
You're so cool!
Man, how pathetic.
What a lame duel.
I thought he'd have more guts
than that. What a disappointment.
What's with you?!
Tryin' to cheat like that!
You cowardly weakling!
Can't you at least fight honestly?!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I'm just a lowly, pathetic man!
You'd get nothing out of killing someone like me!
Right?! Right?!
Can't you just let me go?
W-Wait!
Nami!
R-Right! If it's money you want,
she has plenty!
Just please don't shoot me!
Please spare my life!
Wait a sec!
Now you're groveling behind a woman?
Anyway-
No! Forget what I just said!
She's an innocent bystander!
I can't drag her into this,
even if it means I get shot!
Usopp...
Please! Leave her out of it!
"Usopp?"
Is your name Usopp, boy?
Yeah.
It couldn't be...
Do you know a man named
Yasopp of the Red Hair Pirates?
Yasopp? That's my old man's name.
Y-You've met my dad before?!
I see. You're his son...
Papa?
I've never once told a soul
what happened on that day,
but I'll make an exception.
It happened in a sweltering port town like this.
Let's do it, Ensign Masterson!
We each get one shot!
One! Two! Three!
Kill me! I have no reason to live now I've lost.
What're you doing?
Your daughter?
Give it back...
To think a marine like you would treasure something like this...
You must really spoil her.
Don't lecture me, you filthy pirate!
Fine by me!
You were great, Yasopp!
It was nothin'.
The wound I took shows I have a lot to learn.
You beat Daddy Masterson though!
You won because you're already awesome!
Yeah, we never would've stood a chance...
Thanks, Boss!
I appreciate you watching the duel!
That's the stuff!
You want some, Ensign?
Family, huh...
Havin' a family's not so bad.
But I'm no good at it.
Huh?
I got a son of my own.
His name's Usopp.
Haven't seen him in years now.
I hit the high seas around
the time he was a toddler.
Why? Don't you love him?
It wasn't like that.
It was about the flag...
I heard the call of the Jolly Roger.
You tell 'im, Yasopp!
At this point,
there's nothing I can do for my son.
We don't need another hopeless
father like me out there!
Stay by your daughter's side if you
can. Don't let her get lonely.
Though I probably shouldn't talk!
I lost our duel!
Yasopp! Finish me!
Don't give me your lousy pity!
Forget it!
You marines might have to hang your enemies,
but us pirates are free to kill or spare who we please!
See ya!
Papa! You didn't really lose to a pirate, did you?!
But that's amazing!
Your dad must be really skilled!
Usopp?
Seriously?!
Would you normally tell someone like me...
about when your life was spared?!
You told me that to give me courage!
Most people would be too ashamed to tell a story like that,
but you told me about it anyway!
Just so I would know what my old man is like!
No weakling or coward
could do what you just did!
Carol! Your dad
is the bravest man alive!
You can find strong guys anywhere!
But the ones who'd risk their honor for others are rare!
I... I can't give in, either! I gotta be
brave, or I'll shame your dad!
Daddy! Give me another chance!
Face me in another life or death duel!
I won't cheat this time!
All right.
This will be our real showdown.
Choose the weapon
you're most comfortable with.
Good. Now, then. Let's see...
Try and hit that weathervane.
Weathervane? That?!
Miss it, and...
Y-Yeah! You can shoot
me right through the heart!
Usopp!
My life is on the
line for real this time!
There's...
There's no way he can hit it with that thing.
You missed!
No, Papa! Don't shoot him! Papa!
I can't shoot him 'cause he shot right through its crown!
Y-You really did it!
He's right!
Usopp!
You're an excellent shot.
I'd expect no less of Yasopp's son.
If you hold onto the bravery you just showed,
you'll be just like your old man someday!
Go to the Grand Line.
I'm certain Yasopp is there.
Daddy...
You're pretty good, old man!
Aren't these...
It's okay! See ya!
Papa!
Carol, you know that's not lady-like.
It's poor manners to say, "see ya!"
Right! Sorry, Papa!
I'm going to grow up to be a proper
lady worthy of being your daughter!
So please forgive me!
You're already worthy the way you are!
Well, I'm still going to be an even nicer lady!
Even if people consider him a disgrace,
he'll continue to protect the one he loves.
I'm going to be a
brave man like Daddy!
Someday I'll be a great warrior and stand before my dad proudly!
I know it!
You?!
Is that any way to greet...
your only regular patron?
You shouldn't blame me.
I only come here as a loyal customer.
It's not my fault that the pirates around here are cowards now.
You had a customer? That's rare.
I'd like some rum.
There's no booze here for you!
Don't be like that.
Today's a special day.
Wouldn't you agree?
That's the stuff.
I can still see it like it was yesterday.
How Roger looked at the very end...
It was a humid afternoon,
just like today...
His hands were shackled as
he was led down the main street...
towards the town square,
where the execution platform stood.
Yet, he waltzed along like
it was a victory parade.
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger obtained everything
the world had to offer.
Even though he was
walking towards death,
he acted like it was his coronation.
The tides of time,
humanity's dreams and inherited will...
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
Do you have any last words?!
Mind taking these off?
They're beginning to chafe.
I can't do that!
You think I would run?
Guess I'm on my own.
All right,
let's get this over with.
Hey, Pirate King!
Where did you hide
all the treasure you found?!
Is it in the Grand Line?!
You had it, right?!
That legendary treasure!
Shut up, you!
That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
Don't speak without permission!
It's yours, if you can find it.
Everything is right where I left it!
Execute!!
That's how it all began...
Hey!
Hey, here's a new wanted poster!
Put it where people can see it!
C-Captain Smoker!
Pardon the intrusion, sir!
U-Umm...
That's a straw hat...
That kid was Monkey D. Luffy!
There it is...
The place where the
greatest pirate in history died.
The place where it all began.