Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country and live freely!
Starting today,
we're brothers!
Yeah!
How long are you gonna keep moping?
All the treasure we hid
in the midway forest is gone.
But that pile of loot doesn't matter anymore.
Sabo and I were gonna use it.
It was our pirate fund.
But in the end, Sabo didn't use it.
And so, I won't worry about it either.
There's no point in gathering
treasure you can't even protect.
A-Ace...
I...
I wanna get stronger!
And stronger...
and stronger...!
Stronger and stronger!
Lots stronger!
Stronger!
Lots and lots stronger!
Stronger and stronger!
So much stronger!
And stronger and stronger!
And even stronger than that!
And then, I'll be able to protect anything.
I won't have to lose anyone ever again!
So please...
Ace... don't die!
Don't be ridiculous!
You should worry more
about yourself, not me!
You're way weaker than me!
Listen up, and remember this, Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!
Sabo made that request, too.
I promise. I won't die!
I won't leave my crybaby brother behind!
I'm not very clever, so I don't know
who—or even what—killed Sabo.
But whatever happened,
it was definitely the opposite of freedom!
Sabo died before he could truly be free.
But the two of us, who shared
a toast with Sabo, are still alive!
So, listen up, Luffy.
We have to live our lives... with no regrets!
In this kingdom...
we become true nobles on our 18th birthday.
So before that,
I'll leave this country at 17!
Someday, we'll head out to sea,
so we can live however we want!
We'll be more free than anyone!
I'm sure we'll make lots
of enemies because of that.
Even Grandpa will fight us.
We'll be risking our lives.
We set sail at 17!
And then...
we will become pirates!
Video Editing
Sewil
Timing
Bastia
PhosCity
Timing
Sewil
Bastia
PhosCity
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin
Yibis
Translation
DemonRin
Yibis
Opening Raw
Gavynnnnn
Again, we turn back time a little...
to the night when the Celestial Dragon's
ship docked in Goa Kingdom.
Will of the Winds
In a certain region of the East Blue,
in a small seaside village...
Did you see the guy
with the huge face this afternoon?!
Yeah! I've never seen anything like it!
Look! His ship is huge too!
Five hundred and eighty...
Five hundred and eighty-one...
Five hundred and eighty-two...
Five hundred and eighty-three...
Five hundred and eighty-four...
You are late, Dragon!
How long did you plan to make us vayyt?!
I'm sorry.
Vhaat did you...?!
This is awful!
Quickly! Get a doctor! It's an emergency!
Right away!
But really! Vherre did you go?!
I was watching the ceremony
for the world nobles.
How could you go attend
on your own viithout tellingk me?!
With you there too, we would've
stuck out like sore thumbs.
You mean... thiss...?!
We must strive to grow
ever stronger, and with haste!
How are our provisions?
There was a village dojo
that offered us food.
Then we set sail!
We will return to Baltigo.
Some months later,
the World Government having concluded
their inspection of the Kingdom of Goa...
They've brought more trash!
The people are returning to their old ways,
and the Gray Terminal is back,
just like it was before.
Here I come, Ace!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
What the hell was that?
You call this a fight?
You might pack a punch,
but what's the use if you miss every time?
I told you, rubber really isn't suited for battle.
Shut up! Don't say that!
Okay, what?!
Wanna prove me wrong?!
You're just an anchor
who's immune to bulletfire!
The Gum-Gum Fruit is awesome!
Someday, I'll prove you wrong!
Soon, my pistol isn't
gonna be my only move!
Luffy, great work!
Your arm stretched a lot further
than it did yesterday!
Sabo! You're too soft on Luffy!
I knew I was getting stronger!
Even more than yesterday!
Right, Sabo?!
Sabo was a nicer older brother.
Say what?!
You wish I'd died instead?!
Huh?
I've founded my own country.
A country?
Another?
Me too!
Ace's Country
Luffy's Country
Is this really what we're doin' now?!
I'm gonna learn to survive on my own.
You guys can be Dadan's country.
I'll borrow the bath sometimes.
Ace's Country
Luffy's Country
Ace! Help me out! It's a bear!
You're gonna survive on your own, right?
Dammit!
Luffy!
Hey! Dadan's country! Anyone there?!
Luffy got hurt! He needs first aid!
Magra! Please, help Luffy!
Now, take it easy!
Hurry! Bring him in!
Now, take it easy. This is no joke.
If his wounds had been any worse,
he could have died!
You used to take on these
wild beasts as a trio, right?
It's my fault!
I should've already learned my lesson that fighting on your own
doesn't prove that you're strong!
I'm worthless!
Completely worthless!
Ace...
I'm so sorry, Luffy!
So sorry!
Hey, you guys!
Makino-chan came all the way
out here to bring us some drinks!
How to greet people properly?
Yeah.
Why the sudden interest in manners?
Well, it's 'cause I'm Luffy's big brother.
I'd like to formally meet this Captain Red Hair
and thank him for everything he did for Luffy.
What's that look for?!
I'm sorry.
Okay then, here's what you say.
So, first of all...
They ate and ran!
Wait!
Oh, we're being rude here!
Right...
Thanks for the food!
Shut up, you damn kids!
Just pay the bill!
I'm gonna win today!
Yes!
Tonight, we're having bear stew!
7 Years Later
Ace, 17 Years Old
Luffy, 14 Years Old
Take care, Ace!
Sure! See you later, Luffy!
I'll be going on ahead!
Yeah! And in three years
when I set out, I'll be much stronger!
Give it your all, Ace!
Take care of yourself!
Try not to catch a cold!
Just you wait! I'll make
a name for myself real soon!
Ace, the son of the Pirate King,
grew up in complete secrecy.
His departure from the coast of Mount Colubo
was kept modest as well.
There he goes.
Isn't anyone worried
about how Garp will take this?
You're gonna raise him, Dadan!
No, wait! Whose kid is that?!
Boss...
Ace just left.
Did he, now? I'd better brace
myself to get scolded by Garp.
That brat was nothin' but hopeless.
Oh, and Ace left a message for you!
What?! He's gone, but he wants
to complain one last time?!
He said, "Sorry for all the trouble, and thanks."
Why'd that moron have to go and say that?!
What? Boss, are you crying?
I'm not crying, you idiot!
Only three more years for me!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Damn! Just a little off.
That was close, Luffy!
Try aiming just a little lower.
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
I'm getting stronger!
Much stronger!
Several Months Later
Luffy!
Check out the newspaper!
What's up?
Look! Look!
So cool! Ace is famous now!
It's a picture of his pirate ship and crew!
Amazing! Ace is amazing!
I gotta catch up to him!
3 Years Later
Luffy, 17 Years Old
Hey, come on!
I'm leaving. You gonna see me off?
Hey!
Shut up!
The mayor and Makino might know us,
but we'd send the rest of Foosha Village
into a panic if we came down the mountain!
But...
Just get going already!
Oh, okay. Well then, guys,
thanks for everything!
Oh, don't embarrass us.
No need for thanks.
Now, take it easy.
Yep! Sure thing!
Oh, right!
Dadan! I hate mountain bandits!
Shut up, you little turd!
But I like you guys!
Don't say dumb stuff like that!
Just get lost, dammit!
You're really just all the same!
What, are you crying?
No! I'm absolutely not!
Foosha Village, at the outskirts of the
Kingdom of Goa on Dawn Island...
Hey! You're going out to sea, so just
take my old fishing boat, Luffy!
You'll sink right away in that thing!
A rowboat? C'mon!
It's gotta be this way!
This is where everything begins for me!
Sabo!
Look at me!
I'm setting out to sea too!
Sabo was first. Ace was second.
I'm the third to go,
but I won't lose to them!
Wait for me, Ace!
Soon, I'm gonna catch up!
What's all this, Luffy?
Shouting to yourself like that?
Is it some sort of good luck charm?
It's not a charm. It's a challenge!
Who's Ace?
Not a clue.
Alright, I'm outta here!
Well, Mayor, he's finally off.
I'm gonna miss him.
He's disgracing our village
by becoming a pirate!
What a nice day to set sail!
That's...
If it isn't our local sea monster.
You don't know who you're messing with.
Here's a technique 10 years in the making!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
That'll teach ya, damn fish!
Incredible! He beat the
Lord of the Coast with one punch!
He's sure grown strong.
First, I've gotta gather a crew.
Ten people oughta do it!
I'll also need a Jolly Roger!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna be...
king of the pirates!
We return to the present.
His brother Ace is dead, and Luffy...
sheds his tears.
Luffy-kun...
Me? The pirate king?
I'm...
so weak!
It's Garp-san!
Foosha Village, Kingdom of Goa, East Blue
Garp-san's returned on his battleship!
On official business?!
Garp-san! We read all about the war!
The Navy had a resounding victory, right?!
Yeah, and I'm glad to see you're all well.
Is Luffy okay?!
With Whitebeard dead,
what'll happen to the world?!
Tell us, Garp-san!
These past few days, we've seen
a lot of pirate ships on the open sea.
The thought of getting raided
keeps us awake at night!
Rest easy!
I just sank three of 'em on the way here.
Really? That's good to hear!
Buncha amateurs like them
can't even spell the word "battle"!
Although, Whitebeard was a stabilizing factor...
With him gone, every sea in the world
will be a turbulent place for some time.
Don't let your guard down just because
you live in a remote part of the East Blue.
Hey.
Yes, sir!
"Protected Area – Vice Admiral Garp, Navy Headquarters," huh?
That's so reassuring!
There's nothing to be afraid of now!
Garp-san, we have another problem.
Bandits came down out of the
mountains and took over Makino's bar!
Bandits?
Stop! Don't!
Hey, Garp!
Oh, that's her!
You've got some nerve
showing your face here again!
Garp-san!
Boss!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Stand down!
She and I go way back.
You...
You were right there on the battlefield!
They were right in front of you!
So, what the hell were you doing?!
What the hell were you doing?!
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why?! Why?!
Why did you just stand there and let Ace die?!
Your job always came before your family!
Right, Garp?!
And they call you the Hero of the Navy!
Shrivel up and die, you geezer!
Now, take it easy, boss!
That's too far!
Boss...
Garp, cat got your tongue?!
You could have saved him!
Why'd you let it happen?!
Stand up! Get on your feet!
You inhuman filth!
That's enough, Dadan-san!
Makino...
They may have been within arm's reach,
but there was nothing he could do!
The one hurting most here is Garp-san!
Y-You're wrong...
You're wrong...
You're wrong!
The one who's hurting most... is Luffy!
Now, try to imagine that he's
right here in front of you.
I'm Ace! Who the hell are you?
That's a no-go.
"Who the hell" is too rude.
Is it, "Oh, it's you?!"
Who might you be?
And just who are you?
Is it, "Who's that?"
All wrong. Are you even trying?
It's your fault for buzzing
around with nonsense!
Quit it!
Hey, Ace!
Yesterday, I found the nest of a giant snake,
and it was filled with humongous eggs!
Let's go get them!
Huh? Humongous eggs?
No, not right now!
I'm studying how to greet people!
It'll be real bad if that giant snake
catches me when I go by myself!
But I'll be fine if you're with me. C'mon!
Shut up!
You have to know how much
he looked up to his brother!
Makino!
Garp...
How's Luffy?
The newspaper says he's gone missing.
Mayor...
He escaped in a submarine.
The Navy pursued him with everything they had,
and they searched the area thoroughly.
But the vessel eluded them.
At least for now... he's alive!
Thank goodness!
Still, don't you think it's strange that
Navy Headquarters' Vice Admiral Garp
and this bandit know each other?
Good point.
Luffy might be an idiot,
but no matter what kind of pirate
he becomes, I will always stand beside him.
When I think about how he must be feeling,
it only breaks my heart.
Luffy!
You'll get through this!
Now, we take a look far away...
to somewhere in the second half
of the Grand Line, the New World.
Red Hair...
How can I thank you for this?
Don't even mention it.
Though he and I were foes, Whitebeard
deserved the respect he commanded.
Even Sengoku agrees.
Well, it's time we parted ways.
Yeah. Thanks.
Luffy, this must be difficult for you.
Word of Ace's final moments
took me by surprise.
Take back what you just said!
Don't you dare mock the man who saved me!
This era belongs to Whitebeard!
His actions were unmistakably... Captain Roger's.
I often wished my captain would retreat.
I wished he would cry.
Pay attention, Luffy.
When you experience both victory and defeat,
when you flee from battle and shed tears,
that is when you become a man.
Allow yourself to cry.
Overcome this!
Isle of Women, Calm Belt
Dammit! I'm so weak!
I can't protect anyone!
Luffy-kun.
Go away!
Go away...! Just leave me alone!
I can't do that! If I did, that would mean
letting you hurt yourself further!
It's my body to hurt!
I'll do what I want to it!
Then by the same token, Ace-san
was allowed to hurt his own body...
and died regardless of how we felt!
Just shut up!
One more word, and I'll kick your ass!
Then try it, if you think it'll help!
I, too, am injured, but I won't lose.
Not as you currently are!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Jinbe...
While I was out chasing Teach...
I met my little brother
for the first time in three years...
in the Kingdom of Arabasta.
As soon as I saw him, I felt relieved.
Do you know why?
Ow! That hurts!
I said that hurts, you punk!
What happened to your perspective?!
Where's that confidence that
saw you through every obstacle?!
Or that strength you never once doubted?!
A horde of enemies suddenly shatters your
beliefs and renders you unable to do a thing...
Your brother was your guiding light!
Indeed, this is a great loss.
There's something obstructing your view
of the entire world around you!
You can no longer see the path ahead!
Dark clouds of regret and guilt consume you!
Your pain overwhelms you, Luffy,
but fight it!
You can't just dwell on your loss!
What's gone is gone!
But ask yourself this:
What do you still have?!
Luffy, don't mess around up here!
My regimen needs focus!
Luffy, hurry and get everyone into position!
A storm's just ahead!
Luffy, check it out!
You'll bear witness as I snag a huge fish!
Luffy, it's almost done.
Be patient and wait!
Luffy, no matter the injury, you'll be fine!
I'll always just fix you up, good as new!
Oh, Luffy.
If you're interested,
I can teach you about archaeology.
Hey, Luffy! The cola engine
is purring like a kitten today!
Don't worry 'bout the Sunny!
Just leave 'er to me!
Luffy-san, good day to you! It's morning!
Well then, let's get started with a morning ditty!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
My crew...
I still have my crew!
Zoro! Nami! Usopp!
Sanji! Chopper! Robin!
Franky! Brook!
My friends are still here!
I see.
We promised to meet up somewhere.
Guys, meet back at the Sunny in three days!
Right!
I gotta get there,
even though I'm running late.
I'm sure they're all waiting for me!
It's because of what I saw there... Jinbe...
I have a reckless little brother,
which worries your big brother.
And I'm sure he does nothing
but stress you all out.
Take care of him for me.
I saw that Luffy's no longer that kid
who couldn't help but follow me everywhere.
You see now...
he has a crew he can rely on.
No matter what happens, he'll be just fine.
I was so relieved.
I... wanna see them.
I really wanna see them!