Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
Translation & initial timing
Yibis
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
Fine timing & typesetting
Sewil
Timing
Galaxy 9000
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
Halee
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
Soundtracking
Halee
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Video editing         Sewil
Raw provider      GS-Raws
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Just what has happened to his majesty?
The entire country has fallen into a panic.
I felt that there was something strange about him when he ran out of the palace earlier.
But for him to do something like this...
Since this is no longer a matter we can handle ourselves, I've contacted the Navy.
Captain Vergo said that he would handle things.
Father...
Snow?
Monet? What are you doing here?
Why is a maid like you opening the palace gates?
Princess Viola, if you were to use your Clairvoyance,
then you should be able to see what is truly going on in this country.
I am now preparing to welcome the new royal family.
The eastern tower is on fire!
Pirates have invaded the palace!
Viola-sama has been taken hostage!
This palace has a good view.
It's not bad.
Yeah, it's great -dasuyan.
It's a palace worthy of the young master -in!
Stop right there!
Are you Doflamingo's subordinates?!
Monet, release Viola-sama!
Did you guys do something to his majesty?!
My, things are going to get busy.
We must clean out the royal palace.
Why is the Riku Royal Army doing this?!
Please stop!
If I'm forced to hurt my citizens...
I'd rather just die!
Someone please, kill me!
Why are you doing this, King Riku?
Have we done something wrong?
You were always righteous.
You were...
the king we were proud of.
Since you asked for our money...
We gave you everything we had.
You've always thought of us first and foremost.
We were proud of our king!
King Riku...
King Riku has trampled on our feelings!
He's trying to kill us and steal our money!
For his own greed, he's treating us like trash!
Curse you, King Riku!
I hate you!
You're...
You're the scum of humanity!
The Riku Royal Army is coming!
Hey, get out of there, run away!
S-Save-
Who are you people?
I've come to save this country.
My name is Donquixote Doflamingo.
H-He's a pirate.
But they beat the Riku Royal Army.
That was a beautiful dance, King Riku.
Trébol, Pica, Diamante. Go clean up the trash.
He did it!
We're saved.
Doflamingo! Doflamingo! Doflamingo!
Fall into depravity, embrace violence.
In just one night, the country fell under Doflamingo's control.
What a story, it's like a nightmare.
He's a cunning man.
I-I-I'll never forgive you, Doflamingo!
At the time, we too believed that King Riku had gone crazy, and approached the new king, Doflamingo.
This was the result.
I am ashamed that we couldn't believe in King Riku.
I see, it's really too bad.
Everyone loved the king so much, yet he died while being cursed for a crime he never committed.
No, King Riku is still alive.
Doflamingo wanted the ability of the princess at the time, Viola-sama.
So she gave him a condition.
If you promise not to kill my father, then
I will serve under you!
She is alive right now as Doflamingo's subordinate.
She changed her name to Violet, and is now a commander in the Family.
C-Commander?
Then, thanks to the princess, King Riku is...
Yes, he is alive somewhere in this country.
But, the pain he has gone through these past ten years is unimaginable.
And how hard it must have been for Viola-sama.
Fear, anger, tears!
I wonder how she's spent the last ten years.
She was controlled just like King Riku was, and forced to hurt the citizens.
The anger of those soldiers must be just as large.
Weren't King Riku's soldiers killed on that night?
Some were killed and some bowed down to Doflamingo.
They now live as his guards.
They changed sides!
I believe they were forced to make a difficult decision.
Don't screw with us!
They were under orders from the crazed King Riku.
Allow me to make them my subordinates.
If that's the case then they make me want to cry!
Every last one of them!
The soldiers that were killed, and the ones that bowed down.
Even if we add them up, they're too few to make up the army of a country.
What are you talking about?
I mean that I have lost memories as well.
Fraland. I showed you in town, correct?
We remember everything from when we were human,
but everyone else, even our families, forgot everything about us.
Nobody knows they've forgotten about people important to them.
That is the greatest tragedy of Dressrosa,
and it goes for us toys as well.
So among all those toys walking around town, there may be some of your old comrades.
But you yourself have forgotten them so you don't know?
Exactly.
Also, everyone who was turned into a toy harbors hatred toward Doflamingo.
Doflamingo has buried anyone who opposed him.
Which means that in the country's darkness, there are countless people who oppose him.
That unknown number of tragedies is the key to our plan.
I see, so that's it.
That's what you meant when you said you still have a chance.
True, with just these numbers, taking on a Warlord and his crew would be near impossible.
But if every toy in the country were to join us,
then that would make for quite the fighting force.
Hey, wait up a bit!
Why are you trying to go after Doflamingo as well?!
Our only goal is the destruction of the factory.
When we've done that, we're getting out of this country.
Isn't that right, Robin?
I won't forgive Doflamingo.
Today is the day of our long awaited final battle!
The event of this morning was a challenge to us!
And the fact that Usoland appeared here today is no coincidence!
It is the heavens telling us to fight!
The event of this morning?
When Doflamingo temporarily abdicated his throne.
Oh that, yeah, we were the-
Can you imagine our delight when we heard the news?
We thought a miracle had occurred.
And then the notice that it was misinformation.
To us, it was like being dropped from heaven into the depths of hell.
So it was only natural for us to make today the day we fight him.
Umm, I'm really sorry.
Beneath Dressrosa
Even though you're retired, you brought a ship over here?
Scrap Yard
Well I don't have anyone to take over the Happou Navy.
If only I had a grandchild.
I see.
So things aren't going well, even for the villains.
Is it just my imagination?
I feel like there's a gap in my memory.
I had the same feeling ten years ago.
What the hell, where on earth am I going?!
Gramps, save me!
What did they do to me, the lone wolf, Abdullah?!
What did they do to me, the maverick warrior, Jeet?!
Help!
Corrida Colosseum
Zoro!
Damn that hen-comb guy.
He said he'd show me the way, then he just collapsed.
Is Zoro really here?
Hey, Zoro, Kin'emon!
Luffy!
You're being too loud, you idiot!
I had my doubts, but it would appear that the odd-speaking fellow was able to carry out his mission.
Where is he?
He just collapsed on the way here.
I finally found you, Straw Hat!
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Get it done before the tournament ends.
Do so, and you'll finally be a member of the Family.
Sorry about this, Straw Hat.
Ah, there you are, Bellamy.
Are you done with the assassination yet?
Doesn't seem like it.
What do you want, Dellinger?!
Donquixote Family (♦Diamante Army)
Combatant, Dellinger
Well, I figured...
you'd lose your nerve and be unable to kill him.
What?!
Well, I guess it was unavoidable, seeing who the target was.
Well, it doesn't really matter whether you succeed or not.
What's that supposed to mean?!
The assassination order was just one of his whims.
He said it was a pain having you cling to him all the time,
so I'm meant to kill you right here.
Under the young master's orders.
What... the hell?!
Oops!
I wasn't supposed to mention that!
Sorry!
You've gotta be kidding me!
The steel bridge on the outskirts of Dressrosa
Mes!
Bullet Thread!
So what will you do, Law?
Dressrosa is right behind you.
Hey, Doffy.
Oh, sorry. Were you busy?
Not particularly. Go on.
Violet has betrayed us.
Black Leg just showed up earlier, so I wondered what had happened.
The plan was to have her expose Straw Hat's plan with her Glare Fruit powers,
but it seems we'll have to remain ignorant.
Oh, no problems there.
Diamante, station Lao G and the others around the entrances to the Smile factory.
Don't be ridiculous.
They're supposed to participate in the finale, to make things more exciting for the audience.
You'll be more than enough to entertain them.
Oh, you talk as if I'm some kind of prodigy.
But you are. Only you can do it.
No really, stop acting like I'm-
You are a prodigy!
If you must insist, then very well!
Law. You were going to distract me,
and then the Straw Hats would use that chance to destroy the factory.
Once the factory was destroyed, then it wouldn't matter if you were alive or dead.
Having lost the Smiles, I would get killed by Kaidou.
That was the plan, right?
But you were defeated much sooner than you anticipated,
and the Straw Hats will fall in turn.
You may say you were just using them,
but this plan required an immense amount of trust in the Straw Hats.
Why do you...
believe so strongly in him?
"D" will definitely...
cause another storm!
So what did you want, Zoro?
Listen, if there was a tournament like this going on, why didn't you invite me?!
Sorry!
Dressrosa
In front of the Corrida Colosseum
Here we are running all over town while you're just having fun!
That was not our message, sir!
Vice-Admiral Bastille!
Just as we thought, that man is the Pirate Hunter!
What's more, we believe the man inside the Colosseum is Straw Hat Luffy!
Vice-Admiral at Navy HQ
Shark-Slicer Bastille
You mean the winner of Block C, Lucy?
That explains his strength.
So he's in this country, just like Smoker reported.
Shall we capture him?
No, let him swim free for now.
That place is crawling with...
pirates, bounty-hunters and mercenaries renowned throughout the New World.
If we go in there and cause a ruckus trying to capture Straw Hat,
we'll be found out.
We'll capture all the villains who come out of the colosseum, without letting a single one go free.
If we're gonna do this, we might as well take them all down in one fell swoop.
The fighters who have been defeated are...
Block C's Don Chinjao, and...
I don't recognize any of these names.
Who are we even here to capture?
What?
Will this do?
What are you doing?
Sanji-dono told me to call him once we meet Luffy-dono.
Okay.
Oh right, Luffy.
The navy has surrounded the colosseum.
So casual! That's what we came to say!
The seas surrounding Dressrosa
That's Kin'emon.
Oh, Sanji? It's me.
Luffy?
Right, Chopper. Use that one to contact Usopp.
Alright.
Usopp here!
So now we've got everyone except Law.
What's going on over there on your ends?
Franky here!
Usopp and Robin are here too.
What are you doing?!
Listen up, all of you.
We're here together with the rebels fighting Doflamingo, the Riku Royal Army.
Army?
An army of dwarves.
Dwarves?
Usoland, what are you doing?
We're having a hero's meeting! Don't eavesdrop!
Very well.
Excuse us!
Hey Luffy,
you remember that strange soldier we met in front of the colosseum?
Yeah. So what's this about dwarves?
It turns out he was the captain of this army.
And the gang gathered here are planning to fight Doflamingo, today.
Wait, soldier?
He intends to sacrifice his own life...
to bring down this kingdom!
Oh, right! About that toy-soldier...
He's the one Rebecca wanted to stop!
Franky, you've gotta stop that army!
Like hell!
I'm trying to say the exact opposite of that!
Did you talk to that Rebecca-girl?
Yeah. She's really nice.
She's poor, and she still bought me three lunch-boxes!
But once she entered the fight, the audience started really pissing me off!
I agree.
Luffy. I...
can't follow Traf's plan!
H-Hey, Franky, what are you saying?!
Traf's plan was like this, right?
We destroy the factory, and then let Doflamingo live so that we can use him to get to Kaidou.
But if we do that...
what becomes of the guys who are planning to fight Doflamingo today?
The dwarves won't back down.
This country may have seemed like fun,
but there's a deep, deep darkness here.
They're all about to put their lives on the line to destroy that darkness!
Considering their size, that's really inspiring.
This tiny, brave army is standing up to that filthy, gigantic foe.
I...
can't abandon them.
Do you think that we should still let Doflamingo win in spite of that?
Luffy. It doesn't matter what you say...
I won't back down!
Franky...
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Franky.
Do whatever you want!
We'll be right there!
Thanks!
Alright, let's turn around.
Whaaat?!
I knew it!
Shores of Dressrosa
What?
What's going on in the city?!
Issho-san, there's a huge fight taking place in the city!
Let's move.
What's that? I heard a loud noise from your end.
What could that be? The city is...
Whatever it is, it's getting closer!
What's going on?! I can't see!
What?!
Vice-Admiral Bastille, is that...
Doflamingo!
Traf!
You brat!
Hey, Traf!
Why are you with Doflaming-
You got too cocky for your own good.
Cora-san...
Traf!