Nami's been kidnapped?
It's my fault.
They were huge, but I still didn't notice them until they were right in front of us.
First it's centaurs, now it's beastmen?!
This island's crawling with weirdos.
Maybe they're testing us for weaknesses.
So, they didn't come to rescue Brown-gator?
Their true objective seemed to be the children,
and our lives!
But it sounded like Master hired them to silence Brownbeard first.
Even though they're supposed to be friends.
Even though Brownbeard admired Master so much.
Master is the kind-hearted god of salvation.
Luffy, Master really is a twisted individual.
I would never let the children go back
to such a cruel person!
I'm also worried about Nami-Franky, who got kidnapped.
Who knows what they could be doing to her?!
Yeah, we're definitely getting her back.
Okay, I'll leave the kids to you!
Hold it, Luffy!
It was my body that they took.
Chopper, I can't fight in this body.
Gimme some of those beans that you use to transform.
The beans that make you a monster.
Beans?  The Rumble Ball is a dangerous drug!
It'd probably be impossible for you to control it!
I'll super-overcome that with fighting spirit!
Just hurry up and gimme 'em!
Okay, but just one.
Got it?  You can only be a monster for three minutes.
After that, you won't be able to fight.
If possible, just use Kung-fu Point which I showed you earlier.
Vvvvvvvvuper!
Too soon!
Let's go, Franky.  This way!
Why are you attacking me?!
It's no good!  I knew he'd go berserk!
So... what was Franky planning to do?
After the rampage he won't be able to move,
so I don't think he'll be much help... at all.
He's just going to be in the way.
Caesar's Laboratory
I don't know where he got it,
but it seems that the metal man Franky
installed one of Vegapunk's lasers into his body.
After we dissect him and take the laser system, there'll be no other use for him.
Might as well throw him in the incinerator.
Understood.
And can you tell me what happened
to those stupid Marines who came to take a ship?
Y-Yes, sir.
The battle has become quite chaotic...
So... you're saying that you can't handle it?
Well, you see...
Oh, I know just the thing!
Master?
We are fighting the Navy.
This is a perfect situation to put him to the test.
Oh, that's good.  Let's do that.
Immediately contact the centaurs that are out on patrol.
Yes, sir!
And tell the rest of the soldiers to use this time to evacuate.
If they want to live, that is.
Laboratory - Far Side of the Mountain
Lemme go!  Lemme go, you idiot!
What are you perverts doing?!
Why are you kidnapping me?
Although I am cute, and proportioned,
so I understand why you would want to kidnap me.
What is this man saying?
He must be queer.  Pretty cool.
But it doesn't matter what you do!
Luffy won't let you get away!
You're gonna get beaten to a pulp!
Shut up now.  People who talk too much...
are not cool.
But apparently,
the weapon that's built into your body...
is cool.
And when we hand you over to Master,
the reward will be...
so cool!
Rock
But it's really cold today.
Scotch
Yeah, our bodies are too cool.
- Hit Men of Snowy Mountain -
Yeti Cool Brothers
Put some clothes on!
With the difference in size between us,
these rifles are like cannons to you.
We have poison-gas bullets, too.
And if we don't show ourselves
then there's no way to defeat us.
You got friends coming?  Of course you do.
We arranged for them to come here!
It's only natural that they'll follow our footsteps.
Footsteps!  Footsteps!  Man, this is great!
It's so easy to see where they're going.
Hey!  Franky!  I said to cut it out!
Huh?
The footsteps disappeared.
Luffy?  And Chopper... No, that's Franky!
Nami!
Watch out!  There are enemies here!
Let's go, Scotch.
Okay.
He must be pretty thick
if he didn't even notice the cliff.
There's spikes below!
This is almost too easy.
The ice spikes will pierce him!
Color of Arms - Hardening
I see.
I guess the normal tricks won't be enough.
Dead end!
Using this technique to deflect attacks
in random directions isn't much good in a fight.
Rayleigh taught me that.
Instead, turn it into a counterattack by sending
every bullet back at your enemy with double power!
Gun Salute
Rock!
I said cut it out, Franky!
Why is he the one giving you the most trouble here?!
Now I'm hot and bothered.
They're fighting amongst themselves?
They're underestimating us!
Quit it!
I'll show you! The frozen mountain has all kinds of weapons!
Look out!  The frozen summit's falling!
Luffy!  Franky!  Look up!  Up!
You won't be able to dodge
that block of ice after I'm done!
They're attacking from the sides!  Enemies!
This KYP gas-bullet will knock you out instantly!
Die, just like your other friends!
He did something useful!
Great job, Franky!
Hey, gimme a break!
That's the strongest attack you've used today!
Luffy!
Dammit!  Sorry, Franky-Chopper.
I'll have Chopper look at your injuries later.
Stop right there!
I thought we told you.
The mountain is our playground.
It's impossible to catch me.
Save me!
He doesn't give up.  But he can't match my reach.
He's like a monkey.
Alright!
Dammit.  The mountain's huge,
so if he gets away then it'll be impossible to find him.
Him?
Well, if it isn't Trafalgar Law, the freeloader.
It's a good thing I ran into you.  Right now, Straw Hat Luffy is...
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Thank you!
Wait... Hey, you!  Gimme my body back!
Nami!
Luffy!
Oh, it's Traf!  So you saved Nami?
I've been thinking.
There's something
I'd like to discuss with you, Straw-Hatter.
It may have been just a coincidence that you came to this island,
but there's actually a key hidden here.  One with
the power to throw the entire New World into chaos.
There are two ways to survive in the New World.
Either be protected by one of the Four Emperors,
or fight all of them.
You're not the kind of guy
who'll serve under someone else, are you?
That's right.  I prefer being the captain!
In that case, form an alliance with me.
An alliance?
If you and I work together, we might be able to do it.
I've got a plan to dethrone one of the Four Emperors.
An alliance?
Are you suggesting that if we work together
we could defeat one of the Four Emperors?
That's ridiculous!  I don't know what you're after, but...
Luffy, don't fall for his fast talk.
I didn't say we'd be able to do it now.
But if we play our cards right
we should eventually be able to create an opportunity.
What do you say, Straw-Hatter?
Which one of the Four Emperors are you talking about?
Hold on, Luffy!  Why are you listening to him?
You can't trust someone like him!
I see.
Okay!  We're in!
What?!
Straw Hat Pirates' Temporary Shelter
Whaaaat?!
We're forming an alliance with the Heart Pirates?!
You just went to get Nami back,
so how did it come to such a crazy deal?!
Like I said-
I won't be able to sleep at night if we form an alliance with such an enigmatic, unpredictable bastard!
Come on Luffy, everybody's against it.
We don't have to do it.
There's no reason to do something this dangerous.
We should continue our voyage at our own pace.
That's right, Luffy!
It's far too soon to try to take on the Four Emperors!
There's no way we could fight them.
So what about this raccoon dog?
I'm not a raccoon dog anymore!
Whaa?!
It's me!
S-Super...
What happened to me?!
Luffy...
I'll follow your decision, but...
pirate alliances and betrayal go hand in hand.
They might not be suited
for someone as overly trusting as you.
Hey, you gonna betray me?
Nope.
Hey!  Try to be a little skeptical!
Anyway,
I think a pirate alliance sounds like a lot of fun!
I think Traf's a good guy...
but even if he isn't, there's no need to worry!
You guys have trained a lot in the past two years
and can back me up.
Whaaa?!
Luffy, you...
Oh, cut it out!  It's embarrassing.
Hey, you can super-rely on us.
We do manage to help out every now and then...
but it's not like we're happy, you jerk!
A-Alright then, Luffy!  You can rely on us!
If Zoro and the others chicken out,
I will convince them!
I'm back!  Back in my perfect body!
Yep, being me is best for me!
Super!
That's great, Franky.
I hope you never wind up back in Chopper's body,
ever again.
I'm also...
back to normal.
But how could you leave my body all broken?!
What the hell were you thinking,
treating other people's bodies like this?!
Oh, sorry.
It's all his fault.
What?!
You were the one rampaging in Chopper's body!
My only choice was to stop you!
But still, you didn't have to use an attack powerful enough to take out the kraken!
You're both just as bad!
Oh, sorry.
Isn't it enough just to be in your own body, Chopper?
Why am I the only one who has to bear this pain?!
First Franky's body and now Sanji-kun.
Don't laugh at others' expense!  I can't believe you!
There's nothing we can do.
We have Chopper and Franky's bodies,
so their souls can return to the right places...
but Sanji took your body to search for the samurai.
Your soul was left over,
so it had to go into Sanji's body.
Can't you do anything?  Come on!
It's impossible without a body.
So these are the children?
Yeah, I wanna save these kids.
They're more trouble than they're worth.  Leave 'em.
Apparently they're all addicted to drugs.
We know that!  I examined them!
That's why I want to take them back to their homes, but it'll take time to get the drug out of their system.
And they've been turned into giants too.
What a terrible experiment they performed on them
They've been researching
how to turn humans into giants for centuries.
The project was run by the World Government.
The Government?  Why would they do such a thing?
Most likely to make soldiers.
Nobody could stand against the Government
if they turned all of their soldiers into giants.
If Caesar successfully perfects the process
then he would trump the Government and Vegapunk...
but of course it isn't an easy thing to do.
You really want to save them?
They're just some random kids from here and there.
Yes.  Maybe we've never met
or even seen these kids before...
but the kids cried and begged that we save them.
Master may have done a good job
of tricking them to bring them here,
but some of the older children are already realizing that this facility isn't exactly what it seems.
Until I make sure that these kids are safe,
I will never leave this island!
So, are you planning to stay here by yourself?
We don't leave anybody behind.
Nami and Chopper want to do it,
so I'll help them.
Oh, and Sanji went to put the samurai back together.
If you're going to be allied with us
then you gotta help us out.
Jeez, I knew you had no idea what was going on.
The "alliance" he asked you to form...
only means that we're working together for the
sole purpose of achieving a certain objective, right?
Naturally.
That's what you meant, but when Luffy
hears the word "alliance" he thinks of something else.
Like friends, right?
If you thought you could get him to follow some plan,
that isn't gonna happen.
Yep, that's right.
Once he gets some wild idea, he won't budge.
That's the problem with Luffy.  It's always like this.
In terms of self-centered stubbornness, Luffy's on par with the Four Emperors.
Wow, that sounds terrible.
But what your crew member is currently trying to do
has absolutely nothing to do with our-
Hey!  Don't flick boogers on me, you asshole!
Oh, my bad!
I can't even dodge when I'm like this!
My bad.
Oh, all right.  We don't have time to argue.
You guys can take care of the samurai yourselves.
I'll investigate the drug
that was administered to the children.
Which one of you is the doctor?
Come with me.  We'll have to distract Caesar.
Okay, this should do it.
Sorry.  I can't move right now so I'll have to rely on you.
Don't drop him, Traf!
Sorry... can't stop... laughing!
Super-cute!
We're counting on you, Chopper.
Leave it to me.
It should be clear
from the actions of the two assassins...
Caesaro plans to kill both you and White Hunter's G-5,
and then take the kids back.
He'll keep coming until he gets what he wants.
Four years ago, as a former Government scientist, he was judged a criminal after the accident.
If word gets out that there are people on this island, which is supposed to be off-limits to everyone,
then he'll lose this perfect hideout.
That's why he'll do everything he can to kill you.
He has a bounty of 300 million beli.
He possesses weapons of mass destruction as well as
the powers of the Gas Gas Fruit, a logia-type.
That's the Caesar Clown we're dealing with.
300 million...
People who can't wield haki
should definitely stay away from him.
He isn't your average scientist.
Our haki-users are me, Zoro, and Sanji.
And you, I presume?
That should be enough.
I'll head to the laboratory first.
Then when we get there,
we'll all kidnap Master together.
That's right.
But... what do you mean by kidnap?
For ransom?  But wouldn't Master have the money?
If you kidnap him, who's going to pay us?
The objective isn't money.  It's confusion.
Confusion?
What do you mean?
There's no point in talking about it, until we succeed.
Anyways, focus on capturing Caesar Clown.
It won't be easy.
When the time comes,
I'll lay out the entire plan to everyone.
But once we succeed in capturing Caesar,
the situation's naturally going to be chaotic.
When that happens, there's no turning back.
I guess this is our last chance to change our minds.
It's fine.  I'll work with you.
In that case, I also accept your wishes.
Make sure to convince the rest of your crew as well.
Yeah, got it.
Caesar Clown's Laboratory - Main Entrance
Take this!  You damn monster!
Iron-joint Smoodge!
Fein Bock the Gourd!
Chappe the Rope-puller!
Smoker-san!
There's no doubt, these are all former prisoners.
Though their bodies have been changed.
What is this?!
The accident report from four years ago said that none of the prisoners survived.  Was that a lie?
Smo-san, who are these guys?!
Hell if I know!
Just focus on drawing the enemy inland for now!
We will get on board that ship,
and set sail to make our report!
Master, the Snail Phone's ringing.
No need to answer it.
They're going to say, "We opened the door."
And then, "Something came out of it."
"Some of our men died.  Save us."
And then screams.
It's hard on the ears.
We have more than enough people like that.
We can always capture more test subjects.
Can you hear me?!  Master!  Can you hear me?!
Please come in!
This is the Burning Lands!
We opened the door, just like you said!
It's no use!  Master isn't answering!
It's coming!
What the hell is that thing
that came out of the warehouse?
We've already lost too many men.  Just run!
It's as big as a mountain!  What the hell is that blob?!
It's right behind us!  Save us!
Master!
Let me introduce my pet.
It's an extremely rare life-form, a slime.
Ma...ster...
No one will make it off this island alive!
How's it feel to be free after so long?
Smiley!