Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Meggo
Graphics
Datenshi
Girl-Krillin
DemonRin
Datenshi
Girl-Krillin
DemonRin
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
iconsumekidneys
Subtitle Editing
JT-421
Zenef
Translation
Funimation
Gaijin
Raws
df68
Enter: Sanji
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Huh? That was way off!
What are you up to?
Cannon practice!
But they sure don't fly too good!
I'm telling you, let me try!
Judging from
the last shot's trajectory...
That should do it.
Fire!
Awesome!
You hit it on your first try!
I really hit it...
What do you think?! I'm awesome
at target practice! Impressed?!
Yeah! Yeah!
It's settled! You're our marksman!
What?! I don't get to be the captain?!
I'm the captain!
Well, whatever!
I'll humor you for now!
But if you do anything too cowardly,
I'm taking over immediately!
Yeah, that's fine.
But anyway, I was thinking,
we need to fill one other position
before going to the Grand Line!
Yeah! We do have a fancy kitchen!
If you pay me, I can do it!
They're a necessity on long journeys!
Yeah! All pirate ships need one, huh?!
A musician!
Are you an idiot?!
What do you think a voyage is?!
I thought you'd finally
say something smart...
But pirates sing, you know!
Get out here, you damn pirates!
What?! What?! Who are you?!
Shut up!
Who I am doesn't matter!
How many are there?
One... I think?
Then he can handle it.
We've taken the heads
of many a pirate!
Tattoo: "Sea"
Are you nameless pirate wannabes
trying to kill my partner?!
That voice...
What do you mean, "partner"?!
I dunno what's going on,
but stop breaking our ship!
L-Lost by a hair...
What's going on?
Hey! Is that you, Johnny?!
Who the hell are you
to say my name?!
B-Big Bro Zoro?!
It is you, Johnny!
Why are you on a pirate ship?!
Is something wrong? Where's Yosaku?
Well...
What? Does Zoro know that guy?
What's going on?
Y-Yosaku is...
He's sick?
He was fine until a few days ago.
All of a sudden, he went pale
and kept fainting.
I have no idea what's causing it.
Eventually, teeth began falling out,
and an old wound was bleeding again.
I didn't know what to do any more.
So, I took him to rest
on a rocky islet. But then...
a cannonball came
flying from this ship...
– W-We're sorry!
Sorry doesn't cut it.
Isn't that right, partner?
Big Bro, is he going to die?
Are you all stupid?
What'd you say?!
Wh-What're you doing?!
Ouch!
If you mock my
partner's death, you'll pay for–
Luffy! Usopp!
Remember the limes in the pantry?
Are you listening?!
Bring them here. Now!
– Yes ma'am!
– Out of my way!
It's scurvy.
Scurvy?
If we're not too late,
he'll be fine in just a few days.
R-Really, Big Sis?!
Big Sis, is he really...
Stop... calling me that.
In the past, it was a hopeless disease
that came with sailing.
– Here, drink it. Drink a lot.
– Here... drink more. Drink more.
But the cause was simply
a deficiency of plant-based nutrients.
Back then, ships didn't carry
fresh produce since it didn't keep.
You're amazing!
You're like a doctor!
Well, I always thought
you were a can-do kind of girl.
You should already know this!
One day it could kill you!
Wha...
– Yaay! Yaay! Yaay!
Those nutrients brought me back!
All right, partner!
There's no way you can
recover that quickly!
Sorry for the late introduction.
My name is Johnny.
I'm Yosaku.
Johnny and Yosaku
Bounty Hunter Duo
The pirate bounty hunter duo!
We used to work with Big Bro Zoro.
Glad to make your acquaintance.
I never thought
I'd see you guys here.
We're just as surprised as you are.
Hard to believe Pirate Hunter Zoro
would become a pirate himself.
Yeah, I know.
Big Bro!
H-Hey, partner?!
This is a lesson.
Yeah. There are pitfalls like this
on extended voyages.
We'll have to balance our nutrition
using the limited food we have on board.
If you think about it,
I suppose it requires a set of skills.
A required set of skills, huh?
Okay, then! A seafaring cook!
– What?
Let's go find a seafaring cook!
That's it! Then we'll be able
to eat well even at sea!
Exactly!
If you're looking for a cook like that,
there's a perfect place for it.
But this place is close
to the Grand Line.
Rumor has it,
it's close to where you'll find
the hawk-eyed man.
Set course for...
north-northeast!
Huh!
All right!
Our destination is...
the Sea Restaurant...
Baratie!
Baratie
The Sea Restaurant
– Whoa!
What do you think, everyone?!
Whoa! It's a huge fish!
How lovely!
That's pretty funky!
Right?! Just like I told you, right?!
Wh-What the...
At a place like this...
A Marine ship...
Th-There's no way they'd
shoot at us, would they?
Wh-When did they show up?!
I've never seen that pirate flag.
Darn it!
We're not pirates!
Lieutenant "Ironfist" Fullbody
Marine Headquarters
I'm from Marine Headquarters!
Lieutenant Ironfist Fullbody!
Hey, who's your captain?!
Come out and state your name!
I'm Luffy!
I'm Usopp!
We just made our pirate flag
the day before yesterday!
And I'm the one who drew it!
Hmph! Oh, you're just...
Hm?
You two over there,
I remember seeing you before.
If I recall correctly, you're a pair of
small-time bounty hunters.
Wh-What?!
So you finally got caught by pirates?
W-We are...
That's a laugh.
C'mon, let's get going.
Okay.
You think small-time bounty hunters
would go after these guys?!
Hm?
Now, let's go to the restaurant.
They're an eyesore. Sink them.
– Yes, sir!
He ignored us.
Next time we see him,
we'll shut him up!
What is this?
They're wanted pirates,
Big Sis Na–
In other words, if we defeat them,
we'll get the reward money.
A profitable business.
Right, Big Sis?
Th-This is bad!
They're aiming right at us!
Leave it to me!
Gum-Gum...
Slingshot!
Ow...
Chef Zeff!
Are you all right, Head Chef Zeff?!
Chef Zeff, are you all right?!
Head Chef Zeff, are you really okay?
I'm saying I'm not okay!
Never mind, just get back to
the restaurant already! Get to work!
B-But Chef Zeff, you're...
You idiots! Are you
trying to piss me off?!
Feeding customers is a cook's job!
Are you morons trying to put
my restaurant out of business?!
We brought him in.
He's the one responsible.
I-I-I-I'm very sorry!
Ahhh! Your leg...
Idiot!
O-Oh, then it was already like that.
Head Chef & Proprietor Zeff
Sea Restaurant
But I'm bruised all over.
The medical fees and the repairs
for the ship will cost you a fortune!
I won't ask you to reduce the charges.
Oh?
But...
I don't have money!
Tch! You've gotta be kidding me.
Well, if you don't have money,
you have no choice
but to work here.
Yeah, I'll be sure to pay you back.
You'll do chores unpaid, for a year.
Okay! Chores unpaid, for a year!
I'll let you off the hook with that.
A-A year?! A-A year...
You mean a year?!
What's taking Luffy so long?
Yeah.
Maybe they'll make him
do chores for a month or so.
He should've pinned it on the Marines,
that simple, honest fool.
Hey, look.
Just as I thought, the man
sitting there is Lieutenant Fullbody.
He's a lieutenant
from Marine Headquarters.
Huh?
He's gorgeous. How elegant.
It's amazing.
Everyone's looking at you.
Well, they're admiring you.
This is good!
Th-This flavor...
Hmm... This scent...
It has a hint of the soil
from Micqueot, the Northlands.
Dry with plenty of body, a tad sour...
This wine is...
Ithürzburger Stein!
Aren't I right, waiter?!
That's...
damn wrong, sir.
Your soup is getting cold.
Please eat it while it's hot.
By the way, I'm Sanji, the sous-chef.
Sous-Chef Sanji
Sea Restaurant
All the waiters ran off yesterday.
You really shouldn't laugh.
But he looked so confident!
Do you know a lot...
about wine?
Well, yeah...
although it seems my sense
of taste is a bit off today...
Hey, what's going on?
I'm sure I requested the owner to serve us
that wine when I made the reservation.
What do you mean by that?
Please reduce it to a week.
Tch. You've gotta be kidding me.
Two weeks!
Hey! You wrecked my restaurant
and seriously injured me, the head chef.
You can't settle that with just
one or two weeks of unpaid work.
I've decided! Three weeks!
Stop...
kidding around!
No!
Hm?
I've patiently waited ten years
to become a pirate.
I definitely don't want
to be stuck here for another year!
Hmm?
Okay, I've decided.
I'll get you to let me
off the hook in a week.
That's my decision.
Oh? If you value time so much,
I'll tell you what you can do
to settle it quickly.
Ow!
Leave one of your legs here.
No!
Ha! You've gotta be kidding me!
Waiter!
Hmm?
Didn't I tell you that I'm not a waiter?
But my, how beautiful you are!
Say, miss, would you like to have
some wine with me over there?
Hm?
Hey! Do you serve soup
with bugs in it to customers?!
Bugs?
What the hell is this bug?!
Hmph! This will torpedo
this restaurant's reputation!
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't know.
I don't know much about insects.
Don't mess with me!
You could've eaten it had you taken
that bug out, couldn't you?
I spent three days and nights
on this soup, skimming the scum.
Aren't you acting a bit
too big for your britches?
I'm a customer! I'm paying you!
Fullbody, please stop!
Shut up!
F-Fullbody...
Can money...
satisfy your hunger?
What'd you say?
I'm asking you...
Can it satisfy your hunger?!
No!
No! No!
Don't think that you can survive
by repeating "no," kid.
No!
You're kidding me!
F-Fullbody...
Sanji...
Sous-Chef!
Hmm?
A fight?
Don't... waste food.
Remember this:
Crossing a cook at sea
is tantamount to suicide.
I can't... hold it anymore...
Serving customers! That is "love"!
And "love" means "restaurant"!
The customer is king!
Motto! Motto! It's my service motto!
Service is about pleasant greetings!
Cook Patty
Sea Restaurant
Welcome, ya damn crook.
Please never come back.
I'm terribly sorry.
Ten thousand belly coming in!
You look pathetic! Yahoo!
Alright!
I took a healthy dump,
and I'm doing great today!
Oh? Welcome, ya damn crook.
Motto! Motto! It's my
service motto! The customer is–
Ahh! Our customer!
Again, Sanji?! What are you
doing to our customer?!
And he's a Marine lieutenant to boot!
What is it, you crappy cook?!
Don't call my name
as if I were your friend!
A crappy cook has no right
to call me "crappy cook"!
Customers make the restaurant!
Hurting our precious customer...
What do you think you're doing?!
Who cares about customers?
He wasted his food
and insulted the cooks.
So I taught him a lesson.
What's with this restaurant?!
No restaurant should
treat its customers like this.
I'll shut it down...
I'll shut this restaurant down!
I'll shut it down!
I'll contact the government
immediately and...
Then I'd better finish you off here.
Stop it, Sous-Chef!
Just looking at an arrogant blowhard
like you makes my blood boil!
What are you doing?!
Keep it up, and we'll be in big trouble!
Stop it, Sanji!
Stop it! You're going too far, Sanji!
So you think you're
a big shot?! Huh?!
Oh, boy...
What happened?
What now?
Boy... that surprised me.
Chef Zeff! What the heck
are you doing?!
Oh, dammit! My restaurant's ceiling!
It's your fault, you brat!
You broke it yourself!
What are you doing, Chef Zeff?!
You can do that after you
help us hold back Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Are you going on a rampage
in the restaurant again, you idiot?!
Shut up, you old fart!
What'd you say?! Who do
you think you're talking to?!
Are you trying to put
my restaurant out of business?!
You brat!
You, too! Get out of here already!
What's with this restaurant?
His bad attitude is just like a...
It's as if... as if...
this were a pirate ship!
Listen up! The customer is king!
Just those who eat
your damn crappy dishes.
Patty! Sanji!
If you wanna fight,
do it in the kitchen!
Are these idiots really cooks?
L-Lieutenant! Lieutenant Fullbody!
W-We've got trouble!
Man, what a wild restaurant.
One of Krieg's pirates escaped!
What?!
After seven of us finally captured him
to get a lead on the Krieg Pirates...
Can't be! When we captured him
three days ago, he was close to starving!
And we haven't fed him at all since!
K-Krieg Pirates...
It's said they're the strongest pirates
in the East Blue...
I'm very...
We have a new customer.
He better not go
on a rampage in my place.
A pirate, huh?
Anything's fine. Bring me food.
This is a restaurant, right?
Welcome, ya damn crook.
I'll only say it once more,
so listen good. Bring me food.
That cook is gonna get killed...
Um, sir, I'm terribly sorry,
but do you have money for that?
Would a bullet do?
So you don't have money, right?
What?!
Patty, that dumbass!
He broke the chair.
Wow, he's strong!
If you can't pay for the food,
you're not a customer.
Good job, cook!
Beat that pirate up, Patty!
Oh... Your stomach
is grumbling, pirate.
That was a fart, you stupid tanuki.
Just bring me food.
If you're not a customer,
beat it already!
I-I've had enough already!
I don't want anything
to do with this restaurant!
I-I'll never come back here!
Now, dear customers,
please continue your meal!
Please never come back.
Dammit! Normally,
that bastard couldn't touch me.
Eat up.
The ocean is vast and cruel.
I get how scary it is
to lose food and water at sea.
How hard it is.
I know what hunger feels like
more than anyone.
You can die for
your pride if you want,
but if you eat and survive,
you'll live to see tomorrow, right?
I'm so ashamed.
Sorry... Thank you...
I thought I was gonna die.
I thought I was done for.
Delicious... It's so delicious.
I've never eaten food so delicious.
It's damn good, isn't it?
I found a good cook!
Hey you, it's a good thing
he gave you food!
You almost died!
Hey you, cook! Join my crew!
Huh?
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
– Huh?!