Hamidashita kimochi tsunagara nakute
More feelings than I can hold but I can’t make you understand
Kimi no te o gyutto ni girikaesu yo
Be that as it may, I just can’t bear to let go of your hand
Hitori demo boku wa arukidasu kara
I’ve still gotta move, even if I’m alone I’ll walk along
Tooku made zutto mitsumeteite ne
Just promise that you’ll still keep
an eye on me when I am gone
Kesa kara chotto kangaeteita
As soon as I woke up, couldn’t get it off my mind
Doushite konna ni atsui no
“Why the hell’s it so hot? I can hardly breathe!”
Itsu kara ka sonna koto bakari ga
It’s been quite a while,
but those thoughts just won’t seem to let go
Hanarenai yo
But hey, what do I know?
Kakedashita kimochi tsukamaetakute
Guess I want a taste of that thing people call a “runner’s high”
Jibun sae mou oikoshite yuku yo
Think I chased too hard, and ended up leaving myself behind
Tobidashita yume o dakishimetetai
All I want’s a taste of a dream that a sentence can’t define
Issho nara boku wa hashitte yukeru
Stick right by my side, and I can run, run, run until I die