Team One Pace
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Timing
Datenshi
Graphics
Soundtracking
Halee
Quality Control
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Pepperjack
Zenef
Flambé Age Fix
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Feeso
Zenef
Typesetting
PhosCity
Zenef
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Translation
Crunchyroll
Special Thanks
CyberLariat
RedHawk02
An Unknown Mama
Screw that little rabbit...
Let's go, jinni !
Did you call for me, Master?!
That little rabbit...
I'm gonna chop her up!
Time to show you
what we can do!
Minister Daifuku!
You're putting us in danger!
What are you aiming at, jinni-san ?
I won't let you get away!
Come this way!
How annoying!
Jinn-uinely Enraged Cleave!
Please stop, Minister Daifuku!
That little...!
That rat! She stole another helm!
That crafty little rabbit!
She's jumping from ship to ship
and making them attack each other!
She sure is something...
Yeah! She's awesome, right?!
She's like a little sister to me!
When the moon cycle and the weather
are in their favor,
the minks are quite strong.
The moon cycle and the weather?
Mm-hm...
It is said that when the minks gaze
at a full moon on a clear night,
their feral instincts are awakened
from the depths of their memories.
That white, beastly form is known as...
the moon lion, Sulong!
Sulong?!
Originally, the transformation
made them lose their minds
and attack everyone in sight,
so it was quite troublesome...
both for others and themselves.
For themselves?
What do you mean by that?
If a mink is unable to control it,
they will get exhausted after a single night...
and die.
What?!
Die?!
So it's a double-edged sword...
It's a combat technique that could cost them their life.
Carrot-san... stealing the enemy helms
is truly a genius strategy.
With that in mind, I will provide assistance
until we are close enough to fight, too!
Provide assistance?
Won't you fall into the sea?!
Don't worry about me...
That's right!
He can run on water...
because he's so light!
Let's have those two secure our escape route,
and we'll keep moving forward at full speed!
– Yeah!
– Mm-hm!
Stop right there!
Dodge to the left!
To the right!
Sluggie-gie!
Prometheus...
Zeus...
Mama?
Brother Peros!
Mama's acting strange!
Lick. Yeah, I know!
She's getting skinnier
and is having a hard time breathing!
Prometheus... Zeus...
Napoleon! What happened
to Zeus and Prometheus?!
I'm calling them over now!
It's been almost eight hours
since she started on her ravenous rampage!
We've never had a problem
stopping them before,
and I've never seen Mama this hungry.
Even we have no idea
what will happen to Mama.
She's truly an unknown monster now. Lick.
Will she make it to Cacao Island?
By the way, Brother Peros,
A report came in, saying that Pudding is
currently transporting the cake this way on a ship!
Oh, really?!
She's our guardian angel!
Well, there's a problem, Big Brother!
It's true that Pudding
is coming with the cake...
but the ship is... Bege's, apparently...
Lick? Did you say Bege?!
Why is the cake that's going to save this country
on that assassin's ship?!
I-I don't know!
What do you mean you don't know?!
What are we gonna do now?!
We can't trust that cake anymore!
Bege's Ship
Within the Territory...
What are you doing, Black Leg?!
That's what I should be saying!
Screw you!
I will absolutely not
let you poison the cake!
This cake will definitely
reach Big Mom's mouth, right?!
Knowing that, what kind of idiot
wouldn't add in poison or explosives?
This is our opportunity to take out
one of the Four Emperors!
Do you realize how big of an opportunity
this is right now?!
Shut up! This is a battle
with a cook's pride on the line!
Don't interfere!
The taste alone will take care of our enemy!
Huh?! Stop dreaming!
Big Mom is a woman who has eaten tons of delicious
snacks from around the world in her lifetime,
and you think you can make a cake
that will surpass her wildest imagination?!
That's impossible!
You're right! If that cake isn't good enough,
then we're done for!
But I'll take you up on that bet!
Even if we do succeed,
they won't let us leave alive!
Cut the crap!
I guess you don't know Big Mom's history!
Mark my words, we will regret
not killing her when we had the chance!
Father!
What did you do to Father?!
Black Leg!
What did you make Father eat?!
Ask him that.
This cream... it's so good that
I could go to heaven right now.
What?! He's about to die
from the deliciousness?!
Father, thank goodness-rero !
Listen to me, Bege...
You're free to try
and assassinate her if you want...
but... you can do it after
I have filled the stomach of my guest!
I will feed anyone who wants to eat!
That is the job of a cook!
Madam Pudding!
Why are you collapsing?!
Bege! It's been a while,
but even I helped with this!
Believe in the power of sweets!
Oh, damn...
It's like I've been hypnotized!
Maybe this cake will work on Big Mom, too...
Yeah... Okay...
Now, let's hurry up!
Have you finished coating the cake?!
Just a little more to go!
Madam Chiffon!
Two of the cooks have fallen to the sweet smell!
Guys! Get a hold of yourselves
until it's finished!
Yes, madam!
Stay safe, Nami-san,
I'm on my way!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Prometheus and Zeus
At Sea, Within the Territory
Which way?
Straight ahead!
I can feel Napoleon's presence!
This is your fault, Prometheus.
You went back to eat the forest fire!
Who's the one that caused me
so much harm, Zeus?!
I can't believe you let yourself
be used by the enemy!
We are special homies that were born
straight from Mama's soul.
The next time you betray Mama to eat,
you won't be let off so easily!
I'm sorry... but...
those thunderclouds were delicious!
Are you really listening to me?!
We can't steer the ship!
We're going to be swept away!
The Sunny
Within the Territory
A path opened up!
We can break through the enemy line!
Carrot is amazing!
Chopper! We have to protect the ship!
Yeah!
No, they're coming back!
Carrot-san, wonderful!
Hey! That skeleton's running on the sea!
Stop him in his tracks!
I must keep up with her, too!
Shoot! Shoot!
I'm starting to lose consciousness!
I'll have to stop soon.
How many ships are left?
Damn that little rabbit!
Jinn-uinely Enraged Cleave!
He saved me the work!
We'll get her this time!
Jinni...
Carrot-san !
...Shredder!
Go to hell, brat!
I'm sorry, Pedro...
Baron Corpse!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Even though it was only a little bit of assistance...
I put one of the ships over there to sleep!
You've already done enough.
Let's go back!
You saved me! Thank you!
That's our line.
How do you turn back to normal?
If I block my eyes
from seeing the moonlight...
using a hat or some sunglasses...
or by simply closing my eyes...
The moonlight from a full moon
enhances our abilities!
That was truly beautiful!
Carrot, are you all right?!
Yeah...
Thank you!
You helped us out of a big pinch!
We were surrounded by enemies
and our ship was almost sunk!
I'm glad I was able to help.
Can I go into a room
where there's no moonlight?
Of course! Leave it to us
and get some rest!
Brother Peros!
Big Brother Daifuku can't fight anymore!
His fleet is drifting away!
How useless... Daifuku!
Mama... Are you really all right?!
There they are...
They're coming, Mama!
Zeus! Prometheus!
We're on our way!
Mama?! She looks like a different person...
Why is she so light?!
Is it because she's so hungry?!
Lick. How long has it been
since I saw Mama move so fast?!
Give me the wedding cake!
Big Mom is coming!
Napoleon!
Transform into a sword!
Yes, Mama!
What the hell is that?!
Mama...
Straw Hat!
No way!
Big Mom!
What has she turned into?!
Where is my wedding cake?
Stand back, guys!
Be prepared to abandon ship!
But...
Oh... I'm so hungry.
But nothing else can satisfy me.
Where is it?!
Where is the wedding cake?!
No! The Sunny !
Oh, no!
How are we going to chase off
such a monster?!
Flour Town
Wheat Island
That scared me!
Mirrors are...
Flour Town
Wheat Island
If this continues,
all of the mirrors in this town will be gone!
I didn't expect him to fight this long
against Commander Katakuri in the Mirro-world...
Whole Cake Island
We keep getting reports of mirror-breakings
from various islands.
It's already 9:30 p.m.-soir.
It's been almost 12 hours
since the assault on the tea party!
What's going on? Dammit!
Hey, everyone...
Do you wanna know something interesting?
Hey, stop!
Their chance of survival will lower even more.
What is it, Mistress Stussy?
At the tea party, Linlin revealed...
the Tamate Box from Ryugu Palace.
She got it...
from Straw Hat Luffy, didn't she?
So what?
That Tamate Box...
contained explosives.
Are you sure-bon ?
Mirro-world
Oh... he's still so perfect and cool.
Big Brother Katakuri!
And...
haven't you gotten a
clear shot yet, sniper?
Well, I've been shooting at him
without being noticed...
but he's moving so fast!
Damn!
Man...! You're useless!
This sucks!
If we don't take out Straw Hat soon,
Big Brother Katakuri will bring him down.
Everyone! Whose head is
going to be patted by Big Brother?!
Of course, it's Lady Flambé's!
I thought so!
I have 41 older brothers.
And 40 of them voted in the Best Little Sister Awards.
I won!
Everyone loves me!
That means I'm everyone's favorite!
Charlotte Flambé
36th Daughter of the Charlotte Family (15 Years Old)
(Katakuri Fan Club President and Suicide Squad Captain)
Charlotte Flambé
36th Daughter of the Charlotte Family (15 Years Old)
(Katakuri Fan Club President and Suicide Squad Captain)
I'm gonna be the king of the little sisters!
So cute!
Everyone wants to be
Big Brother Katakuri's favorite!
But he's an icon for all
his 38 younger sisters!
Even all his younger brothers admire him.
There are too many rivals!
So I wanna help him now
to earn some bonus points!
We know how you feel, Lady Flambé!
We want Commander Katakuri
to like us, too!
I don't care about you guys!
When we got here,
he didn't seem like himself.
But now he's as cool as always!
Anyway, I can't stand to see him
having a hard time against an enemy.
He should be perfect at all times...
or I'll be disappointed!
You're right.
But he's not having a hard time now.
It's just that the enemy's persistent!
He must've received mortal wounds
dozens of times, but he keeps getting up.
What a fool!
How laughable.
Wedding cake!
Did you hide it in here?!
Wait, Big Mom!
I don't see it!
It's not here!
Stop! There's no cake on this ship!
What?!
Don't be ridiculous...
That can't be true!
Because my son told me that it's here!
If it's not here, then I'll have to take
my eldest son's life with my own hands!
Sh-She remembers!
If you're lying to me,
you'll pay with your lifespan!
Just how conscious is she right now?!
I thought I could get away with it!
Don't you dare call my son a liar!
Hey, Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
Let's do it.
Cognac!
I'll burn you and cut you in half!
A big flaming sword!
No chance! Get away, Jinbe!
Go to hell!
Shark Skin!
Blade of Destruction!
What in the world?!
He stopped Cognac!
Jinbe!
Don't think...
you can overpower me,
you damn shark!
Jinbe-san !
Oh, no!
Jinbe!
Where is it?! Bring out the cake!
I'm starving to death!
Carrot!
Stop it, Big Mom!
Carrot is in that room!
If you want me to stop...
Nami!
Tell me where it is!
I'm fine!
Oh, no! The sail caught
fire from Big Mom's head!
Where did you hide...
Run, Nami!
that massive cake?!
Guard Point!
Chopper!
Well, well...
Look what you've turned into!
They're getting more and more exotic.
I'll definitely add you
to my collection of strange beasts!
You chubby little tanuki...
I'm not a tanuki ! I'm a reindeer!
Once I get the wedding cake,
both you and Soul King will belong to me!
Let go of me! The cake isn't here,
and I'm not your plaything!
Chopper!
Oh! If Mama sinks their ship,
maybe my lie will go down with it!
If the Straw Hats lose their ship,
they'll basically be done for!
The ship...!
The ship's burning!
Gum-Gum...
Hawk Stamp!
Did he try to dodge?
Why won't the lights go out...
in your...
eyes!
I don't understand you.
Falling down to the ground is disgraceful.
The ship...!
The ship is burning!
Now, where is the wedding cake?
Let go of me!
Chopper!
What should I do? What should I do?
We have to put out the fire!
Water! Water!
Ocean Current...
Shoulder Throw!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Damn! Suddenly, the water...!
Jinbe-san !
Mama!
Get off of this ship, Big Mom!
If that's what you want...
then hand over the cake!
Fishman Karate Secret Technique!
Vagabond Drill!
Mama!
What?!
Yay! He kicked her out!
Jinbe, you're amazing!
Thank goodness!
You did it!
Guys!
If we allow them
to damage the ship any further,
how will we face Luffy and the others?!
The ship cannot slow down!
If Perospero and the others
catch up to us, that'll be the end of the line!
Yeah!
Okay!
You can count on us!
I'm sorry, but...
Big Mom will regain her footing right away!
How's Carrot?
She's okay!
Let's lose them at full speed!
Mama, are you okay?
Yeah!
That wasn't so bad, Jinbe!
Here she comes!
Oh! I have an idea!
Let's slice it up!
That's a good idea, Mama!
Then, I'm sure I'll find it!
The wedding cake!
It stretched this time!
If she swings that sword around...
...the ship will be finished!
At least Big Mom isn't on the ship anymore!
All right, Zeus-chan...
You like these, right?
Those are...!
Black Ball!
It's delicious!
It's delicious! So delicious!
Yum-yum!
That's right! Now, help yourself!
What should I do?!
Humph! The same trick won't work twice!
Don't try to fool me, you temptress!
Nami!
It's me.
Oh, please!
That's right... I don't have any flesh,
so lightning doesn't affect me.
Oh yeah?
Do you wanna fight me again, Soul King?!
I remember that you couldn't even
scratch me with your sword before!
You're right... So may I at least...
see your panties?!
Huh?!
What?!
Okay.
It's done!
Three-Pace Hum...
Soul...
Notch Slash!
From the very beginning,
our target was you alone, Zeus!
Ow, ow, ow! Damn!
I let my guard down!
Stay with us, Zeus!
Positive Charge Black Ball!
Discharge and feel better, Zeus-chan !
You...!
Th-This is...
What is it?!
Mama!
You're kidding me, Mama!
Zeus discharged!
Mama!
We did it!
We bought some time!
Let's make some headway now!
Hurry up, Brook!
Okay!
Grab this!
I'm back!
Yay! Welcome back!
Brook, well done!
We tried to minimize the damage,
but it's quite bad.
Oh, yeah.
I brought something back.
Oh, Zeus!
I-Isn't he dangerous?
I don't think he has much energy left...
Oh, where am I?
Nice to see you again, Zeus.
Nice... to... see you... too...
As I recall, you tried to...
strike me with lightning earlier.
I'm sorry...
If "sorry" were enough,
there would be no need for sheriffs or the Navy.
I bet you got the wrong idea earlier...
I didn't ask you to be my friend...
What?
I'll ask you one more time...
Will you be my servant...
or would you rather...
die?
Think about it carefully.
Mama! Mama!
Shut up...
Mama!
Chase them, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!